<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T09:40:06</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228797</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228797</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>it</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>FIBER DUST</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Лазери за медицински цели; Медицински устройства за грижа за кожата; Медицински изделия за козметична и дерматологична употреба; Хирургически, медицински, стоматологични и ветеринарни апарати и инструменти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Lasery pro lékařské účely; Lékařská zařízení pro péči o pokožku; Léčebná zařízení ke kosmetickým a dermatologickým účelům; Chirurgické, lékařské, stomatologické a veterinární přístroje a nástroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Lasere til medicinske formål; Medicinsk udstyr til hudpleje; Medicinsk udstyr til kosmetisk og dermatologisk brug; Kirurgiske, medicinske, odontologiske og veterinære apparater og instrumenter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Laser für medizinische Zwecke; Medizinsche Hautpflegegeräte; Medizinische Geräte für kosmetische und dermatologische Zwecke; Chirurgische, ärztliche, zahn- und tierärztliche Apparate und Instrumente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Λέιζερ ιατρικής χρήσης· Ιατρικές διατάξεις περιποίησης του δέρματος· Ιατρικές διατάξεις για καλλωπιστική και δερματολογική χρήση· Όργανα και εργαλεία χειρουργικά, ιατρικά, οδοντιατρικά και κτηνιατρικά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Lasers for medical purposes; Skin care medical devices; Medical devices for cosmetic and dermatological use; Surgical, medical, dental and veterinary apparatus and instruments.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Láseres para uso médico; Dispositivos médicos para el cuidado de la piel; Dispositivos médicos para uso cosmético y dermatológico; Aparatos e instrumentos quirúrgicos, médicos, dentales y veterinarios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meditsiinilised laserid; Meditsiinilised nahahooldusvahendid; Kosmeetikas ja dermatoloogias kasutatavad meditsiiniseadmed; Kirurgiline-, meditsiiniline-, stomatoloogiline ja veterinaarne aparatuur ja instrumendid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Laserit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Ihonhoitoon tarkoitetut lääketieteelliset laitteet; Lääkintälaitteet kosmeettiseen ja dermatologiseen käyttöön; Kirurgiset, lääketieteelliset, hammaslääketieteelliset ja eläinlääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Lasers à usage médical; Dispositifs médicaux de soin de la peau; Dispositifs médicaux à usage cosmétique et dermatologique; Appareils et instruments chirurgicaux, médicaux, dentaires et vétérinaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Laseri za medicinske namjene; Medicinski uređaji za njegu kože; Medicinski uređaji za kozmetičku i dermatološku uporabu; Kirurški, liječnički, stomatološki i veterinarski instrumenti i uređaji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Lézerek orvosi célokra; Bőrápoló gyógyászati eszközök; Orvosi készülékek kozmetikai és bőrgyógyászati használatra; Sebészeti, orvosi, fogorvosi és állatorvosi berendezések és műszerek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Laser per uso medico; dispositivi medici per la cura della pelle; dispositivi medici ad uso cosmetico e dermatologico; apparecchi e strumenti chirurgici, medici, dentari e veterinari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Lazeriai (medicinos reikmėms); Odos priežiūros medicininiai prietaisai; Medicinos prietaisai kosmetikos ir dermatologiniams reikmėms; Chirurginiai, medicininiai, dantų gydymo ir veterinariniai aparatai bei instrumentai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Medicīniskiem nolūkiem paredzētie lāzeri; Ādas aprūpes medicīnas ierīces; Medicīniskas iekārtas lietošanai kosmētikā un dermatoloģijā; Ķirurģijas, medicīnas, zobārstniecības un veterinārijas aparāti, ierīces un instrumenti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Lejżers għal skopijiet mediċi; Strumenti mediċi għall-kura tal-ġilda; Tagħmir mediku għall-użu kożmetiku u dermatoloġiku; apparat u strumenti kirurġiċi, mediċi, dentali u veterinarji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Lasers voor medisch gebruik; Medische toestellen voor de huidverzorging; Medische inrichtingen voor cosmetisch en dermatologisch gebruik; Chirurgische, medische, tandheelkundige en diergeneeskundige toestellen en instrumenten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Lasery do celów medycznych; Przyrządy medyczne do pielęgnacji skóry; Urządzenia medyczne do celów kosmetycznych i dermatologicznych; Urządzenia i przyrządy chirurgiczne, medyczne, dentystyczne i weterynaryjne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Lasers para uso médico; Dispositivos médicos para os cuidados da pele; Dispositivos médicos para uso cosmético e dermatológico; Aparelhos e instrumentos cirúrgicos, médicos, dentários e veterinários.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Lasere de uz medical; Dispozitive medicinale de îngrijire a pielii; Dispozitive medicale de uz cosmetic și dermatologic; Aparate şi instrumente chirurgicale, medicale, stomatologice şi veterinare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Laser na lekárske použitie; Lekárske zariadenia pre starostlivosť o pleť; Lekárske zariadenia na kozmetické a dermatologické účely; Chirurgické, lekárske, zubárske a zverolekárske prístroje a nástroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Laserji za medicinsko uporabo; Medicinske naprave za nego kože; Medicinske naprave za kozmetično in dermatološko uporabo; Kirurški, medicinski, zobozdravstveni in veterinarski aparati in instrumenti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Lasrar för medicinska ändamål; Medicinska hudvårdsanordningar; Medicinska anordningar för kosmetisk och dermatologisk användning; Kirurgiska, medicinska, odontologiska och veterinära apparater och instrument.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/080</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/151</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-11</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>820227</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>16581</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
