<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-07T08:34:29</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228503</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228503</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-05</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-07</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>GOODVISH</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Калъфи за смартфони; Калъфи за смартфони; Защитни тънкослойни покрития, пригодени за смартфони; Портативни устройства за измерване на спортна активност; Подложки за уши за слушалки; Връзки (аксесоари) за мобилни телефони; Радио; Електронни устройства за телекомуникация; Дихателни маски [с изключение на такива за изкуствено дишане]; Защитни работни маски за лице; Защитни маски; Електрифицирани огради; Зарядни устройства; Слушалки; Слушалки за поставяне в ушите; Преносими цифрови електронни кантари; Съединители [устройства за обработване на данни]; Слушалки за телефон; Бебефони; Шлемове за виртуална реалност.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kryty na chytré telefony (smartphony); Pouzdra na chytré telefony (smartphony); Ochranné fólie na chytré telefony; Monitorovací zařízení nošená na těle; Náušníky do sluchátek; Šňůrky na mobilní telefony; Rádia; Elektronická telekomunikační zařízení; Dýchací masky, ne pro umělé dýchání; Pracovní ochranné obličejové štíty; Ochranné masky; Elektrické ohradníky; Nabíječky baterií; Sluchátka; Sluchátka do uší; Přenosné digitální elektronické váhy; Vazební členy [zařízení pro zpracování dat]; Sluchátka k telefonům; Chůvičky; Náhlavní soupravy pro virtuální realitu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Covers til smartphones; Etuier til smartphones; Beskyttelsesfilm tilpasset til smartphones; Wearable aktivitetstrackere; Ørepuder til hovedtelefoner; Mobiltelefonremme; Radioapparater; Elektroniske telekommunikationsapparater; Åndedrætsmasker, undtagen til kunstigt åndedræt; Beskyttende ansigtsskærme til arbejdere; Beskyttelsesmasker; Stødgivende indhegninger; Opladere til batterier; Hovedtelefoner; Øretelefoner; Bærbare digitale, elektroniske vægte; Sammenkoblere [databehandlingsudstyr]; Headsets til telefoner; Babyalarmer; Virtual reality-headsets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Hüllen für Smartphones; Schalen für Smartphones; Angepasste Schutzfolien für Smartphones; Tragbare Activity Tracker; Ohrpolster für Kopfhörer; Riemen für Mobiltelefone; Radios; Elektronische Telekommunikationsgeräte; Atemmasken, ausgenommen für künstliche Beatmung; Gesichtsschutzschirme für Arbeiter; Schutzmasken; Elektrozäune; Ladegeräte für Batterien; Kopfhörer; In-Ear-Kopfhörer; Tragbare digitale elektronische Waagen; Koppler [Datenverarbeitung]; Kopfhörer mit Mikrofon für Telefone; Babyüberwachungsgeräte; Virtual-Reality-Headsets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καλύμματα για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Θήκες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Προστατευτικές μεμβράνες προσαρμοσμένες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Φορετοί ανιχνευτές δραστηριότητας· Μαξιλαράκια αυτιού για ακουστικά· Λουράκια για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Συσκευές ραδιοφωνικές· Ηλεκτρονικές τηλεπικοινωνιακές συσκευές· Αναπνευστικές μάσκες, εκτός αυτών που προορίζονται για τεχνητή αναπνοή· Προστατευτικές ασπίδες προσώπου· Προστατευτικές μάσκες· Περιφράξεις ηλεκτροφόρες· Φορτιστές μπαταριών· Κάσκες ακουστικών· Κεφαλόφωνα [ακουστικά] για τοποθέτηση εντός του αυτιού· Φορητές ψηφιακές ηλεκτρονικές ζυγαριές· Ζεύκτες [εξοπλισμός για την επεξεργασία δεδομένων]· Τηλεφωνικά μικρόφωνα-ακουστικά κεφαλής· Μέσα παρακολούθησης βρεφών· Ακουστικά κεφαλής εικονικής πραγματικότητας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Covers for smartphones; cases for smartphones; protective films adapted for smartphones; wearable activity trackers; ear pads for headphones; cell phone straps; radios; electronic telecommunications apparatus; respiratory masks, other than for artificial respiration; workmen's protective face-shields; protective masks; electrified fences; battery chargers; headphones; in-ear headphones; portable digital electronic scales; couplers [data processing equipment]; headsets for telephones; baby monitors; virtual reality headsets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Carcasas para teléfonos inteligentes; Estuches para teléfonos inteligentes; Películas de protección para teléfonos inteligentes [smartphones]; Monitores de actividad física ponibles; Almohadillas para auriculares; Cordones para teléfonos celulares; Aparatos de radio; Aparatos electrónicos de telecomunicación; Máscaras respiratorias que no sean para la respiración artificial; Pantallas de protección facial para obreros; Máscaras de protección; Vallas electrificadas; Cargadores de pilas y baterías; Auriculares; Auriculares internos; Balanzas electrónicas digitales portátiles; Acopladores [equipos de procesamiento de datos]; Cascos para teléfonos; Dispositivos de audio y vídeo para la vigilancia de bebés; Cascos de realidad virtual.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Nutitelefonide katted; Nutitelefonide ümbrised; Nutitelefonide kaitsekiled; Kantavad aktiivsusmonitorid; Kõrvaklappide kõrvapadjad; Mobiiltelefonide rihmad; Raadiod; Elektroonilised sideseadmed; Respiraatormaskid, respiraatorid, v.a kunstliku hingamise seadmed; Tööliste näokaitsesirmid; Kaitsemaskid; Elektrikarjused; Akulaadurid, patareilaadurid; Kõrvaklapid; Kõrvasisesed kuularid; Portatiivsed digitaalsed elektronkaalud; Sidestid [andmetöötlusseadmed]; Telefoni kõrvaklapid; Beebimonitorid; Virtuaalreaalsuse peakomplektid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Älypuhelinten suojukset; Älypuhelinten kuoret; Älypuhelimille tarkoitetut suojakalvot; Puettavat aktiivisuusmittarit; Korvakuulokkeiden pehmikeosat; Matkapuhelimen hihnat; Radiot; Elektroniset tietoliikennelaitteet; Hengityssuojaimet [paitsi tekohengitykseen]; Työntekijöiden kasvonsuojukset; Suojanaamarit; Sähköaidat; Latauslaitteet sähköparistoille; Kuulokkeet; Korvakuulokkeet; Kannettavat digitaaliset elektroniset vaa'at; Liittimet [tietojenkäsittelylaitteiden osina]; Kuulokkeet puhelimiin [headsetit]; Vauvamonitorit; Kuulokemikrofoniyhdistelmät virtuaalitodellisuutta varten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Coques pour smartphones; Étuis pour smartphones; Films de protection conçus pour ordiphones [smartphones]; Capteurs d'activité à porter sur soi; Bonnettes de casques à écouteurs; Cordonnets pour téléphones mobiles; Appareils de radio; Appareils de télécommunications électroniques; Masques respiratoires autres que pour la respiration artificielle; Écrans de protection faciaux pour ouvriers; Masques de protection; Clôtures électrifiées; Chargeurs de piles et batteries; Casques à écouteurs; Écouteurs intra-auriculaires; Balances électroniques numériques portables; Coupleurs [équipements de traitement de données]; Casques pour téléphones; Dispositifs audio et vidéo pour la surveillance de bébés; Casques de réalité virtuelle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Navlake za pametne telefone; Etuiji za pametne telefone; Zaštitne folije prilagođene za pametne telefone; Uređaji za praćenje aktivnosti koji se nose; Navlake za slušalice; Trake za mobilne telefone; Radioaparati; Elektronički uređaji za telekomunikaciju; Maske za disanje,osim za umjetno disanje; Zasloni za zaštitu lica radnika; Zaštitne maske; Elektrificirane ograde; Akumulatori (punjači električnih akumulatora); Slušalice; In-ear slušalice; Prijenosne digitalne elektroničke vage; Spojnice [oprema za obradu podataka]; Slušalice za telefone; Monitori za bebe; Slušalice za generiranje virtualne stvarnosti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tokok okostelefonokhoz; Tokok okostelefonhoz; Védőfóliák okostelefonokhoz; Viselhető aktivitásészlelők; Fülbetétek fejhallgatókhoz; Szíjak, pántok mobiltelefonokhoz; Rádiókészülékek; Elektronikus távközlési berendezések; Légzőmaszkok nem mesterséges lélegeztetéshez; Munkavédelmi arcvédő pajzsok; Védőálarcok/-maszkok; Elektromos kerítések; Akkumulátor- és elemtöltők; Fejhallgatók; Fülbe helyezhető fejhallgatók; Hordozható digitális elektronikus mérlegek; Csatolók [adatfeldolgozó berendezés]; Headsetek telefonokhoz; Bébiőrök; Virtuális valóság headsetek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Copertine per smartphone; Custodie per smartphones; Pellicola protettiva adattata per smartphone; Tracciatori di attività fisica indossabili; Cuscinetti auricolari per cuffie; Cinghie per cellulari; Apparecchi radio; Apparecchi elettronici di telecomunicazione; Maschere respiratorie non per la respirazione artificiale; Schermi per la protezione del viso degli operai; Maschere di protezione; Recinti elettrificati; Caricabatterie; Cuffie per la musica; Auricolari interni; Bilance elettroniche digitali portatili; Combinatori [informatica]; Cuffie per telefoni; Dispositivi audio e video per la sorveglianza dei neonati; Caschi per realtà virtuale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Išmaniųjų telefonų dangteliai; Išmaniųjų telefonų dėklai; Išmaniųjų telefonų ekranų apsauginės plėvelės; Dėvimieji fizinio aktyvumo įrašymo įrenginiai; Ausinių pagalvėlės; Mobiliųjų telefonų dirželiai; Radijo aparatai; Elektroniniai telekomunikacijų aparatai; Respiratorių kaukės [ne dirbtinio kvėpavimo]; Apsauginiai darbininkų veido skydeliai; Apsauginės kaukės; Elektrinės užtvaros; Baterijų įkrovimo įtaisai; Radijo ausinės; Į ausis kišamosios ausinės; Nešiojamosios skaitmeninės elektroninės svarstyklės; Komutacijos įrenginiai [duomenų dorojimo įrenginiai]; Telefono ausinės; Prietaisai kūdikiams stebėti; Virtualiosios realybės ausinės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Viedtālruņu vāciņi; Viedtālruņu maciņi; Aizsargplēves, kas īpaši paredzētas viedtālruņiem; Valkājamas ierīces fiziskās aktivitātes izsekošanai; Ausu spilventiņi galvas telefoniem (austiņām); Mobilo telefonu aukliņas; Radioaparāti; Telekomunikāciju elektroniskās ierīces; Respiratoru maskas, izņemot mākslīgajai elpināšanai paredzētās maskas; Aizsargmaskas strādniekiem; Aizsargmaskas; Elektriskie žogi; Akumulatoru uzlādes ierīces; Austiņas; Ausīs liekamas austiņas; Portatīvi elektroniskie svari; Savienotāji datu apstrādes iekārtām; Galvas tālruņi; Elektroniskas ierīces zīdaiņu uzraudzībai; Virtuālās realitātes galvas ierīču komplekti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kavers għal smartfowns; Kaxxi għall-ismartphones; Films protettivi adattati għal smartfowns; Apparat li jirreġistra l-attività li jista' jinġarr; Kuttunar artab tal-widnejn għall-kuffji; Ċineg tat-telefons ċellulari; Radjijiet; Tagħmir elettroniku tat-telekomunikazzjoni; Apparat tan-nifs, minbarra dak għal nifs artifiċjali; Lqugħ protettiv tal-wiċċ għal ħaddiema; Maskri protettivi; Ċnut elettriċizzati; Karikaturi għal batteriji elettriċi; Kuffji; Kuffji ta' ġol-widna; Imwieżen diġitali u elettroniċi li jinġarru; Couplers [tagħmir għall-ipproċessar tad-dejta]; Kuffji għal telefoni; Moniters tat-trabi; Ħedsets tar-realtà virtwali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Hoezen voor smartphones; Etuis voor smartphones; Beschermende folie aangepast aan smartphones; Draagbare activiteitsmeters; Oorpads voor koptelefoons; Koordjes voor mobiele telefoons; Radio's; Elektronische telecommunicatieapparatuur; Ademhalingsmaskers, anders dan voor beademing; Gezichtsbeschermers [schermen] voor werklieden; Beschermende maskers; Schrikdraad-omheiningen; Batterij-laders; Hoofdtelefoons; Oortjes; Digitale draagbare elektronische weegschalen; Koppelaars [gegevensverwerkende inrichtingen]; Headsets (oortjes) voor gebruik bij telefoons; Babyfoons; Virtual reality headsets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pokrowce na smartfony; Etui na smartfony; Folie ochronne dostosowane do smartfonów; Przyrządy do śledzenia aktywności do noszenia na sobie; Nauszniki do słuchawek; Paski do telefonów komórkowych; Radia [odbiorniki radiowe]; Elektroniczne urządzenia telekomunikacyjne; Maski do oddychania, inne niż do sztucznego oddychania; Osłony ochronne na twarz dla robotników; Maski ochronne; Ogrodzenia zelektryfikowane; Ładowarki do baterii; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Słuchawki dokanałowe; Przenośne cyfrowe wagi elektroniczne; Sprzęgacze [urządzenia przetwarzające dane]; Zestawy słuchawkowe do telefonów; Urządzenia do monitorowania niemowląt; Zestawy na głowę do rzeczywistości wirtualnej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Coberturas para smartphones; Capas para smartphones; Películas protetoras adaptadas para smartphones; Dispositivos de uso corporal para registo de atividade física; Almofadas para auscultadores; Correias para telefones móveis; Aparelhos de rádio; Aparelhos eletrónicos de telecomunicações; Máscaras respiratórias, sem ser para a respiração artificial; Telas para a proteção do rosto de operários; Máscaras de proteção; Vedações eletrificadas; Carregadores de baterias; Auriculares; Fones para ouvidos; Balanças eletrónicas digitais portáteis; Acopladores [informática]; Conjunto auscultador-microfone para telefones; Dispositivos para vigilância de bebés; Headsets de realidade virtual.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Huse pentru telefoane inteligente; Carcase pentru telefoane inteligente; Folii de protecție adaptate pentru telefoane inteligente; Dispozitive portabile de urmărire a activității; Bureți pentru căști; Curele pentru telefonul mobil; Radiouri; Dispozitive electronice de telecomunicații; Măști respiratorii, altele decât cele pentru respirație artificială; Măști de protecție pentru muncitori; Măști de protecție; Garduri electrificate; Alimentatoare pentru acumulatoare; Căști audio; Căști in-ear; Cântare electronice digitale portabile; Cuploare [echipamente de procesare a datelor]; Căști pentru telefoane; Dispozitive de monitorizare a bebelușilor; Căști pentru realitate virtuală.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kryty na smartfóny; Puzdrá na smartfóny; Ochranné fólie na smartfóny; Zariadenia na sledovanie fyzickej aktivity nosené na tele; Náušníky pre slúchadlá; Šnúrky na mobilné telefóny; Rádiá; Elektronické telekomunikačné zariadenia; Dýchacie masky (nie na umelé dýchanie); Tvárové štíty (ochranné pracovné prostriedky); Ochranné masky; Elektrifikované ohrady; Nabíjačky batérií; Slúchadlá; Slúchadlá do uší; Prenosné digitálne elektronické váhy; Spojovacie prvky (vybavenie zariadení na spracovanie údajov); Telefónne slúchadlá s mikrofónom; Audiovizuálne prístroje na monitorovanie bábätiek; Súpravy okuliarov a slúchadiel na virtuálnu realitu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Ohišja za pametne telefone; Etuiji za pametne telefone; Zaščitne folije, prilagojene za pametne telefone; Nosljive naprave za spremljanje aktivnosti; Ušesne blazinice za slušalke; Trakovi za prenosne telefone; Radii; Elektronski telekomunikacijski aparati; Dihalne maske, razen za umetno dihanje; Zaščita za obraz za delavce; Zaščitne maske; Elektrificirane ograje; Električni polnilniki za baterije; Slušalke; Slušalke za v uho; Prenosne digitalne elektronske tehtnice; Spojke [oprema za obdelavo podatkov]; Naglavne slušalke za telefone; Otroške varuške; Slušalke z mikrofonom za navidezno resničnost.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Fodral för smartphones; Skal för smartphones; Skyddsfilm för smartphones; Bärbara aktivitetsband; Öronkuddar för hörlurar; Band för mobiltelefoner; Radioapparater; Elektroniska telekommunikationsapparater; Andningsmasker, inte för konstgjord andning; Skyddsvisir för arbetare; Skyddsmasker; Elektriska stängsel; Batteriladdare; On-ear hörlurar; In-ear hörlurar; Portabla digitala elektroniska vågar; Kopplingsenheter [databehandlingsutrustning]; Hörlurar för telefoner; Övervakningsapparater för spädbarn; Hörlurar med mikrofon för virtual reality bruk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Чаши; Чинии за маса, не от благороден метал; Чифт дървени пръчици, употребявани като прибори за хранене; Съдове за домакински или кухненски цели [с изключение на такива от благороден метал]; Ръкавици за домакински цели; Дюзи за маркучи за поливане; Тоалетни принадлежности; Инструменти за чистене [ръчни]; Четки; Дезодориращи апарати за индивидуална употреба; Козметични принадлежности; Бърсалки от плат; Тоалетни кутии за домашни любимци; Кухненски принадлежности, не от благороден метал; Тампони за почистване на медицински инструменти; Аерозолни дозатори, не за медицински цели; Пръскащи приспособления; Перушинени бърсалки за прах; Топлоизолирани съдове; Изотермични чанти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Šálky; Stolní talíře; Jídelní hůlky; Dózy, boxy a nádoby pro použití v domácnosti a kuchyni; Rukavice pro použití v domácnosti; Trysky na zavlažovací hadice; Toaletní potřeby; Ruční nástroje na čištění; Kartáče; Zařízení pro deodoraci pro osobní potřebu; Kosmetické pomůcky; Utěrky [hadry] na utírání prachu; Toalety pro zvířata; Kuchyňské potřeby; Tampony pro čištění lékařských nástrojů; Aerosolové dávkovače, ne dávkovače pro léčebné účely; Rozstřikovací zařízení; Péřové prachovky; Tepelně izolované nádoby; Termoizolační tašky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kopper; Tallerkener; Spisepinde; Beholdere til husholdnings- eller køkkenbrug; Handsker til husholdningsbrug; Dyser til vandslanger; Toiletredskaber; Rengøringsredskaber [håndredskaber]; Børster; Desodoriseringsapparater til personlig brug; Redskaber til kosmetisk brug; Støveklude; Afføringsbakker til kæledyr; Køkkenredskaber; Servietter til rengøring af medicinske instrumenter; Aerosolapparater, ikke til medicinsk brug; Vandingsindretninger; Fjerkoste; Varmeisolerende beholdere; Isotermiske tasker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Tassen; Teller; Essstäbchen; Gefäße für Haushalt oder Küche; Haushaltshandschuhe; Sprührohre für Bewässerungsschläuche; Toilettegeräte [Körperpflege]; Handbetätigte Putzgeräte; Bürsten; Desodorierungsgeräte für den persönlichen Gebrauch; Kosmetische Geräte; Staubtücher; Streukästen für Haustiere; Küchengeräte; Reinigungsstäbchen für medizinischen Instrumente; Aerosolzerstäuber, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Beregnungsgeräte; Staubwedel; Isolierbehälter, -gefäße; Kühltaschen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κύπελλα (όχι από πολύτιμα μέταλλα)· Πιάτα φαγητού· Ράβδοι μαγειρικών εσχαρών· Δοχεία οικιακά ή μαγειρικά· Γάντια οικιακής χρήσης· Πιστόλια νερού για λάστιχα ποτίσματος· Τουαλέτας (Σκεύη -)· Εργαλεία καθαρισμού, χειροκίνητα· Βούρτσες· Αποσμητικές (Συσκευές -) για χρήση προσωπική· Καλλυντικά (Σκεύη -)· Ξεσκόνισμα (μάκτρα) [πανιά] --ος· Κάδοι καθαριότητας κατοικίδιων ζώων· Σκεύη μαγειρικής χρήσης· Βαμβακοφόροι στυλεοί για τον καθαρισμό ιατρικών εργαλείων· Αεροζόλ (Συσκευές ρίψης -) για μη ιατρική χρήση· Όργανα (Ψεκασμού ύδατος -)· Φτερά ξεσκονίσματος· Θερμομονωτικά δοχεία· Τσάντες ισοθερμικές.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Cups; table plates; chopsticks; containers for household or kitchen use; gloves for household purposes; nozzles for watering hose; toilet utensils; cleaning instruments, hand-operated; brushes; deodorizing apparatus for personal use; cosmetic utensils; dusting cloths [rags]; litter boxes for pets; kitchen utensils; swabs for cleaning medical instruments; aerosol dispensers, not for medical purposes; watering devices; feather-dusters; heat-insulated containers; isothermic bags.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Tazas; Platos; Palillos chinos [utensilios de mesa]; Recipientes para uso doméstico o culinario; Guantes para uso doméstico; Boquillas para mangueras de riego; Utensilios de tocador; Instrumentos de limpieza accionados manualmente; Cepillos; Aparatos desodorizantes para uso personal; Utensilios cosméticos; Paños [trapos] para quitar el polvo; Bandejas higiénicas para animales de compañía; Utensilios de cocina; Hisopos para limpiar instrumentos médicos; Aerosoles [recipientes] que no sean para uso médico; Instrumentos de riego; Plumeros; Recipientes térmicos; Bolsas isotérmicas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tassid; Taldrikud; Söögipulgad; Köögi- või majapidamismahutid; Majapidamiskindad; Kastmisvooliku otsakud; Tualett-tarbed; Puhastusriistad [käsi-tööriistad]; Harjad; Desodoraatorid isiklikuks tarbeks; Kosmeetikatarbed; Tolmulapid; Lemmikloomade käimlakastid; Köögitarbed; Meditsiiniriistade puhastustampoonid; Aerosoolijaoturid, v.a meditsiinilised; Kastmisvahendid; Sulgharjad tolmu pühkimiseks; Soojusisolatsiooniga mahutid; Isotermilised kotid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kupit; Lautaset; Syömäpuikot; Säiliöt koti- tai keittiökäyttöön; Käsineet kotitalouskäyttöön; Suuttimet kasteluletkuihin; Toalettivälineet; Siivousvälineet, käsikäyttöiset; Harjat; Hajunpoistovälineet henkilökohtaiseen käyttöön; Kosmetiikkavälineet; Pölyrievut; Lemmikkieläinten kuivikelaatikot; Keittokattilasarjat; Vanutupot lääketieteellisten instrumenttien puhdistukseen; Aerosolisumuttimet, ei-lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Kasteluvälineet; Pölyhuiskut; Lämpöeristetyt astiat; Isotermiset laukut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Tasses; Assiettes; Baguettes [instruments de cuisine]; Récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine; Gants de ménage; Lances pour tuyaux d'arrosage; Ustensiles de toilette; Instruments de nettoyage actionnés manuellement; Brosses; Appareils de désodorisation à usage personnel; Ustensiles cosmétiques; Torchons [chiffons] pour épousseter; Bacs à litière pour animaux de compagnie; Ustensiles de cuisine; Tampons pour le nettoyage d’instruments médicaux; Appareils destinés à la projection d'aérosols non à usage médical; Instruments d'arrosage; Plumeaux; Récipients calorifuges; Sacs isothermes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Šalice; Tanjuri [posuđe]; Štapići [kuhinjski pribor]; Posude za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju; Rukavice za kućanstvo; Mlaznice za cijevi za zalijevanje; Toaletni pribor; Ručni pribor za čišćenje; Četke; Aparati za dezodoriranje za osobnu upotrebu; Kozmetički pribor; Prašina [krpe za brisanje prašine]; Kutije s pijeskom za kućne ljubimce; Posuđe (kuhinjsko metalno posuđe); Štapići za čišćenje medicinskih instrumenata; Uređaji za raspršivanje aerosola, za nemedicinske potrebe; Naprave za polijevanje; Peruške [čistač prašine]; Toplinski izolirane posude; Termičke izolacijske vrećice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Csészék; Tányérok; Evőpálcikák (Kínai -); Tárolók, tároló edények háztartási vagy konyhai célokra; Kesztyűk háztartási használatra; Szórófejek öntözőcsőhöz; Toaletteszközök; Tisztítóeszközök, kézi működtetésű; Kefék; Dezodoráló szerek személyes használatra; Kozmetikai eszközök; Porrongyok; Alomtálcák házi kedvenceknek; Konyhai eszközök, kis méretű; Tisztítópálcikák orvosi műszerek tisztításához; Aeroszol adagolók, nem gyógyászati használatra; Öntözőberendezések; Portörlő tollseprűk; Hőszigetelt tartályok, konténerek; Izotermikus táskák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Tazze; Piatti; Bastoncini [strumenti da cucina]; Recipienti per la casa o per la cucina; Guanti per uso domestico; Lance per tubi d'innaffiamento; Utensili per la toilette; Strumenti per la pulizia azionati manualmente; Spazzole; Apparecchi di deodorizzazione per uso personale; Utensili cosmetici; Strofinacci per spolverare; Cassette igieniche per animali domestici; Utensili da cucina; Tamponi per la pulizia di strumenti medici; Apparecchi per la proiezione di aerosol per uso non medico; Strumenti per l'innaffiamento; Piumini per spolverare; Recipienti coibenti; Borse isotermiche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Puodukai; Valgomosios lėkštės; Valgomosios lazdelės; Buitinės ar virtuvinės talpyklos; Buitinės pirštinės; Laistymo žarnų purkštukai; Tualetiniai indai; Valymo reikmenys [rankiniai]; Šepečiai; Dezodoravimo įtaisai (asmeninėms reikmėms); Kosmetikos reikmenys; Dulkių šluostukai; Pakratų dėžutės naminiams gyvūnėliams; Virtuviniai indai; Tamponai medicinos instrumentams valyti; Aerozoliniai įtaisai (išskyrus medicininius); Drėkinimo įrenginiai; Plunksninės šluotelės; Izoterminės talpyklos; Izoterminiai maišeliai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tases; Galda šķīvji; Irbuļi ēšanai; Tilpnes mājturības vai virtuves nolūkiem; Cimdi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Laistīšanas šļūteņu uzgaļi; Tualetes piederumi; Ar roku darbināmas tīrīšanas ierīces; Sukas; Dezodorēšanas ierīces personiskai lietošanai; Kosmētikas piederumi; Putekļu lupatiņas no auduma; Mājas (istabas) dzīvnieku tualetes kastītes; Ēdienu gatavošanas trauku komplekti; Tamponi medicīnisko instrumentu tīrīšanai; Aerosolu izsmidzināšanas ierīces, ne medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Laistīšanas ierīces; Spalvu slotiņas; Karstumu izolējošas tvertnes; Izotermiskas somas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kikkri; Platti tal-mejda; Ċopstiks; Kontenituri għal użu domestiku jew għal użu fil-kċina; Ingwanti għal skopijiet domestiċi; Żennuni għall-pajpijiet li jsaqqu; Utensili għat-tojlit; Strumenti tat-tindif, li jinħadmu bl-idejn; Pniezel; Apparat deodorizzanti, għal użu personali; Utensili kożmetiċi; Biċċiet tat-tfarfir [ċraret]; Kaxxi tal-ħmieġ għall-annimali domestiċi; Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir; Tajjar assorbenti għat-tindif ta' strumenti mediċi; Dispensers tal-erosol, mhux għal skopijiet mediċi; Tagħmir li jbexx; Xkupi tar-rix; Kontenituri li jżommu s-sħana; Boroż isotermiċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kopjes; Eetborden; Eetstokjes; Houders voor de huishouding of de keuken; Handschoenen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Spuitmonden voor tuinslangen; Toiletgerei; Reinigingsinstrumenten, handbediend; Borstels; Desodorisatietoestellen voor persoonlijk gebruik; Cosmetisch gerei; Stofdoeken; Kattenbakken; Keukengerei; Wattenstaafjes voor het reinigen van medische instrumenten; Spuitbussen, niet voor medisch gebruik; Sproei-instrumenten; Plumeaus; Warmte-isolerende houders; Koeltassen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Filiżanki; Talerze; Pałeczki [sprzęt kuchenny]; Pojemniki do użytku domowego lub kuchennego; Rękawice do użytku domowego; Dysze do węży zraszających; Przybory toaletowe; Narzędzia do czyszczenia, ręczne; Szczotki; Urządzenia dezodoryzujące do użytku osobistego; Przybory kosmetyczne; Ściereczki do kurzu; Kuwety dla zwierząt domowych; Przybory kuchenne; Gaziki do czyszczenia instrumentów medycznych; Urządzenia rozpylające do aerozoli, nie do celów medycznych; Zraszacze; Miotełki do kurzu; Pojemniki termoizolacyjne; Torby izotermiczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Taças; Pratos de mesa; Hashi/fachi [pauzinhos]; Recipientes para uso doméstico ou para cozinha; Luvas para uso doméstico; Agulhetas para mangueiras de rega; Utensílios para casa de banho; Instrumentos para limpeza, manuais; Escovas; Aparelhos desodorizantes, para uso pessoal; Utensílios cosméticos; Panos para limpeza de pó [trapos]; Caixas de areia para animais de estimação; Utensílios para cozinha; Zaragatoas para limpar instrumentos médicos; Dispensadores de aerossóis, sem ser para uso médico; Instrumentos de rega; Espanadores; Recipientes térmicos; Sacos isotérmicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cești; Platouri [veselă]; Bețișoare chinezești [tacâmuri]; Recipiente pentru menaj sau bucătărie; Mănuși de menaj; Duze pentru furtunuri de apă; Toaletă (Ustensile de -); Curățat (instrumente pentru -, acționate manual); Perii; Deodorizant (aparate -e) pentru uz personal; Cosmetice (Ustensile -); Ștergerea prafului (Cârpe pentru -); Litiere pentru animale de companie; Ustensile de bucătărie; Tampoane pentru curățarea instrumentelor medicale; Aerosoli (aparate pentru răspândirea -lor) [altele decât cele folosite în scopuri medicale]; Stropire (Instrumente pentru -); Pămătufuri de praf; Recipiente termoizolante pentru alimente; Sacoșe termoizolante.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Šálky; Taniere; Paličky na jedenie; Nádoby na použitie v domácnosti alebo v kuchyni; Rukavice pre domácnosť; Dýzy polievacích hadíc; Toaletné pomôcky; Nástroje na čistenie na ručný pohon; Kefy; Prístroje na odstraňovanie zápachu na osobné použitie; Kozmetické pomôcky; Prachovky; Odpadové nádoby pre zvieratá chované v domácnosti; Kuchynský riad; Tampóny na čistenie lekárskych nástrojov; Aerosólové dávkovače (nie na lekárske účely); Pomôcky na zavlažovanie, polievanie; Čističky peria; Tepelnoizolačné nádoby (termosky); Izotermické vrecká.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Skodelice; Namizni krožniki; Jedilne palčke; Posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo; Rokavice za gospodinjske namene; Cevni nastavki za škropilnice; Toaletne potrebščine; Čistilne priprave, ročne; Krtače; Naprave za dezodoriziranje, za osebno uporabo; Kozmetični pripomočki; Cunje za brisanje prahu; Stranišča za hišne ljubljence; Kuharski pripomočki; Vatirane paličice za čiščenje medicinskih instrumentov; Pršilci aerosolov, ne za medicinske namene; Škropilnice; Omela iz perja; Toplotno izolirane posode; Termične izolacijske vrečke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bägare; Tallrikar; Ätpinnar; Behållare för hushålls- eller köksändamål; Handskar för hushållsändamål; Sprinkelmunstycken för vattenslangar; Toalettutensilier; Rengöringsredskap (handdrivna); Borstar; Luktborttagningsapparater för personligt bruk; Kosmetikutensilier; Dammtrasor; Lådor för husdjurströ; Köksgeråd; Bomullstoppar för rengöring av medicinska instrument; Aerosolbehållare, inte för medicinska ändamål; Vattningsredskap; Dammvippor; Värmeisolerande behållare; Isotermiska väskor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/079</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/148</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-06</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081959</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017950422</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-05-27</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
