<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-21T09:52:48</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228527</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228527</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-10-20</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-21</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>RPF</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>2</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Облицовки за стъкло и Оцветени ламинати; Оптични покрития, А именно, покрития за филтриране на синя светлина и UV светлина; Неотразяващи покрития за стъкло; Оцветители; Багрила, оцветители и нюанси за използване в състави за повърхностно покритие; Бои [багрила], Пигменти и оцветители, които блокират светлината с ултравиолетова и синя дължина на вълната; Бои, оцветители и багри за използване в производството на екрани.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nátěry na sklo a Tónované laminace; Optické povrchové materiály, Jmenovitě nátěry pro účely filtrace modrého světla a UV záření; Antireflexní nátěry skel; Barviva; Barvy a barviva k použití v materiálech nanášených na povrchy; Barviva, Barvy a barviva, které blokují ultrafialové a modré světlo; Barvy a barviva k použití při výrobě obrazovek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Belægninger til glas og Toningslaminater; Optiske belægninger, Nemlig belægninger til filtrering af blåt lys og UV-lys; Antirefleksbelægninger til glas; Farvestoffer; Farver, farvestoffer og blæk til brug i overfladebelægningsstoffer; Farver, Farver og tonfarver, som blokerer ultraviolet og blåt bølgelys; Farver, farvestoffer og blæk til brug inden for fremstilling af skærme til fremvisning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Glasbeschichtungen und Farbbeschichtungen; Optische Beschichtungen, Nämlich Beschichtungen zum Filtern von blauem Licht und UV-Licht; Entspiegelungsbeschichtungen für Glas; Färbemittel; Farben, Farbstoffe und Abtönfarben zur Verwendung bei Oberflächenbeschichtungsstoffen; Färbemittel, Farbstoffe und Tinten zum Blockieren von UV-Licht und blauem Licht; Farben, Farbstoffe und Abtönfarben zur Verwendung bei der Herstellung von Bildschirmen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Επιστρώσεις για επιφάνειες υάλου και Κεχρωσμένα ελάσματα· Οπτικές επιστρώσεις, Συγκεκριμένα επιστρώσεις για τη διήθηση του μπλε φωτός και της υπεριώδους ακτινοβολίας· Αντιανακλαστικές επιστρώσεις για επιφάνειες υάλου· Χρωστικές ουσίες· Βαφές, χρωστικές ουσίες και προϊόντα βαφής για χρήση σε συνθέσεις επίστρωσης επιφανειών· Βαφές, Χρωστικές και βαφές για αποκλεισμό του φωτός υπεριώδους και μπλε μήκους κύματος· Βαφές, χρωστικές ουσίες και προϊόντα βαφής για χρήση στην κατασκευή οθονών οπτικής παρουσίασης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Glass coatings and tint laminations; optical coatings, namely coatings for the purpose of filtering blue light and UV light; anti-reflective coatings for glass; colorants; dyes, colorants and tints for use in surface coating compositions; dyes, colorants and tints that block ultraviolet and blue wavelength light; dyes, colorants and tints for use in the manufacture of display screens.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Revestimientos de cristal y Laminaciones tintadas; Revestimientos ópticos, En concreto, enlucidos para el filtrado de la luz azul y la luz ultravioleta; Revestimientos antirreflectantes para cristal; Materias tintóreas; Tintes, colorantes y materias tintóreas para su uso en composiciones de revestimientos superficiales; Tintes, Colorantes y tintes que bloquean la luz de longitud de onda ultravioleta y azul; Tintes, colorantes y materias tintóreas para su uso en la fabricación de pantallas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Klaasipinnakatted ja Toonivad laminaadid; Optikavahendite katteained, Nimelt pinded sinise valguse ja UV-valguse filtreerimiseks; Peegeldusvastased klaasipinded; Värvained; Pinnakattesegudes kasutatavad värvained, värvid ja tindid; Värvid, Ultraviolett- ja sinise valguse lainepikkuse blokeerimise värvained ja tindid; Ekraanide tootmisel kasutatavad värvained, värvid ja tindid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lasipinnoitteet ja Sävytetyt laminoinnit; Optiset pinnoitteet, Nimittäin sinisen valon ja UV-valon suodattamiseen tarkoitetut pinnoitteet; Heijastuksenestopinnoitteet lasia varten; Väriaineet; Pintapäällysteseoksissa käytettävät värit ja väriaineet; Väriaineet, Väriaineet ja -sävyt, jotka estävät ultravioletilla ja sinisellä aallonpituudella olevan valon; Näyttöruutujen valmistuksessa käytettävät värit ja väriaineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Revêtements pour verre et Feuilles colorées; Revêtements optiques, À savoir enduits pour filtrer la lumière bleue et la lumière ultraviolette; Revêtements anti-reflets pour verre; Matières tinctoriales; Teintures, colorants et teintes pour enduits de revêtement de surface; Teintures, Colorants et teintures pour bloquer la lumière à longueur d'onde ultraviolette et bleue; Teintures, colorants et teintes pour la fabrication d'écrans d'affichage.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Premazi za staklo i Obojeni laminati; Optički premazi, I to premazi za filtriranje plavog svjetla i UV svjetla; Premazi za staklo protiv refleksije; Bojila; Boje i bojila za upotrebu u spojevima za površinsko premazivanje; Boje [tinkture], Bojila i boje za blokiranje ultraljubičastog svjetla i plavog svjetla; Boje i bojila za upotrebu u proizvodnji zaslona.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Üvegbevonatok és Színrétegződések; Optikai bevonatok, Nevezetesen a kék fény és az UV fény szűrésére szolgáló bevonatok; Tükröződésmentes üvegbevonatok; Festőanyagok; Felületbevonó keverékekben használatos festékek, színezőanyagok és színek; Tinktúrák, Színezékek és színezők, amelyek blokkolják az ultraibolya és kék hullámhosszúságot; Kijelző képernyők gyártásánál használatos festékek, színezőanyagok és színek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Rivestimenti per vetro e Laminazioni colorate; Rivestimenti ottici, Ovvero rivestimenti per filtrare la luce blu e la luce UV; Rivestimenti antiriflesso per vetro; Materie tintorie; Tinture, coloranti e tinte per composti per il rivestimento di superfici; Tinture, Coloranti e tinture che bloccano raggi ultravioletti e a lunghezza d'onda blu; Tinture, coloranti e tinte per la fabbricazione di schermi di visualizzazione.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Stiklo padengimas ir Dažų laminatai; Optinės dangos, Būtent dangos, skirtos filtruoti mėlyną ir UV šviesą; Skaidrintosios stiklo dangos; Dažymo medžiagos; Dažikliai, dažančios medžiagos ir atspalvių pigmentai paviršiaus dangos kompozicijoms; Dažikliai, Dažikliai ir atspalviai, blokuojantys ultravioletinę ir mėlyną bangų ilgio šviesą; Dažikliai, dažančios medžiagos ir atspalvių pigmentai, skirti naudoti monitorių ekranų gamyboje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Stikla pārklājums un Tonēšanas lamināti; Optiskie pārklājumi, Proti, pārklājumi zilās un UV gaismas filtrēšanai; Neatstarojošs pārklājums stiklam; Krāsvielas; Krāsas, krāsvielas un toņi izmantošanai virsmas pārklājumu savienojumos; Krāsvielas, Krāsvielas un krāsas, kas bloķē ultravioleto un zilā viļņa garumu; Krāsas, krāsvielas un toņi izmantošanai displeju izgatavošanā.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kisi għall-ħġieġ u Laminazzjonijiet skuri; Kisi ottiku, Jiġifieri kisjiet bl-iskop ta' filtrazzjoni tad-dawl blu u tad-dawl UV; Kisi li ma jirriflettix għall-ħġieġ; Koloranti; Żebgħa, koloranti u żebgħa għall-użu fil-kompożizzjonijiet tal-kisi tal-uċuħ; Kuluri taż-żbigħ, Koloranti u sfumaturi li jimblokkaw id-dawl b'tul ta' mewġa ultravjola u blu; Żebgħa, koloranti u żebgħa għall-użu fil-manifattura ta' skrins tad-displej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Deklagen voor glas en Kleurlamineringen; Optische coatings, Te weten coatings voor het filteren van blauw licht en ultraviolet licht; Antireflectiecoatings voor glas; Kleurstoffen; Verfstoffen, kleurstoffen en kleurmiddelen voor gebruik in samenstellingen voor oppervlaktecoatings; Verfstoffen, Kleurstoffen en tinten voor het blokkeren van ultraviolet licht en licht met een blauwe golflengte; Verfstoffen, kleurstoffen en kleurmiddelen voor gebruik bij de fabricage van weergaveschermen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Powłoki do szkła i Barwione laminaty; Pokrycia optyczne, Mianowicie powłoki do filtrowania światła niebieskiego (z urządzeń elektronicznych) i światła ultrafioletowego (UV); Antyodblaskowe powłoki do szkła; Barwniki; Farby, barwniki i kolory do użytku w mieszankach do powlekania powierzchni; Koloranty, Barwniki i barwniki, które blokują światło ultrafioletowe (UV) i światło o długości fali światła niebieskiego; Farby, barwniki i kolory do użytku w produkcji ekranów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Revestimentos para vidro e Laminados com cor; Revestimentos ópticos, Especificamente revestimentos para fins de filtração de luz azul e de luz UV; Revestimentos anti-reflectores para vidro; Matérias tinturiais; Tintas, corantes e tinturas para uso em composições de revestimento de superfícies; Tinturas, Produtos de coloração para bloqueio de luz ultravioleta e com comprimento de onda azul; Tintas, corantes e tinturas para uso no fabrico de ecrãs de visualização.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Acoperiri pentru sticlă şi Produse de laminare nuanţate; Substanţe de acoperire optice, Și anume straturi pentru filtrarea luminii albastre și luminii UV; Straturi antireflex pentru sticlă; Materiale colorante; Vopsele, coloranţi şi nuanţe destinate utilizării în compoziţii pentru straturi de acoperire a suprafeţelor; Coloranţi, Coloranți și vopsele care blochează lumina ultravioletă și lungimea de undă albastră; Vopsele, coloranţi şi nuanţe destinate utilizării la fabricarea de ecrane de afişare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Povrchové vrsvy pre sklo a Farebné laminácie; Optické nátery, Menovite nátery na účely filtrovanie modrého svetla a UV žiarenia; Antireflexné nátery na sklo; Farbivá; Farby a farbivá pre látky na natieranie povrchov; Farby, nátery, Farbivá na blokovania UV žiarenia a svetla v modrých vlnových dĺžkach; Farby a farbivá pre látky na použitie pri výrobe obrazoviek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Premazi za steklo in Barvani laminati; Optični premazi, In sicer premazi za filtriranje modre in ultravijolične svetlobe; Premazi za steklo proti bleščanju; Barvilna sredstva; Barve, barvila in barvilne snovi za uporabo v sestavkih za premazovanje površin; Barvila, Barvila in tinte, ki blokirajo svetlobo ultravijolične in modre valovne dolžine; Barve, barvila in barvilne snovi za uporabo pri proizvodnji prikazovalnih zaslonov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Beläggningar för glas och Färglaminering; Optiska beläggningar, Nämligen beläggningar för att filtrera blått ljus och UV-ljus; Antireflexbeläggningar för glas; Färgämnen; Färgämnen, färgmedel och nyanser för användning i ytbeläggningskompositioner; Färgmedel, Färgämnen och färgtoner som blockerar ultraviolett ljus och ljus av blå våglängd; Färgämnen, färgmedel och nyanser för användning vid tillverkning av bildskärmar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Защитно фолио адаптирано за дисплейни екрани; Оптични филтри за екрани; Цветни филтри; Филтри за компютърни екрани; Оптично стъкло; Компютърни екрани; Видеоекрани; Екрани; Екрани за компютри, които реагират на докосване; Табла, които реагират на докосване; Екрани за смартфони; Светодиоди [LED]; Излъчващи светлина диодни екрани; Органични светодиоди [OLED]; Монитори; Протектори за екран от закалено стъкло; Защитно фолио, пригодено за екрани на смартфони,; LCD монитори; Уреди за обработка на данни; Лаптопи; Смартфони; VR слушалки (слушалки за виртуална реалност); Очила [оптични]; Слънчеви очила; Контактни лещи; Филтри за екрани; Ултравиолетови филтри, не за медицински цели; Филтри за светлина със синя дължина на вълната.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Ochranné fólie přizpůsobené na obrazovky displejů; Optické filtry do obrazovek; Barevné filtry; Filtry na počítačové obrazovky; Optické sklo; Počítačové obrazovky; Obrazovky; Obrazovky; Dotykové počítačové obrazovky; Dotykové panely; Displeje pro chytré telefony; Elektroluminiscenční diody [LED]; LED displeje; Organické elektroluminiscenční diody [OLED]; Monitory; Ochrany displeje z kaleného skla; Ochranné fólie přizpůsobené pro chytré telefony; LCD monitory; Zařízení ke zpracování dat a počítače; Laptopy; Chytré telefony (smartphony); Náhlavní soupravy pro VR; Brýle; Sluneční brýle; Čočky kontaktní; Filtry obrazovek; Ultrafialové filtry, jiné než pro lékařské účely; Filtry pro modré světlo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beskyttende film tilpasset til anvendelse på skærme; Optiske skærmfiltre; Farvefiltre; Skærmfiltre til computerskærme; Optisk glas; Computerskærme; Videoskærme; Skærme; Berøringsfølsomme computerskærme; Berøringspaneler; Skærme til smartphones; Lysemitterende dioder [LED]; Lysemitterende diodedisplays; Organiske lysdioder [OLED]; Monitorer (skærme); Skærmbeskyttere af hærdet glas; Beskyttende folie beregnet til smartphones; LCD-monitorer; Udstyr til databehandling; Bærbare computere; Smartphones; Virtual reality-hovedtelefoner; Briller [optik]; Solbriller; Og kontaktlinser; Skærmfiltre; Ultraviolette filtre, ikke til medicinsk brug; Filtre til lys med blå bølgelængder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">An Bildschirme angepasste Schutzfolien; Optische Filter für Bildschirme; Farbfilter; Filterschirme für Computerbildschirme; Optisches Glas; Computermonitore; Videobildschirme; Bildschirme; Berührungsbildschirme für Computer; Bildschirmtastfeld; Bildschirme für Smartphones; Leuchtdioden [LEDs]; LED-Anzeigen; Organische Leuchtdioden [OLED]; Bildschirme; Schutzglas für Bildschirme; Schutzfolien für Smartphones; LCD-Bildschirme; Computergeräte; Laptops; Smartphones; VR-Kopfhörergarnituren; Brillen [Optik]; Sonnenbrillen; Kontaktlinsen; Bildschirmfilter; Ultraviolettfilter für nicht medizinische Zwecke; Filter für blaues Licht.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Προστατευτικές μεμβράνες για οθόνες οπτικής παρουσίασης· Οπτικά φίλτρα για οθόνες· Έγχρωμα φίλτρα· Φίλτρα για οθόνες ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Γυαλί οπτικό· Οθόνες ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Οθόνες βίντεο· Οθόνες οπτικής παρουσίασης· Οθόνες αφής ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Πάνελ αφής· Οθόνες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Δίοδοι εκπομπής φωτός· Οθόνες διόδου εκπομπής φωτός (LED)· Οργανικές φωτοδίοδοι [OLED]· Οθόνες παρακολούθησης· Προστατευτικά οθόνης κατασκευασμένα από σκληρυμένο γυαλί· Προστατευτικές μεμβράνες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Οθόνες υγρών κρυστάλλων [LCD]· Υπολογιστικές συσκευές· Φορητοί ηλεκτρονικοί υπολογιστές· Έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Κεφαλόφωνα εικονικής πραγματικότητας· Διόπτρες· Γυαλιά ηλίου· Και φακοί επαφής· Φίλτρα για οθόνες· Φίλτρα υπεριώδους ακτινοβολίας, όχι για ιατρική χρήση· Φίλτρα για φως μπλε μήκους κύματος.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Protective films adapted for display screens; optical screen filters; color filters; computer screen filters; optical glass; computer screens; video screens; display screens; computer touch screens; touch panels; smartphone screens; light-emitting diodes (LED); light-emitting diode (LED) displays; organic light emitting diodes (OLED); monitors; tempered glass screen protectors; protective films adapted for smart phones; liquid crystal display (LCD) monitors; computing devices; laptops; smartphones; VR head-sets; eye glasses; sunglasses; and contact lenses; display screen filters; ultraviolet filters, other than for medical use; filters for blue wavelength light.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Películas de protección adaptadas para pantallas de visualización; Filtros ópticos para pantallas; Filtros de color; Filtros para pantallas de ordenador; Cristal óptico; Monitores de ordenador; Pantallas de vídeo; Pantallas de visualización; Pantallas táctiles de ordenador; Paneles táctiles; Pantallas para teléfonos inteligentes; Diodos electroluminiscentes [LED]; Pantallas de diodos luminiscentes (led); Diodos electroluminiscentes orgánicos; Monitores; Protección de pantalla de vidrio templado; Películas de protección adaptadas para teléfonos inteligentes; Monitores de cristal líquido [LCD]; Dispositivos informáticos; Ordenadores portátiles; Teléfonos inteligentes; Cascos de realidad virtual; Gafas [óptica]; Gafas de sol; Y lentes de contacto; Filtros para pantallas de visualización; Filtros ultravioletas excepto para uso médico; Filtros para la luz de longitud de onda azul.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kuvaekraanidele kohandatud kaitsekiled; Ekraanide optilised filtrid; Värvifiltrid; Arvuti ekraanifiltrid; Optiline klaas; Arvutiekraanid; Videoekraanid; Kuvaseadmed; Arvutite puuteekraanid; Puuteekraanid, -paneelid; Nutitelefonide ekraanid; Valgust kiirgavad dioodid [LED]; Valgust kiirgavad dioodkuvarid; Orgaanilised valgusdioodid [OLED]; Monitorid; Karastatud klaasist ekraanikaitsed; Nutitelefonide kohandatud kaitsekiled; LCD-monitorid; Andmetöötlusseadmed ja arvutid; Sülearvutid; Nutitelefonid; Virtuaalreaalsuse peakomplektid; Prillid [optika]; Päikeseprillid; Kontaktläätsed; Kuvariekraani filtrid; Ultraviolettfiltrid (v.a meditsiiniliseks kasutamiseks); Sinise lainepikkuse valguse filtrid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Näyttöruuduille tarkoitetut suojakalvot; Näyttöruutujen optiset suodattimet; Värisuodattimet; Tietokonenäyttöjen suodattimet; Optinen lasi; Tietokonenäytöt; Videokuvaruudut; Näyttöruudut; Tietokoneiden kosketusnäytöt; Kosketuspaneelit; Älypuhelimien näyttöruudut; Valodiodit [ledit]; Valodiodinäytöt; Orgaaniset valodiodit; Monitorit; Näytönsuojukset karkaistusta lasista; Älypuhelimille tarkoitetut suojakalvot; Nestekidenäytöt; Tietojenkäsittelylaitteet; Kannettavat tietokoneet; Älypuhelimet; Virtuaalitodellisuuden kuulokemikrofonit; Silmälasit [optiikka]; Aurinkolasit; Piilolasit; Näyttösuodattimet; Ultraviolettisuotimet, muuhun kuin lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Suodattimet sinisellä aaltopituudella olevaa valoa varten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Films de protection conçus pour écrans d'affichage; Filtres optiques pour écrans; Filtres de couleur; Filtres d'écrans d'ordinateurs; Verre optique; Écrans d'ordinateurs; Écrans vidéo; Écrans d'affichage; Écrans tactiles pour ordinateurs; Panneaux tactiles; Écrans pour smartphones; Diodes électroluminescentes [DEL]; Écrans à diodes électroluminescentes; Diodes électroluminescentes organiques; Moniteurs; protection d'écran en verre trempé; Films de protection pour smartphones; Moniteurs à cristaux liquides [moniteurs LCD]; Appareils informatiques; Ordinateurs portables; Ordiphones [smartphones]; Casques d'écoute pour la réalité virtuelle; Lunettes [optique]; Lunettes de soleil; Et verres de contact; Filtres pour écrans d'affichage; Filtres ultraviolets, autres qu'à usage médical; Filtres pour la lumière à longueur d'onde bleue.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Zaštitne folije prilagođene za zaslone; Optički filtri za zaslone; Filtri boja; Filteri za računalne zaslone; Optička stakla; Monitori računala; Video ekrani; Zasloni; Ekrani računala osjetljivi na dodir; Paneli na dodir [elktroničke vizualni prikazivači]; Zasloni za pametne telefone; Svjetleće diode [LED]; LED zasloni [zasloni sa svjetlećim diodama]; Organske svjetleće diode [OLED]; Zasloni; Zaštite za ekrane od kaljenog stakla; Zaštitne folije prilagođene za pametne telefone; LCD monitori; Uređaji za obradu podataka; Prijenosna računala; Pametni telefoni; Naglavni uređaji za virtualnu stvarnost; Naočale [optika]; Sunčane naočale; Kontaktne leće; Filtri za zaslone; Ultrazvučni filteri, osim za medicinsku uporabu; Filtri za plavo svjetlo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Képernyőkhöz adaptált védőfóliák; Optikai szűrők képernyőkhöz; Festékszűrők; Monitorszűrők számítógép képernyőkhöz; Optikai üveg; Számítógép képernyők, monitorok; Videoképernyők; Kijelzők; Számítógépes érintőképernyők; Érintőpanelek; Okostelefon-képernyők; Fénykibocsátó diódák [LED]; Fénykibocsátó diódás kijelzők; Szerves fénykibocsátó diódák [OLED]; Monitorok; Képernyővédők edzett üvegből; Okos telefonokhoz készült védőfóliák; LCD-monitorok; Adatfeldolgozási berendezések és számítógépek; Laptopok; Okostelefonok; VR (virtuális valóság) headsetek; Szemüvegek [optika]; Napszemüvegek; Kontaktlencsék; Képernyőszűrők; Ultraibolya szűrők, nem gyógyászati használatra; Szűrők kék hullámhosszú fényhez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pellicola di protezione adattata per schermo di visualizzazione; Filtri ottici per schermi; Filtri di colore; Filtri per schermi per computer; Vetri ottici; Monitor per computer; Videoschermi; Schermi di visualizzazione; Schermi tattili per computer; Pannelli a sfioramento; Schermi per smartphone; Diodi ad emissione luminosa [LED]; Visualizzatori a diodi ad emissione luminosa; Diodi organici ad emissione luminosa [OLED]; Monitor; Protezione di schermi in vetro temprato; Pellicole protettive specifiche per telefoni intelligenti; Monitor a cristalli liquidi; Dispositivi d'elaborazione; Computer portatili; Smartphone; Cuffie VR; Occhiali [ottica]; Occhiali da sole; Lenti a contatto; Filtri per videoschermi; Filtri ultravioletti, non per uso medico; Filtri per raggi a lunghezza d'onda blu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Apsauginės plėvelės, pritaikytos ekranams; Optiniai ekranų filtrai; Spalvų filtrai; Kompiuterių monitorių filtriniai ekranai; Optinis stiklas; Kompiuterių ekranai; Vaizdo [video-] ekranai; Vaizduokliai; Kompiuterių liečiamieji ekranai; Jutikliniai ekranai; Išmaniųjų telefonų ekranai; Šviesos diodai [LED]; Šviesos diodų ekranai; Organiniai šviesos diodai; Monitoriai; Grūdinto stiklo ekrano apsaugos; Apsauginės plėvelės, pritaikytos išmaniesiems telefonams; Skystųjų kristalų monitoriai; Duomenų apdorojimo įranga ir kompiuteriai; Nešiojami kompiuteriai; Išmanieji telefonai; VR ausinių komplektai; Akiniai [optika]; Saulės akiniai; Glaustiniai (kontaktiniai) lęšiai; Ekrano filtrai; Ultravioletinių spindulių filtrai (ne medicinos reikmėms); Mėlynos bangos ilgio šviesos filtrai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Displeju ekrāniem pielāgotas aizsargplēves; Optiskie filtri ekrāniem; Krāsu filtri; Datoru ekrānu filtri; Optiskais stikls; Datoru ekrāni; Videoekrāni; Monitori; Datoru pieskārienekrāni; Skārienpaliktņi; Viedtelefonu ekrāni; Gaismas diodes [LED]; Gaismas diožu displeji; Organiskās gaismas diodes [OLED]; Vizuālās informācijas bloki; Rūdīta stikla ekrāna aizsargs; Viedtālruņiem pielāgotas aizsargplēves; Šķidro kristālu monitori; Datu apstrādes iekārtas un datori; Klēpjdatori; Viedtālruņi; VR galvas komplekti; Brilles; Saulesbrilles; Kontaktlēcas; Displeju ekrānu filtri; Ultravioleto staru filtri nemedicīniskiem nolūkiem; Filtri zilajam viļņa garumam.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Films protettivi adattati għall-iskrins tal-wiri; Filtri ottiċi għall-iskrins; Filtri tal-kulur; Skrins bħala filtri għall-iskrins tal-kompjuter; Ħġieġ ottiku; Skrins tal-kompjuter; Skrins tal-vidjo; Skrins tad-displej; Skrins tal-kompjuter li jaħdmu bil-mess; Pannelli li jippermetti l-użu tal-kompjuter billi wieħed imiss partijiet mill-pannelli (touch panels); Skrins għal smartfowns; Dajowds li jarmu d-dawl [LED]; Displej tad-dajowds li jagħtu d-dwal; Dajowds organiċi li jagħtu d-dawl [OLED]; Moniters; Protezzjoni tal-iskrin tal-ħġieġ imwebbes; Films protettivi adattati għal smartfowns; Moniters LCD; Tagħmir u kompjuters li jipproċessaw id-data; Leptops; Smartfowns; Kuffji tar-realtà virtwali; Nuċċalijiet [ottiċi]; Nuċċalijiet tax-xemx; Lenti tal-kuntatt; Filtri tal-iskrin; Filtri tal-ultravjola, minbarra għall-użu mediku; Filtri għad-dawl b'tul tal-mewġa blu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Speciale beschermende folies voor beeldschermen; Optische filters voor schermen; Kleurenfilters; Filterschermen voor computerschermen; Optisch glas; Computermonitors; Videoschermen; Beeldschermen; Aanraakbeeldschermen voor computers; Touchpanels; Beeldschermen voor slimme telefoons; Light Emitting Diodes; LED-schermen; Organische lichtemitterende diodes [OLED]; Monitoren; Schermbeschermers van gehard glas; Speciale beschermende folies voor smartphones; Lcd-monitoren; Computerapparatuur; Laptops; Smartphones; Hoofdtelefoons voor virtuele werkelijkheid; Brillen; Zonnebrillen; En contactlenzen; Beeldschermfilters; Filters (Ultraviolet -), anders dan voor medisch gebruik; Filters voor licht met een blauwe golflengte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Folie ochronne przystosowane do ekranów wyświetlaczy; Filtry optyczne do ekranów; Filtry barwne; Filtry do ekranów komputerowych; Szkło optyczne; Monitory komputerowe; Ekrany wideo; Wyświetlacze; Komputerowe ekrany dotykowe; Panele dotykowe; Ekrany do smartfonów; Diody świecące [LED]; Wyświetlacze z diodami elektroluminescencyjnymi; Organiczne diody elektroluminescencyjne [OLED]; Monitory; Ochrona ekranu ze szkła hartowanego; Folie ochronne przystosowane do smartfonów; Monitory ciekłokrystaliczne [LCD]; Urządzenia do przetwarzania informacji i komputerów; Laptopy; Smartfony; Zestawy słuchawkowe do rzeczywistości wirtualnej; Okulary [optyka]; Okulary przeciwsłoneczne; Kontaktowe (szkła -); Filtry do ekranów; Filtry ultrafioletowe, inne niż do celów medycznych; Filtry do światła o długości fali światła niebieskiego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Películas de proteção para ecrãs de visualização; Filtros óticos para ecrãs; Filtros de cor; Filtros para ecrãs de computador; Vidro ótico; Monitores de computador; Ecrãs de vídeo; Monitores de visualização; Ecrãs tácteis de computador; Painéis sensíveis ao toque; Ecrãs para telefones inteligentes; Díodos eletroluminiscentes [LED]; Ecrãs de díodos emissores de luz; Díodos emissores de luz orgânicos [OLED]; Monitores; Proteção de ecrã em vidro temperado; Películas de proteção para telefones inteligentes; Monitores com ecrãs de cristais líquidos; Dispositivos informáticos; Computadores portáteis; Smartphones; Headsets de realidade virtual; Óculos [ótica]; Óculos de sol; E lentes de contacto; Filtros para ecrãs de visualização; Filtros para raios ultravioletas, sem ser para uso médico; Filtros para luz com comprimento de onda azul.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Folii de protecție adaptate pentru ecrane de afișare; Filtre optice pentru ecrane; Fotografii color; Filtre pentru ecrane de calculator; Sticlă optică; Ecrane de computer; Ecrane video; Ecrane de afişare; Ecrane tactile computerizate; Ecrane tactile; Ecrane pentru telefoane inteligente; Diode electroluminescente [LED]; Ecrane cu diode emiţătoare de lumină; Diode organice electroluminescente [OLED]; Monitoare; Protecție de ecran din sticlă securizată; Folii de protecţie adaptate pentru telefoane inteligente; Monitoare LCD; Aparate pentru prelucrarea datelor; Laptop-uri; Telefoane inteligente; Căști VR; Ochelari [optică]; Ochelari de soare; Lentile de contact; Filtre pentru ecrane de afişare; Filtre ultraviolete, altele decât cele de uz medical; Filtre pentru lumina cu lungime de undă albastră.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ochranné fólie prispôsobené pre obrazovky; Optické filtre pre obrazovky; Farebné filtre; Filtre pre počítačové obrazovky; Optické sklo; Počítačové monitory; Video obrazovky; Obrazovky; Počítačové dotykové obrazovky; Dotykové panely; Obrazovky na smartfóny; Elektroluminiscenčné diódy (LED diódy); LED displeje; Organické elektroluminiscenčné diódy [OLED]; Monitory; Chrániče obrazoviek z temperovaného skla; Ochranné fólie prispôsobené pre smartfóny; LCD monitory; Vybavenie na spracovanie údajov a počítače; Notebooky; Smartfóny; Headsety pre virtuálnu realitu; Okuliare; Slnečné okuliare; Kontaktné šošovky; Filtre obrazoviek; Ultrafialové filtre na iné ako lekárske účely; Filtre svetla v modrých vlnových dĺžkach.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zaščitne folije, prilagojene za zaslone prikazovalnikov; Optični filtri za zaslone; Barvni filtri; Filtri računalniških ekranov; Optično steklo; Računalniški zasloni; Video zasloni; Prikazovalni zasloni; Računalniški zasloni na dotik; Plošče na dotik; Zasloni za pametne telefone; Svetleče diode [LED]; Prikazovalniki LED diod; Organske svetleče diode [OLED]; Monitorji; Ščitnik zaslona iz kaljenega stekla; Zaščitne folije, prilagojene za pametne telefone; LCD zasloni; Oprema in računalniki za procesiranje podatkov; Prenosni računalniki; Pametni telefoni; VR slušalke; Očala [optika]; Sončna očala; Kontakne leče; Filtri za prikazovalne zaslone; Ultravijolični filtri, razen za medicinsko uporabo; Filtri za svetlobo modre valovne dolžine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Skyddsfilmer anpassade för bildskärmar; Optiska filter för skärmar; Färgfilter; Filterskärmar för datorskärmar; Optiskt glas; Datorbildskärmar; Videoskärmar; Bildskärmar; Beröringskänsliga bildskärmar för datorer (touch screens); Beröringskänsliga paneler; Skärmar för smarttelefoner; Lysdioder [LED]; LED-displayer; Organiska ljusemitterande dioder [OLED]; Monitorer (skärmar); Skärmskydd av härdat glas; Skyddsfilmer anpassade för smarttelefoner; LCD-bildskärmar; Databehandlingsapparater; Bärbara datorer [laptops]; Smartphones; VR-headsets; Glasögon; Solglasögon; Samt kontaktlinser; Filter för visningsskärmar; Ultravioletta filter, (inte för medicinska ändamål); Filter för ljus av blå våglängd.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги в областта на рекламата и маркетинга; Насърчаване на продажбите [за трети лица]; Консултантски услуги във връзка с комуникационна стратегия за реклама.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Reklama a marketing; Podpora prodeje jiných osob; Poradenství v oblasti komunikační strategie v reklamě.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Reklame- og annoncevirksomhed samt marketing; Salgsfremmende foranstaltninger for andre; Rådgivning om reklamestrategier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werbung und Marketing; Verkaufsförderung [Sales promotion] [für Dritte]; Beratung in Bezug auf Kommunikationsstrategien in der Werbung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαφήμιση και μάρκετινγκ· Προώθηση πωλήσεων [για τρίτους]· Παροχή συμβουλών σε σχέση με στρατηγική επικοινωνίας μέσω διαφήμισης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Advertising and marketing services; sales promotion for others; consultancy regarding advertising communication strategies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicidad y marketing; Promoción de ventas para terceros; Consultoría en estrategias de comunicación [publicidad].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reklaami- ja turundusteenused; Müügikampaaniad, -reklaam teenusena; Reklaami kommunikatsioonistrateegiakonsultatsiooniteenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mainonta ja markkinointi; Myynninedistäminen [muille]; Mainosviestintästrategiaa koskeva konsultointi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publicité et marketing; Promotion des ventes pour des tiers; Conseils en communication [publicité].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Oglašavanje i marketing; Promicanje prodaje za treće osobe; Konzultantske usluge za komunikacijsku strategiju za oglašavanje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Reklám és marketing; Értékesítési promóciós szolgáltatások; Reklámkommunikációs stratégiára vonatkozó tanácsadás.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicità e marketing; Promozione delle vendite per i terzi; Consulenza nelle strategie di comunicazione nella pubblicità.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Reklama ir rinkodara; Prekių pardavimo skatinimas [kitiems]; Reklamos skleidimo strategijos parinkimo konsultacijos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reklāmas un mārketinga pakalpojumi; Preču noieta veicināšana trešajām personām; Konsultācijas saistībā ar reklāmas komunikācijas stratēģiju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reklamar u kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Il-promozzjoni tal-bejgħ għal oħrajn; Konsulenza relatata ma' strateġija ta' komunikazzjoni tar-reklamar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reclame en marketing; Verkooppromotie [voor derden]; Consultancy over reclame communicatie strategie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Reklama i marketing; Promocja sprzedaży dla osób trzecich; Doradztwo w dziedzinie strategii komunikacyjnych w reklamie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicidade e marketing; Promoção de vendas [para terceiros]; Consultoria sobre estratégias de comunicações publicitárias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicitate şi marketing; Promovarea vânzărilor pentru terţi; Consultanţă cu privire la strategia de comunicare în domeniul publicităţii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reklama a marketing; Podpora predaja (pre tretie osoby); Poradenstvo v oblasti komunikácie (reklama).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oglaševanje in marketing; Pospeševanje prodaje (za druge); Svetovanje o komunikacijski strategiji za oglaševanje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Annons- och reklamverksamhet samt marknadsföring; Sales promotiontjänster; Konsultverksamhet avseende kommunikationsstrategier för reklam.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Тестване, анализ и оценка на стоките на други лица за определяне на съответствието с указанията и стандартите за безопасност; Издаване на сертификати и/или марки за качество на тествани услуги, материали, вещества, продукти, производствени съоръжения, процеси, документация и/или информационни документи; Тестване на модели на продуктие оборудване и апарати по отношение на съответствието с основните изисквания, както е посочено в действащите в момента насоки; Разработване на продукти и консултантски услуги; Услуги за контрол на качествотото и за удостоверяване; Изпитване на материали; Проучване и разработване на продукти, за трети лица.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Testování, analýzy a hodnocení výrobků druhých za účelem stanovení shody s bezpečnostními směrnicemi a normami; Vydávání certifikátů a/nebo značek kvality pro testované služby, materiály, látky, výrobky, výrobní zařízení, procesy, dokumentaci a/nebo informační dokumenty; Testování modelů výrobků, zařízení a přístrojů z hlediska shody se základními požadavky uvedenými v aktuálně platných směrnicích; Vývoj výrobků a konzultační služby; Služby kontroly kvality a ověřování; Testování materiálů; Vývoj a výzkum výrobků pro druhé.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Afprøvning, analyse og vurdering af tredjeparts varer med henblik på sikring af overensstemmelse med sikkerhedsvejledninger og -standarder; Udstedelse af certifikater og/eller kvalitetsmærker til afprøvede tjenesteydelser, materialer, stoffer, produkter, produktionsanlæg, processer, dokumentation og/eller informationsdokumenter; Testning af produktmodeller, udstyr og apparater med henblik på overholdelse af grundlæggende krav som specificeret i de indeværende gældende retningslinjer; Produktudvikling og rådgivning; Kvalitetskontrol og autentificeringstjenester; Afprøvning af materialer; Forskning og udvikling af produkter (for andre).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Prüfung, Analyse und Bewertung der Waren Dritter zur Feststellung der Einhaltung von Sicherheitsrichtlinien und -standards; Ausstellung von Zertifikaten und/oder Qualitätszeichen für geprüfte Dienstleistungen, Materialien, Substanzen, Produkte, Produktionsanlagen, Prozesse, Dokumentations- und/oder Informationsdokumente; Prüfung von Produktmodellen, Ausrüstung und Apparaten hinsichtlich der Einhaltung der Mindestanforderungen gemäß der Angaben in den aktuell geltenden Richtlinien; Produktentwicklung und -beratung; Qualitätskontrolle und Authentifizierungsdienstleistungen; Materialprüfung; Forschung und Entwicklung von Produkten für Dritte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δοκιμή, ανάλυση και αξιολόγηση προϊόντων τρίτων για καθορισμό της συμμόρφωσης προς κατευθυντήριες οδηγίες και πρότυπα ασφαλείας· Έκδοση πιστοποιητικών και/ή σημάτων ποιότητας για δοκιμασμένες υπηρεσίες, υλικά, ουσίες, προϊόντα, εγκαταστάσεις παραγωγής, διαδικασίες, έγγραφα τεκμηρίωσης και/ή πληροφοριών· Δοκιμή μοντέλων προϊόντων, εξοπλισμού και συσκευών σε σχέση με τη συμμόρφωσή τους προς τις βασικές απαιτήσεις όπως αυτές ορίζονται στις ισχύουσες κατευθυντήριες γραμμές· Υπηρεσίες ανάπτυξης προϊόντων και παροχής συμβουλών· Υπηρεσίες ελέγχου ποιότητας και πιστοποίησης γνησιότητας· Δοκιμασία υλικών· Έρευνα και ανάπτυξη προϊόντων, για λογαριασμό τρίτων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Testing, analysis and evaluation of the goods of others to determine conformity with safety guidelines and standards; issuing of certificates and/or quality marks for tested services, materials, substances, products, production facilities, processes, documentation and/or information documents; testing of product models, equipment and apparatus regarding conformity with basic requirements as specified in currently effective guidelines; product development and consulting services; quality control and authentication services; material testing; research and development of products for others.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pruebas, análisis y evaluación de productos de terceros para determinar la conformidad con las normas y directrices de seguridad; Emisión de certificados y/o marcas de calidad para servicios, materiales, sustancias, productos, instalaciones de producción, procesos, documentación y/o documentos de información probados; Prueba de modelos de producto, equipos y aparatos en lo referente a la conformidad con los requisitos básicos establecidos en las directrices actualmente vigentes; Servicios de consultoría y desarrollo de producto; Servicios de control de calidad y autenticación; Ensayo de materiales; Investigación y desarrollo de productos, para terceros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kolmandate isikute kaupade testimine, analüüsimine ja hindamine turvajuhistele ja standarditele vastavuse tagamiseks; Testitud teenuste, materjalide, ainete, toodete, tootmisrajatiste, protsesside, dokumentatsiooni ja/või teabedokumentide sertifikaatide ja/või kvaliteedimärkide väljastamine; Tootemudelite, seadmestike ja seadmete testimine seoses kehtivates suunistes määratletud põhinõuetega; Tootearendus- ja -konsultatsiooniteenused; Kvaliteedikontrolli- ja autentimisteenused; Materjalitestid, materjalide teimimine, testimine, katsetamine; Toodete uuringud ja arendamine kolmandatele isikutele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Muiden tarjoamien tavaroiden testaus, analysointi ja arviointi turvallisuusohjeiden ja -standardien noudattamisen varmistamiseksi; Todistusten ja/tai laatumerkkien myöntäminen testatuille palveluille, materiaaleille, aineille, tuotteille, tuotantotiloille, prosesseille, dokumentaatiolle ja/tai tietoasiakirjoille; Tuotemallien, laitteiden ja kojeiden testaus, joka liittyy sillä hetkellä voimassa olevissa ohjeissa määritettyjen perusvaatimusten noudattamiseen; Tuotekehitys- ja konsultointipalvelut; Laadunvalvonta- ja todentamispalvelut; Tekstiilien koestus; Tuotteiden tutkimus ja kehitys muiden lukuun.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Test, analyse et évaluation de produits de tiers afin de déterminer la conformité aux directives et normes de sécurité; Émission de certificats et/ou de marques de qualité pour services, matériaux, substances, produits, installations de production, procédés, documentation et/ou documents d'information testés; Test de modèles réduits de produits, équipements et appareils concernant la conformité aux exigences fondamentales telles que spécifiées dans les directives actuellement en vigueur; Services de développement et d'assistance en matière de produits; Services de contrôle qualité et d'authentification; Essai de matériaux; Recherche et développement de produits, pour des tiers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Testiranje, analiza i procjena proizvoda drugih radi utvrđivanja usklađenosti sa sigurnosnim smjernicama i standardima; Izdavanje certifikata i/ili oznaka kvalitete za testirane usluge, materijale, tvari, proizvode, postrojenja za proizvodnju, postupke, dokumentaciju i/ili informativne dokumente; Testiranje modela proizvoda, opreme i uređaja u vezi s usklađenosti s osnovnim zahtjevima navedenima u trenutačno važećim smjernicama; Usluge razvoja proizvoda i savjetovanja; Usluge kontrole kvalitete i utvrđivanja autentičnosti; Ispitivanje materijala; Istraživanje i razvoj novih proizvoda za treće osobe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Mások áruinak tesztelése, elemzése és kiértékelése a biztonsági irányelveknek és szabványoknak való megfelelés meghatározása céljából; Tanúsítványok és / vagy minőségi jelek kiadása a tesztelt szolgáltatások, anyagok, készítmények, termékek, gyártóberendezések, folyamatok, dokumentáció és / vagy információs dokumentumok számára; Terméktípusok, berendezések és készülékek tesztelése az alapvető követelményeknek való megfelelés szempontjából, a jelenleg hatályos iránymutatásokban meghatározottak szerint; Termékfejlesztési és tanácsadási szolgáltatások; Minőségbiztosítási és hitelesítési szolgáltatások; Anyagtesztelés; Termékek kutatása és fejlesztése külső felek számára.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Verifica, analisi e valutazione dei prodotti di terzi per determinare la conformità con linee guida e standard di sicurezza; Rilascio di certificati e/o marchi di qualità per servizi esaminati, materiali, sostanze, strutture di produzione, processi, documentazione e/o documenti informativi; Verifica di modelli di prodotto, apparecchiature e apparecchi riguardanti la conformità con le specifiche fondamentali delle linee guida attualmente effettive; Servizi di sviluppo e consulenza di prodotto; Servizi di controllo della qualità e di autenticazione; Collaudi di materiali; Ricerca e sviluppo di prodotti per conto terzi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kitų prekių testavimas, analizė ir įvertinimas, siekiant nustatyti atitiktį saugos gairėms ir standartams; Patikrintų paslaugų, medžiagų, medžiagų, gaminių, gamybos įrenginių, procesų, dokumentacijos ir (arba) informacinių dokumentų sertifikatų ir (arba) kokybės ženklų išdavimas; Gaminių modelių, įrangos ir aparatų tikrinimas, ar jie atitinka pagrindinius reikalavimus, nurodytus šiuo metu galiojančiose gairėse; Produktų kūrimo ir konsultavimo paslaugos; Kokybės tikrinimo ir tapatybės patvirtinimo paslaugos; Medžiagų bandymai; Produktų tyrimas ir tobulinimas tretiesiems asmenims.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Trešo personu preču pārbaude, analīze un novērtēšana, lai noteiktu atbilstību drošības vadlīnijām un standartiem; Sertifikātu un/vai kvalitātes zīmju izsniegšana pārbaudītajiem pakalpojumiem, materiāliem, vielām, izstrādājumiem, ražošanas objektiem, procesiem, dokumentācijai un/vai informācijas dokumentiem; Ražojumu modeļu, aprīkojuma un aparātu pārbaude attiecībā uz atbilstību pamatprasībām, kā noteikts pašreiz spēkā esošajās vadlīnijās; Produktu izstrāde un konsultāciju pakalpojumi; Kvalitātes kontroles un autentificēšanas pakalpojumi; Materiālu pārbaude; Preču izpēte un izstrāde trešo personu interesēs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ittestjar, analiżi u evalwazzjoni tal-prodotti ta' oħrajn biex tiġi ddeterminata l-konformità mal-linji gwida u l-istandards tas-sigurtà; Ħruġ ta' ċertifikati u/jew marki ta' kwalità għas-servizzi, għall-materjali, għas-sustanzi, għall-prodotti, għall-faċilitajiet tal-produzzjoni, għall-proċessi, għad-dokumentazzjoni u/jew għad-dokumenti ta' informazzjoni ttestjati; Ittestjar tal-mudelli tal-prodotti, tat-tagħmir u tal-apparat fir-rigward tal-konformità mar-rekwiżiti bażiċi kif speċifikat fil-linji gwida attwalment effettivi; Servizzi ta' żvilupp u konsultazzjoni tal-prodott; Servizzi ta' awtentikazzjoni u kontroll tal-kwalità; Testijiet ta' materjali; Riċerka u żvilupp ta' prodotti, għal terzi persuni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Het testen, analyseren en evalueren van de goederen van derden voor het vaststellen van de conformiteit met veiligheidsrichtlijnen en -normen; Afgifte van certificaten en/of kwaliteitsmerken voor tests, materialen, substanties, producten, productiefaciliteiten, processen, documentatie en/of informatiedocumenten; Het testen van productmodellen, uitrusting en apparaten in verband met de naleving van basiseisen zoals gespecificeerd in op dit moment geldende richtlijnen; Productontwikkeling en -advies; Diensten op het gebied van kwaliteitscontrole en authenticatie; Testen van materialen; Onderzoek en ontwikkeling van producten voor derden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Testowanie, analiza i ocena towarów innych osób do celów określania zgodności z wytycznymi i ze standardami w zakresie bezpieczeństwa; Wydawanie certyfikatów i/lub ocen jakości testowanych usług, materiałów, substancji, produktów, obiektów produkcyjnych, procesów, dokumentacji i/lub dokumentów zawierających informacje; Testowanie modeli produktów, sprzętu i urządzeń pod kątem zgodności z podstawowymi wymaganiami określonymi w aktualnie obowiązujących wytycznych; Rozwój produktów i usługi konsultacyjne; Usługi kontroli jakości i uwierzytelniania; Testowanie materiałów; Działalność badawczo-rozwojowa, dla osób trzecich.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Teste, análise e avaliação de produtos de terceiros tendo em vista determinar a conformidade com diretrizes e normas de segurança; Emissão de certificados e/ou de marcas de qualidade para serviços, materiais, substâncias, produtos, instalações de produção, processos, documentação e/ou documentos informativos testados; Teste de modelos de produtos, equipamentos e aparelhos no que respeita à conformidade com os requisitos básicos especificados nas diretrizes em vigência; Serviços de desenvolvimento e consultadoria no domínio dos produtos; Serviços de controlo de qualidade e de autenticação; Testes a materiais; Investigação e desenvolvimento de produtos para terceiros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Testare, analiză și evaluare a produselor altor persoane în vederea stabilirii conformității cu îndrumările și standardele de siguranță; Eliberare de certificate și/sau însemne de calitate pentru servicii testate, materiale, substanțe, produse, spații de produse, procese, documentație și/sau documente cu informații; Testare de modele de produse, echipamente și aparate cu privire la conformitatea cu cerințele de bază așa cum este specificat în prevederile în vigoare; Servicii de dezvoltare și consultanță cu privire la produse; Servicii de control de calitate și de autentificare; Testarea materialelor textile; Cercetare si dezvoltare de produse, pentru terti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Testovanie, analýzy a posudzovanie tovaru klientov s cieľom určiť zhodu s bezpečnostnými normami a predpismi; Vydávanie certifikátov a/alebo značiek kvality pre testované služby, materiály, látky, výrobky, výrobné zariadenia, procesy, dokumentáciu a/alebo informačné dokumenty; Testovanie modelov výrobkov, zariadení a prístrojov v zmysle súladu so základnými požiadavkami stanovenými v platných usmerneniach; Služby vývoja produktov a konzultačné služby; Služby kontroly kvality a overovania; Testovanie materiálov; Výskum a vývoj produktov pre tretie osoby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Testiranje, analiza in ocenjevanje izdelkov drugih za ugotavljanje skladnosti z varnostnimi smernicami in standardi; Izdajanje certifikatov in/ali oznak kakovosti za testirane storitve, materiale, snovi, izdelke, proizvodne obrate, procese, dokumentacijo in/ali dokumente z informacijami; Testiranje modelov izdelkov, opreme in aparatov za skladnost z osnovnimi zahtevami, kot je določeno v trenutno veljavnih smernicah; Storitve razvoja izdelkov in svetovanja o njih; Storitve nadzora kakovosti in preverjanja pristnosti; Testiranje materialov; Raziskave in razvoj izdelkov, za tretje osebe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Provning, analys och utvärdering av andras varor för att avgöra överensstämmelse med riktlinjer och normer för säkerhet; Utfärdande av certifikat och/eller kvalitetsmärken för provade tjänster, material, ämnen, produkter, produktionsanläggningar, processer, dokumentation och/eller informationsdokument; Provning av produktmodeller, utrustning och apparater avseende överensstämmelse med de grundläggande krav som anges i nu gällande riktlinjer; Produktutveckling och konsulttjänster; Kvalitetskontroll- och verifieringstjänster; Materialprovning; Forskning och utveckling av produkter (för andras räkning).</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/130</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-13</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/201</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-21</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>785266</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>10618</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
