<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-06T08:34:23</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228492</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228492</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-10-03</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>it</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-06</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>OSSERVATORIO IMMAGINO</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Електронни публикации, които могат да бъдат прехвърляни върху друг носител; Електронни публикации под формата на списания, с възможност за изтегляне от интернет; Електронни публикации [за сваляне] , достъпни чрез бази данни или интернет; Компютърни софтуерни приложения, за сваляне; Приложен софтуер.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Stahovatelné elektronické publikace; Elektronické publikace ke stažení v podobě časopisů; Elektronické publikace [ke stažení] dostupné prostřednictvím databází nebo internetu; Stahovatelné počítačové aplikace; Software aplikace.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Elektroniske publikationer, downloadable; Elektroniske tidsskrifter, der kan downloades; Elektroniske publikationer, der kan downloades fra databaser eller internettet; Softwareapplikationer til computere, downloadable; Applikationssoftware.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Herunterladbare elektronische Publikationen; Herunterladbare elektronische Publikationen in Form von Magazinen; Aus Datenbanken oder dem Internet herunterladbare elektronische Veröffentlichungen; Herunterladbare Software-Anwendungen für Computer; Anwendungssoftware.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ηλεκτρονικές εκδόσεις, με δυνατότητα μεταφόρτωσης· Τηλεφορτώσιμες ηλεκτρονικές εκδόσεις με τη μορφή περιοδικών· Ηλεκτρονικές εκδόσεις [με δυνατότητα τηλεφόρτωσης] από βάσεις δεδομένων ή από το Διαδίκτυο· Εφαρμογές λογισμικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών, μεταφορτώσιμες· Λογισμικό εφαρμογών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Electronic publications, downloadable; Downloadable electronic publications in the nature of magazines; Electronic publications (downloadable) available from databases or the Internet; Computer software applications, downloadable; Applications software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicaciones electrónicas descargables; Publicaciones electrónicas descargables [revistas]; Publicaciones electrónicas (descargables) desde bases de datos o Internet; Aplicaciones informáticas descargables; Software de aplicaciones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Elektroonilised allalaaditavad publikatsioonid; Allalaaditavad digiajakirjad; Elektronväljaanded [allalaaditavad] andmebaasidest või internetist; Allalaaditavad arvutitarkvararakendused; Rakenduslik tarkvara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Elektroniset julkaisut [järjestelmästä toiseen poimittavat]; Ladattavat elektroniset julkaisut aikakauslehtien muodossa; Tietokannoista tai Internetistä saatavat (ladattavat) elektroniset julkaisut; Ladattavat tietokoneohjelmistosovellukset; Sovellusohjelmistot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publications électroniques téléchargeables; Publications électroniques téléchargeables sous forme de revues; Publications électroniques [téléchargeables] pouvant être obtenues à partir de bases de données ou d'internet; Applications logicielles informatiques téléchargeables; Logiciels d'application.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Elektronske publikacije koje se mogu preuzeti s Interneta; Elektronske publikacije u obliku časopisa koje se mogu preuzimati; Elektroničke publikacije [koje se mogu preuzimati] dostupne putem baza podataka ili interneta; Aplikacije za računalne programe koje se mogu preuzeti s Interneta; Aplikacijski softver.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Letölthető elektronikus kiadványok, publikációk; Letölthető elektronikus kiadványok magazinok formájában; Adatbázisokról vagy Internetről megszerezhető [letölthető] elektronikus publikációk; Számítógépes szoftveralkalmazások, letölthető; Alkalmazási szoftver.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicazioni elettroniche [scaricabili]; pubblicazioni elettroniche scaricabili sotto forma di riviste; pubblicazioni elettroniche [scaricabili] ottenibili da banche dati o internet; applicazioni per computer software, scaricabili; software applicativi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektroniniai leidiniai [parsisiunčiamieji]; Parsisiunčiamieji žurnalų pobūdžio elektroniniai leidiniai; Elektroniniai leidiniai [atsisiunčiami], teikiami iš duomenų bazių ar interneto; Parsisiunčiamoji kompiuterių programinė įranga; Taikomoji programinė įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Lejupielādējamas elektroniskās publikācijas; Lejupielādējamas elektroniskās publikācijas periodisku izdevumu veidā; Elektroniskas publikācijas [lejupielādējamas], kuras var iegūt no datu bāzēm vai interneta; Lejupielādējamas datorprogrammu lietotnes; Lietojumprogrammu programmatūra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi, li jistgħu jitniżżlu; Pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi li jistgħu jitniżżlu fl-għamla ta' rivisti; Pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi [li jistgħu jitniżżlu] jinkisbu minn dejtabejżis jew l-Internet; Applikazzjonijiet ta' softwer tal-kompjuter, li jitniżżlu; Softwer ta' applikazzjoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Elektronische publicaties [te downloaden]; Downloadbare elektronische publicaties in de vorm van tijdschriften; Elektronische publicaties [downloadbaar] te verkrijgen vanuit databases of via internet; Downloadbare computersoftware-applicaties; Toepassingssoftware.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Publikacje elektroniczne, do pobrania; Publikacje elektroniczne do pobrania w postaci magazynów; Publikacje elektroniczne (do pobrania), udostępniane za pośrednictwem baz danych lub internetu; Aplikacje komputerowe do pobrania; Oprogramowanie użytkowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicações eletrónicas descarregáveis; Publicações eletrónicas para download sob a forma de revistas; Publicações eletrónicas [transferíveis] através de bases de dados ou da Internet; Aplicações de software informático descarregáveis; Software de aplicação.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicații electronice descărcabile; Publicații electronice descărcabile sub formă de reviste; Publicaţii electronice [descărcabile] care pot fi obţinute din baze de date sau de pe internet; Aplicații software de calculator, descărcabile; Software de aplicaţii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Elektronické publikácie (sťahovateľné); Stiahnuteľné elektronické publikácie v podobe časopisov; Elektronické publikácie [s možnosťou stiahnutia] poskytované z databázy alebo internetu; Počítačové softvérové aplikácie (sťahovateľné); Aplikačný softvér.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Naložljive elektronske publikacije; Naložljive elektronske publikacije v obliki revij; Elektronske publikacije [prenosljive], ki so na voljo v podatkovnih bazah ali na internetu; Računalniška programska oprema, naložljiva preko računalniške mreže; Aplikacijska programska oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tidskrifter (elektroniska), nedladdningsbara; Nedladdningsbara elektroniska publikationer i form av tidskrifter; Elektroniska publikationer [nedladdningsbara] som kan erhållas från databaser eller internet; Softwareapplikationer för datorer, nedladdningsbara; Tillämpningsprogram.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Печатни публикации; Списания (публикации); Печатни доклади за проучвания.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Tištěné publikace; Časopisy (publikace); Tištěné průzkumné zprávy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Trykte publikationer; Blade (publikationer); Trykte forskningsrapporter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Schriften [Veröffentlichungen]; Magazine (Veröffentlichungen); Gedruckte Forschungsberichte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Έντυπες εκδόσεις· Περιοδικά (εκδόσεις)· Έντυπες ερευνητικές εκθέσεις.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Printed publications; Magazines (publication); Printed research reports.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicaciones impresas; Revistas (publicación); Informes de investigación impresos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Trükiväljaanded; Ajakirjad (väljaanded); Trükitud uuringuaruanded.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Julkaisut (painetut); Aikakauslehdet (julkaisut); Painetut tutkimusraportit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publications imprimées; Magazines (publications); Rapports de recherche imprimés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Publikacije; Časopisi (objavljivanje); Tiskana izvješća o istraživanjima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nyomtatott publikációk; Magazinok (kiadványok); Nyomtatott kutatási beszámolók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicazioni [stampate]; riviste [pubblicazioni]; rapporti di ricerca stampati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Spausdintiniai leidiniai; Žurnalai (leidyba); Spausdintinės tyrimų ataskaitos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Iespiestas publikācijas; Žurnāli (publikācijas); Iespiesti izpētes ziņojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pubblikazzjonijiet stampati; Magazins (pubblikazzjoni); Rapporti stampati dwar ir-riċerka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Gedrukte publicaties; Tijdschriften (uitgave); Gedrukte onderzoeksrapporten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Publikacje drukowane; Czasopisma (publikacja); Drukowane raporty z badań.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicações impressas; Revistas (publicação); Relatórios de pesquisa impressos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicații imprimate; Reviste (publicaţii); Rapoarte de cercetare tipărite.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Tlačené publikácie; Časopisy (publikácie); Tlačené výskumné správy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Tiskane publikacije; Revije (publikacija); Tiskana poročila o raziskavah.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tryckta publikationer; Tidskrifter (publikationer); Tryckta forskningsrapporter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Анализ на търговски данни; Статистически оценки на маркетинг данни; Статистически анализи и отчитане; Услуги за потребителски проучвания; Предоставяне на бизнес информация и съвети на клиентите във връзка със стоки и услуги; Пазарни проучвания; Услуги, свързани с провеждане на пазарни изследвания; Рекламни проучвания; Предоставяне на продуктова маркетингова информация и анализ и осигуряване на информационни и аналитични услуги относно продуктови продажби и информация; Консултантски услуги относно потребителските изследвания; Подготовка и компилация на бизнес и търговски доклади и информация.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Analýza obchodních dat; Statistické hodnocení marketingových dat; Statistické analýzy a podávání zpráv; Spotřebitelský výzkum; Poskytování obchodních informací a poradenství klientům v souvislosti s výrobky a službami; Analýzy trhu; Provádění marketingových studií; Reklamní průzkum; Poskytování marketingových informací a analýz výrobků a poskytování prodejních informací a analýz výrobků; Poradenství pro spotřebitelský průzkum; Příprava a sestavování zpráv a informací ohledně obchodní činnosti, obchodních zpráv a informací.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Analyse af forretningsmæssige data; Statistiske evalueringer af markedsføringsdata; Statistisk analyse og rapportering; Forskning i forbrugeranliggender; Salgsinformation og rådgivning til kunder om valg af produkter og tjenesteydelser; Markedsanalyse; Gennemførelse af marketingundersøgelser; Undersøgelser vedrørende annonce- og reklamevirksomhed; Formidling af markedsføringsoplysninger og -analyse vedrørende produkter og tilvejebringelse af oplysninger og analyse mht. salget af produkter; Rådgivning med hensyn til forbrugerundersøgelser; Udfærdigelse og kompilering af forretnings- og erhvervsrapporter og oplysninger.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Analyse von Handelsdaten; Statische Auswertungen von Marketingdaten; Erstellen von statistischen Analysen und Berichten; Verbraucherforschung; Bereitstellung von kommerziellen Informationen und Beratung für Verbraucher in Bezug auf Waren und Dienstleistungen; Marktanalysen; Leitung von Marketingstudien; Werbeforschung; Bereitstellung von Auskünften und Analysen zum Produktmarketing und Bereitstellung von Auskünften und Analysen zu Produktverkäufen; Beratung in Bezug auf Verbraucherforschung; Erarbeitung und Zusammenstellung von Geschäfts- und Handelsberichten und -informationen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ανάλυση εμπορικών δεδομένων· Στατιστική αξιολόγηση δεδομένων μάρκετινγκ· Στατιστική ανάλυση και αναφορά· Υπηρεσίες έρευνας καταναλωτών· Παροχή επιχειρηματικών πληροφοριών και συμβουλών σε πελάτες σε σχέση με προϊόντα και υπηρεσίες· Ανάλυση αγοράς· Διεξαγωγή μελετών μάρκετινγκ· Μελέτες προώθησης· Παροχή πληροφοριών και αναλύσεων εμπορίας (μάρκετινγκ) προϊόντων και παροχή πληροφοριών και αναλύσεων σε σχέση με πωλήσεις προϊόντων· Παροχή συμβουλών σε σχέση με έρευνα καταναλωτών· Κατάρτιση και συλλογή επιχειρηματικών και εμπορικών εκθέσεων και πληροφοριών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">commercial data analysis; Statistical evaluations of marketing data; Statistical analysis and reporting; Consumer research; Providing commercial information and advice for consumers in the choice of products and services; Market analysis; Conducting of marketing studies; Advertising research; providing product marketing information and analysis and providing product sales information and analysis services; consumer research consulting; Preparation and compilation of business and commercial reports and information.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Análisis de datos comerciales; Evaluaciones estadísticas de datos de mercadotecnia; Análisis y elaboración de informes estadísticos; Servicios de investigación sobre consumidores; Facilitación de información y asesoramiento comercial en relación con productos y servicios; Análisis de mercado; Realización de estudios de marketing; Investigación publicitaria; Prestación de servicios de información y análisis de marketing de productos y prestación de servicios de información y análisis de ventas de productos; Servicios de consultoría sobre investigación de consumidores; Preparación y compilación de información e informes comerciales y de negocios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Äriandmeanalüüs; Turundusandmete statistilised hinnangud; Statistikaanalüüs ja -aruandlus; Tarbijauuringuteenused; klientidele äriteabe ja -nõustamise pakkumine seoses kaupade ja teenustega; Turuanalüüs; Turu-uuringute teostamine; Reklaamiuuringud; Tooteturundusteabe ja -analüüsi pakkumine ning tootemüügi teabe- ja analüüsiteenuste pakkumine; Tarbijauuringute konsulteerimine; Äri- ja kaubandusaruannete ja -info ettevalmistamine ja koostamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kaupallinen data-analyysi; Markkinatietojen tilastollinen arviointi; Tilastoanalyysit ja -raportit; Kuluttajatutkimuspalvelut; Asiakkaille yritystietojen ja -neuvonnan tarjoaminen tavaroiden ja palveluiden alalla; Markkina-analyysit; Markkinointitutkimukset; Mainontatutkimukset; Tuotemarkkinointiin liittyvien tietojen ja analyysien tarjoaminen ja tuotemyyntiin liittyvien tietojen ja analyysien tarjoaminen palveluna; Kuluttajatutkimuksia koskeva konsultointi; Liiketoiminta- ja kaupallisten raporttien ja tietojen valmistelu ja kokoaminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Analyse de données commerciales; évaluations statistiques de données de marketing; Rapports et analyses statistiques; Services de recherche en matière de consommation; Mise à disposition d'informations et de conseils commerciaux aux clients en lien avec des produits et services; Analyse de marché; Réalisation d'études de marketing; Études publicitaires; Fourniture d'informations et d'analyses liées au marketing de produits et fourniture de services d'informations et d'analyses liées aux ventes de produits; Assistance liée à la recherche marketing en matière de consommation; Services de préparation et regroupement de rapports et renseignements commerciaux et d'affaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Analiza komercijalnih podataka; Statistička procjena marketinških podataka; Statistička analiza i izvještavanje; Usluge istraživanja u vezi s potrošačima; Pružanje poslovnih informacija i savjeta klijentima u vezi s proizvodima i uslugama; Analize tržišta; Vođenje marketinških studija; Istraživanje u području reklamiranja; Pružanje marketinških informacija i analiza o proizvodima, te pružanje usluga informiranja i analize prodaje proizvoda; Savjetovanje o istraživanju potrošača; Priprema i sastavljanje poslovnih i komercijalnih izvješća te informacija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kereskedelmi adatelemzés; Marketingadatok statisztikai értékelése; Statisztikai elemzés és jelentéskészítés; Fogyasztókkal kapcsolatos kutatási szolgáltatások; Üzleti információk és tanácsadás az ügyfelek számára árukkal és szolgáltatásokkal kapcsolatban; Piacanalízis; Marketing tanulmányok készítése; Reklámozási kutatás; Termékmarketing-információk és -elemzés biztosítása, valamint termékértékesítési információk és elemzési szolgáltatások nyújtása; Fogyasztókutatási tanácsadás; Üzleti és kereskedelmi beszámolók és információk előkészítése és összeállítása.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Analisi di dati commerciali; valutazione statistica di dati di marketing; analisi e rapporti statistici; servizi di ricerca sui consumatori; fornitura di informazioni commerciali e consulenza ai consumatori nella scelta di prodotti e servizi; analisi di studi di mercato; conduzione di studi di marketing; Ricerche pubblicitarie; Informazioni e analisi di marketing su prodotti e informazioni di vendite e servizi di analisi su prodotti; Consulenza in materia di ricerca sui consumatori; preparazione e compilazione di rapporti e informative aziendali e commerciali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Komercinių duomenų analizė; Rinkodaros statistinių duomenų vertinimas; Statistinė analizė ir ataskaitų rengimas; Vartotojų tyrimų paslaugos; Verslo informacijos ir patarimų, susijusių su prekėmis ir paslaugomis, teikimas klientams; Rinkos analizė; Rinkodaros nagrinėjimas; Reklamos tyrimų paslaugos; Teikiant produktų rinkodaros informaciją ir analizę bei teikiant produktų pardavimo informacijos ir analizės paslaugas; Vartotojų mokslinių tyrimų konsultacijos; Verslo ir prekybos ataskaitų bei informacijos ruošimas ir rinkimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Komerciālo datu analīze; Tirgvedības datu statistikas vērtēšana; Statistiskā analīze un pārskati; Patērētāju izpētes pakalpojumi; Klientiem uzņēmējdarbības informācijas un konsultēšanas piedāvāšana saistībā ar precēm un pakalpojumiem; Tirgus analīze; Mārketinga pētījumu veikšana; Reklāmas pētījumi; Preču tirgvedības informācijas un analīzes nodrošināšana, tostarp preču tirdzniecības informācijas un analīzes pakalpojumu nodrošināšana; Patērētāju izpētes konsultācijas.; Uzņēmējdarbības un tirdzniecības atskaišu un informācijas sagatavošana un apkopošana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Analiżi ta' dejta kummerċjali; Analiżi statistika ta' data tal-kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Analiżi permezz tal-istatistika u rappurtaġġ; Servizzi ta' riċerka dwar il-konsumaturi; Provvista ta' informazzjoni u konsulenza kummerċjali lill-konsumaturi fil-qasam ta' oġġetti u servizzi; Analiżi tas-suq; It-tmexxija ta' studji dwar il-kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Riċerka dwar l-irreklamar; Il-provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar marketing ta' prodotti u l-analiżi u l-provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar bejgħ ta' prodotti u servizzi ta' analiżi; Konsulenza għal riċerka dwar il-konsumatur; It-tħejjija u l-ġabra ta' rapporti u informazzjoni dwar in-negozju u l-kummerċ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Commerciële analyse van gegevens; Statistische evaluatie van marketinggegevens; Statistische analyse en rapportage; Onderzoek naar consumenten; Het aan klanten ter beschikking stellen van zakelijke informatie en adviezen inzake goederen en diensten; Marktanalyse; Marketingstudies; Reclame-onderzoek; Het aanbieden van informatie en analyse met betrekking tot productmarketing en het aanbieden van informatie en analyse met betrekking tot productverkoop; Advies inzake consumentenonderzoek; Het op- en samenstellen van zakelijke en commerciële rapporten en informatie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Analiza danych handlowych; Statystyczne oceny danych marketingowych; Analizy i raporty statystyczne; Usługi w zakresie badań konsumenckich; Oferowanie klientom informacji i doradztwa handlowego w zakresie towarów i usług; Analiza rynku; Prowadzenie badań marketingowych; Badania w zakresie reklamy; Usługi udzielania informacji i udostępniania analiz dotyczących marketingu produktu oraz udzielania informacji i udostępniania analiz dotyczących sprzedaży produktu; Doradztwo dotyczące badań konsumentów; Przygotowywanie i kompilacja raportów i informacji biznesowych i handlowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Análise de dados comerciais; Avaliações estatísticas de dados de marketing; Análise e preparação de relatórios de estatísticas; Serviços de pesquisa sobre os consumidores; Serviços de aconselhamento e informação comercial aos consumidores na escolha de produtos e serviços; Análises de mercado; Execução de estudos de marketing; Investigação em publicidade; Fornecimento de informações e análises sobre marketing de produtos e fornecimento de serviços de informações e análises sobre vendas de produtos; Consultadoria em matéria de pesquisas de consumo; Preparação e compilação de relatórios e informações comerciais e de negócios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Analiză de date comerciale; Evaluări statistice de date de marketing; Analize și rapoarte statistice; Servicii de studii pe consumatori; Furnizarea de informații și asistență pentru clienți în legătură cu produse și servicii; Analize de piață; Efectuarea studiilor de marketing; Cercetare în domeniul publicității; Furnizarea de informații și analize despre marketingul produselor și furnizarea de servicii de informații și analiză despre vânzările de produse; Consultanță în cercetarea clienților; Pregătire și compilare de rapoarte și informații de afaceri și comerciale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Analýza komerčných údajov; Štatistické vyhodnocovanie marketingových údajov; Štatistická analýza a správy; Prieskum spotrebiteľov; Poskytovanie obchodných informácií a poradenstva klientom v oblasti tovaru a služieb; Analýza trhu; Vedenie marketingových štúdií; Prieskum v oblasti reklamy; Poskytovanie produktových marketingových informácií a analýz a poskytovanie informačných a analytických služieb v oblasti predaja produktov; Konzultácie v oblasti spotrebiteľského prieskumu; Príprava a zostavovanie podnikateľských a obchodných správ a informácií.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Analiza komercialnih podatkov; Statistično vrednotenje tržnih podatkov; Statistična analiza in poročanje; Raziskovalne storitve za potrošnike; Nudenje poslovnih informacij in svetovanj strankam v zvezi z izdelki in storitvami; Analize trga; Izvajanje tržnih študij; Oglaševalsko raziskovanje; Nudenje informacij in analize trženja izdelkov ter nudenje informacij in analize prodaje izdelkov; Svetovanje v zvezi s potrošniki; Priprava in zbiranje poslovnih in komercialnih poročil ter informacij.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Analys av kommersiella data; Statistisk utvärdering av marknadsföringsdata; Statistisk analys och rapportering; Konsumentforskning; Erbjudande om affärsinformation och -rådgivning till kunder avseende varor och tjänster; Marknadsanalys; Utförande av marknadsföringsstudier; Undersökningar avseende reklam; Tillhandahållande av produktmarknadsföringsinformation och analys och tillhandahållande av produktförsäljningsinformation och analystjänster; Konsumentforskningskonsultation; Förberedelse och sammanställning av företags- och kommersiella rapporter och information.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за електронно публикуване; Доставка на онлайн електронни публикации [без възможност да бъдат прехвърляни върху друг носител]; Услуги за видео, аудио и мултимедийни цифрови публикации за развлечение; Мултимедийно издаване на списания, журнали и вестници; Организиране и провеждане на конференции, конвенции, изложби, лекции, дисертации, семинари и работни срещи [обучение]; Провеждане на образователни мероприятия.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vydávání elektronických publikací; Poskytování elektronických publikací online bez možnosti stažení; Digitální video, audio a multimediální zábavní vydavatelské služby; Multimediální publikování časopisů, žurnálů a novin; Organizování a realizace konferencí, setkání, výstav, lekcí, disertací, seminářů a workshopů [vzdělávání]; Vedení vzdělávacích akcí.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Elektronisk desktop publicering; Tilvejebringelse af online elektroniske publikationer, ikke downloadable; Udsendelsestjenester vedrørende digital video-, lyd- og multimedieunderholdning; Multimedieudgivelse af blade, tidsskrifter og aviser; Arrangering og ledelse af konferencer, møder, udstillinger, undervisning, afhandlinger, seminarer og workshopper (kurser); Ledelse af uddannelsesarrangementer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Publizieren von elektronischen Veröffentlichungen; Online-Bereitstellung von nicht herunterladbaren elektronischen Publikationen; Veröffentlichung von digitaler Video-, Audio- und Multimediaunterhaltung; Multimediaveröffentlichung von Zeitschriften, Journalen und Zeitungen; Planung und Durchführung von Konferenzen, Tagungen, Ausstellungen, Vorlesungen, Kolloquien, Seminaren und Workshops [Ausbildung]; Veranstaltung von Bildungsveranstaltungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ηλεκτρονικές εκδόσεις,· Παροχή ηλεκτρονικών εκδόσεων, χωρίς δυνατότητα τηλεφόρτωσης· Υπηρεσίες ψυχαγωγικών εκδόσεων ψηφιακού βίντεο, ήχου και πολυμέσων· Πολυμεσική έκδοση περιοδικών και εφημερίδων· Οργάνωση και διεξαγωγή συνεδρίων, διασκέψεων, εκθέσεων, διαλέξεων, διατριβών, σεμιναρίων και εργαστηρίων [επιμόρφωση]· Διεξαγωγή εκπαιδευτικών εκδηλώσεων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Electronic publishing services; Providing online electronic publications, not downloadable; Digital video, audio and multimedia entertainment publishing services; Multimedia publishing of magazines, journals and newspapers; Arranging and conducting of conferences, conventions, exhibitions, classes, lectures, seminars and workshops [training]; Conducting of educational events.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicación electrónica; Suministro de publicaciones electrónicas en línea, que no sean descargables; Servicios de publicación de contenidos de entretenimiento multimedia, de audio y de vídeo digital; Publicación multimedia de revistas, revistas especializadas y diarios; Organización y realización de conferencias, congresos, exposiciones, clases, presentaciones, seminarios y talleres [formación]; Celebración de eventos educativos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Elektrooniline kirjastamine; Elektronväljaannete pakkumine arvutivõrgus, v.a allalaaditavad; Digitaalsed video-, audio- ja multimeediameelelahutuse avaldamisteenused; Ajakirjade ja ajalehtede avaldamine multimeedias; Konverentside, kokkutulekute, näituste, loengute, arutelude, seminaride ja õpikodade korraldamine ja läbiviimine [koolitus]; Haridusürituste läbiviimine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Elektroniset julkaisupalvelut; Sähköisten, ei-ladattavien julkaisujen on-line tarjoaminen; Digitaalisen video-, ääni- ja multimediaviihteen julkaisupalvelut; Aikakauslehtien, lehtien ja sanomalehtien multimediajulkaiseminen; Konferenssien, kokousten, näyttelyjen, luentojen, tieteellisten tutkielmien, seminaarien ja työpajojen järjestäminen ja toteutus (koulutus); Koulutustapahtumien toteuttaminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publication par voie électronique; Mise à disposition de publications électroniques en ligne non téléchargeables; Services d'édition de divertissement multimédia, audio et vidéo numérique; Édition multimédia de revues, de revues spécialisées et de journaux; Organisation et réalisation de conférences, conventions, expositions, cours, dissertations, séminaires et ateliers [formation]; Coordination d'évènements éducatifs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Elektroničko izdavaštvo; Pružanje elektroničkih publikacija koje se ne mogu preuzimati; Izdavačke usluge za digitalnu, audio i multimedijsku zabavu; Multimedijsko izdavanje časopisa, žurnala i novina; Organiziranje i provođenje konferencija, skupova, izložbi, predavanja, disertacija, seminara i radionica [izobrazba]; Izvođenje obrazovnih događanja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Elektronikus kiadványok megjelentetése; Online elektronikus kiadványok biztosítása, nem letölthetők; Digitális videó, audió és multimédia kiadási szolgáltatások; Magazinok, folyóiratok és újságok multimédiás megjelentetése; Konferenciák, összejövetelek, kiállítások, előadások, disszertációk, szemináriumok és workshopok szervezése és lebonyolítása [képzés]; Oktatási rendezvények lebonyolítása.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicazioni tramite computer; fornitura online di pubblicazioni elettroniche non scaricabili; servizi di pubblicazione di contenuti ricreativi multimediali e di audio e video digitali; pubblicazione multimediale di riviste, riviste specializzate e giornali; organizzazione e realizzazione di conferenze, convention, esposizioni, lezioni, dissertazioni, seminari e workshop [formazione]; realizzazione di eventi educativi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektroninės leidybos paslaugos; Elektroninių publikacijų tiesioginis pateikimas per kompiuterių tinklą (ne parsisiunčiamųjų); Skaitmeninės vaizdo, garso ir pramoginės multimedijos leidybos paslaugos; Žurnalų, specializuotų žurnalų ir laikraščių multimedijos leidyba; Konferencijų, suvažiavimų, ekspozicijų, paskaitų, disertacijų, seminarų ir dirbtuvių [mokymo] organizavimas ir rengimas; Švietimo renginių vedimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elektroniskā publicēšana; Nelejupielādējamu elektronisku publikāciju nodrošināšana tiešsaistē; Digitālās video, audio un multivides izklaides publicēšanas pakalpojumi; Periodisko izdevumu, žurnālu un laikrakstu publicēšana multividē; Konferenču, izstāžu, lekciju, priekšlasījumu, semināru un darbsemināru [apmācības] organizēšana un vadība; Izglītojošu pasākumu vadīšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' pubblikar elettroniku; Provvista ta' pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi onlajn, li ma jistgħux jitniżżlu; Servizzi ta' pubblikazzjoni ta' vidjo diġitali, ta' awdjo u ta' divertiment multimedjali; Pubblikazzjoni multimedjali ta' magazins, ġurnali u gazzetti; Organizzazzjoni u twettiq ta' konferenzi, konvenzjonijiet, esibizzjonijiet, lezzjonijiet, teżijiet, seminars u workshops [taħriġ]; Tmexxija ta' avvenimenti edukattivi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Desktop publishing; Ter beschikking stellen van online, niet-downloadbare elektronische publicaties; Uitgeven van digitale video-, audio- en multimedia entertainment; Multimediale uitgeverij van magazines, tijdschriften en kranten; Organisatie en uitvoering van conferenties, congressen, exposities, lessen, dissertaties, seminars en workshops [opleiding]; Het uitvoeren van educatieve evenementen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Publikowanie elektroniczne; Udostępnianie publikacji elektronicznych [nie do pobrania]; Usługi publikowania cyfrowych materiałów wideo, audio i rozrywki multimedialnej; Publikowanie multimedialne magazynów, czasopism i gazet; Organizowanie i realizowanie konferencji, zjazdów, wystaw, zajęć, rozpraw naukowych, seminariów i warsztatów [szkoleń]; Prowadzenie imprez edukacyjnych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de publicação eletrónica; Serviços online de publicações eletrónicas, não descarregáveis; Serviços de publicação de conteúdos de entretenimento de vídeo, áudio e multimédia; Publicação multimédia de revistas, revistas especializadas e jornais; Organização e realização de conferências, convenções, exposições, aulas, dissertações, seminários e oficinas de trabalho [formação]; Realização de eventos educativos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de publicare electronică; Furnizare de publicații electronice online, nedescărcabile; Servicii de publicare de divertisment video digital, audio și multimedia; Publicare multimedia de reviste, jurnale și ziare; Organizare și realizarea de de conferințe, convenții, expoziții, lecții, dizertații, seminare și ateliere de lucru [formare]; Coordonare de evenimente educative.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Elektronické publikovanie; Online poskytovanie elektronických publikácií (bez možnosti kopírovania); Služby vydávania digitálnych videozáznamov, audiozáznamov a multimediálnej zábavy; Multimediálne vydávanie časopisov, denníkov a novín; Organizovanie a realizácia konferencií, schôdzí, výstav, prednášok, vedeckých rozpráv, seminárov a tvorivých dielní [vzdelávanie]; Vedenie vzdelávacích podujatí.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve elektronskega založništva; Nudenje spletnih elektronskih publikacij, nenaložljivih; Digitalne video, avdio in multimedijske razvedrilne založniške storitve; Multimedijsko objavljanje revij, dnevnikov in časopisov; Organizacija in izvedba konferenc, konvencij, razstav, predavanj, disertacij, seminarjev in delavnic [usposabljanje]; Izvajanje izobraževalnih prireditev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Elektroniska publiceringstjänster; Upplåtande av elektroniska publikationer online, inte nedladdningsbara; Publiceringstjänster avseende digital video-, ljud- och multimedieunderhållning; Multimediepublicering av tidskrifter, journaler och tidningar; Anordnande och genomförande av konferenser, konvent, utställningar, lektioner, avhandlingar, kollokvier, seminarier och workshoppar [utbildning]; Genomförande av utbildningsevenemang.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/119</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-26</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/191</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-06</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>702017</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>11418</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
