<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-06T09:03:36</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228826</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228826</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-10-03</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-06</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162459970</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/228/018228826/000162459970.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>28.03</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Антибактериални препарати за миене на ръце; Антисептици; Дезинфектанти; Дезинфектанти за хигиенни цели; Превръзки за очи за медицински цели; Фумиганти за медицински цели; Билкови екстракти за медицински цели; Билкарски продукти, А именно, Комплекти за ароматерапия, съдържащи билки за успокояване на главоболие, безсъние и синусов дискомфорт; Превръзки [лечебни]; Вода за уста за медицински цели; Лепенки за медицински цели; Вагинални промивки за медицински цели; Трансдермални лепенки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Antibakteriální prostředky na mytí rukou; Antiseptika; Dezinfekční přípravky; Dezinfekční prostředky pro hygienické účely; Pásky na oči pro léčebné účely; Přípravky na vykuřování pro léčebné účely; Bylinné výtažky pro léčebné účely; Bylinné přípravky, Jmenovitě, Aromaterapeutické polštářky obsahující byliny používané k úlevě od bolestí hlavy, nespavosti a problémů s dutinami; Krytí (zdravotnické potřeby); Ústní vody pro léčebné účely; Lepicí náplasti pro lékařské použití; Léčebné vaginální výplachy; Transdermální náplasti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Antibakterielle håndvaskemidler; Antiseptiske midler; Desinfektionsmidler; Desinfektionsmidler til hygiejniske formål; Øjenklapper til medicinske formål; Røgelsespræparater til medicinske formål; Urteekstrakter til medicinske formål; Helsekostprodukter, Nemlig, Aromaterapipakker med urter til lindring af hovedpine, søvnløshed og bihuleirritation; Forbindsmaterialer, medicinske; Mundskyllevand til medicinske formål; Klæbende plastre til medicinske formål; Vaginale skyllepræparater til medicinske formål; Transdermale plastre.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Antibakterielle Handwaschmittel; Antiseptika; Desinfektionsmittel; Desinfektionsmittel für hygienische Zwecke; Augenklappen für medizinische Zwecke; Räuchermittel für medizinische Zwecke; Kräuterextrakte für medizinische Zwecke; Kräuterprodukte, Nämlich, Aromatherapiepackungen mit Kräutern zur Linderung von Kopfschmerzen, Schlaflosigkeit und Beschwerden der Nasennebenhöhlen; Verbandmaterial; Mundspülungen für medizinische Zwecke; Heftpflaster für medizinische Zwecke; Vaginalspülungen für medizinische Zwecke; Transdermale Pflaster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αντιβακτηριακά προϊόντα για το πλύσιμο των χεριών· Αντισηπτικά· Απολυμαντικά· Απολυμαντικά για υγειονομική χρήση· Προστατευτικά καλύμματα ματιού για ιατρική χρήση· Καπνού εκπομπή (Προϊόντα εκπομπής -) ιατρικής χρήσης· Εκχυλίσματα από βότανα για ιατρική χρήση· Προϊόντα βοτάνων, Συγκεκριμένα, Επιθέματα αρωματοθεραπείας με βότανα για χρήση στην ανακούφιση κεφαλαλγίας, αϋπνίας και ρινικών ενοχλήσεων· Υλικά επίδεσης, ιατρικά· Στοματικά διαλύματα για ιατρική χρήση· Αυτοκόλλητα έμπλαστρα για ιατρική χρήση· Κολπικές πλύσεις για ιατρική χρήση· Διαδερμικά τσιρότα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Antibacterial handwashes; Antiseptics; Disinfectants; Disinfectants for hygiene purposes; Eyepatches for medical purposes; Fumigation preparations for medical purposes; Herbal extracts for medical purposes; Herbal products, namely, aromatherapy packs containing herbs used for relief from headaches, insomnia and sinus discomfort; Medical dressings; Mouthwashes for medical purposes; Sticking plasters for medical use; Vaginal washes for medical purposes; Transdermal patches.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Productos antibacterianos para lavar las manos; Antisépticos; Desinfectantes; Desinfectantes para uso higiénico; Parches oculares para uso médico; Productos de fumigación para uso médico; Extractos de plantas para uso médico; Productos de herboristería, En concreto, Paquetes de aromaterapia que contienen hierbas utilizadas para aliviar dolores de cabeza, insomnio y molestias en los senos nasales; Artículos para apósitos; Enjuagues bucales para uso médico; Emplastos adhesivos para uso médico; Duchas vaginales para uso médico; Parches transdérmicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Antibakteriaalsed kätepesuained; Antiseptikumid; Desinfektsioonivahendid; Hügieenilised desinfektsioonivahendid; Meditsiiniotstarbelised silmalapid; Meditsiinilised fumigandid; Meditsiinilised taimeekstraktid; Ürditooted, Nimelt, Aroomiteraapiapakid, mis sisaldavad ravimtaimi, mida kasutatakse peavalude, unetuse ja põskkoopavaevuste leevendamiseks; Meditsiinilised sidemed; Meditsiinilised suuloputusveed, suuveed; Meditsiinilised plaastrid; Meditsiinilised tupeloputusvedelikud; Transdermaalsed plaastrid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Antibakteeriset käsienpesuliuokset; Antiseptiset aineet; Desinfiointiaineet; Desinfiointiaineet hygieenisiin tarkoituksiin; Silmälaput lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Suitsukevalmisteet lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Yrttiuutteet lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Luontaistuotteet, Nimittäin, Aromiterapiapakkaukset, jotka sisältävät päänsäryn, unettomuuden ja poskiontelovaivojen helpottamiseen tarkoitettuja yrttejä; Sidontatarvikkeet (Haavan -); Suuvedet lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Laastarit lääkintätarkoituksiin; Emätinhuuhteet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Laastarit lääkkeiden antamiseen ihon läpi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits antibactériens pour le lavage des mains; Antiseptiques; Désinfectants; Désinfectants à usage hygiénique; Caches oculaires à usage médical; Produits fumigatoires à usage médical; Extraits de plantes à usage médical; Produits d' herboristerie, À savoir, Paquets d'aromathérapie contenant des herbes pour soulager les maux de tête, l'insomnie et la gêne sinusale; Pansements à usage médical; Produits pour les soins de la bouche à usage médical; Sparadraps adhésifs à usage médical; Bains vaginaux à usage médical; Timbres transdermiques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Antibakterijska sredstva za pranje ruku; Antiseptici; Dezinfekcijska sredstva; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za higijenske namjene; Štitnici za oči za medicinske potrebe; Proizvodi za kađenje za medicinske potrebe; Biljni ekstrakti za medicinsku upotrebu; Biljni proizvodi, Odnosno, Aromaterapijski pakunzi koji sadrže bilje koje se koristi za glavobolje, nesanice i sinusne smetnje; Medicinske obloge za rane; Sredstvo za ispiranje usta za medicinsku uporabu; Samoljepljivi flasteri za medicinsku primjenu; Tekućine za vaginalno ispiranje za medicinske svrhe; Transdermalni flasteri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Antibakteriális kézmosók; Fertőtlenítőszerek, antiszeptikus készítmények; Fertőtlenítőszerek; Fertőtlenítőszerek higiéniai célokra; Szemtapaszok gyógyászati célokra; Fumigációs készítmények gyógyászati célokra; Gyógynövénykivonatok orvosi célokra; Gyógynövény termékek, Nevezetesen, Aromaterápiás csomagok, amelyek fejfájásra, álmatlanságra és homlok-/arcüreg-/orrmelléküreg (sinus) diszkomfortra használt gyógynövényeket tartalmaznak; Orvosi kötszerek; Szájöblítő szerek gyógyászati használatra; Ragtapaszok gyógyászati használatra; Hüvelyöblítők egészségügyi célokra; Transzdermális tapaszok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Prodotti antibatterici per lavare le mani; Antisettici; Disinfettanti; Disinfettanti per uso igienico; Mascherine oculari ad uso medico; Prodotti per fumigazioni per uso medico; Estratti di erbe ad uso medico; prodotti erboristici, Ovvero, Impacchi per aromaterapia contenenti erbe per alleviare il mal di testa, l'insonnia e i disturbi del seno nasale; Articoli per medicazioni; Collutori orali per uso medico; Cerotti adesivi per uso medico; Lavaggi vaginali per uso medico; Cerotti transdermici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Antibakteriniai rankų plovimo skysčiai; Antiseptikai [vaistai nuo pūlinės infekcijos]; Dezinfekavimo preparatai; Dezinfekavimo priemonės (higienos reikmėms); Akių raiščiai medicinos reikmėms; Smilkalai (medicinos reikmėms); Žolių ekstraktai (medicinos reikmėms); Vaistažolių preparatai, Būtent,, Aromaterapiniai paketai su žolelėmis, skirtomis malšinti galvos skausmus, nemigą ir nemalonius pojūčius sinusų srityje; Tvarsliava [medicininė]; Burnos skalavimo preparatai (medicinos reikmėms); Medicininiai lipieji pleistrai; Makšties plovimo skysčiai (medicinos reikmėms); Transderminiai pleistrai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Antibakteriālie roku mazgāšanas līdzekļi; Antiseptiskie līdzekļi; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi higiēniskiem nolūkiem; Acu pārsēji medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Kvēpināmie preparāti medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Zāļu ekstrakti medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Ārstniecisko augu preparāti, Proti, Aromterapijas komplekti, kas satur augus palīdzībai pret galvassāpēm, bezmiegu un sinusa diskomfortu; Pārsēji, medicīniski; Mutes skalošanas līdzekļi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Medicīniskais leikoplasts; Maksts skalošanas līdzekļi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Transdermāli plāksteri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ħasil tal-idejn antibatteriku; Antisettiċi; Diżinfettanti; Diżinfettanti għal skopijiet ta' iġjene; Għata tal-għajnejn għal skopijiet mediċi; Preparazzjonijiet għall-fumigazzjoni għal skopijiet mediċi; Estratti erbali għal skopijiet mediċinali; Prodotti ta' preparazzjonijiet tal-ħxejjex, Jiġifieri, Pakki tal-aromaterapija li fihom ħwawar għas-serħan minn uġigħ ta' ras, insomnja u skonfort kawża tas-sinus; Ilbies għall-feriti, mediċi; Likwidu għat-tlaħliħ tal-ħalq, għal skopijiet mediċi; Stikks adeżivi għal skopijiet mediċi; Prodotti għat-tlaħliħ vaġinali għal skopijiet mediċi; Garżi b'sustanzi li jgħaddu mill-ġilda.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Antibacteriële handzeep; Antiseptische middelen; Ontsmettingsmiddelen; Desinfecterende middelen voor hygiënisch gebruik; Ooglapjes voor medisch gebruik; Berokingsproducten voor medisch gebruik; Kruidenextracten voor medische doeleinden; Kruidenproducten, Te weten, Aromatherapiekussentjes met kruiden voor verlichting van hoofdpijn, slapeloosheid en sinusklachten; Verbandartikelen; Mondverzorgingsproducten voor medisch gebruik; Pleisters voor medische doeleinden; Vaginale baden voor medische doeleinden; Transdermale pleisters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Antybakteryjne środki do mycia rąk; Antyseptyki; Środki odkażające; Środki dezynfekcyjne do celów higienicznych; Przepaski na oczy do celów medycznych; Preparaty do odymiania do celów medycznych; Ekstrakty ziołowe do celów medycznych; Produkty ziołowe, Mianowicie, Paczuszki aromaterapeutyczne zawierające zioła do łagodzenia bólów głowy, bezsenności i dyskomfortu w rejonie zatok; Materiały opatrunkowe, medyczne; Płyny do płukania jamy ustnej do celów medycznych; Plastry samoprzylepne do użytku medycznego; Płyny do przemywania pochwy do celów medycznych; Plastry transdermalne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Preparações antibacterianas de lavagem de mãos; Antisséticos; Desinfectantes; Desinfetantes para uso higiénico; Palas oculares [oclusores] para uso médico; Produtos de fumigação para uso medicinal; Extratos de plantas para fins medicinais; Produtos de ervanária, Nomeadamente, Embalagens de aromaterapia contendo ervas para o alívio de dores de cabeça, insónias e desconforto nasal; Pensos médicos; Elixires bocais para uso médico; Emplastros adesivos para uso medicinal; Banhos vaginais para fins medicinais; Adesivos transdérmicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Soluţii antibacteriene pentru spălarea mâinilor; Antiseptice; Dezinfectante; Dezinfectante folosite pentru igienă; Bandaje de uz medical pentru ochi; Produse pentru fumigaţie, de uz medical; Extracte din plante de uz medical; Produse de plafar, Şi anume, Pachete pentru aromoterapie care conţin plante folosite la calmarea durerilor de cap, a insomniei şi a disconfortului sinusurilor; Pansamente de uz medical; Apă de gură de uz medical; Leucoplast de uz medical; Spălături vaginale de uz medical; Plasturi transdermali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Antibakteriálne tekuté mydlá; Antiseptické prípravky, dezinfekčné prípravky; Dezinfekčné prostriedky; Dezinfekčné prípravky na hygienické použitie; Pásky na oči na lekárske použitie; Fumigačné prípravky na lekárske použitie; Bylinkové výťažky na lekárske použitie; Bylinkové prípravky, Menovite, Aromatické zábaly, obsahujúce byliny, na zmierňovanie bolestí hlavy, nespavosti a ťažkostí v dutinách; Obväzový materiál; Ústne vody na lekárske použitie; Náplasti pre lekárske účely; Vaginálne kúpele na lekárske použitie; Transdermálne náplasti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Antibakterijska čistila za roke; Antiseptiki; Dezinfekcijska sredstva; Razkužila za higienske namene; Očesne blazinice za medicinske namene; Razkuževalni pripravki za medicinske namene; Zeliščni ekstrakti za medicinske namene; Zeliščni pripravki, In sicer, Paketi za aromaterapijo z zelišči za blažitev glavobola, nespečnosti in težav s sinusi; Medicinske obveze; Ustne vode za medicinske namene; Samolepilni obliži za medicinsko uporabo; Vaginalna izpirala za medicinske namene; Transdermalni obliži.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bakteriedödande handtvättmedel; Antiseptiska medel; Desinfektionsmedel; Desinfektionsmedel för hygieniska ändamål; Ögonlappar för medicinska ändamål; Desinficerande rökningspreparat för medicinska ändamål; Örtextrakt för medicinska ändamål; Naturapoteksprodukter, Nämligen, Aromaterapiförpackningar innehållande örter för lindring av huvudvärk, sömnlöshet och bihålebesvär; Förband (medicinska); Munvatten för medicinska ändamål; Häftplåster för medicinskt bruk; Preparat för vaginal hygien för medicinska ändamål; Transdermala plåster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Игли за акупунктура; Поддържащи бандажи; Електрически инструменти за акупунктура; Електроди за медицинско използване; Дезинфекциращи [опушващи] апарати за медицински цели; Хемостатични инструменти за зашиване на рани; Лазери за медицински цели; Маски за медицински персонал; Медицински водачи; Поддържащи бандажи; Хирургични материали; Вагинални помпи; Оборудване за физиотерапия; Санитарни маски за медицински цели; Хирургически маски; Възглавници, пълни с лечебни билки; Възглавници за ароматерапия за лекуване на главоболия, облекчаване на стреса, лекуване на инсомния.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Akupunkturní jehly; Ortopedické bandáže; Elektrické akupunkturní nástroje; Elektrody pro lékařské použití; Fumigační přístroje pro lékařské účely; Hemostatické nástroje na šití; Lasery pro lékařské účely; Roušky pro lékařský personál; Lékařské vodicí dráty; Ortopedické bandáže; Materiál na sešívání ran; Vaginální stříkačky; Fyzioterapeutické přístroje; Hygienické masky pro lékařské účely; Chirurgické masky; Polštáře plněné léčebnými bylinami; Aromaterapeutické polštáře pro léčbu bolesti hlavy, úlevu od stresu, léčbu nespavosti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Akupunkturnåle; Bandager til led, anatomiske; Elektriske akupunkturinstrumenter; Elektroder til medicinsk brug; Røgfrembringelsesapparater til medicinsk brug; Hæmostatiske suturinstrumenter; Lasere til medicinske formål; Masker til brug for medicinsk personel; Medicinske trådbølgeledere; Bandager til led, anatomiske; Suturmaterialer; Vaginalsprøjter; Udstyr til fysisk terapi; Sanitære masker til medicinske formål; Operationsmasker; Puder fyldt med urtemedicin; Aromaterapeutiske puder til behandling af hovedpine, afhjælpning af stress, helbredelse af søvnløshed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Akupunkturnadeln; Orthopädische Gelenkbandagen; Elektroakupunkturgeräte; Elektroden für medizinische Zwecke; Räucherapparate für medizinische Zwecke; Hämostatische Wundnahtinstrumente; Laser für medizinische Zwecke; Masken für medizinisches Personal; Medizinische Führungsdrähte; Orthopädische Gelenkbandagen; Chirurgisches Nahtmaterial; Vaginalspritzen; Geräte für physikalische Therapie; Mundschutz für medizinische Zwecke; Chirurgischer Mundschutz; Mit Heilkräutern gefüllte Kopfkissen; Aromatherapiekissen zur Behandlung von Kopfschmerzen, Linderung von Stress, Heilung von Schlaflosigkeit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Βελόνες για βελονισμό· Υποστήριξης επίδεσμοι· Βελονισμού (Ηλεκτρικά όργανα -)· Ηλεκτρόδια για ιατρική χρήση· Καπνού εκπομπή (συσκευές ατμοθεραπείας) ιατρικής χρήσης· Αιμοστατικά όργανα για ράμματα· Λέιζερ ιατρικής χρήσης· Μάσκες για το ιατρικό προσωπικό· Ιατρικά σύρματα καθοδήγησης· Υποστήριξης επίδεσμοι· Υλικό χειρουργικών ραμμάτων· Κολπικές (Σύριγγες -)· Εξοπλισμός φυσικοθεραπείας· Μάσκες υγιεινής για ιατρική χρήση· Χειρουργικές μάσκες· Μαξιλάρι παραγεμισμένα με ιατρική κάνναβη· Μαξιλάρια αρωματοθεραπείας για την αντιμετώπιση πονοκεφάλων, την ανακούφιση από το στρες, τη θεραπεία της αϋπνίας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Acupuncture needles; Bandages for joints, anatomical; Electric acupuncture instruments; Electrodes for medical use; Fumigation apparatus for medical purposes; Hemostatic suture instruments; Lasers for medical purposes; Masks for use by medical personnel; Medical guidewires; Supportive bandages; Suture materials; Vaginal syringes; Physiotherapy apparatus; Sanitary masks for medical purposes; Surgical masks; Medical herb stuffed pillows; Aromatherapy pillows for treating headaches, relieving stress, curing insomnia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Agujas de acupuntura; Vendas ortopédicas para las articulaciones; Instrumentos eléctricos de acupuntura; Electrodos para uso médico; Aparatos de fumigación para uso médico; Instrumentos de sutura hemostáticos; Láseres para uso médico; Mascarillas para personal médico; Hilos de guía para uso médico; Vendas ortopédicas para las articulaciones; Material de sutura; Jeringas vaginales; Equipos de terapia física; Mascarillas sanitarias para uso médico; Mascarillas quirúrgicas; Almohadas rellenas de hierbas medicinales; Almohadas de aromaterapia para tratar cefaleas, aliviar el estrés, curar el insomnio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Akupunktuurinõelad; Anatoomilised liigesesidemed; Elektrilised akupunktuuriinstrumendid; Meditsiinilised elektroodid; Meditsiinilised suitsutusaparaadid; Hemostaatilised haavaõmblusinstrumendid; Meditsiinilised laserid; Maskid meditsiinipersonalile; Meditsiinilised sondid; Anatoomilised liigesesidemed; Õmblusmaterjalid; Vaginaalsüstlad, tupesüstlad; Füsioteraapiaseadmed; Meditsiinilised hügieenilised maskid; Kirurgimaskid; Ravimtaimedega täidetud padjad; Aroomiteraapiapadjad peavalude ravimiseks, stressi leevendamiseks, unetuse ravimiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Akupunktuurineulat; Anatomiset siteet nivelille; Sähköiset akupunktuurilaitteet; Elektrodit lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Kaasun tai höyryn sisäänhengityslaitteet lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Verenvuotoa tyrehdyttävät ompeluvälineet; Laserit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Suojanaamarit lääkintähenkilökuntaa varten; Ohjausjohtimet, lääketieteelliset; Anatomiset siteet nivelille; Haavanompelutarvikkeet; Emätinneulat [-ruiskut]; Fysioterapiassa käytettävät välineet; Saniteettinaamarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Kirurgin naamarit; Lääkintäyrteillä täytetyt tyynyt; Aromaterapiatyynyt päänsäryn hoitoon, stressin lievittämiseen, unettomuuden parantamiseen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Aiguilles d'acupuncture; Bandages orthopédiques pour les articulations; Instruments électriques pour l'acupuncture; Électrodes à usage médical; Appareils pour fumigations à usage médical; Instruments de suture hémostatique; Lasers à usage médical; Masques utilisés par le personnel médical; Fils de guidage médicaux; Bandages orthopédiques pour les articulations; Matériel de suture; Seringues vaginales; Équipement de thérapie physique; Masques hygiéniques à usage médical; Masques chirurgicaux; Oreillers contenant des herbes à usage médical; Oreillers d'aromathérapie pour traiter les maux de tête, soulager le stress, soigner l'insomnie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Igle za akupunkturu; Ortopedski zavoji za zglobove; Električni instrumenti za akupunkturu; Elektrode za medicinske potrebe; Uređaji za dimljenje za medicinske potrebe; Hemostatski instrumenti za šivanje; Laseri za medicinske namjene; Maske za medicinsko osoblje; Medicinske žice koje služe kao smjernice; Ortopedski zavoji za zglobove; Pribor za kirurško šivanje; Vaginalne šprice; Oprema za fizikalnu terapiju; Sanitarne maske za medicinske svrhe; Kirurške maske; Jastuci napunjeni ljekovitim biljem; Jastuci za aromaterapiju za liječenje glavobolje, ublažavanje stresa, liječenje nesanice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Akupunktúrás tűk; Anatómiai kötések ízületekre; Elektromos akupunktúrás eszközök; Elektródák gyógyászati használatra; Fertőtlenítő készülékek gyógyászati használatra; Hemosztatikus varróeszközök; Lézerek orvosi célokra; Maszkok egészségügyi személyzet általi használatra; Orvosi vezetődrótok, hullámvezetők; Anatómiai kötések ízületekre; Sebészeti varratanyagok; Hüvelyi [vaginális] fecskendők; Fizikoterápiás készülékek; Gyógyászati célú egészségügyi maszkok; Sebészeti maszkok; Gyógynövényes töltött párnák; Aromaterápiás párnák fejfájás kezelésére, a stressz enyhítésére, az álmatlanság gyógyítására.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Aghi per agopuntura; Fasciature per articolazioni; Strumenti elettrici per l'agopuntura; Elettrodi per uso medico; Apparecchi per fumigazioni per uso medico; Strumenti per la sutura emostatica; Laser per uso medico; Maschere utilizzate dal personale medico; Fili guida per uso medico; Fasciature per articolazioni; Materiale di sutura; Siringhe vaginali; Attrezzatura per terapie fisiche; Maschere igieniche per uso medico; Mascherine chirurgiche; Cuscini imbottiti con erbe medicinali; Cuscini per aromaterapia per trattare emicranie, alleviare lo stress, curare l'insonnia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Akupunktūros adatos; Anatominiai sąnarių tvarsčiai; Elektriniai akupunktūros instrumentai; Elektrodai (medicinos reikmėms); Smilkymo prietaisai (medicinos reikmėms); Hemostatiniai žaizdų susiuvimo instrumentai; Lazeriai (medicinos reikmėms); Kaukės medicinos personalui; Medicininės vielinės kateterių kreipiamosios; Anatominiai sąnarių tvarsčiai; Žaizdų siuvimo medžiagos; Makšties švirkštai; Fizioterapijos įranga; Sanitarinės kaukės medicinos reikmėms; Chirurginės kaukės; Medicininėmis žolelėmis kimštos pagalvės; Aromaterapinės pagalvės galvos skausmui gydyti, stresui malšinti, nemigai išgydyti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Akupunktūras adatas; Anatomiskie locītavu pārsēji; Elektriskie akupunktūras instrumenti; Elektrodi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Fumigācijas aparatūra medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Instrumenti hemostatisku šuvju uzlikšanai; Medicīniskiem nolūkiem paredzētie lāzeri; Medicīnas personālam paredzētās maskas; Medicīniskas zondes; Anatomiskie locītavu pārsēji; Ķirurģiskie šuvju materiāli; Vaginālās šļirces; Fizikālās terapijas iekārtas; Sanitārās maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Ķirurģiskās maskas; Ar medicīniskajiem augiem pildīti spilveni; Aromterapijas spilveni galvassāpju ārstēšanai, stresa mazināšanai, bezmiega atveseļošanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Labar tal-akupuntura; Faxex t'appoġġ għall-ġogi; Strumenti elettriċi tal-akupuntura; Elettrodi għal skopijiet mediċi; Apparat ta' fumigazzjoni għal skopijiet mediċi; Strumenti għas-suturi emostatiċi; Lejżers għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri għal personal mediku; Wajers ta' gwida mediċi; Faxex t'appoġġ għall-ġogi; Materjali għas-sutura; Siringi tal-vaġina; Tagħmir għat-terapija fiżika; Maskri sanitarji għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri kirurġiċi; Imħaded mimlija magħmula mill-ħxejjex mediċinali; Imħaded tal-aromaterapija għat-trattament tal-uġigħ ta' ras, is-serħan mill-istress u l-kura tal-insomnja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Acupunctuurnaalden; Gewrichtsverbanden, orthopedisch; Elektrische instrumenten voor acupunctuur; Elektroden voor medisch gebruik; Berokingsapparaten voor medisch gebruik; Hemostatische hechtinstrumenten; Lasers voor medisch gebruik; Maskers te gebruiken door medisch personeel; Geleidedraden voor medisch gebruik; Gewrichtsverbanden, orthopedisch; Hechtmateriaal; Vaginaspuiten; Apparaten voor lichamelijke behandeling; Hygiënische maskers voor medische doeleinden; Gezichtsmaskers voor chirurgisch gebruik; Kussens gevuld met medicinale kruiden; Aromatherapiekussens voor het behandelen van hoofdpijn, ter verlichting van stress, tegen slapeloosheid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Igły do akupunktury; Bandaże usztywniające na stawy; Przyrządy elektryczne do akupunktury; Elektrody do użytku medycznego; Urządzenia do fumigacji do celów medycznych; Hemostatyczne instrumenty do zakładania szwów; Lasery do celów medycznych; Maski stosowane przez personel medyczny; Prowadniki do celów medycznych; Bandaże usztywniające na stawy; Materiały do zszywania stosowane w chirurgii; Strzykawki dopochwowe; Urządzenia i przyrządy do fizjoterapii; Maski sanitarne do celów medycznych; Maski chirurgiczne; Poduszki medyczne wypchane ziołami leczniczymi; Poduszki do aromaterapii do leczenia bólu głowy, łagodzenia objawów stresu, leczenia bezsenności.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Agulhas de acupuntura; Ligaduras para as articulações; Instrumentos elétricos para acupuntura; Elétrodos para uso médico; Aparelhos de fumigação, para uso médico; Instrumentos de sutura hemostática; Lasers para uso médico; Máscaras para pessoal médico; Fios de guia para uso médico; Ligaduras para as articulações; Material de sutura; Seringas vaginais; Equipamento de fisioterapia; Máscaras higiénicas para uso médico; Máscaras cirúrgicas; Almofadas com enchimento de ervas medicinais; Almofadas de aromaterapia para o tratamento de dores de cabeça, para o alívio do stress e para o tratamento de insónias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ace de acupunctură; Bandaje ortopedice pentru articulaţii; Instrumente electrice pentru acupunctură; Electrozi de uz medical; Aparate de fumigaţie pentru uz medical; Instrumente de sutură hemostatice; Lasere de uz medical; Măşti utilizate de personalul medical; Cabluri de ghidaj pentru uz medical; Bandaje ortopedice pentru articulaţii; Material de sutură; Vaginale (Seringi -); Echipament pentru exerciţii fizice; Măşti sanitare de uz medical; Măşti chirurgicale; Perne umplute cu plante medicinale; Perne de aromoterapie pentru tratarea durerilor de cap, calmarea stresului, tratarea insomniei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Akupunktúrne ihly; Podporné bandáže (ortopedické); Elektrické prístroje na akupunktúru; Elektródy na lekárske použitie; Inhalačné prístroje na lekárske použitie; Hemostatické nástroje na šitie; Laser na lekárske použitie; Rúška (pre nemocničný personál); Lekárske vodiace vlákna; Podporné bandáže (ortopedické); Materiály na zašívanie rán; Vaginálne irigátory; Fyzioterapeutické zariadenia; Sanitárne masky na lekárske účely; Chirurgické masky; Vankúšiky plnené liečivými bylinami; Aromaterapeutické vankúšiky na liečenie bolestí hlavy, zmierňovanie stresu, liečenie nespavosti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Akupunkturne igle; Anatomski povoji za sklepe; Električni instrumenti za akupunkturo; Elektrode za medicinsko uporabo; Aparati za razkuževanje za medicinsko uporabo; Instrumenti za hemostatsko šivanje; Laserji za medicinsko uporabo; Maske za medicinsko osebje; Medicinske vodilne žice; Anatomski povoji za sklepe; Kirurški material za šivanje; Vaginalne brizgalke; Naprave za fizikalno terapijo; Higienske maske za medicinske namene; Kirurške maske; Vzglavniki, polnjene z zdravilnimi zelišči; Aromaterapevtski vzglavniki za zdravljenje glavobolov, lajšanje stresa, zdravljenje nespečnosti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Akupunkturnålar; Stödbandage; Elektriska akupunkturinstrument; Elektroder för medicinsk användning; Apparater för inandning av gas eller ånga för medicinska ändamål; Hemostatiska suturinstrument; Lasrar för medicinska ändamål; Munskydd för medicinsk personal; Medicinska venvidgare; Stödbandage; Suturmaterial; Vaginalsprutor; Utrustning för fysioterapi; Sanitetsmasker för medicinska ändamål; Operationsmasker; Kuddar fyllda med medicinalörter; Aromaterapikuddar för behandling av huvudvärk, stresslindring, botemedel mot sömnsvårigheter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/119</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-26</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/191</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-06</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082054</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>71845</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
