<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-23T16:40:04</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228530</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228530</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-10</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>dotlive</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Софтуер; Компютърни софтуерни платформи; Компютърни софтуерни приложения; Софтуер; Софтуер за комуникация; Софтуер за електронна поща; Софтуер за управление на съдържанието; Софтуер за геодезия; Компютърни софтуерни приложения, за сваляне; Компютърни програми за обработка на данни; Софтуер за обработка на данни за графични изображения; Софтуер за предаване на данни; Компютърен софтуер за обработка на съобщения; Софтуер за обработка на изображения, графики и текст.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Počítačový software; Platformy počítačového softwaru; Aplikační software; Počítačový software; Počítačový komunikační software; E-mailový software; Software pro správu obsahu; Geodetický software; Stahovatelné počítačové aplikace; Počítačové programy na zpracování dat; Software na zpracování dat pro grafické prezentace; Software na datové komunikace; Počítačový software na zpracování komunikací; Software na zpracování obrazu, grafiky a textu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Software; Computersoftwareplatforme; Applikationssoftware; Software; Kommunikationssoftware; Software til e-mails; Software til administration af indhold; Software til brug ved opmåling; Softwareapplikationer til computere, downloadable; Computerprogrammer til databehandling; Software til databehandling til brug i forbindelse med grafiske fremstillinger; Software til datakommunikation; Computerprogrammer til kommunikationsarbejde; Software til behandling af billeder, grafik og tekst.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Software; Computersoftwareplattformen; Anwendungssoftware; Kommunikationssoftware; E-Mail-Software; Content-Management-Software; Vermessungssoftware; Herunterladbare Software-Anwendungen für Computer; Datenverarbeitungssoftware; Datenverarbeitungssoftware für grafische Darstellungen; Datenkommunikationssoftware; Computersoftware für die Kommunikationsverarbeitung; Software zum Verarbeiten von Bildern, Grafik und Text; Software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Λογισμικό· Πλατφόρμες λογισμικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Λογισμικό εφαρμογών· Λογισμικό· Λογισμικό επικοινωνίας· Λογισμικό ηλεκτρονικού ταχυδρομείου· Λογισμικό διαχείρισης περιεχομένου· Τοπογραφικό λογισμικό· Εφαρμογές λογισμικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών, μεταφορτώσιμες· Προγραμματισμός ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για επεξεργασία δεδομένων· Λογισμικό για την επεξεργασία δεδομένων για γραφικές αναπαραστάσεις· Λογισμικό διαβίβασης δεδομένων· Λογισμικό ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για την επεξεργασία επικοινωνιών· Λογισμικό επεξεργασίας εικόνων, γραφικών και κειμένων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Computer software; Platform software; Application software; Software; Communications software; Communication software; Email software; Content management software; Surveying software; Software applications; Computer software applications; Data processing software; Data processing software for graphic representations; Computer programmes for data processing; Data communications software; Communications processing computer software; Software for processing images, graphics and text.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Software informático; Plataformas de software para ordenadores; Programas de aplicación; Software; Software informático de comunicaciones; Software de correo electrónico; Software de gestión de contenidos; Software para mediciones geodésicas; Aplicaciones informáticas descargables; Software de ordenador para el tratamiento de la información; Software de tratamiento de datos para representaciones gráficas; Software informático para la comunicación de datos; Software para el procesamiento de la comunicación; Software para procesar imágenes, gráficos y textos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arvutitarkvara; Arvutitarkvara platvormid; Rakenduslik tarkvara; Arvutitarkvara; Sidetarkvara; Elektronpostitarkvara; Sisuhaldustarkvara; Geodeesia mõõtetarkvara; Allalaaditavad arvutitarkvararakendused; Arvutiprogrammid andmetöötluseks; Andmetöötlustarkvara graafilisteks esitlusteks; Andmesidetarkvara; Arvutitarkvara sidetöötluseks; Pildi-, graafika- ja tekstitöötlustarkvara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ohjelmistot; Tietokoneohjelmistoympäristöt; Sovellusohjelmistot; Ohjelmistot; Viestintään tarkoitetut ohjelmistot; Sähköpostiohjelmistot; Sisällönhallintaohjelmistot; Mittausohjelmistot; Ladattavat tietokoneohjelmistosovellukset; Tietojenkäsittelyohjelmistot; Tietojenkäsittelyohjelmistot graafisten esitysten laatimiseen; Datasiirto-ohjelmistot; Tietoliikenteen prosessointiohjelmistot; Kuvan-, grafiikan- ja tekstinkäsittelyohjelmistot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Logiciels pour ordinateurs; Plates-formes logicielles; Logiciels d'applications; Logiciel; Logiciels de communication; Logiciels de courrier électronique; Logiciels de gestion de contenus; Logiciels de mesure géodésique; Applications logicielles informatiques téléchargeables; Programmes informatiques de traitement de données; Logiciels de traitement de données pour représentations graphiques; Logiciels de communication de données; Logiciels pour le traitement des communications; Logiciels de traitement d'images, de graphismes et de textes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Softver; Računalne programske platforme; Aplikacijski softver; Softver; Komunikacijski računalni program; Softver za elektroničku poštu; Softver za upravljanje sadržajem; Nadzorni softver; Aplikacije za računalne programe koje se mogu preuzeti s Interneta; Softver za obradu podataka; Softver za obradu podataka za grafičke prikaze; Softver za komunikaciju podataka; Računalni program za obradu komunikacija [softveri]; Softver za obradu slika, grafika i teksta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szoftverek; Számítógépes szoftverplatformok; Applikációs szoftver; Szoftverek; Kommunikációs szoftverek; E-mail szoftverek; Tartalomkezelő szoftverek; Felmérő szoftverek; Számítógépes szoftveralkalmazások, letölthető; Adatfeldolgozó szoftverek; Adatfeldolgozó szoftverek grafikai ábrázolásokhoz; Adatkommunikációs szoftverek; Kommunikáció feldolgozó számítógépes szoftver; Szoftver képek, grafikák és szövegek feldolgozásához.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Software; Piattaforme software; Software specializzati; Software; Software per le comunicazioni; Software per la posta elettronica; Software per la gestione di contenuti; Software geodetici; Applicazioni per computer software, scaricabili; Programmi per computer per l'elaborazione di dati; Software di elaborazione dati per rappresentazioni grafiche; Software per comunicazione dati; Software per l'elaborazione di comunicazioni; Software per l'elaborazione di immagini, grafica e testo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Programinė įranga; Kompiuterių programinės įrangos platformos; Taikomoji programinė įranga; Programinė įranga; Ryšių programinė įranga; Elektroninio pašto programinė įranga; Turinio valdymo programinė įranga; Topografinio matavimo programinė įranga; Parsisiunčiamoji kompiuterių programinė įranga; Kompiuterių duomenų dorojimo programos; Duomenų apdorojimo programinė įranga grafinio vaizdavimo reikmėms; Duomenų perdavimo programinė įranga; Ryšių apdorojimo kompiuterių programinė įranga; Vaizdo, grafikos ir teksto tvarkymo programinė įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Datoru programmatūra; Datoru programmatūras platformas; Lietojumprogrammatūra; Programmatūra; Komunikāciju programmatūra; E-pasta programmatūra; Satura vadības programmatūra; Ģeodēzijas programmatūra; Lejupielādējamas datorprogrammu lietotnes; Datorprogrammas datu apstrādei; Datu apstrādes programmatūra grafiskajai attēlošanai; Datu komunikācijas programmatūra; Komunikāciju apstrādājoša datorprogrammatūra; Attēlu, grafisko attēlu un teksta apstrādes programmatūra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Softwer; Pjattaformi għal softwer tal-kompjuter; Softwer għal applikazzjonijiet; Softwer; Softwer tal-komunikazzjoni; Softwer tal-email; Softwer għall-ġestjoni tal-kontenut; Softwer tal-istħarriġ; Applikazzjonijiet ta' softwer tal-kompjuter, li jitniżżlu; Programmi tal-kompjuter għall-ipproċessar ta' data; Softwer għall-ipproċessar tad-data għal rappreżentazzjonijiet grafiċi; Softwer għall-komunikazzjoni tad-data; Softwer tal-kompjuter għall-ipproċessar tal-komunikazzjonijiet; Softwer għall-ipproċessar ta' stampi, grafika u test.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Software; Softwareplatforms; Softwaretoepassingen; Software; Communicatiesoftware; Emailsoftware; Contentbeheer software; Landmeetsoftware; Downloadbare computersoftware-applicaties; Computerprogramma's voor de gegevensverwerking; Gegevensverwerkende software voor grafische afbeeldingen; Datacommunicatie-software; Software voor het verwerken van mededelingen; Software voor het bewerken van beelden, grafische afbeeldingen en tekst.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Oprogramowanie; Platformy oprogramowania komputerowego; Oprogramowanie użytkowe; Oprogramowanie; Oprogramowanie komunikacyjne; Oprogramowanie do poczty elektronicznej; Oprogramowanie do zarządzania treścią; Oprogramowanie miernicze; Aplikacje komputerowe do pobrania; Programy komputerowe do przetwarzania danych; Oprogramowanie do przetwarzania danych do prezentacji graficznych; Oprogramowanie komputerowe do przesyłania danych; Oprogramowanie komputerowe do przetwarzania komunikacji; Oprogramowanie do przetwarzania obrazów, grafiki i tekstu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Software; Plataformas de software; Software de aplicação; Software; Software para comunicações; Software de correio eletrónico; Software para gestão de conteúdos; Software de agrimensura; Aplicações de software informático descarregáveis; Programas de computador para processamento de dados; Software de processamento de dados para representações gráficas; Software de comunicações de dados; Software para processamento de comunicações; Software para processamento de imagens, gráficos e texto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Software; Platforme de software de calculator; Aplicații software; Software; Software de comunicații; Software pentru e-mail; Software de management de conținut; Software pentru topografie; Aplicații software de calculator, descărcabile; Software de prelucrare a datelor; Software de procesare a datelor pentru reprezentări grafice; Software pentru comunicarea de date; Software de calculator pentru prelucrarea datelor de comunicare; Software pentru prelucrarea imaginilor, materialelor grafice și textelor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Softvér; Počítačové softvérové platformy; Aplikačný softvér; Softvér; Komunikačný softvér; Softvér pre e-maily; Softvér pre správu obsahu; Zameriavací geodetický softvér; Počítačové softvérové aplikácie (sťahovateľné); Počítačové programy na spracovanie údajov; Softvér na spracovanie dát pre grafické zobrazenia; Softvér pre dátovú komunikáciu; Počítačový softvér na spracovanie komunikácie; Softvér na spracovanie obrazov, grafiky a textu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Programska oprema; Platforme računalniške programske opreme; Aplikacijska programska oprema; Programska oprema; Komunikacijska programska oprema; Programska oprema za elektronsko pošto; Programska oprema za upravljanje vsebine; Merilna programska oprema; Računalniška programska oprema, naložljiva preko računalniške mreže; Računalniški programi za obdelavo podatkov; Programska oprema za obdelavo podatkov za grafične prikaze; Programska oprema za podatkovno komunikacijo; Računalniška programska oprema za komunikacijsko procesiranje; Programska oprema za obdelavo slik, grafik in besedil.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Datormjukvaror; Datorprogramvaruplattformar; Applikationsprogramvaror (appar); Mjukvaror; Programvara för kommunikation; Programvara för e-post; Programvara för innehållshantering; Programvara för mätning; Softwareapplikationer för datorer, nedladdningsbara; Datorprogramvara för databehandling; Databehandlingsprogramvaror för grafiska framställningar; Datorprogram för datakommunikation; Programvaror för behandling av kommunikation; Programvara för behandling av bilder, grafik och text.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Организиране на събития, изложби, панаири и шоу програми с търговски, промоционални и рекламни цели; Маркетингови услуги; Търговски маркетингови услуги; Преодставяне на съвети относно маркетинг; Бизнес съвети, свързани с маркетинг; Услуги за изследване във връзка с реклама и маркетинг; Изготвяне на отчети за маркетинг; Услуги, свързани с провеждане на пазарни изследвания; Маркетингови услуги, предоставени посредством цифрови мрежи; Рекламиране и рекламни услуги; Маркетинг на събития; Организиране и провеждане на маркетингови събития; Уреждане и провеждане на рекламни мероприятия; Организиране на събития за търговски и рекламни цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Organizování akcí, výstav, prodejních trhů a přehlídek pro obchodní, propagační a reklamní účely; Marketing; Obchodní marketingové služby; Marketingové poradenské služby; Obchodní poradenské služby vztahující se k marketingu; Služby výzkumu v oblasti reklamy a marketingu; Poskytování marketingových zpráv; Provádění marketingových studií; Marketingové služby poskytované prostřednictvím digitálních sítí; Propagace; Event marketing (získávání zákazníků pořádáním akcí); Příprava a pořádání marketingových akcí; Pořádání a řízení reklamních akcí; Organizování akcí pro komerční a reklamní účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Organisering af events, udstillinger, messer og shows med kommercielle, salgsfremmende og reklamemæssige formål; Marketing; Ydelser inden for forretningsmæssig marketing; Marketingrådgivning; Forretningsmæssig konsulentbistand vedrørende marketing; Undersøgelser vedrørende annoncering og markedsføring; Levering af marketingrapporter; Gennemførelse af marketingundersøgelser; Markedsføringstjenester ydet via digitale netværk; Reklamevirksomhed; Event marketing; Arrangering og afholdelse af markedsføringsarrangementer; Formidling og gennemførelse af reklameforanstaltninger; Organisering af arrangementer med kommercielle og reklamemæssige formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Organisation von Veranstaltungen, Ausstellungen, Messen und Shows für kommerzielle, verkaufsfördernde und Werbezwecke; Marketing; Unternehmensmarketingdienste; Beratung auf dem Gebiet des Marketings; Unternehmensberatung in Bezug auf das Marketing; Nachforschungen im Zusammenhang mit Werbung und Marketing; Erstellung von Marketingberichten; Leitung von Marketingstudien; Über digitale Netze bereitgestellte Marketingdienstleistungen; Werbung; Event-Marketing; Organisation und Durchführung von Marketingveranstaltungen; Organisation und Durchführung von Werbeveranstaltungen; Organisation von Veranstaltungen zu Reklame- und Werbezwecken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Οργάνωση εκδηλώσεων, εκθέσεων, εμπορικών εκθέσεων και επιδείξεων για εμπορικούς και διαφημιστικούς σκοπούς και προώθηση· Υπηρεσίες μάρκετινγκ· Υπηρεσίες μάρκετινγκ επιχειρήσεων· Συμβουλευτική σε θέματα μάρκετινγκ· Συμβουλευτική επιχειρήσεων στον τομέα του μάρκετινγκ· Υπηρεσίες έρευνας σε σχέση με τη διαφήμιση και το μάρκετινγκ· Εκπόνηση εκθέσεων μάρκετινγκ· Διεξαγωγή μελετών μάρκετινγκ· Υπηρεσίες μάρκετινγκ παρεχόμενες μέσω ψηφιακών δικτύων· Διαφήμιση· Μάρκετινγκ εκδηλώσεων· Διοργάνωση και διεξαγωγή εκδηλώσεων μάρκετινγκ· Οργάνωση και διεξαγωγή διαφημιστικών εκστρατειών· Οργάνωση εκδηλώσεων για εμπορικούς διαφημιστικούς σκοπούς.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Organization of events, exhibitions, fairs and shows for commercial, promotional and advertising purposes; Marketing services; Business marketing services; Advisory services relating to marketing; Business advice relating to marketing; Research services relating to advertising and marketing; Provision of marketing reports; Conducting of marketing studies; Marketing services provided by means of digital networks; Advertising services; Event marketing; Arranging and conducting of marketing events; Arranging and conducting of advertising events; Organisation of events for commercial and advertising purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Organización de eventos, exhibiciones, ferias y espectáculos con fines comerciales, promocionales y publicitarios; Marketing; Servicios de marketing comercial; Asesoramiento en marketing; Asesoramiento comercial sobre marketing; Servicios de investigación sobre publicidad y marketing; Facilitación de informes de marketing; Realización de estudios de marketing; Servicios de marketing prestados por medio de redes digitales; Publicidad; Marketing mediante eventos; Organización y celebración de eventos de marketing; Organización y realización de actividades publicitarias; Servicios de organización de eventos con fines comerciales y promociones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ürituste, näituste ja messide korraldamine äri ja reklaami eesmärgil; Turundus; Äriturundusteenused; Turundusalane nõustamine; Turundusega seotud ärialane nõustamine; Reklaami ja turundusega seotud uurimisteenused; Turuülevaadete koostamine; Turu-uuringute teostamine; Turundusteenused digitaalsete võrkude kaudu; Reklaam; Ürituste turundamine; Turundusürituste korraldamine ja läbiviimine; Reklaamiürituste korraldamine ja läbiviimine; Kaubandus- ja reklaamürituste korraldamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tapahtumien, näyttelyiden, messutapahtumien ja esitysten järjestäminen myynninedistämis- ja mainostarkoituksiin; Markkinointipalvelut; Yritysten markkinointipalvelut; Markkinointiin liittyvän neuvonnan tarjoaminen; Markkinointiin liittyvä yritysneuvonta; Mainontaan ja markkinointiin liittyvät tutkimuspalvelut; Markkinointiraporttien valmistelu; Markkinointitutkimukset; Markkinointipalvelut digitaalisten verkkojen välityksellä; Mainonta; Tapahtumien markkinointi; Markkinointitapahtumien järjestäminen ja toteutus; Mainostilaisuuksien järjestäminen ja toteutus; Tapahtumien järjestäminen kaupallisiin tai mainontatarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Organisation d'événements, d'expositions, de foires et de spectacles à des fins commerciales, promotionnelles et publicitaires; Marketing; Services de marketing commercial; Prestations de conseils en marketing; Conseils commerciaux en rapport avec le marketing; Services de recherche en matière de publicité et marketing; Mise à disposition de rapports de marketing; Réalisation d'études de marketing; Services de marketing fournis au moyen de réseaux numériques; Publicité; Services de marketing événementiel; Organisation et conduite de manifestations de marketing; Services d'organisation et de réalisation d'événements publicitaires; Organisation d'événements à des fins commerciales et publicitaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Organiziranje događanja, izložbi, sajmova i priredbi u komercijalne, promotivne i reklamne svrhe; Marketing; Usluge poslovnog marketinga; Marketinško savjetovanje; Usluge poslovnog savjetovanja u području marketinga; Usluge istraživanja u vezi s oglašavanjem i marketingom; Pružanje marketinških izvještaja; Vođenje marketinških studija; Marketinške usluge koje se pružaju putem digitalnih mreža; Oglašavanje; Event marketing; Organizacija i provedba marketinških događanja; Organiziranje i provođenje promidžbenih događaja; Organiziranje događanja u komercijalne i reklamne svrhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Rendezvények, kiállítások, vásárok és bemutatók szervezése kereskedelmi, promóciós és reklámozási célokra; Marketing szolgáltatások; Üzleti marketing szolgáltatások; Marketing tanácsadás; Marketinggel kapcsolatos üzleti tanácsadás; Kutatási szolgáltatások reklámozással és marketinggel kapcsolatban; Marketing beszámolók készítése; Marketing tanulmányok készítése; Digitális hálózatok útján nyújtott marketing szolgáltatások; Hirdetési- és reklámszolgáltatások; Eseménymarketing; Marketingrendezvények megrendezése és lebonyolítása; Reklámcélú rendezvények szervezése és lebonyolítása; Kereskedelmi és reklámcélú rendezvények szervezése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Organizzazione di eventi, esposizioni, fiere e spettacoli per fini commerciali, promozionali e pubblicitari; Marketing; Servizi di marketing aziendale; Fornitura di consulenza in materia di marketing; Consulenza aziendale in materia di marketing; Servizi di ricerca inerenti la pubblicità e il marketing; Fornitura di relazioni di mercato; Studi di marketing; Servizi di comunicazione disponibili tramite reti digitali; Pubblicità; Marketing degli eventi; Organizzazione e direzione di eventi di marketing; Organizzazione e attuazione di eventi promozionali; Organizzazione di eventi a scopo commerciale e pubblicitario.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Renginių, parodų, mugių ir pristatymų organizavimas komercijos, pardavimų skatinimo ir reklamos tikslais; Rinkodara; Verslo rinkodaros paslaugos; Rinkodaros patarimai; Verslo konsultacijų, susijusių su rinkodara, teikimas; Reklamos ir rinkodaros tyrimų paslaugos; Rinkodaros ataskaitų teikimas; Rinkodaros nagrinėjimas; Rinkodaros paslaugos, teikiamos skaitmeniniais tinklais; Reklama; Renginių rinkodaros paslaugos; Rinkodaros renginių rengimas ir vedimas; Reklaminių renginių organizavimas ir vedimas; Renginių organizavimas komercijos ir reklamos reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pasākumu, izstāžu, gadatirgu un izrāžu rīkošana komerciālos, veicināšanas un reklāmas nolūkos; Mārketinga pakalpojumi; Uzņēmumu mārketinga pakalpojumi; Padomu un ieteikumu došana mārketinga jomā; Biznesa konsultāciju pakalpojumi saistībā ar tirgvedību; Izpētes pakalpojumi, kas attiecas uz reklamēšanu un tirgvedību; Tirgvedības atskaišu nodrošināšana; Mārketinga pētījumu veikšana; Mārketinga pakalpojumi, ko nodrošina pa digitāliem tīkliem; Reklāma; Pasākumu mārketings; Tirgvedības pasākumu organizēšana un vadīšana; Reklāmas pasākumu starpniecība un realizēšana; Pasākumu organizēšana komerciāliem un reklāmas nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">L-organizzazzjoni ta' avvenimenti, esibizzjonijiet, fieri u wirjiet għal skopijiet kummerċjali, promozzjonali u ta' reklamar; Servizzi ta' kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Servizzi ta' kummerċjalizzazzjoni tan-negozju; Servizzi ta' pariri relatati mal-kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Pariri dwar negozju relatati mal-kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Servizzi ta' riċerka dwar reklamar u markiting; Il-provvista ta' rapporti tal-kummerċjalizzazzjoni; It-tmexxija ta' studji dwar il-kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Servizzi ta' marketing ipprovduti permezz ta' netwerks diġitali; Reklamar; Marketing b'użu ta' eventi; Organizzazzjoni u tmexxija ta’ avvenimenti ta’ kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Organizzazzjoni u tmexxija ta' attivitajiet pubbliċitarji; L-organizzazzjoni ta' avvenimenti għal skopijiet kummerċjali u ta' reklamar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Organisatie van evenementen, tentoonstellingen, beurzen en shows voor commerciële, promotionele en reclamedoeleinden; Marketing; Bedrijfsmarketingdiensten; Verstrekken van advies met betrekking tot marketing; Advisering inzake bedrijfsmarketing; Onderzoek met betrekking tot reclame en marketing; Verschaffen van marketingrapporten; Marketingstudies; Marketing via digitale netwerken; Publiciteit; Eventmarketing; Organiseren en houden van marketingevenementen; Organiseren en houden van reclame evenementen; Organisatie van evenementen voor publicitaire en/of commerciële doeleinden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Organizowanie imprez, wystaw, targów i pokazów do celów handlowych, promocyjnych i reklamowych; Usługi marketingowe; Usługi w zakresie marketingu gospodarczego; Doradztwo w zakresie marketingu; Doradztwo w zakresie działalności gospodarczej dotyczące marketingu; Usługi badawcze w zakresie reklamy i marketingu; Udostępnianie raportów marketingowych; Prowadzenie badań marketingowych; Usługi marketingowe świadczone za pomocą sieci cyfrowych; Reklama; Marketing imprez i wydarzeń; Organizacja i przeprowadzanie wydarzeń marketingowych; Organizacja i przeprowadzanie imprez reklamowych; Organizowanie imprez w celach handlowych i reklamowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Organização de eventos, exposições, feiras e espetáculos para fins comerciais, promocionais e publicitários; Marketing; Serviços de marketing empresarial; Assessoria em marketing; Assessoria de negócios comerciais relacionada com marketing; Serviços de pesquisa relacionados com publicidade e marketing; Fornecimento de relatórios de marketing; Execução de estudos de marketing; Serviços de marketing prestados por meio de redes digitais; Publicidade; Marketing sob a forma de eventos; Organização e realização de eventos de marketing; Organização e realização de atividades publicitárias; Organização de eventos com fins comerciais e publicitários.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Organizare de evenimente, expoziții, târguri și spectacole în scopuri comerciale, promoționale și publicitare; Servicii de marketing; Servicii de marketing comercial; Servicii de consiliere privind marketingul; Servicii de consultanță în afaceri privind marketingul; Servicii de cercetare cu privire la publicitate și marketing; Întocmire de rapoarte de marketing; Efectuarea studiilor de marketing; Servicii de marketing furnizate prin intermediul rețelelor digitale; Publicitate; Marketing pentru evenimente; Organizare și coordonare de evenimente de marketing; Organizare și realizare de evenimente publicitare; Organizare de evenimente în scopuri comerciale și publicitare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Organizovanie podujatí, výstav, veľtrhov a prezentácií na obchodné a reklamné účely a podporu predaja; Marketing; Marketingové služby v oblasti podnikania a obchodu; Marketingové poradenstvo; Obchodné poradenské služby v oblasti marketingu; Výskumné služby v oblasti reklamy a marketingu; Poskytovanie marketingových správ; Vedenie marketingových štúdií; Marketingové služby poskytované prostredníctvom digitálnych sietí; Reklama; Získavanie zákazníkov usporadúvaním reklamných podujatí (event marketing); Organizovanie a vedenie marketingových podujatí; Organizovanie a vedenie reklamných podujatí; Organizovanie podujatí na obchodné alebo reklamné účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Organizacija prireditev, razstav, sejmov in predstav za trgovske, promocijske in oglasne namene; Storitve trženja; Poslovno marketinške storitve; Marketinško svetovanje; Poslovno svetovanje v zvezi z marketingom; Storitve raziskav v zvezi z oglaševanjem in trženjem; Priprava trženjskih poročil; Izvajanje tržnih študij; Storitve trženja, ki se nudijo prek digitalnih omrežij; Oglaševanje in oglaševalske storitve; Trženje dogodkov; Prirejanje in izvajanje trženjskih dogodkov; Prirejanje in izvajanje oglaševalskih prireditev; Organizacija dogodkov za komercialne in oglasne namene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Organisering av evenemang, utställningar, mässor och shower för kommersiella, säljfrämjande verksamhet och reklamändamål; Marketing; Företagsmarknadsföringstjänster; Marknadsföringsrådgivning; Företagsrådgivning rörande marknadsföring; Undersökningstjänster avseende reklam och marknadsföring; Utarbetande av marknadsföringsrapporter; Utförande av marknadsföringsstudier; Marknadsföringstjänster tillhandahållna via digitala nät; Reklam; Evenemangsmarknadsföring; Arrangerande och genomförande av marknadsföringsevenemang; Anordnande och genomförande av reklamevenemang; Anordnande av tillställningar för kommersiella- och reklamändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>38</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Електронна поща; Комуникационни услуги; Безжични цифрови съобщителни услуги; Комуникационни услуги за предаване на данни; Предаване на информация посредством електронна поща; Предаване на данни за трети лица; Предаване на съобщения, информация и изображения с помощта на компютър; Услуги за цифрово разпространение; Телекомуникационни услуги; Услуги за електронни и телекомуникационни излъчвания; Доставяне на съобщения и данни по електронен път; Услуги за електронна вътрeшна размяна на данни; Електронен обмен на данни, съхраняващи се в бази данни, достъпни чрез телекомуникационни мрежи; Услуги за незабавано получаване на електронни съобщения; Предаване на кодирани съобщения и изображения; Предаване на кратки съобщения [SMS], съобщения с изображения, реч, звук, музика и текст между мобилни телекомуникационни устройства.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přenos elektronické pošty; Komunikační služby; Služby v oblasti bezdrátového digitálního zasílání zpráv; Přenos dat; Přenos informací elektronickou poštou; Přenos dat pro třetí osoby; Přenos zpráv, informací a obrazu pomocí počítače; Služby v oblasti digitálního přenosu; Telekomunikační služby; Služby v oblasti elektronického a telekomunikačního přenosu; Doručování zpráv a dat prostřednictvím elektronického přenosu; Služby v oblasti elektronické výměny dat; Elektronická výměna dat uložených v databázích přístupných prostřednictvím telekomunikačních sítí; Služby elektronických zpráv v reálném čase (instant messaging); Přenos zakódovaných zpráv a obrazů; Přenos krátkých zpráv [SMS], obrazové, hlasové, zvukové, hudební a textové komunikace mezi mobilními telekomunikačními přístroji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Transmission af e-mail; Telekommunikationsydelser; Trådløse tjenester til udsendelse af digitale meddelelser; Datatransmission; Transmission af data via mail; Datatransmission for andre; Computerstøttet transmission af meddelelser, informationer og billeder; Tjenester inden for digital transmission; Telekommunikation; Elektronisk transmission og transmission via telekommunikation; Levering af meddelelser og data ved hjælp af elektronisk transmission; Elektroniske dataudvekslingstjenester; Elektronisk udveksling af data lagret i en database og som er tilgængelige via telekommunikationsnetværk; Tjenester til øjeblikkelig udsendelse af meddelelser; Udsendelse af kodede meddelelser og billeder; Transmission af sms-beskeder, billeder, tale, lyd, musik og tekstkommunikation mellem mobile telekommunikationsenheder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Übermittlung von elektronischer Post; Kommunikationsdienste; Drahtlose digitale Nachrichtenübertragung; Datenübertragung; Datenübertragung mittels E-Mail; Datenübertragung für Dritte; Computergestützte Übertragung von Nachrichten, Informationen und Bildern; Digitale Übertragungsdienste; Telekommunikationsdienstleistungen; Elektronische und Telekommunikationsübertragungsdienste; Übermittlung von Nachrichten und Daten durch elektronische Übertragung; Elektronischer Austausch von Daten; Elektronischer Austausch von Daten aus Datenbanken, die über Telekommunikationsnetze zugänglich sind; Unmittelbare elektronische Nachrichtenübermittlung; Übertragung von verschlüsselten Nachrichten und Bildern; Übertragung von Kurznachrichten [SMS], Bildern, Gesprochenem, Tönen, Musik und Textmitteilungen zwischen Kommunikationsgeräten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ταχυδρομείο ηλεκτρονικό· Υπηρεσίες επικοινωνίας· Υπηρεσίες ασύρματης ψηφιακής μηνυματοδοσίας· Υπηρεσίες μετάδοσης δεδομένων· Μετάδοση δεδομένων μέσω ηλεκτρονικού ταχυδρομείου· Μετάδοση δεδομένων για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Μετάδοση πληροφοριών, μηνυμάτων και εικόνων με τη βοήθεια υπολογιστή· Υπηρεσίες ψηφιακής μετάδοσης· Υπηρεσίες τηλεπικοινωνίας· Υπηρεσίες ηλεκτρονικής και τηλεπικοινωνιακής μετάδοσης· Παράδοση μηνυμάτων και δεδομένων μέσω συστημάτων ηλεκτρονικής μετάδοσης· Υπηρεσίες ανταλλαγής ηλεκτρονικών δεδομένων· Ηλεκτρονική ανταλλαγή δεδομένων αποθηκευμένων σε βάσεις δεδομένων προσβάσιμες μέσω τηλεπικοινωνιακών δικτύων· Υπηρεσίες στιγμιαίας ηλεκτρονικής μηνυματοδοσίας· Μετάδοση κωδικοποιημένων μηνυμάτων και εικόνων· Μετάδοση σύντομων γραπτών μηνυμάτων [SMS], εικόνων, ομιλίας, ήχου, μουσικής και κειμένου μεταξύ κινητών τηλεπικοινωνιακών συσκευών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Email services; Provision of email services; Communication services; Wireless digital messaging services; Data transmission; Data transmission by electronic mail; Data transmission for others; Computer aided transmission of messages, information and images; Digital transmission services; Telecommunication services; Electronic and telecommunication transmission services; Delivery of messages and data by electronic transmission; Electronic data interchange services; Electronic mail services; Electronic exchange of data stored in databases accessible via telecommunication networks; Instant messaging services; Transmission of coded messages and images; Transmission of short messages [SMS], images, speech, sound, music and text communications between mobile telecommunications devices.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Transmisión de mensajes de correo electrónico; Servicios de comunicaciones; Servicios de mensajería digital inalámbrica; Transmisión de datos; Transmisión de información por medio de correo electrónico; Transmisión de datos para terceros; Transmisión asistida por ordenador de mensajes, informaciones e imágenes; Servicios de transmisión digital; Servicios de telecomunicaciones; Servicios de transmisión electrónica y de telecomunicaciones; Entrega de mensajes e información mediante transmisión electrónica; Servicios de intercambio electrónico de datos; Intercambio electrónico de datos almacenados en bases de datos accesibles a través de redes de telecomunicaciones; Servicios de mensajería electrónica instantánea; Transmisión de mensajes y de imágenes codificadas; Transmisión de mensajes cortos [SMS], imágenes, voz, sonido, música y textos entre dispositivos móviles de telecomunicación.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Elektronpost; Sideteenused; Traadita digitaalse sõnumside teenused; Andmete edastamine; Andmeedastus e-posti teel; Andmeedastus kolmandate isikute jaoks; Sõnumite, teabe ja piltide edastus arvuti abil; Digitaaledastusteenused; Sideteenused; Elektrooniliste ja telekommunikatsiooniseadmete vahendusel edastamise teenused; Sõnumite ja andmete elektrooniline edastamine; Elektroonilise andmevahetuse teenused; Telekommunikatsioonivõrkude vahendusel ligipääsetavates andmebaasides talletatavate andmete elektrooniline vahetus; Vahetud elektronsõnumiteenused; Kodeeritud sõnumite ja kujutiste edastamine; Lühisõnumite [SMS], kujutiste, kõne, heli, muusika ja teksti sideedastus mobiilsideseadmete vahel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sähköpostien välitys; Viestintäpalvelut; Langattomat digitaaliset viestipalvelut; Tiedonsiirto; Datansiirto sähköpostin kautta; Datansiirto muiden lukuun; Viestien, tietojen ja kuvien lähetys tietokoneen välityksellä; Digitaaliset tiedonsiirtopalvelut; Kaukoviestintä; Elektroniset ja tietoliikennelähetyspalvelut; Sanomien ja datan jakelu sähköisesti; Elektroniset tiedonvaihtopalvelut; Tietokantoihin tallennettujen tietojen vaihto sähköisesti tietoliikenneverkkojen kautta; Välittömät elektroniset viestintäpalvelut; Koodattujen viestien ja kuvien siirto; Tekstiviestien [SMS], kuvien, puheen, äänen, musiikin ja tekstien siirto langattomien tietoliikennelaitteiden välillä.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Transmission de courriels; Services de communication [télécommunications]; Services de messagerie numérique sans fil; Services de transmission de données; Transmission de données par courrier électronique; Transmission de données pour des tiers; Transmission de messages, d'informations et d'images assistée par ordinateur; Services de transmission numérique; Services de télécommunications; Services de transmission électronique de données et de télécommunication; Services de messages et données par transmission électronique; Services d'échange de données électroniques; Services d'échange électronique de données stockées dans des bases de données accessibles via des réseaux de télécommunications; Services de messagerie instantanée; Transmission de messages et d'images codés; Transmission de messages courts [SMS], d'images, de discours, de sons, de musique et de textes entre des dispositifs de télécommunication mobile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Elektronička pošta; Komunikacijske usluge; Usluge bežičnog prijenosa digitalnih poruka; Prijenos podataka; Prijenos podataka elektroničkom poštom; Prijenos podataka za druge; Računalno potpomognut prijenos poruka, podataka i slika; Usluge digitalnog prijenosa; Telekomunikacijske usluge; Usluge elektroničkog i telekomunikacijskog prijenosa; Isporuka poruka i podataka elektroničkim prijenosom; Elektronička razmjena podataka; Elektronička razmjena podataka spremljenih u baze podataka kojima je moguće pristupiti putem telekomunikacijskih mreža; Usluge slanja elektroničkih izravnih poruka u realnom vremenu; Prijenos šifriranih poruka i slika; Prijenos kratkih poruka [SMS], slika, govora, zvuka, glazbe i tekstovnih komunikacija između mobilnih telekomunikacijskih naprava.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Elektronikus levelezés, e-mail; Kommunikációs szolgáltatások; Vezeték nélküli digitális üzenetküldő szolgáltatások; Adatátviteli szolgáltatások; Adattovábbítás elektronikus levélben; Adatátviteli szolgáltatás; Üzenetek, információk és képek továbbítása számítógép segítségével; Digitális átviteli szolgáltatások; Távközlési szolgáltatások; Elektronikus és távközlési továbbítási szolgáltatások; Üzenetek és adatok közvetítése elektronikus átadással; Elektronikus adatcsere-szolgáltatások; Távközlési hálózatról elérhető adatbázisban tárolt adatok elektronikus cseréje; Közvetlen elektronikus üzenetközvetítő szolgáltatások; Kódolt üzenetek és képek átvitele; Rövid üzenetek [SMS], képek, beszédhang, hangok, zene és szöveges kommunikáció mobilkommunikációs eszközök közti átvitele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Trasmissione di posta elettronica; Servizi di comunicazione; Invio di messaggi digitale senza filo; Trasmissione di dati; Trasmissione d' informazioni mediante posta elettronica; Trasmissione dati per conto terzi; Trasmissione computerizzata di messaggi, informazioni e immagini; Servizi di trasmissione digitale; Servizi di telecomunicazione; Servizi di trasmissione elettronica e telecomunicazione; Trasmissione di messaggi e dati per via elettronica; Servizi elettronici di interscambio dati; Scambio elettronico di dati archiviati in banche dati accessibili tramite reti di telecomunicazione; Messaggeria elettronica istantanea; Trasmissione di messaggi e di immagini codificate; Trasmissione di messaggeria breve [SMS], immagini, voci, suoni, musica e testo tra dispositivi di telefonia mobile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektroninio pašto perdavimas; Ryšių paslaugos; Belaidžio skaitmeninių pranešimų perdavimo paslaugos; Duomenų perdavimas; Duomenų perdavimas elektroniniu paštu; Duomenų perdavimas kitiems; Pranešimų, informacijos ir vaizdų perdavimas kompiuteriu; Skaitmeninio perdavimo paslaugos; Telekomunikacijų paslaugos; Elektroninio ir telekomunikacijų perdavimo paslaugos; Pranešimų ir duomenų pristatymas elektroninio perdavimo būdu; Elektroniniai duomenų mainai; Elektroniniai duomenų, saugomų telekomunikacijų tinklais pasiekiamose duomenų bazėse, mainai; Elektroninių tikralaikių pokalbių parūpinimo paslaugos; Koduotųjų pranešimų ir vaizdų perdavimas; Trumpųjų pranešimų [SMS], paveikslų, kalbos, garso, muzikos ir tekstinių mainų perdavimas tarp mobiliųjų telekomunikacijų įtaisų.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elektroniskā pasta pakalpojumi; Sakaru pakalpojumi; Bezvadu digitālās ziņojumapmaiņas pakalpojumi; Datu pārraides pakalpojumi; Datu pārraide pa elektronisko pastu; Datu pārraide trešajām personām; Datorizēta ziņojumu, datu un attēlu pārraide; Cipardatu pārraidīšanas pakalpojumi; Telesakaru pakalpojumi; Elektroniskas un telekomunikāciju transmisijas pakalpojumi; Paziņojumu un datu piegāde, izmantojot elektronisko pārraidi; Elektronisko datu apmaiņas pakalpojumi; Elektroniska apmaiņa ar datubāzēs saglabātiem datiem, izmantojot telekomunikāciju tīklus; Tūlītējas elektronisko paziņojumu apmaiņas pakalpojumi; Kodētu ziņu un attēlu pārraide; Īsziņu [SMS], attēlu, runu, audio satura, mūzikas un teksta komunikācija nosūtīšana starp mobilajām telekomunikāciju ierīcēm.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Posta elettronika; Servizzi ta' komunikazzjoni; Servizzi ta' trasmissjoni bla fili għal messaġġi diġitali; Servizzi tat-trasmissjoni tad-data; Trasmissjoni ta' informazzjoni permezz tal-posta elettronika; Trasmissjoni ta' dejta għall-oħrajn; It-trasmissjoni bl-għajnuna tal-kompjuter ta' messaġġi, informazzjoni u xbihat; Servizzi ta' trasmissjoni diġitali; Servizzi tat-telekommunikazzjoni; Servizzi tat-trasmissjoni elettronika u tat-telekomunikazzjoni; It-tqassim ta' messaġġi u data permezz ta' trasmissjoni elettronika; Servizzi ta' interkambju ta' dejta elettronika; Skambju elettroniku ta' dejta maħżuna ġo bażi ta' dati aċċessibbli permezz ta' netwerks tat-telekomunikazzjoni; Servizzi ta' messaġġi elettroniċi istantanji; Trasmissjoni ta' messaġġi u immaġini kkodifikati; Trasmissjoni ta' messaġġi qosra [SMS], immaġni, leħen, ħoss, mużika u komunikazzjonijiet testwali bejn tagħmir ċellulari tat-telekomunikazzjonijiet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verzending van elektronische berichten; Communicatiediensten; Draadloze digitale berichtverzending; Datatransmissiediensten; Verzenden van informatie via elektronische post; Gegevensoverdracht voor derden; Computerondersteunde verzending van berichten, informatie en beelden; Digitale overdracht; Telecommunicatiediensten; Elektronische verzending en telecommunicatieverzending; Het bezorgen van boodschappen en gegevens via elektronische verzending; Voor elektronische gegevensuitwisselingsdiensten; Elektronische uitwisseling van gegevens opgeslagen in databases en beschikbaar via telecommunicatienetwerken; Directe elektronische berichtendienst; Overdracht van gecodeerde berichten en beelden; Verzenden van korte berichten [SMS], afbeeldingen, spraak, geluid, muziek en tekstcommunicatie tussen mobiele telecommunicatietoestellen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Poczta elektroniczna; Usługi łączności; Usługi bezprzewodowego przesyłania wiadomości cyfrowych; Transmisja danych; Transmisja danych za pośrednictwem poczty elektronicznej; Transmisja danych na rzecz osób trzecich; Wspomagana komputerowo transmisja wiadomości, danych i obrazów; Usługi transmisji cyfrowej; Usługi telekomunikacyjne; Usługi transmisji elektronicznej i telekomunikacyjnej; Dostarczanie wiadomości i danych w drodze transmisji elektronicznej; Usługi elektronicznej wymiany danych; Elektroniczna wymiana danych przechowywanych w bazach danych dostępnych za pośrednictwem sieci telekomunikacyjnych; Usługi natychmiastowego przesyłania wiadomości elektronicznych; Przesyłanie zakodowanych wiadomości i obrazów; Transmisja krótkich wiadomości [SMS], obrazów, mowy, dźwięku, muzyki i komunikatów tekstowych pomiędzy mobilnymi urządzeniami telekomunikacyjnymi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Transmissão de correio eletrónico; Serviços de comunicação; Serviços de transmissão de mensagens digital sem fios; Transmissão de dados; Transmissão de dados por correio eletrónico; Transmissão de dados para terceiros; Transmissão de mensagens, informações e imagens assistida por computador; Serviços de transmissão digital; Serviços de telecomunicações; Serviços de transmissão eletrónica e de telecomunicação; Distribuição de mensagens e dados por transmissão eletrónica; Serviço de intercâmbio eletrónico de dados; Intercâmbio eletrónico de dados armazenados em bases de dados acessíveis através de redes de telecomunicações; Serviços de mensagens eletrónicas instantâneas; Transmissão de mensagens e imagens codificadas; Transmissão de mensagens curtas [SMS], imagens, voz, som, música e textos entre dispositivos móveis de telecomunicação.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Mesaje electronice; Servicii de comunicații; Servicii de mesagerie digitală fără fir; Servicii de transmisie de date; Transmisie de date prin poștă electronică; Transmisie de date pentru terți; Transmisie de mesaje, date și imagini asistată de calculator; Servicii de transmisii digitale; Servicii de telecomunicații; Servicii de transmisie electronică și de telecomunicații; Transmitere de mesaje și date prin transmisie electronică; Servicii de schimb de date electronice; Schimb electronic de date stocate în baze de date accesibile prin intermediul rețelelor de telecomunicații; Servicii de mesagerie electronică instantanee; Transmisie de mesaje și imagini codificate; Transmitere de mesaje scurte [SMS], de imagini, de voce, de sunete, de muzică și de comunicații în format text între dispozitive de telecomunicații mobile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Prenos elektronickej pošty; Komunikačné služby; Služby v oblasti bezdrôtového posielania správ; Prenos údajov; Prenos informácií prostredníctvom elektronickej pošty; Prenos údajov pre tretie osoby; Počítačový prenos správ, informácií a obrazov; Služby digitálneho prenosu; Telekomunikačné služby; Elektronické a telekomunikačné prenosové služby; Dodanie správ a dát prostredníctvom elektronického prenosu; Služby elektronickej výmeny údajov; Služby v oblasti elektronickej výmeny dát uložených v databázach prístupných prostredníctvom telekomunikačnej siete; Služby okamžitého posielania elektronických správ; Transmisia zakódovaných správ a obrazov; Prenos SMS správ, obrázkov, reči, zvuku, hudby a textovej komunikácie medzi mobilnými telekomunikačnými zariadeniami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Elektronska pošta; Komunikacijske storitve; Storitve brezžičnega digitalnega sporočanja; Prenos podatkov; Prenos informacij po elektronski pošti; Prenos podatkov za druge; Računalniško podprt prenos sporočil, informacij in slik; Storitve digitalnega prenosa; Telekomunikacijske storitve; Storitve elektronskega in telekomunikacijskega prenosa; Dostava sporočil in podatkov z elektronskim prenosom; Elektronska izmenjava podatkov; Elektronska izmenjava podatkov, shranjenih v podatkovnih bazah, dostopnih preko telekomunikacijskih omrežij; Storitve trenutnega elektronskega sporočanja; Prenos kodiranih sporočil in slik; Prenos kratkih sporočil [SMS], slik, govora, zvoka, glasbe in besedilne komunikacije med mobilnimi telekomunikacijskimi napravami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Elektronisk post; Kommunikationstjänster; Trådlösa digitala meddelandetjänster; Dataöverföring; Överföring av information med hjälp av e-post; Dataöverföring för andra; Datorstödd överföring av meddelanden, information och bilder; Digitala överföringstjänster; Telekommunikationstjänster; Elektronisk överföring och telekommunikationsöverföring; Leverans av meddelanden och data via elektronisk överföring; Elektronisk dataväxling; Elektroniskt utbyte av data lagrade i databaser som är åtkomliga via telekommunikationsnät; Tjänster avseende omedelbar elektronisk överföring av meddelanden; Överföring av kodade meddelanden och bilder; Överföring av korta meddelanden [SMS], bilder, tal, ljud, musik och textkommunikation mellan mobila telekommunikationsapparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/085</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-07</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>956409</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>88413</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003125957</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-07-10</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>SE</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>2016-00007</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2016-01-02</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>533541</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2016-07-29</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>DotLive</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>76488</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
