<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-17T08:58:42</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228500</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228500</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-13</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-17</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>GREENCARE</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162456016</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/228/018228500/000162456016.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>24.13.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>24.17.07</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.05.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.05.18</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.05</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.21</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.07</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Хигиенни мъжки гащи; Гащи, абсорбиращи, за хора, страдащи от инконтиненция; Бебешки пелени; Дрехи за хора с инконтиненция; Асептичен памук; Пелени за изпускащи се хора; Пластири; Превръзки при инконтиненция; Антисептичен памук; Дамски превръзки; Превръзки за очи за медицински цели; Наркотици за медицински цели; Аптечки [преносими] пълни; Санитарни кърпички за еднократна употреба; Дамски превръзки; Пелени за възрастни; Бинтове за превързване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Hygienické kalhotky; Absorpční kalhotky pro inkontinentní pacienty; Dětské plenkové kalhotky; Inkontinenční oděvy; Aseptická vata; Inkontinenční pleny; Náplasti; Vložky hygienické pro inkontinentní osoby; Antiseptická vata; Hygienické vložky; Pásky na oči pro léčebné účely; Drogy pro léčebné účely; Přenosné vybavené lékárničky; Dezinfekční ubrousky; Hygienické tampóny; Pleny pro dospělé; Obvazy na ošetření ran.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Hygiejnebenklæder; Absorberende inkontinensbenklæder; Blebukser til spædbørn; Inkontinensbeklædning; Aseptisk vat; Bleer til inkontinens; Hæfteplaster; Inkontinensbind; Antiseptisk vat; Hygiejnebind; Øjenklapper til medicinske formål; Droger til medicinske formål; Rejseapoteker; Renseservietter; Menstruationstamponer; Bleer til voksne; Bandager til forbinding.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Monatshöschen; Saugfähige Inkontinenzhosen; Babyhöschenwindeln; Inkontinenzbekleidung; Aseptische Baumwolle; Inkontinenzwindeln; Heftpflaster; Inkontinenzeinlagen; Antiseptische Baumwolle; Damenbinden; Augenklappen für medizinische Zwecke; Drogen für medizinische Zwecke; Reiseapotheken [Arzneimittel-Sets]; Desinfektionstücher für medizinische Zwecke; Tampons für hygienische Zwecke; Windeln für Erwachsene; Bandagen für Verbandszwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κυλότες υγιεινής· Κυλόττες υγιεινής για την ακράτεια· Πάνες [βρεφικές πάνες]· Εσώρουχα για την ακράτεια· Ασηπτικό βαμβάκι· Πάνες υγιεινής για την ακράτεια· Λευκοπλάστης με γάζα· Επιθέματα ακράτειας· Αντισηπτικό βαμβάκι· Σερβιέτες υγιεινής· Προστατευτικά καλύμματα ματιού για ιατρική χρήση· Ναρκωτικά για ιατρική χρήση· Φαρμακεία φορητά ταξιδίου· Μαντιλάκια καθαρισμού· Ταμπόν για χρήσεις υγιεινής· Πάνες για ενήλικες· Επίδεσμοι για επιδέσεις.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">menstruation knickers; pants,absorbent, for incontinence; babies' napkin-pants; Incontinence garments; aseptic cotton; diapers for incontinents; adhesive plasters; Incontinence pads; antiseptic cotton; sanitary pads; sanitary panties; eyepatches for medical purposes; drugs for medical purposes; medicine cases, portable, filled; sanitary towels; sanitizing wipes; sanitary tampons; Adult diapers; bandages for dressings.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bragas higiénicas; Bragas absorbentes para la incontinencia; Pañales-braga para bebés; Ropa interior especial para incontinentes; Algodón aséptico; Pañales higiénicos para la incontinencia; Esparadrapos; Compresas para incontinentes; Algodón antiséptico; Compresas higiénicas; Parches oculares para uso médico; Drogas para uso médico; Botiquines de viaje; Paños desinfectantes; Tampones higiénicos; Pañales para adultos; Vendas para apósitos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hügieenipüksikud; Pidamatushaigete imavad püksikud; Imikute mähkmepüksid; Uriinipidamatusrõivad; Aseptiline vatt; Pidamatushaigete mähkmed; Plaastrid; Pidamatushaigete sidemed; Antiseptiline vatt; Hügieenisidemed; Meditsiiniotstarbelised silmalapid; Meditsiinilised rohud, ravimid; Täidetud käsiapteegid; Desinfitseerivad lapid; Tampoonid; Täiskasvanute mähkmed; Sidemed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hygieniasuojat; Pidätyskyvyttömille tarkoitetut vaippahousut, imukykyiset; Vauvojen vaippahousut; Inkontinenssivaatteet; Aseptinen [puhdas] vanu; Inkontinenssivaipat; Laastarit, sidontatarvikkeet; Inkontinenssityynyt; Antiseptinen vanu; Terveyssiteet; Silmälaput lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Rohdokset; Lääkelaukut [valmiiksi varustettuina]; Desinfiointipyyhkeet; Kuukautistamponit; Aikuisten vaipat; Sidontatarvikkeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Culottes hygiéniques; Culottes hygiéniques pour incontinents; Couches-culottes pour bébés; Vêtements spéciaux d'incontinence; Coton aseptique; Couches hygiéniques pour personnes incontinentes; Sparadrap; Couches d'incontinence; Coton antiseptique; Serviettes hygiéniques; Caches oculaires à usage médical; Drogues à usage médical; Droguiers de voyage; Lingettes désinfectantes; Tampons hygiéniques; Couches pour adultes; Bandes pour pansements.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Higijenske gaćice; Upijajuće gaćice za inkontinenciju; Nepromočive gaćice-pelene za bebe; Odjeća za inkontinenciju; Aseptična vata; Pelene za inkontinenciju; Flasteri; Ulošci za inkontinenciju; Antiseptička vata; Higijenski ulošci; Štitnici za oči za medicinske potrebe; Droge za medicinske potrebe; Priručna apoteka za putovanje; Dezinfekcijske maramice; Higijenski taponi; Pelene za odrasle; Zavoji za obloge za rane.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Egészségügyi fehérneműk; Egészségügyi nedvszívó nadrágok inkontinenciában szenvedőknek; Nadrágpelenkák babáknak; Ruhák inkontinenciában szenvedőknek; Aszeptikus vatta; Inkontinencia pelenkák; Sebtapaszok; Inkontinencia betétek; Antiszeptikus vatta; Menstruációs betétek; Szemtapaszok gyógyászati célokra; Gyógyszerek, orvosságok gyógyászati célokra; Gyógyszertartó dobozok, hordozható, feltöltve; Fertőtlenítő törlőkendők; Tamponok; Pelenkák felnőtteknek; Kötszerek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Mutandine igieniche; Mutande igieniche per persone incontinenti; Pannolini a mutandina per bebè; Indumenti per l'incontinenza; Cotone asettico; Pannolini igienici per persone incontinenti; Cerotti adesivi; Assorbenti per l'incontinenza; Cotone antisettico; Assorbenti igienici; Mascherine oculari ad uso medico; Droghe per uso medico; Borse medicinali da viaggio; Salviette disinfettanti; Tamponi per la mestruazione; Pannolini per adulti; Bendaggi per medicazioni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Higieninės vaikiškos kelnaitės; Nelaikančiųjų sugeriamosios kelnaitės [sauskelnės]; Kūdikių sauskelnės-vystyklai; Drabužiai inkontinencijos reikmėms; Bemikrobė [aseptinė] vata; Nelaikančiųjų sauskelnės; Lipnieji pleistrai; Šlapimo nelaikančiųjų įklotai; Antiseptinė vata; Higieniniai rankšluostukai; Akių raiščiai medicinos reikmėms; Vaistai (medicinos reikmėms); Nešiojamosios medicinos reikmenų dėžutės (pilnos); Dezinfekuojamosios šluostės; Higieniniai tamponai; Suaugusiųjų sauskelnės; Tvarsliava.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apakšbikses higiēniskiem nolūkiem; Absorbējošas biksītes inkontinences gadījumiem; Autiņbiksītes bērniem; Apģērbi lietošanai urīna nesaturēšanas gadījumos; Aseptiskā vate; Pieaugušo autiņi inkontinences gadījumiem; Adhezīvi plāksteri; Paketes urīna un fēču nesaturēšanas gadījumiem; Antiseptiskā vate; Sieviešu higiēniskās paketes; Acu pārsēji medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Zāles (medikamenti); Nokomplektētas pārnēsājamās aptieciņas; Dezinfekcijas drāniņas; Sieviešu higiēniskie tamponi; Pieaugušajiem paredzēti autiņi; Pārsēji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Qliezet ta' taħt sanitarji; Qliezet assorbenti, tal-inkontinenza; Ħrieqi-qliezet ta' taħt tat-trabi; Ħwejjeġ għall-persuni li jbatu bl-inkontinenza; Tajjar mhux settiku; Ħrieqi għall-inkontinenza; Impjastri; Peds għall-inkontinenza; Qoton antisettiku; Faxex tal-mestrwazzjoni; Għata tal-għajnejn għal skopijiet mediċi; Drogi għal skopijiet mediċi; Kaxxetti tal-mediċina, li jinġarru, mimlija; Biċċiet tal-imsiħ għal skop ta' iġjene; Tampuni; Ħrieqi għall-adulti; Faxex għall-infaxxar ta' feriti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Menstruatieslips; Absorberende broekjes voor incontinenten; Luierbroekjes; Incontinentiekleding; Aseptisch katoen; Luiers voor incontinenten; Hechtpleisters; Incontinentieverband; Antiseptisch katoen; Maandverband; Ooglapjes voor medisch gebruik; Verdovende middelen voor medisch gebruik; Reisapotheken [gevuld]; Hygiënische doekjes; Menstruatietampons; Luiers voor volwassenen; Verband.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Majtki higieniczne; Majtki chłonne dla osób cierpiących na inkontynencję; Pieluchomajtki dziecięce; Ubrania dla osób cierpiących na inkontynencję; Wata aseptyczna; Pieluchy dla osób cierpiących na inkontynencję; Plastry; Podpaski dla osób cierpiących na inkontynencję; Wata antyseptyczna; Podpaski higieniczne; Przepaski na oczy do celów medycznych; Narkotyki do celów medycznych; Apteczki przenośne z wyposażeniem; Chusteczki odkażające; Tampony; Pieluchy dla dorosłych; Bandaże opatrunkowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cuecas higiénicas para a menstruação; Cuecas absorventes para incontinência; Fraldas-calça para bebés; Peças de vestuário para a incontinência; Algodão assético; Fraldas higiénicas para incontinência; Esparadrapo; Compressas para incontinência; Algodão antissético; Toalhas higiénicas; Palas oculares [oclusores] para uso médico; Drogas para uso medicinal; Caixas de medicamentos portáteis; Toalhetes higiénicos; Tampões higiénicos para a menstruação; Fraldas para adultos; Ligaduras para pensos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Chiloți igienici; Chiloți absorbanți pentru incontinență; Scutece chiloței pentru bebeluși; Îmbrăcăminte pentru incontinență; Vată sterilă (aseptică); Incontinență (Scutece igienice pentru -); Plasturi; Tampoane pentru persoanele care suferă de incontinență; Tampoane de vată antiseptice; Prosoape sanitare; Bandaje de uz medical pentru ochi; Droguri de uz medical; Truse medicale de voiaj; Șervețele dezinfectante; Tampoane pentru menstruație; Scutece pentru adulți; Bandaje pentru pansat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Hygienické nohavičky; Absorpčné nohavičky pre osoby postihnuté inkontinenciou; Detské plienkové nohavičky; Inkontinenčné odevy; Aseptická vlna; Hygienické vložky pre osoby postihnuté inkontinenciou; Náplasti; Inkontinenčné vložky; Antiseptická vata; Hygienické obrúsky; Pásky na oči na lekárske použitie; Drogy na lekárske použitie; Dávkovače liekov (plné); Dezinfekčné utierky; Hygienické tampóny; Plienky pre dospelých; Ovínadlá.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Sanitarne hlačke; Vpojne hlačke za inkontinenco; Hlačne plenice za dojenčke; Oblačila za inkontinenco; Aseptična vata; Plenice za osebe z inkontinenco; Obliži; Vložki za inkontinenco; Antiseptični bombaž; Menstruacijski vložki; Očesne blazinice za medicinske namene; Droge za medicinske namene; Potovalne torbe z zdravili; Dezinfekcijski robčki; Tamponi; Plenice za odrasle; Povoji za obveze.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Sanitetsbyxor; Byxblöjor för inkontinens; Blöjbyxor för spädbarn; Skyddskläder mot inkontinens; Aseptisk bomull; Blöjor för inkontinens; Plåster; Bindor för inkontinenta; Antiseptisk bomull; Dambindor; Ögonlappar för medicinska ändamål; Droger för medicinska ändamål; Reseapotek, utrustade; Steriliserande torkservetter; Menstruationskompresser; Blöjor för vuxna; Gasbindor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Акушерски матраци; Санитарни маски за медицински цели; Надуваеми матраци за медицински цели; Ръкавици за медицински цели; Надуваеми подложки за медицински цели; Предпазители за пръсти за медицински цели; Ръкавици за медицински цели; Хирургически стерилни покривки за операции; Постелки при инконтиненция; Стерилни чаршафи [хирургия]; Колани за медицински цели; Подложки за медицински цели; Облекло специално за операционни зали; Маски за медицински персонал; Адхезивни чаршафи за употреба в хирургията; Защитно облекло за медицински цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Porodnické matrace; Hygienické masky pro lékařské účely; Nafukovací matrace pro lékařské účely; Návleky na ruce pro lékařské použití; Nafukovací polštáře pro lékařské účely; Chrániče prstů k lékařským účelům; Rukavice pro lékařské účely; Operační roušky; Inkontinenční prostěradla; Chirurgická sterilní prostěradla; Pásy pro lékařské účely; Podušky pro lékařské účely; Oděvy určené pro operační sály; Roušky pro lékařský personál; Lepicí roušky k chirurgickému použití; Ochranné oděvy pro lékařské účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Fødemadrasser; Sanitære masker til medicinske formål; Luftmadrasser til medicinske formål; Undersøgelseshandsker; Luftpuder til medicinsk brug; Fingerskånere til medicinsk brug; Handsker til medicinske formål; Kirurgiske afdækningsstykker; Inkontinenslagner; Sterile lagner, kirurgiske; Bælter til medicinske formål; Puder til medicinske formål; Beklædning specielt til operationsstuer; Masker til brug for medicinsk personel; Selvklæbende afdækningsstykker til kirurgiske formål; Beskyttelsesbeklædning til medicinske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Matratzen für Entbindungen; Mundschutz für medizinische Zwecke; Luftmatratzen für medizinische Zwecke; Handschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Luftgefüllte Kopfkissen für medizinische Zwecke; Fingerlinge für medizinische Zwecke; Handschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Operationstücher; Unterlagen für Inkontinente; Sterile Tücher für Operationen; Gürtel für medizinische Zwecke; Kissen für medizinische Zwecke; OP-Kleidung; Masken für medizinisches Personal; Hafttücher für chirurgische Zwecke; Schutzbekleidung für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Στρώματα τοκετού· Μάσκες υγιεινής για ιατρική χρήση· Στρώματα αέρα για ιατρική χρήση· Μονοκόμματα γάντια ιατρικής χρήσης· Αέρα (Μαξιλάρια -) για ιατρική χρήση· Δακτυλήθρες για ιατρική χρήση· Γάντια ιατρικής χρήσης· Σεντόνια χειρουργικά· Σεντόνια για την ακράτεια· Αποστειρωμένα σεντόνια, χειρουργικά· Ζώνες ιατρικές· Μαξιλάρια για χρήση ιατρική· Ενδύματα (Ειδικά για χειρουργεία -)· Μάσκες για το ιατρικό προσωπικό· Αυτοκόλλητα χειρουργικά πεδία· Προστατευτικά ενδύματα για ιατρική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">childbirth mattresses; sanitary masks for medical purposes; air mattresses, for medical purposes; Mittens for medical use; air pillows for medical purposes; finger guards for medical purposes; gloves for medical purposes; surgical drapes; incontinence sheets; sterile sheets, surgical; belts for medical purposes; cushions for medical purposes; clothing especially for operating rooms; masks for use by medical personnel; Adhesive drapes for surgical use; Protective clothing for medical purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Colchones para el parto; Mascarillas sanitarias para uso médico; Colchones de aire para uso médico; Manoplas para uso médico; Almohadas de aire para uso médico; Dediles para uso médico; Guantes para uso médico; Sábanas quirúrgicas; Sábanas para personas incontinentes [empapadores]; Campos quirúrgicos [sábanas estériles]; Cinturones médicos; Cojines para uso médico; Ropa especial para quirófano; Mascarillas para personal médico; Paños adhesivos para uso quirúrgico; Ropa protectora para fines médicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sünnitusmadratsid; Meditsiinilised hügieenilised maskid; Meditsiinilised õhkmadratsid; Meditsiinilised kindad; Meditsiinilised õhkpadjad; Meditsiinilised sõrmekaitsmed; Meditsiinilised kindad; Kirurgilised steriilsed riided; Kusepidamatushaigete linad; Kirurgias kasutatavad steriilsed linad; Ravivööd, meditsiinilised vööd; Meditsiinilised padjad; Eririietus operatsioonisaalides viibimiseks, operatsiooniriietus; Maskid meditsiinipersonalile; Kirurgias kasutatavad liimlinad; Meditsiinis kasutatavad kaitserõivad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Synnytyspatjat; Saniteettinaamarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Ilmapatjat lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Kintaat lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Ilmatyynyt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Sormustimet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Käsineet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Leikkausliinat; Lakanat pidätyskyvyttömiä varten; Steriloidut lakanat [kirurgiset]; Vyöt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Tyynyt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Vaatteet leikkaussaleja varten, erikoisvalmisteiset; Suojanaamarit lääkintähenkilökuntaa varten; Liimakankaat kirurgiseen käyttöön; Suojavaatteet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Matelas pour l'accouchement; Masques d'hygiène à usage médical; Matelas à air à usage médical; Moufles à usage médical; Oreillers à air à usage médical; Doigtiers à usage médical; Gants à usage médical; Draps chirurgicaux; Draps pour incontinents; Champs opératoires [draps stériles]; Ceintures médicales; Coussins à usage médical; Vêtements spéciaux pour salles d'opération; Masques utilisés par le personnel médical; Draps adhésifs à usage chirurgical; Vêtements de protection à usage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Madraci za porođaje; Sanitarne maske za medicinske svrhe; Zračni madraci za medicinske potrebe; Navlake za ruke bez prstiju za medicinske potrebe; Zračni jastuci za medicinske potrebe; Zaštitne navlake za prste za medicinske svrhe; Rukavice za medicinsku uporabu; Plahte za kirurške potrebe; Plahte kod nezadržavanja mokraće; Sterilne plahte, kirurške; Pojasevi za medicinske svrhe; Jastuci za medicinske potrebe; Specijalna odjeća za operacijske dvorane; Maske za medicinsko osoblje; Ljepljiva platna za kiruršku uporabu; Zaštitna odjeća za medicinske namjene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Matracok, szülészeti; Gyógyászati célú egészségügyi maszkok; Felfújható matracok orvosi célokra; Egyujjas orvosi kesztyűk; Levegővel töltött párnák gyógyászati célokra; Ujjvédők gyógyászati használatra; Kesztyűk gyógyászati használatra; Sebészeti lepedők; Inkontinencia lepedők; Steril sebészeti lepedők; Övek gyógyászati célra; Párnák gyógyászati használatra; Speciális műtőruházat; Maszkok egészségügyi személyzet általi használatra; Öntapadó kendők sebészeti használatra; Védőruházat orvosi célokra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Materassi per il parto; Maschere igieniche per uso medico; Materassi ad aria, per uso medico; Manopole per uso medico; Guanciali ad aria per uso medico; Ditali per uso medico; Guanti per uso medico; Lenzuola chirurgiche; Lenzuola per incontinenti; Lenzuola sterili per uso nel campo operatorio; Cinture per uso medico; Cuscini per uso medico; Vestiti speciali per sale operatorie; Maschere utilizzate dal personale medico; Teli adesivi per uso chirurgico; Abbigliamento protettivo per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Gimdymo čiužiniai; Higieninės kaukės (medicinos reikmėms); Pripučiami čiužiniai (medicinos reikmėms); Medicininės kumštinės pirštinės; Pripučiamos pagalvės (medicinos reikmėms); Apsauginiai antpirščiai (medicinos reikmėms); Pirštinės (medicinos reikmėms); Chirurginiai drabužiai; Nelaikančiųjų paklodės; Steriliosios paklodės [chirurgija]; Diržai (medicinos reikmėms); Medicininės pagalvėlės; Specialieji operaciniai drabužiai; Kaukės medicinos personalui; Chirurginiai lipnieji apklotai; Apsauginiai drabužiai medicininėms reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Dzemdību matrači; Sanitārās maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Piepūšamie matrači medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Medicīnas cimdi; Piepūšamie spilveni medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Gumijas pirkstiņi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Cimdi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Ķirurģiskie pārklāji; Palagi inkontinences gadījumiem; Sterili palagi ķirurģiskiem nolūkiem; Jostas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Medicīniskie spilveni; Speciālie apģērbi operāciju zālēs; Medicīnas personālam paredzētās maskas; Līpoši audumi ķirurģijas nolūkiem; Aizsargtērpi medicīniskām vajadzībām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Saqqijiet tal-ħlas; Maskri sanitarji għal skopijiet mediċi; Saqqijiet tal-arja għal skopijiet mediċi; Ingwanti għal użu mediku; Kuxxini tal-arja għal skopijiet mediċi; Għata tal-plastik għas-swaba' għal skopijiet mediċi; Ingwanti għal skopijiet mediċi; Lożor bħala għata għal waqt operazzjonijiet kirurġiċi; Lożor għall-inkontinenza; Lożor sterilizzati (kirurġiċi); Ċinturini għall-skopijiet mediċi; Kuxxini għal skopijiet mediċi; Ilbies speċjali għas-swali tal-operazzjonijiet; Maskri għal personal mediku; Drapp adeżiv għall-użu kirurġiku; Ħwejjeġ protettivi għall-użu mediku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kraammatrassen; Hygiënische maskers voor medisch gebruik; Luchtmatrassen voor geneeskundig gebruik; Wanten voor medische gebruik; Opblaasbare hoofdkussens voor medisch gebruik; Vingerbeschermers voor medisch gebruik; Handschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Chirurgische lakens; Lakens voor incontinenten; Operatielakens, steriel; Gordels voor medisch gebruik; Kussens voor medisch gebruik; Operatiekleding; Maskers te gebruiken door medisch personeel; Klevende lakens voor chirurgisch gebruik; Beschermende kledingstukken voor medische doeleinden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Materace położnicze; Maski sanitarne do celów medycznych; Materace nadmuchiwane do celów medycznych; Osłony bez palców na ręce do użytku medycznego; Dmuchane poduszki do celów medycznych; Ochraniacze na palce do celów medycznych; Rękawice do celów medycznych; Okrycia chirurgiczne; Prześcieradła dla osób niekontrolujących czynności fizjologicznych; Prześcieradła sterylne chirurgiczne; Pasy do celów medycznych; Poduszki do celów medycznych; Odzież specjalna używana w salach operacyjnych; Maski stosowane przez personel medyczny; Okrycia przylepne do użytku chirurgicznego; Odzież ochronna do celów medycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Colchões para partos; Máscaras higiénicas para uso médico; Colchões de ar para uso médico; Mitenes para uso médico; Travesseiros de ar para uso médico; Dedeiras para uso médico; Luvas para uso médico; Lençóis para cirurgia; Lençóis para incontinentes; Lençóis esterilizados para cirurgia; Cintas medicinais; Almofadas para uso medicinal; Vestuário especial para salas de operação; Máscaras para pessoal médico; Lençóis adesivos para uso cirúrgico; Vestuário de proteção para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Saltele pentru naștere; Măşti sanitare de uz medical; Saltele cu aer de uz medical; Mănuși de uz medical; Perne cu aer pentru uz medical; Apărători de degete pentru uz medical; Mănuși de uz medical; Cearceafuri chirurgicale; Cearceafuri absorbante pentru incontinență; Câmpuri operatorii sterile, chirurgicale; Centuri medicale; Perne de uz medical; Haine speciale pentru săli de operație; Măști utilizate de personalul medical; Câmpuri adezive pentru uz chirurgical; Îmbrăcăminte de protecție de uz medical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Pôrodnícke matrace; Sanitárne masky na lekárske účely; Nafukovacie matrace na lekárske použitie; Návleky na ruky na lekárske použitie; Nafukovacie vankúše na lekárske použitie; Náprstky (chrániče na prsty) na lekárske použitie; Rukavice na lekárske použitie; Chirurgické plachty; Plachty pre osoby postihnuté inkontinenciou; Chirurgické, sterilné plachty; Popruhy na lekárske použitie; Podušky na lekárske použitie; Odevy do operačných sál; Rúška (pre nemocničný personál); Priľnavé rúška na chirurgické použitie; Ochranné odevy na lekárske účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Vzmetnice za porod; Higienske maske za medicinske namene; Zračne vzmetnice medicinske namene; Palčniki [rokavice] za medicinske namene; Zračne blazine za medicinske namene; Ščitniki za prste za medicinske namene; Rokavice za medicinske namene; Kirurške rjuhe; Rjuhe za inkontinentne bolnike; Kirurške sterilizirane rjuhe; Pasovi za medicinske namene; Blazine za medicinske namene; Posebna oblačila za operacijske prostore; Maske za medicinsko osebje; Samolepilna platna za kirurško uporabo; Zaščitna oblačila za medicinske namene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Förlossningsmadrasser; Sanitetsmasker för medicinska ändamål; Luftmadrasser för medicinska ändamål; Tumvantar för medicinskt bruk; Luftkuddar för medicinska ändamål; Fingerskydd för medicinska ändamål; Handskar för medicinska ändamål; Kirurgiska skynken; Inkontinenslakan; Sterila lakan (kirurgiska); Gördlar för medicinska ändamål; Kuddar för medicinska ändamål; Kläder för användning i operationsrum; Munskydd för medicinsk personal; Kirurgtejp; Skyddskläder för medicinska ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/083</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/155</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-17</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1096304</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>38810</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018028848</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Proprietor - Total transfers</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>38810</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-22</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
