<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-12T09:10:22</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228477</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228477</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-22</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-11</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>it</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-22</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-12</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>CACIOBOND   RM caseificio Giuseppe Morese</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162453860</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/228/018228477/000162453860.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>08.03.08</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>24.09.02</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>24.09.11</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>24.09.14</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.13.25</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.01.12</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.13</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.18</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>29</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Млечни произведения и млечни заместители; Сирене, кашкавал; Синьо сирене; Сирене крема; Обработено сирене; Цедено сирене; Бяло сирене; Пушено сирене; Извара; Кашкавалени пръчици; Овче сирене; Заместители на сирене; Сирене от козе мляко; Сирене за намазване; Нискомаслено сирене; Леки закуски на основата на сирене; Твърди сирена; Меко сирене; Топени сирена; Смеси от сирена; Зрели сирена; Прясно неузряло сирене; Продукти с извара; Млечни продукти; Сосове от сирене; Млечни заместители; Смесени сирена.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Mléčné výrobky a jejich náhražky; Sýr; Sýr s modrou plísní; Žervé; Tavený sýr; Hrudkový sýr; Měkký bílý sýr; Uzený sýr; Tvarohový sýr; Sýrové tyčinky; Ovčí sýr; Náhražky sýrů; Kozí sýr; Sýrové pomazánky; Nízkotučný sýr; Chuťovky na bázi sýra; Tvrdý sýr; Měkký sýr; Měkký plísňový sýr; Sýrové směsi; Zrající sýry; Čerstvé nezrající sýry; Tvarohové přípravky; Mléčné výrobky; Sýrové omáčky; Náhražky mléka; Míchaný sýr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Mejeriprodukter og erstatninger for mejeriprodukter; Ost; Blåskimmelost; Flødeoste; Smelteost; Drænet ost; Hvidskimmelost; Røget ost; Kvark; Ostepinde; Fåreost; Osteerstatning; Gedeost; Smøreoste; Ost med lavt fedtindhold; Snackvarer fremstillet på basis af ost; Hård ost; Blød ost; Hvidskimmeloste; Osteblandinger; Modnede oste; Ikke-lagret friskost; Præparater af hytteost; Fødevarerpræparater bestående hovedsageligt af mælk; Ostedip; Mælkeerstatninger; Blandet ost.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Molkereiprodukte und deren Ersatzprodukte; Käse; Blauschimmelkäse; Rahmkäse; Verarbeiteter Käse; Abgetropfter Käse; Leichter Weichkäse; Geräucherter Käse; Quarkkäse; Käsesticks; Schafskäse; Käseersatz; Ziegenmilchkäse; Streichkäse; Magerkäse; Snacks auf Basis von Käse; Hartkäse; Weichkäse; Weichkäse; Käsemischungen; Gereifter Käse; Nicht gereifter frischer Käse; Zubereitungen aus körnigem Frischkäse; Milchprodukte; Käsedips; Milchersatz; Käsemischungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Γαλακτοκομικά προϊόντα και υποκατάστατα γαλακτοκομικών προϊόντων· Τυροκομικά προϊόντα· Τυρί τύπου ροκφόρ· Κρέμα τυριού· Επεξεργασμένο τυρί· Στραγγιστό τυρί· Λευκά τυριά· Καπνιστό τυρί· Νωπό τυρί (τυρόπηγμα)· Μπαστουνάκια τυριού· Πρόβειο τυρί· Υποκατάστατα τυριού· Τυρί από κατσικίσιο γάλα· Παρασκευάσματα τυριού σε μορφή κρέμας· Τυρί με χαμηλά λιπαρά· Μικρογεύματα με βάση το τυρί· Σκληρό τυρί· Μαλακό τυρί· Μαλακά ωριμασμένα τυριά· Μείγματα τυριών· Ώριμα τυριά· Νωπό μη ωριμασμένο τυρί· Παρασκευάσματα από τυρί κότατζ· Γαλακτοκομικά (- προϊόντα)· Σάλτσες (ντιπ) τυριού· Υποκατάστατα γάλακτος· Ανάμεικτο τυρί.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Dairy products and dairy substitutes; Cheese; Blue cheese; Cream cheese; Processed cheese; Strained cheese; Soft white cheese; Smoked cheese; Curd cheese; Cheese sticks; Sheep cheese; Cheese substitutes; Goat cheese; Cheese spreads; Low fat cheese; Cheese-based snack foods; Hard cheese; Soft cheese; Soft-ripened cheeses; Cheese mixtures; Ripened cheeses; Fresh unripened cheeses; Cottage cheese preparations; Milk products; Cheese dips; Milk substitutes; Blended cheese.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Productos lácteos y sustitutivos de la leche; Quesos; Queso azul; Queso crema; Queso procesado; Queso colado; Queso blanco suave; Queso ahumado; Queso tipo requesón; Palitos de queso; Queso de oveja; Sucedáneos del queso; Queso de leche de cabra; Cremas de queso para untar; Queso bajo en grasas; Aperitivos a base de queso; Queso de pasta dura; Quesos de pasta blanda; Quesos de corteza enmohecida; Mezclas de queso; Quesos madurados; Quesos frescos sin madurar; Preparaciones de requesón; Productos lácteos; Queso en forma de salsas para mojar; Sucedáneos de la leche; Mezclas de quesos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Piimatooted ja piima aseained; Juust; Sinihallitusjuust; Toorjuustud; Töödeldud juust; Nõrutatud juust; Valge juust; Suitsujuust; Kohupiim; Juustupulgad; Lambajuust; Juustuasendajad; Kitsepiimajuust; Määrdejuustud; Väherasvane juust; Juustupõhised suupisted; Kõvad juustud; Pehmed juustud; Pehme laagerdunud juust; Juustusegud; Laagerdunud juustud; Värsked valmimata juustud, toorjuustud; Kodujuustutooted; Piimatooted; Juustudipid; Piimaasendajad; Segujuust.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Maitotuotteet ja maitotuotteiden korvikkeet; Juustot; Sinihomejuusto; Tuorejuusto; Käsitelty juusto; Valutettu juusto; Pehmeä valkoinen juusto; Savujuusto; Rahkajuusto; Juustotikut; Lampaanjuusto; Juuston korvikkeet; Vuohenmaitojuusto; Levitejuustot; Vähärasvainen juusto; Juustopohjaiset välipalat; Kovat juustot; Pehmeät juustot; Kypsytetyt juustot; Juustosekoitukset; Kypsytetyt juustot; Kypsyttämättömät tuoreet juustot; Raejuustovalmisteet; Maitotuotteet; Juustodippikastikkeet; Maidon korvikkeet; Juustosekoitukset.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits laitiers et substituts; Fromages; Fromage à pâte bleue; Fromage à tartiner; Fromage à pâte fondue; Fromage filtré; Fromage à pâte fraîche; Fromage fumé; Fromage caillé; Bâtonnets de fromage; Fromage de brebis; Succédanés du fromage; Fromage de chèvre; Fromages à tartiner; Fromage allégé; En-cas à base de fromage; Fromage à pâte dure; Fromage à pâte molle; Fromage à pâte molle à croûte fleurie; Mélanges de fromages; Fromages affinés; Fromages frais non affinés; Préparations à base de fromage frais de type cottage; Produits laitiers; Trempettes [dips] au fromage; Succédanés de lait; Mélange de fromage.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Mliječni proizvodi i njihovi nadomjesci; Proizvodi od sira; Plavi sir; Kremasti sir; Obrađeni sir; Ocijeđeni sir; Mekani bijeli sir; Dimljeni sir; Sir od skute; Štapići od sira; Ovčji sir; Nadomjesci za sir; Sir od kozjeg mlijeka; Sirni namazi; Niskomasni sir; Grickalice na bazi sira; Tvrdi sir; Mekani sir; Mekani zreli sirevi; Mješavine sira; Zreli sirevi; Nezreli svježi sirevi; Pripravci od svježeg sira; Mliječni proizvodi; Umaci od sira; Zamjene za mlijeko; Miješani sir.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tejtermékek és tejtermék-helyettesítők; Sajtok; Kéksajt; Krémsajtok; Feldolgozott sajtok; Friss sajt; Fehér lágy sajtok; Füstölt sajt; Túró; Sajtos pálcikák; Juhsajt; Sajtpótlók; Kecsketejből készült sajt; Kenhető sajtok; Alacsony zsírtartalmú sajtok; Sajtalapú rágcsálnivalók; Kemény sajt; Lágy sajtok; Puhára érlelt sajt; Sajtkeverékek; Érlelt sajtfélék; Friss, nem érlelt sajtok; Túrókészítmények; Tejtermékek; Sajtmártások; Tejhelyettesítők; Sajtkeverék.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Prodotti caseari e loro succedanei; Formaggio; Formaggio erborinato; Formaggio fresco; Formaggio lavorato; Formaggio colato; Formaggio bianco; Formaggio affumicato; Formaggio tipo ricotta; Bastoncini di formaggio; Formaggio di pecora; Succedanei del formaggio; Formaggio di capra; Creme da spalmare a base di formaggio; Formaggio a basso contenuto di grassi; Spuntini a base di formaggio; Formaggio a pasta dura; Formaggio a pasta molle; Formaggi a pasta molle stagionati; Formaggi misti; Formaggi stagionati; Formaggi cremosi; Formaggi freschi non stagionati; Prodotti contenenti formaggi cremosi; Prodotti lattieri; Salse al formaggio; Succedanei del latte; Formaggi; Miscele di formaggi; Formaggi cremosi bianchi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Pieno produktai ir pieno pakaitalai; Sūris; Mėlynasis pelėsinis sūris; Tepamas sūris; Lydyti sūriai; Nukoštas sūris; Minkštas baltas sūris; Rūkytas sūris; Varškės sūris; Sūrio lazdelės; Avių pieno sūris; Sūrio pakaitalai; Ožkų pieno sūris; Tepamieji sūriai; Liesas sūris; Sūrio užkandžiai; Kietas sūris; Minkštas sūris; Minkšti nokinti sūriai; Sūrio mišiniai; Brandinti sūriai; Nebrandintas šviežias sūris; Varškės produktai; Pieno produktai; Sūrio dažiniai; Pieno pakaitalai; Maišyti sūriai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Piena produkti un piena aizstājēji; Siers; Zilais siers; Krējuma siers; Apstrādāts siers; Kāstais siers; Mīkstais baltais siers; Kūpināts siers; Mājas siers; Siera nūjiņas; Aitas siers; Siera aizstājēji; Kazas piena siers; Krēmveida sieri; Siers ar zemu tauku saturu; Uzkodas uz siera bāzes; Cietie sieri; Mīkstais siers; Mīksti gatavināts siers; Siera maisījumi; Nogatavināti sieri; Svaigi nenogatavināti sieri; Biezpiena izstrādājumi; Piena produkti; Siera mērces uzkodu iemērcēšanai; Piena aizstājēji; Siera maisījums.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Prodotti tal-ħalib jew sostituti tal-ħalib; Prodotti mill-ġobon; Ġobon tat-tursina; Ġobon artab frisk; Ġobon ipproċessat; Ġobon imsaffi; Ġobon abjad artab; Ġobon affumikat; Ġobon moxx; Stikek tal-ġobon; Ġobon tan-nagħaġ; Sostituti tal-ġobon; Ġobon mill-ħalib tal-mogħża; Dlik tal-ġobon; Ġobon b'kontenut baxx ta' xaħam; Snekks ibbażati fuq il-ġobon; Ġobon mill-iebes; Ġobon artab; Ġobon artab; Taħlitiet ta' ġobon; Ġobnijiet maturi; Ġobon frisk mhux misjur; Preparazzjonijiet ta' ġobon moxx magħmul minn ħalib xkumat; Prodotti tal-ħalib; Dips tal-ġobon; Sostituti tal-ħalib; Ġobon imħallat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Zuivelproducten en vervangingsmiddelen voor zuivel; Kaas; Blauwe aderkaas; Roomkaas; Kaas (Bewerkte -); Gezeefde verse kaas; Witte kaas; Gerookte kaas; Ongerijpte kaas; Kaassticks; Schapenkaas; Kaasvervangers; Kaas van geitenmelk; Kaassmeersels; Kaas (Magere -); Snacks op basis van kaas; Harde kazen; Zachte kaas; Zachte gerijpte kaas; Kaasmengsels; Gerijpte kazen; Verse niet-gerijpte kazen; Hüttenkäseproducten; Melkproducten; Dipsausen met kaas; Melkvervangers; Gemengde kazen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Nabiał i substytuty nabiału; Produkty serowarskie; Ser pleśniowy; Ser śmietankowy; Przetworzony ser; Ser typu twarogowego; Biały ser; Ser wędzony; Twaróg; Paluszki serowe; Ser owczy; Substytuty serów; Ser z mleka koziego; Sery topione; Ser o niskiej zawartości tłuszczu; Przekąski na bazie sera; Ser twardy; Ser miękki; Miękkie dojrzałe sery; Mieszanki serowe; Sery dojrzewające; Sery świeże niedojrzewające; Przetwory twarożkowe; Mleczne produkty; Dipy serowe; Substytuty mleka; Ser mieszany.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Produtos lácteos e substitutos lácteos; Queijo; Queijo de pasta azul; Queijo para barrar; Queijos processados; Queijo coado; Queijo branco de pasta mole; Queijo fumado; Requeijão; Palitos de queijo; Queijo de ovelha; Sucedâneos de queijo; Queijo de leite de cabra; Pastas de queijo para barrar; Queijo com baixo teor de gordura; Aperitivos à base de queijo; Queijo duro; Queijo de pasta mole; Queijos curados macios; Misturas de queijos; Queijos curados; Queijos frescos não maduros; Preparações com queijo cottage; Produtos lácteos; Molhos espessos de queijo; Substitutos do leite; Queijo de mistura.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Produse lactate și înlocuitori; Brânzeturi; Brânză cu mucegai; Creme de brânză; Brânză prelucrată; Brânză scursă; Brânză albă moale; Cașcaval afumat; Caș; Batoane de brânză; Brânză de oaie; Înlocuitori de brânză; Brânză din lapte de capră; Brânză tartinabilă; Brânză cu conținut scăzut de grăsimi; Gustări pe bază de brânză; Cașcaval; Brânză cu pastă moale; Brânzeturi maturate moi; Amestecuri de brânză; Brânzeturi maturate; Brânzeturi proaspete nematurate; Preparate cu brânză de țară; Lactate (Produse -); Sosuri de brânză; Înlocuitori de lapte; Mix de brânzeturi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Mliečne výrobky a ich náhradky; Syr; Syr s modrou plesňou; Smotanový syr; Spracovaný syr; Hrudkový syr; Mäkký biely syr; Údený syr; Mäkký tvaroh; Syrové tyčinky; Ovčí syr; Náhradky syra; Syr z kozieho mlieka; Syrové nátierky; Nízkotučný syr; Syrové chuťovky; Tvrdý syr; Mäkký syr; Mäkký zrejúci syr s plesňou; Zmesi syra; Zrejúce syry; Nevyzreté čerstvé syry; Prípravky zo syra cottage cheese; Mliečne výrobky; Syrové dipy; Náhradky mlieka; Zmes syrov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Mlečni proizvodi in njihovi nadomestki; Izdelki iz sira; Sir z žlahtno plesnijo; Kremni sir; Predelan sir; Odcejeni sir; Beli mehki sir; Prekajen sir; Sir iz skute; Sirove palčke; Ovčji sir; Nadomestki sira; Kozji sir; Sirni namazi; Manj masten sir; Prigrizki na osnovi sira; Trdi sir; Mehki sir; Mehki zorjeni siri; Mešanice sirov; Zorjeni siri; Sveži nezreli siri; Izdelki iz skute; Mlečni proizvodi; Omake za sir; Nadomestki za mleko; Mešani sir.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Mejeriprodukter och mejeriersättningar; Ost; Ädelost; Mjuk gräddost (cream cheese); Bearbetad ost; Pressad ost; Mjuk vit ost; Rökt ost; Kvark; Ostpinnar; Fårost; Ostersättningar; Getost; Bredbar ost; Ost med låg fetthalt; Ostbaserad snackmat; Hårdost; Mjukost; Mjuka lagrade ostar; Ostblandningar; Lagrade ostar; Färska olagrade ostar; Produkter av kornig färskostmassa; Mjölkprodukter; Ostdipsåser; Mjölkersättningar; Blandade ostar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за търговия на едро във връзка с млечни продукти; Услуги за търговия на дребно във връзка с млечни продукти; Търговия на храни на дребно; Услуги за каталожна търговия на дребно във връзка с храни; Услуги за търговия на дребно чрез поръчки по пощата във връзка с хранителни продукти; Услуги за търговия на дребно чрез глобални компютърни мрежи във връзка с хранителни продукти; Предоставяне на консултации за потребителски стоки във връзка с храни и напитки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Velkoobchodní prodej mléčných výrobků; Maloobchodní prodej mléčných výrobků; Maloobchodní služby vztahující se k potravinám; Maloobchodní služby týkající se potravin poskytované prostřednictvím katalogů; Maloobchodní zásilkové služby týkající se potravin; Maloobchodní služby týkající se potravin poskytované prostřednictvím celosvětových počítačových sítí; Poskytování informací spotřebitelům v souvislosti s potravinami a nápoji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Engroshandel med mejeriprodukter; Detailhandel med mejeriprodukter; Detailhandel i forbindelse med fødevarer; Detailhandel via kataloger med fødevarer; Detailhandel via postordre med fødevarer; Detailhandel via globale computernetværk med fødevarer; Tilrådighedsstillelse af produktinformation til forbrugere relateret til føde- eller drikkevarer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Großhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Milchprodukte; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Milchprodukte; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Lebensmittel; Katalogversandhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Lebensmittel; Versandhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Lebensmittel; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen über weltweite Computernetze in Bezug auf Lebensmittel; Erteilung von Konsumgüterauskünften in Bezug auf Lebensmittel und Getränke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες χονδρικής πώλησης σε σχέση με γαλακτοκομικά προϊόντα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με γαλακτοκομικά προϊόντα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με τρόφιμα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης μέσω καταλόγων σε σχέση με τρόφιμα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης μέσω ταχυδρομικών παραγγελιών σε σχέση με τρόφιμα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης μέσω παγκόσμιων ηλεκτρονικών δικτύων σε σχέση με τρόφιμα· Παροχή πληροφοριών για καταναλωτικά είδη σε σχέση με προϊόντα τροφίμων και ποτών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Wholesale services in relation to dairy products; Retail services in relation to dairy products; Retail services relating to food; Retail services via catalogues related to foodstuffs; Mail order retail services related to foodstuffs; Retail services via global computer networks related to foodstuffs; Providing consumer product information relating to food or drink products.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de venta al por mayor de productos lácteos; Servicios de venta al por menor de productos lácteos; Servicios de ventas al por menor relacionados con alimentos; Servicios de venta minorista mediante catálogos relacionados con productos alimentarios; Servicios de venta minorista mediante pedidos por correo relacionados con productos alimentarios; Servicios de venta minorista mediante redes informáticas mundiales relacionadas con productos alimentarios; Suministro de información sobre productos de consumo en relación con alimentos o bebidas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Piimatoodete hulgimüügiteenused; Piimatoodete jaemüügiteenused; Toiduainete jaemüügiteenused; Jaemüügiteenused toiduainekataloogide vahendusel; Toiduainete postimüügiteenused; Toiduainete jaemüügiteenused ülemaailmse arvutivõrgu kaudu; Tarbekaubateabe pakkumine seoses toidu- ja joogikaupadega.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Maitotuotteisiin liittyvät tukkumyyntipalvelut; Maitotuotteisiin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut; Elintarvikkeiden vähittäismyyntipalvelut; Elintarvikkeiden vähittäismyyntipalvelut luetteloiden avulla; Elintarvikkeisiin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut postimyynnin välityksellä; Elintarvikkeisiin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut maailmanlaajuisen tietokoneverkon välityksellä; Tuotetiedottaminen kuluttajille elintarvikkeista ja juomista.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de vente en gros concernant les produits laitiers; Services de vente au détail concernant les produits laitiers; Services de vente au détail d'aliments; Services de vente au détail par le biais de catalogues liés aux produits alimentaires; Services de commande au détail par correspondance concernant des produits alimenaires; Services de vente au détail à travers des réseaux informatiques mondiaux concernant des produits alimentaires; Fourniture d'informations concernant des produits de consommation tels que des aliments ou des boissons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Veleprodajne usluge u vezi s mliječnim proizvodima; Maloprodajne usluge u vezi s mliječnim proizvodima; Maloprodajne usluge u svezi hrane; Maloprodajne usluge putem kataloga u vezi s prehrambenim proizvodima; Maloprodajne usluge putem naručivanja poštom u vezi s prehrambenim proizvodima; Maloprodajne usluge putem globalne računalne mreže u vezi s prehrambenim proizvodima; Pružanje informacija o potrošačkim proizvodima u vezi s hranom ili pićem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tejtermékekkel kapcsolatos nagykereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Tejtermékekkel kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Élelmiszerekkel kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Katalógusokon keresztül nyújtott, élelmiszerekkel kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Élelmiszerek postai rendelésével kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Globális számítógépes hálózatokon keresztül nyújtott, élelmiszerekkel kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Fogyasztói termékinformációk biztosítása étel vagy italtermékekhez kapcsolódóan.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi all'ingrosso in relazione a prodotti lattiero-caseari; Servizi al dettaglio in relazione a prodotti lattiero-caseari; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio di prodotti alimentari; Vendita al dettaglio tramite catalogo di prodotti alimentari; Vendita al dettaglio per corrispondenza di prodotti alimentari; Vendita al dettaglio tramite reti informatiche mondiali di prodotti alimentari; Fornitura di informazioni su prodotti di consumo relativi a alimenti o bevande.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Didmeninė prekyba pieno produktais; Mažmeninė prekyba pieno produktais; Mažmeninė prekyba maisto prekėmis; Mažmeninė prekyba maisto produktais per katalogus; Mažmeninė prekyba maisto produktais, užsakant paštu; Mažmeninė prekyba maisto produktais per visuotinį kompiuterių tinklą; Informacija vartotojams apie maisto produktus ar gėrimus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vairumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar piena produktiem; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar piena produktiem; Pārtikas mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, izmantojot katalogu, saistībā ar pārtikas produktiem; Mazumtirdzniecības paklapojumi, izmantojot pasta sūtījumus, saistībā ar pārtikas produktiem; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, izmantojot globālos datoru tīklus, saistībā ar pārtikas produktiem; Patēriņa preču informācijas nodrošināšana saistībā ar pārtiku un dzērieniem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-ingrossa fir-rigward tal-prodotti magħmula mill-ħalib; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut fir-rigward tal-prodotti magħmula mill-ħalib; Servizzi ta' bejgħ relatat mal-ikel; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut permezz ta' katalgi relatati ma' prodotti tal-ikel; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut ta' ordnijiet bil-posta relatati ma' oġġetti tal-ikel; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut permezz ta' netwerks tal-kompjuter globali relatati mal-oġġetti tal-ikel; Provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar prodotti tal-konsumatur relatati ma' prodotti tal-ikel jew ix-xorb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Groothandelsdiensten op het gebied van zuivelproducten; Detailhandelsdiensten op het gebied van zuivelproducten; Detailhandel op het gebied van voedingsmiddelen; Detailhandelsdiensten met behulp van catalogi op het gebied van voedingsmiddelen; Detailhandel met behulp van postorderdiensten op het gebied van voedingsmiddelen; Detailhandel met behulp van wereldwijde computernetwerken op het gebied van voedingsmiddelen; Het verstrekken van advies over consumentenproducten met betrekking tot voedsel en dranken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi sprzedaży hurtowej w związku z produktami mlecznymi; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej w związku z produktami mlecznymi; Usługi handlu detalicznego w zakresie żywności; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej za pomocą katalogów w związku z artykułami spożywczymi; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej za zamówieniem pocztowym związane z artykułami spożywczymi; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej za pomocą globalnych sieci komputerowych związane z artykułami spożywczymi; Udostępnianie informacji o produktach konsumenckich dotyczących żywności lub napojów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços grossistas relacionados com produtos lácteos; Serviços retalhistas relacionados com produtos lácteos; Serviços de venda a retalho relacionados com alimentos; Serviços de venda retalhista por catálogo relacionados com produtos alimentares; Serviços de venda retalhista através de encomenda por correspondência relacionados com produtos alimentares; Serviços de venda retalhista através de redes informáticas mundiais relacionados com produtos alimentares; Fornecimento de informações relativas a produtos de consumo no âmbito de produtos alimentares e bebidas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata în legătură cu produse lactate; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul în legătură cu produse lactate; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul în domeniul alimentației; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul prin catalog în legătură cu produse alimentare; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul prin corespondență în legătură cu produse alimentare; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul prin rețele informatice mondiale în legătură cu produse alimentare; Informare cu privire la produse de consum în legătură cu alimente sau băuturi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Veľkoobchodné služby s mliečnymi výrobkami; Maloobchodné služby s mliečnymi výrobkami; Maloobchodné služby spojené s predajom potravín; Služby maloobchodného predaja potravín prostredníctvom katalógov; Maloobchodné zásielkové služby týkajúce sa potravín; Maloobchodné služby s potravinami prostredníctvom svetovej počítačovej siete; Poskytovanie spotrebiteľských informácií v oblasti potravinárskych výrobkov a nápojov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve prodaje na debelo v zvezi z mlečnimi izdelki; Storitve prodaje na drobno v zvezi z mlečnimi izdelki; Maloprodajne storitve v zvezi s hrano; Maloprodajne storitve prek katalogov v zvezi s prehrambenimi proizvodi; Maloprodajne storitve z naročilom po pošti, povezane s prehrambenimi izdelki; Storitve maloprodaje prek svetovnih računalniških omrežij, povezane s prehrambenimi izdelki; Nudenje informacij o potrošniških izdelkih s področja živil in pijač.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Grosshandel avseende mejeriprodukter; Återförsäljning avseende mejeriprodukter; Återförsäljning avseende mat; Detaljhandel via kataloger avseende livsmedel; Återförsäljning via postorder avseende livsmedel; Återförsäljning via globala datornät avseende livsmedel; Tillhandahållande av produktinformation till kunder avseende livsmedels- och dryckesprodukter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>43</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Приготвяне и предоставяне на храни и напитки за незабавна консумация; Услуги, свързани с взимане на храна и напитки за вкъщи; Услуги за предоставяне на храна; Осигуряване на храни и напитки; Деликатесни ресторанти; Сервиране на храна и напитки; Услуги на ресторант за готова храна за вкъщи; Предоставяне на храна и напитки чрез подвижен щанд (камион); Предоставяне на информация, свързана с приготвянето на храна и напитки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Příprava a poskytování stravování a nápojů pro okamžitou spotřebu; Služby týkající se odnosu jídla s sebou; Služby zajišťující stravování; Poskytování jídla a nápojů; Delikatesy (restaurace); Podávání jídel a nápojů; Služby týkající se restaurací s prodejem jídel s sebou; Poskytování jídla a nápojů prostřednictvím mobilního nákladního auta; Poskytování informací vztahujících se k přípravě jídel a nápojů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tilberedning og levering af mad og drikke til øjeblikkelig indtagelse; Takeawaytjenesteydelser; Tjenester til forplejning af gæster med mad; Tilvejebringelse af mad og drikke; Delikatesserestauranter; Servering af mad og drikke; Restauranter med mad til afhentning [take-out]; Tilvejebringelse af mad og drikke via en mobil lastvogn; Information vedrørende tilberedning af mad og drikke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Zubereitung und Zurverfügungstellen von Speisen und Getränken für den unmittelbaren Verzehr; Verpflegung von Gästen mit Speisen und Getränken zum Mitnehmen; Dienstleistungen zur Verpflegung von Gästen mit Speisen; Verpflegung von Gästen; Verpflegung von Gästen in Feinkostrestaurants; Verpflegung von Gästen mit Speisen und Getränken; Verpflegung von Gästen in Restaurants mit Außer-Haus-Verkauf; Verpflegung von Gästen durch einen mobilen LKW; Beratung in Bezug auf die Zubereitung von Speisen und Getränken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παρασκευή και παροχή τροφίμων και ποτών για άμεση κατανάλωση· Υπηρεσίες φαγητού σε πακέτο· Υπηρεσίες παροχής διατροφής· Παροχή φαγητού και ποτού· Καταστήματα εκλεκτών τροφίμων (ντελικατέσεν) [εστιατόρια]· Σερβίρισμα φαγητού και ποτών· Εστιατόρια παροχής φαγητού σε πακέτο· Παροχή φαγητού και ποτού μέσω κινητού φορτηγού· Παροχή πληροφοριών σχετικά με την προετοιμασία τροφίμων και ποτών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Preparation and provision of food and drink for immediate consumption; Takeaway services; Services for providing food; Services for providing food and drink; Delicatessens [restaurants]; Serving food and drinks; Take-out restaurant services; Providing of food and drink via a mobile truck; Provision of information relating to the preparation of food and drink.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Preparación y suministro de comidas y bebidas de consumo inmediato; Servicios de comidas para llevar; Servicios de suministro de comida; Servicios de restauración [alimentación]; Delicatesen [restaurantes]; Servicios de restauración [alimentos y bebidas]; Restaurantes de comida para llevar; Provisión de comida y bebida mediante vehículo; Facilitación de información relativa a la preparación de alimentos y bebidas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Toidu ja jookide valmistamine ning pakkumine koheseks tarbimiseks; Valmistoidu kaasamüügiteenused; Toitlustusteenused; Toitlustamine; Delikatessirestoranid; Toitude ja jookide serveerimine; Toitu kaasa müüvad restoranid; Toidu ja joogi pakkumine toitlustusautodest (veokitest); Toidu- ja joogivalmistusalane info.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ruokien ja juomien valmistaminen ja tarjoaminen välittömästi nautittavaksi; Noutoateriapalvelut; Ravitsemispalvelut; Ravitseminen ja juomien anniskelu; Katukeittiöt (ravintolat); Ruokien ja juomien tarjoilu; Noutoravintolapalvelut; Ruoan ja juoman tarjoaminen ajoneuvoista; Ruokien ja juomien valmistamiseen liittyvän tiedon tarjoaminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Préparation et mise à disposition d'aliments et de boissons pour la consommation immédiate; Services de plats à emporter [préparation de repas]; Services d’approvisionnement en nourriture; Services de restauration [alimentation]; Épiceries fines [restaurants]; Services de restauration; Services de restaurants vendant des repas à emporter; Fourniture d'aliments et de boissons par le biais d'une camionnette mobile [service de restauration]; Services d'informations concernant la préparation d'aliments et de boissons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Priprema i opskrba hrane i pića za neposrednu konzumaciju; Usluge iznošenja hrane; Usluge pripremanja hrane; Pružanje hrane i pića; Delikatese [restorani]; Serviranje hrane i pića; Restorani koji nude hranu za van; Usluge opskrbe hranom i pićem u mobilnom restoranu-kamionu; Pružanje informacija u svezi s pripremanjem hrane i pića.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ételek és italok készítése és biztosítása azonnali fogyasztásra; Elvihető ételekkel kapcsolatos szolgáltatások; Szolgáltatások ételek biztosításához; Étel- és italellátás; Delikát éttermek, csemegeáruk [éttermek]; Ételek és italok felszolgálása; Elvitelre árusító éttermek; Étel- és italszolgáltatás mobil teherautóból; Étel- és italkészítéssel kapcsolatos információnyújtás.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Preparazione e fornitura di cibi e bevande per consumo immediato; Servizi da asporto; Servizi per la fornitura di alimenti; Fornitura di alimenti e bevande; Gastronomie [ristoranti]; Servizi di ristorazione; Servizi di ristorazione da asporto; Fornitura di alimenti e bevande attraverso un furgone; Servizio fornitura informazioni in materia di preparazione di alimenti e bevande.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Maisto ir gėrimų ruošimas ir patiekimas vartoti nedelsiant; Maisto išsineštinai paslaugos; Maisto parūpinimo paslaugos; Maisto ir gėrimų parūpinimas; Delikatesų restoranai; Maisto ir gėrimų patiekimas; Išsineštinio maisto restoranai; Maisto ir gėrimų parūpinimas iš mobiliųjų prekybinių vagonėlių; Informacijos, susijusios su maisto ir gėrimų ruošimu, teikimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tūlītējam patēriņam paredzēto ēdienu un dzērienu sagatavošana un nodrošināšana; Ēdienu un dzērienu sagatavošana līdzņemšanai; Pārtikas nodrošināšanas pakalpojumi; Apgādes pakalpojumi ar uzturu un dzērieniem; Delikatešu restorānu pakalpojumi; Ēdienu un dzērienu pasniegšana; Līdzņemamo ēdienu restorānu pakalpojumi; Ēdienu un dzērienu nodrošināšana ar mobilo furgonu starpniecību; Informācijas sniegšana par ēdienu un dzērienu sagatavošanu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Preparazzjoni u provvista ta' ikel u xorb għall-konsum immedjat; Servizzi ta' provvista ta' ikel u xorb li jista' jittieħed post ieħor [takeaway]; Servizzi għall-provvista tal-ikel; Il-provvista ta' ikel u xorb; Delicatessens [restoranti]; Tqassim tal-ikel u x-xorb; Servizzi ta' ristoranti fejn il-klijent jista' jieħu l-ikel f'post ieħor [take-out]; Il-provvista ta' ikel u xorb permezz ta' vannijiet mobbli; Provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar it-tħejjija ta' ikel u xorb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Bereiden en verstrekken van voedsel en dranken voor onmiddellijke consumptie; Diensten van afhaalrestaurants; Het verstrekken van voedsel; Het verstrekken van voedsel en drank; Delicatessenzaken [restaurants]; Serveren van voedsel en dranken; Afhaalrestaurants; Verstrekking van voedsel en dranken via mobiele bestelwagens; Bereiden van voedsel en dranken (Informatie inzake -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przygotowywanie i zaopatrywanie w żywność i napoje do bezpośredniego spożycia; Usługi w zakresie jedzenia na wynos; Usługi zaopatrzenia w żywność; Usługi zaopatrzenia w żywność i napoje; Restauracje serwujące wykwintne artykuły spożywcze; Serwowanie jedzenia i napojów; Usługi restauracji sprzedających posiłki na wynos; Dostarczanie żywności i napojów za pośrednictwem furgonetek; Udzielanie informacji związanych z przygotowywaniem żywności i napojów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Preparação e fornecimento de alimentos e bebidas para consumo imediato; Serviços de fornecimento de comida para fora (takeaway); Serviços para fornecimento de alimentos; Serviços de fornecimento de alimentos e bebidas; Restaurantes de iguarias refinadas; Serviços de restauração [alimentação e bebidas]; Serviços de restaurantes que fornecem comida para fora; Fornecimento de alimentos e bebidas em carrinhas; Fornecimento de informações relacionadas com a preparação de alimentos e bebidas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Pregătirea și furnizare de alimente și băuturi destinate consumului imediat; Servicii de mâncare la pachet; Servicii pentru furnizarea de alimente; Asigurarea de hrană și băuturi; Restaurante de delicatese; Servire de alimente și băuturi; Servicii de restaurant cu servire la pachet; Furnizare de alimente și băuturi dintr-o rulotă mobilă; Furnizare de informații cu privire la prepararea alimentelor și băuturilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Príprava a poskytovanie jedál a nápojov na okamžitú konzumáciu; Služby možnosti odnesenia si jedla so sebou; Služby v oblasti poskytovania jedla; Stravovacie služby; Lahôdkárstva (reštaurácie); Podávanie jedál a nápojov; Služby reštaurácií s možnosťou odnesenia si jedla; Poskytovanie potravín a nápojov prostredníctvom pojazdných výdajní; Poskytovanie informácií týkajúcich sa prípravy jedál a nápojov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Priprava in nudenje hrane in pijače za takojšnje zaužitje; Storitve dostave hrane; Storitve nudenja hrane; Nudenje hrane in pijače; Delikatese [restavracije]; Strežba hrane in pijače; Storitve restavracij, kjer lahko hrano odnesemo s seboj; Storitve nudenja hrane in pijače iz mobilnih kombijev; Nudenje informacij v zvezi s pripravo hrane in pijače.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tillagning och tillhandahållande av mat och dryck för omedelbar förtäring; Hämtmatstjänster; Tjänster avseende utskänkning av mat; Tjänster för utskänkning av mat och dryck; Delikatessrestauranger; Servering av mat och dryck; Restaurangtjänster avseende mat för avhämtning; Utskänkning av mat och dryck från mobilt fordon; Upplåtande av information avseende tillagning av mat och dryck.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/082</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/152</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-12</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>676565</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>69271</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
