<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-30T17:28:27</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228496</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228496</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>da</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-20</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>AllMatters</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Немедицинска козметика и козметични тоалетни принадлежности; Етерични масла; Препарати за почистване на тялото и за грижа за красотата; Препарати за грижа за кожата, очите и ноктите; Препарати за коса и за третиране на окосмяването; Хигиенни почистващи кърпички, А именно, Дамски хигиенни почистващи кърпички; Ароматизирани кърпички; Кърпи, импрегнирани с почистващи препарати; Влажни кърпички за козметични цели; Импрегнирани с почистващ препарат кърпички за почистване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Neléčivé kosmetické a toaletní přípravky; Éterické oleje; Přípravky pro osobní hygienu a kosmetické přípravky; Přípravky pro péči o pleť, oči a nehty; Přípravky pro péči o vlasy a přípravky na holení; Hygienické čisticí utěrky, Jmenovitě, Čisticí ubrousky pro dámskou intimní hygienu; Parfémované ubrousky; Ubrousky obsahující čisticí prostředky; Navlhčené ubrousky pro kosmetické účely; Utěrky napuštěné čisticím prostředkem pro čištění.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Ikke-medicinsk kosmetik og toiletartikler; æteriske olier; Præparater til rengøring af kroppen og skønhedspleje; Præparater til hud-, øjen- og neglepleje; Præparater til hår og behandling af hår; Renseservietter til hygiejneformål, navnlig renseservietter til hygiejneformål til kvinder; parfumerede servietter; servietter med rensepræparater; imprægnerede servietter (til kosmetisk brug); servietter imprægneret med midler til rengøring.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Nicht medizinische Kosmetika und Mittel für Körper- und Schönheitspflege; Ätherische Öle; Körperreinigungs- und Körperpflegepräparate; Haut-, Augen- und Nagelpflegemittel; Haarpräparate und Haarkuren; Reinigungstüchlein für Hygienezwecke, Nämlich, Reinigungstüchlein für die weibliche Hygiene; Parfümierte Tücher; Mit Reinigungsmitteln imprägnierte Wischtücher; Feuchttücher für kosmetische Zwecke; Mit einem Reinigungsmittel imprägnierte Putztücher.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μη φαρμακευτικά καλλυντικά και παρασκευάσματα ατομικής περιποίησης· Αιθέρια (Έλαια -)· Παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού σώματος και φροντίδας ομορφιάς· Παρασκευάσματα για την περιποίηση του δέρματος, των ματιών και των νυχιών· Παρασκευάσματα για την περιποίηση και τη θεραπεία των μαλλιών· Μαντιλάκια καθαρισμού και υγιεινής, Συγκεκριμένα, Μαντιλάκια καθαρισμού για τη γυναικεία υγιεινή· Αρωματισμένα μαντιλάκια· Μαντιλάκια με ενσωματωμένα παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού· Προεμποτισμένα μαντιλάκια για καλλυντική χρήση· Πανάκια καθαρισμού εμποτισμένα με καθαριστικό.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Non-medicated cosmetics and toiletry preparations; essential oils; body cleaning and beauty care preparations; Skin, eye and nail care preparations; Hair preparations and treatments; Hygiene cleaning towelettes, namely, feminine hygiene cleaning towelettes; perfumed tissues; wipes incorporating cleaning preparations; pre-moistened wipes (for cosmetic use); cloths impregnated with a detergent for cleaning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Productos cosméticos y preparaciones de tocador no medicinales; Aceites esenciales; Preparaciones para la limpieza y cuidado del cuerpo; Productos para el cuidado de la piel, los ojos y las uñas; Preparaciones y tratamientos para el cabello; Toallitas higiénicas de limpieza, En concreto, Toallitas para la higiene femenina; Pañuelos perfumados; Toallitas que incorporan preparados de limpieza; Toallitas prehumedecidas para uso cosmético; Paños de limpieza impregnados con detergente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ravitoimeta kosmeetika- ja tualett-tarbed; Eeterlikud õlid; Puhastus- ja iluhooldustooted kehale; Naha-, silma- ja küünehoolduspreparaadid; Juuksehooldus- ja -töötlusvahendid; Hügieenilised puhastusrätid, Nimelt, Naiste hügieenilised puhastusrätid; Lõhnastatud salvrätid; Puhastuspreparaate sisaldavad lapid; Eelniisutatud kosmeetilised salvrätid; Puhastusvahendiga immutatud lapid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lääkeaineita sisältämättömät kosmeettiset ja peseytymisvalmisteet; Eteeriset öljyt; Vartalon puhdistus- ja kauneudenhoitovalmisteet; Ihon-, silmien- ja kynsienhoitovalmisteet; Hiusten hoito- ja käsittelyvalmisteet; Hygieeniset pienet puhdistuspyyhkeet, Nimittäin, Kostutetut puhdistusliinat naishygieniaan; Hajustetut paperipyyhkeet; Pyyhkeet sisältäen puhdistusvalmisteita; Valmiiksi kostutetut liinat kosmeettisiin tarkoituksiin; Rievut (pesuaineilla kyllästetyt).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits cosmétiques et préparations de toilette non médicamenteux; Huiles essentielles; Préparations de nettoyage corporel et de soins de beauté; Produits pour le soin de la peau, des yeux et des ongles; Préparations et traitements capillaires; Lingettes nettoyantes pour l'hygiène, À savoir, Lingettes nettoyantes pour l'hygiène féminine; Lingettes parfumées; Lingettes imprégnées de produits nettoyants; Lingettes préhumidifiées à usage cosmétique; Torchons imprégnés d'un détergent pour le nettoyage.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Nemedicinska kozmetika i toaletni pripravci; Esencijalna ulja; Pripravci za čišćenje i njegu tijela; Preparati za njegu kože, očiju i noktiju; Pripravci i tretmani za kosu; Higijenske maramice za čišćenje, Odnosno, Maramice za čišćenje za žensku higijenu; Parfimirane maramice; Maramice koje sadrže preparate za čišćenje; Unaprijed navlažene maramice za kozmetičke potrebe; Krpe namočene deterdžentom za čišćenje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nem gyógyhatású kozmetikumok és piperekészítmények; Esszenciális olajok; Testápolási és szépségápolási készitmények; Bőr-, szem- és körömápoló készítmények; Hajápoló készítmények; Higiéniai tisztító törülközők, Nevezetesen, Női higiéniai tisztító törlőkendők; Illatosított kendők; Tisztítókészítményeket tartalmazó törlőkendők; Előnedvesített törlők kozmetikai célokra; Mosószerrel impregnált ruhák tisztításra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cosmetici e preparati per la toeletta non medicati; Oli essenziali; Preparati per la pulizia del corpo e per la cura della bellezza; Prodotti per la pelle, gli occhi e la cura delle unghie; Preparati e trattamenti per i capelli; Salviette detergenti per l'igiene, Ovvero, Salviettine detergenti per l'igiene femminile; Salviette profumate; Salviette contenenti prodotti per la pulizia; Salviette preimbevute per uso cosmetico; Strofinacci impregnati con un detergente per pulire.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Negydomoji kosmetika ir tualetiniai preparatai; Eteriniai aliejai; Kūno valomieji ir grožio priežiūros preparatai; Odos, akių ir nagų priežiūros preparatai; Plaukų priežiūros preparatai; Higieniniai valymo rankšluosčiai, Būtent,, Valomosios moterų intymiosios higienos servetėlės; Kvepiančios servetėlės; Servetėlės su valymo preparatais; Iš anksto sudrėkintos servetėlės, skirtos kosmetikos reikmėms; Valikliais impregnuotas audeklas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Nemedicīniski kosmētikas un tualetes līdzekļi; Ēteriskās eļļas; Ķermeņa kopšanas un skaistumkopšanas līdzekļi; Ādas, acu un nagu kopšanas līdzekļi; Līdzekļi matiem un matu kopšanas līdzekļi; Higiēniskas tīrīšanas salvetes, Proti, Tīrīšanas salvetes sieviešu intīmai higiēnai; Aromatizētas salvetes; Salvetītes, kurās iestrādāti tīrīšanas līdzekļi; Mitrās salvetes kosmētiskām vajadzībām; Ar tīrīšanas līdzekli impregnētas lupatiņas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kożmetiċi mhux medikati u preparazzjonijiet tat-twaletta; Żjut meħudin minn pjanti; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif tal-ġisem u għall-kura tas-sbuħija; Preparazzjonijiet tal-ġilda, tal-għajnejn u tad-dwiefer; Preparazzjonijiet u trattamenti għax-xagħar; Srievet għat-tindif tal-iġjene, Jiġifieri, Srievet għat-tindif tal-iġjene femminili; Srievet imfewħa; Biċċiet tal-imsiħ li fihom preparazzjonijiet tat-tindif; Karti tal-imsiħ imxarrbin minn qabel għal skopijiet kożmetiċi; Ċraret mgħammra b'diterġent għat-tindif.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Niet-medicinale cosmetica en toiletpreparaten; Etherische oliën; Reinigings- en schoonheidspreparaten voor het lichaam; Huid-, oog- en nagelverzorgingsproducten; Haarverzorgingsproducten en haarbehandelingsproducten; Doekjes voor hygiënische reiniging, Te weten, Intieme reinigingsdoekjes voor vrouwen; Geparfumeerde doekjes; Doekjes bevattende reinigingsmiddelen; Vochtige doekjes voor cosmetische doeleinden; Doeken geïmpregneerd met een reinigingsmiddel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kosmetyki nielecznicze i preparaty toaletowe; Olejki eteryczne; Preparaty do mycia i pielęgnacji ciała; Preparaty do pielęgnacji skóry, oczu i paznokci; Preparaty do włosów; Chusteczki oczyszczające do higieny, Mianowicie, Chusteczki oczyszczające do higieny intymnej dla kobiet; Chusteczki perfumowane; Chusteczki zawierające preparaty czyszczące; Chusteczki nawilżone do celów kosmetycznych; Ściereczki nasączane detergentami, do czyszczenia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Preparações cosméticas e de higiene pessoal, não medicinais; Óleos essenciais; Produtos para limpeza corporal e cuidados de beleza; Produtos para os cuidados da pele, dos olhos e das unhas; Produtos e tratamentos para o cabelo; Toalhetes de limpeza para a higiene, Nomeadamente, Toalhetes de limpeza para a higiene feminina; Lenços perfumados; Toalhetes que incorporam produtos de limpeza; Toalhetes pré-humedecidos para uso cosmético; Panos de limpeza impregnados com detergente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cosmetice şi produse de toaletă nemedicinale; Uleiuri eterice; Preparate pentru curăţarea şi îngrijirea corpului; Preparate pentru îngrijirea pielii, a ochilor şi a unghiilor; Preparate şi tratamente pentru păr; Șervețele pentru curățare igienică, Şi anume, Şerveţele pentru curăţare utilizate pentru igiena intimă feminină; Şerveţele parfumate; Şerveţele impregnate cu preparate de curăţare; Şerveţele umede pentru uz cosmetic; Pânză îmbibată cu detergent, pentru curăţat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Neliečivé kozmetické prípravky a toaletné výrobky; Esenciálne (éterické) oleje; Telové čistiace prípravky a skrášľovacie prípravky; Prípravky na starostlivosť o pleť, oči a nechty; Vlasová kozmetika a prípravky na ošetrenie vlasov; Hygienické čistiace obrúsky, Menovite, Čistiace obrúsky na intímnu dámsku hygienu; Parfumované utierky; Utierky obsahujúce čistiace prípravky; Navlhčené utierky na kozmetické účely; Tkaniny impregnované čistiacimi prípravkami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kozmetični izdelki brez zdravilnih učinkovin in toaletni pripravki; Eterična olja; Preparati za čiščenje telesa in lepotilno nego; Pripravki za nego kože, oči in nohtov; Sredstva za nego in obdelavo las; Brisače za higiensko čiščenje, In sicer, Ženske higienske čistilne brisačke; Parfumirani robčki; Brisačke, ki vsebujejo čistilne pripravke; Navlaženi robčki za kozmetične namene; Krpe prepojene s čistilnim sredstvom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Icke-medicinsk kosmetika och icke-medicinska toalettpreparat; Flyktiga oljor; Preparat för kroppsrengöring och skönhetsvård; Hud-, ögon- och nagelvårdspreparat; Preparat för behandling och vård av hår; Hygieniska rengöringsservetter, Nämligen, Rengöringsservetter för kvinnohygien; Parfymerade servetter; Torkservetter innehållande rengöringsmedel; Våtservetter för kosmetiska ändamål; Dukar impregnerade med tvättmedel för rengöring.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Препарати за грижа за здравето, А именно, Продукти за дамска хигиена, Абсорбиращи артикули за лична хигиена; Почистващи кърпи, импрегнирани с дезинфектант за хигиенични цели; Дезинфектиращ сапун; Антибактериален сапун; Лечебни и хигиенизиращи сапуни и детергенти; Хигиенни меки подложки, Дамски превръзки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Hygienické produkty, Jmenovitě, Dámské hygienické výrobky, Absorpční výrobky pro osobní hygienu; Čisticí ubrousky napuštěné dezinfekčními přípravky pro hygienické účely; Dezinfekční mýdla; Antibakteriální mýdla; Léčebná a dezinfekční mýdla a čisticí přípravky; Menstruační vložky, Hygienické tampóny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Hygiejneartikler, navnlig hygiejneartikler til kvinder; absorberende artikler til personlig hygiejne; rengøringsklude imprægneret med desinficeringsmidler til hygiejneformål; desinficerende sæbe; antibakteriel sæbe; medicinske og desinficerende sæber og rensemidler; menstruationsbind; tamponer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Hygieneprodukte, Nämlich, Damenhygieneartikel, Absorbierende Erzeugnisse für die Körperhygiene; Mit Desinfektionsmitteln getränkte Reinigungstücher für Hygienezwecke; Desinfizierende Seifen; Antibakterielle Seifen; Medizinische und desinfizierende Seifen sowie Detergenzien; Monatsbinden, Tampons für hygienische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Προϊόντα υγιεινής, Συγκεκριμένα, Προϊόντα γυναικείας υγιεινής, Απορροφητικά είδη για προσωπική υγιεινή· Πανιά καθαρισμού εμποτισμένα με απολυμαντικά για σκοπούς υγιεινής· Απολυμαντικά σαπούνια· Αντιβακτηριακά σαπούνια· Φαρμακευτικά και απολυμαντικά σαπούνια και απορρυπαντικά· Σερβιέτες υγιεινής, Ταμπόν για χρήσεις υγιεινής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hygiene products, namely, feminine hygiene products, absorbent articles for personal hygiene; cleaning cloths impregnated with disinfectant for hygiene purposes; disinfectant soap; antibacterial soap; medicated and sanitising soaps and detergents; menstruation bandages, sanitary tampons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Productos higiénicos, En concreto, Productos para la higiene femenina, Productos absorbentes para la higiene personal; Paños de limpieza impregnados con desinfectante para uso higiénico; Jabones desinfectantes; Jabones antibacterianos; Jabones y detergentes medicinales y desinfectantes; Paños menstruales, Tampones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hügieenitooted, Nimelt, Naiste hügieenitooted, Absorbeerivad tooted isiklikuks hügieeniks; Desinfitseerimisvahendiga immutatud puhastuslapid hügieeniks; Desinfitseeriv seep; Antibakteriaalne seep; Ravitoimega ja desinfitseerivad seebid ja pesuained; Hügieenisidemed, Tampoonid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hygieniatuotteet, Nimittäin, Naisten hygieniatuotteet, Imukykyiset henkilökohtaiseen hygieniaan tarkoitetut tuotteet; Desinfiointiaineella kyllästetyt puhdistuspyyhkeet hygieniakäyttöön; Desinfioiva saippua; Antibakteerinen saippua; Lääkeaineita sisältävät ja desinfioivat saippuat ja puhdistusaineet; Terveyssiteet, Kuukautistamponit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits hygiéniques, À savoir, Produits d'hygiène féminine, Articles absorbants destinés à l'hygiène personnelle; Lingettes nettoyantes imprégnées de désinfectants, à usage hygiénique; Savons désinfectants; Savons antibactériens; Savons et détergents désinfectants et médicinaux; Bandes périodiques, Tampons hygiéniques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sanitarni proizvodi, Odnosno, Higijenski proizvodi za žene, Upijajući proizvodi za osobnu higijenu; Krpe za čišćenje impregnirane sredstvom za dezinfekciju za higijenske potrebe; Dezinfekcijski sapuni; Antibakterijski sapun; Medicinski i dezinfekcijski sapuni i deterdženti; Higijenski ulošci, Higijenski taponi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Egészségügyi termékek, Nevezetesen, Higiéniás termékek nőknek, Felszívó árucikkek a személyi higiénéhez; Fertőtlenítőszerrel átitatott tisztítókendők higiéniai célokra; Fertőtlenítő szappanok; Antibakteriális szappan; Gyógyszeres és fertőtlenítő szappanok és tisztítószerek; Menstruációs betétek, Tamponok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Prodotti per l'igiene, Ovvero, Prodotti per l'igiene femminile, Articoli assorbenti per l'igiene personale; Panni per la pulizia imbevuti di disinfettante per uso igienico; Saponi disinfettanti; Saponi antibatterici; Saponi e detergenti medicinali e igienizzanti; Assorbenti periodici, Tamponi per la mestruazione.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Higieniniai produktai, Būtent,, Moterų higienos priemonės, Absorbuojančios priemonės asmeninei higienai; Dezinfekavimo preparatais įmirkytos [impregnuotos] servetėlės (higienos reikmėms); Dezinfekcinis muilas; Antibakterinis muilas; Gydomieji ir dezinfekciniai muilai bei plovikliai; Mėnesinių raiščiai, Higieniniai tamponai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Higiēnas produkti, Proti, Higiēnas izstrādājumi sievietēm, Absorbējoši personiskās higiēnas līdzekļi; Ar dezinfekcijas līdzekļiem piesūcinātas auduma drāniņas tīrīšanai higiēniskos nolūkos; Dezinficējošas ziepes; Antibakteriālās ziepes; Ārstnieciskās un dezinficējošās ziepes un mazgāšanas līdzekļi; Higiēniskās paketes, Higiēniskie tamponi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Prodotti sanitarji, Jiġifieri, Prodotti iġjeniċi għall-mara, Oġġetti assorbenti għall-iġjene personali; Ċraret tat-tindif mimlija b'diżinfettant għal skopijiet iġjeniċi; Sapun diżinfettanti; Sapun antibatteriku; Sapunijiet u deterġenti li jimmedikaw u jtejbu l-iġjene; Peds sanitarji, Tampuni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Hygiënische producten, Te weten, Producten voor vrouwelijk hygiëne, Absorberende producten voor persoonlijke hygiëne; Reinigingsdoekjes geïmpregneerd met ontsmettingsmiddelen voor hygiënische doeleinden; Desinfecterende zeep; Antibacteriële zeep; Medicinale en steriliserende zepen en detergenten; Damesverband, Tampons voor de menstruatie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Produkty higieniczne, Mianowicie, Produkty higieniczne dla kobiet, Substancje chłonne do higieny osobistej; Ściereczki do czyszczenia nasączone środkami dezynfekującymi, do celów higienicznych; Mydła dezynfekujące; Mydła antybakteryjne; Mydła i detergenty lecznicze i odkażające; Podpaski higieniczne, Tampony.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Produtos de higiene, Nomeadamente, Produtos de higiene feminina, Artigos absorventes para higiene pessoal; Panos de limpeza impregnados com desinfetantes para fins de higiene; Sabão desinfetante; Sabão antibacteriano; Sabões e detergentes higiénicos e medicinais; Pensos higiénicos, Tampões.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Produse de igienă, Şi anume, Produse pentru igiena feminină, Articole absorbante pentru igiena personală; Materiale textile pentru curăţare impregnate cu dezinfectant, de uz igienic; Săpunuri dezinfectante; Săpun antibacterian; Săpunuri şi detergenţi medicinali şi dezinfectanţi; Bandaje pentru menstruaţie, Tampoane pentru menstruaţie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Hygienické výrobky, Menovite, Dámske hygienické potreby, Absorbčné výrobky na osobnú hygienu; Čistiace obrúsky napustené dezinfekčnými prípravkami na hygienické účely; Dezinfekčné mydlá; Antibakteriálne mydlá; Mydlá a detergenty s liečivými a dezinfekčnými účinkami; Menštruačné vložky, Hygienické tampóny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Higienski izdelki, In sicer, Ženski higienski proizvodi, Proizvodi za vpijanje za osebno higieno; Čistilne krpe, impregnirane z dezinfekcijskim sredstvom za higienske namene; Dezinfekcijsko milo; Antibakterijska mila; Mila in detergenti z zdravilnimi in razkuževalnimi učinkovinami; Menstruacijski vložki, Tamponi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hygienprodukter, Nämligen, Hygieniska produkter för kvinnor, Absorberande artiklar för personlig hygien; Rengöringstrasor impregnerade med desinfektionsmedel för hygieniska ändamål; Desinficerande tvål; Bakteriedödande tvål; Medicinska och desinficerande tvålar och rengöringsmedel; Dambindor, Menstruationskompresser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>8</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Уреди за хигиена и разкрасяване за хора.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Potřeby k péči o hygienu a krásu osob.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Redskaber til hygiejne- og skønhedsbrug for mennesker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Geräte für hygienische Zwecke und für die Schönheitspflege für Menschen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Σύνεργα υγιεινής και ομορφιάς για ανθρώπους.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hygienic and beauty implements for humans.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Instrumentos de higiene y belleza para personas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hügieeni- ja ilutarvikud inimestele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ihmisten terveyden- ja kauneudenhoitovälineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Ustensiles d'hygiène et de beauté pour êtres humains.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pribor za higijenu i uljepšavanje za ljude.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Higiénés és szépségápoló eszközök emberek számára.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Strumenti d'igiene e di bellezza per l'uomo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Higienos ir grožio priežiūros reikmenys, skirti žmonėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Higiēniskas un skaistumkopšanas ierīces cilvēkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Strumenti għall-kura iġenika u tas-sbuħija għall-bnedmin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Hygiënisch en schoonheidsgerei voor mensen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przybory higieniczne i do pielęgnacji urody dla ludzi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Utensílios para os cuidados de higiene e de beleza para uso humano.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Instrumente pentru igiena şi frumuseţea oamenilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Hygienické a kozmetické náčinie pre ľudí.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Higienske in lepotilne priprave za ljudi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hygien- och skönhetsredskap för människor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Менструални чашки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Menstruační kalíšky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Menstruationskopper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Menstruationstassen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κυπελοειδές διάφραγμα για διακοπή ροής κατά την εμμηνόρροια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Menstrual cups.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Copas menstruales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Menstruatsioonitopsid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kuukautiskupit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Coupes menstruelles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Menstrualne čašice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Menstruációs csészék.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Coppette per mestruazioni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Menstruacinės taurelės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Menstruālās piltuves.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kontenituri għall-mestruwazzjoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Menstruatiecups.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kubeczki menstruacyjne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Coletores menstruais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cupe menstruale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Menštruačné poháriky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Menstrualne skodelice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Menskoppar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Облекло, а именно бельо.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Oděvy, jmenovitě spodní prádlo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beklædningsgenstande i form af undertøj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bekleidungsstücke, nämlich Unterwäsche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ενδύματα, συγκεκριμένα εσώρουχα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Clothing, namely, underwear.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Ropa de vestir, en concreto ropa interior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rõivad, nimelt alusrõivad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatteet, nimittäin alusvaatteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vêtements, à savoir sous-vêtements.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Odjevni artikli, od kojih donje rublje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ruházat, nevezetesen alsóneműk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Articoli d'abbigliamento, ovvero biancheria intima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Drabužiai, apranga, būtent apatiniai drabužiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apģērbs, proti, apakšveļa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ilbies, jiġifieri ħwejjeġ ta' taħt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kleding, te weten ondergoed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odzież, mianowicie bielizna.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vestuário, especificamente roupa interior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Îmbrăcăminte, şi anume lenjerie intimă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Odevy, menovite spodná bielizeň.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oblačila, zlasti spodnje perilo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kläder, nämligen underkläder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за търговия на едро и услуги за търговия на дребно, включително и онлайн, във връзка с хигиенизиращи препарати за хора, немедицински козметични средства и тоалетни препарати, хигиенни почистващи кърпички, дамски хигиенни почистващи кърпички, ароматизирани кърпички, кърпички, съдържащи почистващи препарати, предварително овлажнени козметични кърпички, импрегнирани с почистващ препарат кърпички за почистване; Услуги за търговия на едро и услуги за търговия на дребно, включително и онлайн, във връзка с хигиенни продукти, дамски хигиенни продукти, менструални чашки, абсорбиращи средства за лична хигиена, почистващи платове, напоени с дезинфектанти, за хигиенни цели, дезинфектиращ сапун, антибактериален сапун, медицински и дезинфекциращи сапуни и почистващи препарати; Услуги за търговия на едро и услуги за търговия на дребно, включително и онлайн, във връзка с инструменти за хигиена и разкрасяване за хора, дезинфектиращ сапун, антибактериален сапун, медицински и дезинфектиращи сапуни и почистващи препарати, инструменти за хигиена и разкрасяване за хора, облекло, а именно, бельо.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Velkoobchodní služby a maloobchodní služby, včetně on-line, ve vztahu k výrobkům jako hygienické výrobky pro lidi, neléčivé kosmetické a toaletní přípravky, čisticí hygienické utěrky, čisticí ubrousky pro intimní hygienu žen, parfémované ubrousky, ubrousky obsahující čisticí prostředky, vlhčené kosmetické utěrky, utěrky napuštěné čisticími přípravky na čištění; Velkoobchodní služby a maloobchodní služby, včetně on-line, ve vztahu k výrobkům jako hygienické výrobky, přípravky pro intimní hygienu žen, menstruační kalíšky, absorpční předměty pro osobní hygienu, čisticí utěrky napuštěné dezinfekčními přípravky pro hygienické účely, dezinfekční mýdla, antibakteriální mýdla, léčivá a hygienická mýdla a čisticí prostředky; Velkoobchodní služby a maloobchodní služby, včetně on-line, ve vztahu k výrobkům jako hygienické a kosmetické náčiní pro lidi, dezinfekční mýdla, antibakteriální mýdla, léčivá a hygienická mýdla a čisticí prostředky, hygienické a kosmetické náčiní pro lidi, oděvy, jmenovitě spodní prádlo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Engros- og detailhandel, herunder online, med hygiejnemidler til mennesker, ikke-medicinsk kosmetik og toiletartikler, renseservietter til hygiejneformål, renseservietter til hygiejneformål til kvinder, parfumerede servietter, servietter med rensepræparater, imprægnerede servietter (til kosmetisk brug), servietter imprægneret med midler til rengøring; Engros- og detailhandel, herunder online, med hygiejneartikler, hygiejneartikler til kvinder, menstruationskopper, absorberende artikler til personlig hygiejne, rengøringsklude imprægneret med desinficeringsmidler til hygiejneformål, desinficerende sæbe, antibakteriel sæbe, medicinske og desinficerende sæber og rensemidler; Engros- og detailhandel, herunder online, med redskaber til hygiejne- og skønhedsbrug for mennesker, beklædningsgenstande i form af undertøj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Großhandelsdienstleistungen und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen, auch online, in Bezug auf Hygienepräparate für Menschen, nicht medizinische Kosmetika und Toilettemittel [Körperpflege], Reinigungstüchlein für Hygienezwecke, Reinigungstüchlein für die weibliche Hygiene, parfümierte Tücher, mit Reinigungsmitteln imprägnierte Wischtücher, feuchte Kosmetiktücher, mit einem Reinigungsmittel imprägnierte Putztücher; Großhandelsdienstleistungen und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen, auch online, in Bezug auf Hygieneartikel, Damenhygieneartikel, Menstruationstassen, absorbierende Erzeugnisse für die Körperhygiene, mit Desinfektionsmitteln getränkte Reinigungstücher für Hygienezwecke, desinfizierende Seifen, antibakterielle Seifen, medizinische und desinfizierende Seifen sowie Detergenzien; Großhandelsdienstleistungen und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen, auch online, in Bezug auf Geräte zur Körper- und Schönheitspflege für Menschen, desinfizierende Seifen, antibakterielle Seifen, medizinische und desinfizierende Seifen sowie Detergenzien, Geräte zur Körper- und Schönheitspflege für Menschen, Bekleidungsstücke, nämlich Unterwäsche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες χονδρικής πώλησης και υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης, επίσης και επί γραμμής, σε σχέση με παρασκευάσματα υγιεινής για τον άνθρωπο, μη φαρμακευτικά καλλυντικά και παρασκευάσματα ατομικής περιποίησης, μαντιλάκια καθαρισμού και υγιεινής, μαντιλάκια καθαρισμού για τη γυναικεία υγιεινή, αρωματισμένα μαντιλάκια, μαντιλάκια εμποτισμένα με παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού, υγρά μαντιλάκια για καλλυντική χρήση, πανάκια καθαρισμού εμποτισμένα με απορρυπαντικό· Υπηρεσίες χονδρικής πώλησης και υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης, επίσης και επί γραμμής, σε σχέση με προϊόντα υγιεινής, προϊόντα υγιεινής για γυναίκες, κυπελοειδές διάφραγμα για διακοπή ροής κατά την εμμηνόρροια, απορροφητικά είδη για προσωπική υγιεινή, πανιά καθαρισμού εμποτισμένα με απολυμαντικά για σκοπούς υγιεινής, απολυμαντικά σαπούνια, αντιβακτηριακά σαπούνια, φαρμακευτικά σαπούνια και σαπούνια υγιεινής και απορρυπαντικά· Υπηρεσίες χονδρικής πώλησης και υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης, επίσης και επί γραμμής, σε σχέση με σύνεργα υγιεινής και καλλωπισμού για τον άνθρωπο, απολυμαντικά σαπούνια, αντιβακτηριακά σαπούνια, φαρμακευτικά σαπούνια και σαπούνια υγιεινής και απορρυπαντικά, σύνεργα υγιεινής και καλλωπισμού για τον άνθρωπο, ενδύματα, συγκεκριμένα, εσώρουχα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Wholesale services and retail services, including online, in relation to hygienic preparations for humans, non-medicated cosmetics and toiletry preparations, hygiene cleansing towelettes, feminine hygiene cleansing towelettes, perfumed tissues, wipes incorporating cleaning preparations, pre-moistened cosmetic wipes, cloths impregnated with a detergent for cleaning; Wholesale services and retail services, including online, in relation to hygiene products, feminine hygiene products, menstrual cups, absorbent articles for personal hygiene, cleaning cloths impregnated with disinfectant for hygiene purposes, disinfectant soap, antibacterial soap, medicated and sanitising soaps and detergents; Wholesale services and retail services, including online, in relation to hygienic and beauty implements for humans, disinfectant soap, antibacterial soap, medicated and sanitising soaps and detergents, hygienic and beauty implements for humans, clothing, namely, underwear.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de venta al por mayor y servicios de venta al por menor, también en línea, en relación con preparaciones higiénicas para personas, productos cosméticos y preparaciones de tocador no medicinales, toallitas higiénicas limpiadoras, toallitas limpiadoras de higiene femenina, toallitas perfumadas, toallitas que incorporan preparaciones de limpieza, toallitas cosméticas húmedas y paños de limpieza impregnados con detergente; Servicios de venta al por mayor y servicios de venta al por menor, también en línea, en relación con productos higiénicos, productos de higiene femenina, copas menstruales, artículos absorbentes de higiene personal, paños de limpieza impregnados con desinfectantes con fines higiénicos, jabones desinfectantes, jabones antibacterianos, y jabones y detergentes medicinales y desinfectantes; Servicios de venta al por mayor y servicios de venta al por menor, también en línea, en relación con instrumentos higiénicos y de belleza para personas, jabones desinfectantes, jabones antibacterianos, jabones y detergentes medicinales y desinfectantes, instrumentos higiénicos y de belleza para humanos, prendas de vestir, en concreto ropa interior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Järgmiste kaupade hulgi- ja jaemüük, sh sidusjaemüük: inimeste hügieenitooted, ravitoimeta kosmeetikavahendid ja tualettpreparaadid, hügieenilised puhastusrätid, hügieenilised naiste puhastusrätid, lõhnastatud salvrätid, puhastusainetega pühkelapid, eelnevalt niisutatud kosmeetilised lapid, puhastusvahendiga immutatud lapid; Järgmiste kaupade hulgi- ja jaemüük, sh sidusjaemüük: hügieenitooted, naiste hügieenitooted, menstruatsioonitopsid, imavad materjalid isiklikuks hügieeniks, desinfitseerimisvahendiga immutatud puhastuslapid hügieeniks, desinfitseeriv seep, antibakteriaalne seep, ravitoimega ja hügieenilised seebid ja pesuained; Järgmiste kaupade hulgi- ja jaemüük, sh sidusjaemüük: inimeste hügieeni- ja iluvahendid, desinfitseeriv seep, antibakteriaalne seep, ravitoimega ja hügieenilised seebid ja pesuained, inimeste hügieenilised ja iluvahendid, rõivad, nimelt, alusrõivad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Seuraavien tukkumyyntipalvelut ja vähittäismyyntipalvelut, myös online-periaatteella: hygieniavalmisteet ihmisille, lääkeaineita sisältämättömät kosmeettiset tuotteet ja kosmeettiset ja peseytymisvalmisteet, hygieeniset pienet puhdistuspyyhkeet, naisten hygieeniset puhdistusliinat, hajustetut pyyhkeet, pyyhkeet, joissa on puhdistusvalmisteita, kostutetut hygieeniset pyyhkeet, pesuaineilla kyllästetyt liinat; Seuraavien tukkumyyntipalvelut ja vähittäismyyntipalvelut, myös online-periaatteella: hygieniatuotteet, naisten hygieniatuotteet, kuukautiskupit, imukykyiset tarvikkeet henkilökohtaiseen hygieniaan, desinfiointiaineella kostutetut puhdistuspyyhkeet hygieniakäyttöön, desinfioiva saippua, antibakteerinen saippua, lääkeaineita sisältävät kylpysuolat lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin ja hygieeniset saippuat ja pesuaineet; Seuraavien tukkumyyntipalvelut ja vähittäismyyntipalvelut, myös online-periaatteella: hygieeniset ja kauneudenhoitovälineet ihmisille, desinfioiva saippua, antibakteerinen saippua, lääkeaineita sisältävät kylpysuolat lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin ja hygieeniset saippuat ja pesuaineet, hygieeniset ja kauneudenhoitovälineet ihmisille, vaatteet, nimittäin alusvaatteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de vente en gros et services de vente au détail, y compris en ligne, de préparations d'hygiène pour êtres humains, cosmétiques et produits de toilette non médicamenteux, lingettes purifiantes pour l'hygiène, lingettes purifiantes pour l'hygiène féminine, serviettes parfumées, lingettes imbibées de préparations nettoyantes, lingettes cosmétiques préalablement humidifiées, chiffons imprégnés d'un détergent pour le nettoyage; Services de vente en gros et services de vente au détail, y compris en ligne, de produits d'hygiène, produits pour l'hygiène féminine, coupelles menstruelles, articles absorbants pour l'hygiène personnelle, chiffons nettoyants imprégnés d'un désinfectant à des fins d'hygiène, savon désinfectant, savon antibactérien, savons et détergents médicamenteux et désinfectants; Services de vente en gros et services de vente au détail, y compris en ligne, d'ustensiles d'hygiène et de beauté pour êtres humains, savon désinfectant, savon antibactérien, savons et détergents médicamenteux et désinfectants, ustensiles d'hygiène et de beauté pour êtres humains, vêtements, à savoir sous-vêtements.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Veleprodajne usluge i maloprodajne usluge, uključujući i na mreži, u vezi s higijenskim preparatima za ljude, nemedicinskom kozmetikom i toaletnim preparatima, higijenskim maramicama za čišćenje, ženskim higijenskim maramicama za čišćenje, parfimiranim maramicama, maramicama koje sadrže preparate za čišćenje, unaprijed navlaženim kozmetičkim maramicama, krpama natopljenim deterdžentom za čišćenje; Veleprodajne usluge i maloprodajne usluge, uključujući i na mreži, u vezi s higijenskim proizvodima, ženskim higijenskim proizvodima, menstrualnim čašicama, upijajućim predmetima za osobnu higijenu, krpama za čišćenje natopljenim sredstvima za dezinfekciju za higijenske potrebe, sapunom za dezinfekciju, antibakterijskim sapunom, medicinskim i higijenskim sapunima i deterdžentima; Veleprodajne usluge i maloprodajne usluge, uključujući i na mreži, u vezi s priborom za higijenu i uljepšavanje za ljude, sapunom za dezinfekciju, antibakterijskim sapunom, medicinskim i higijenskim sapunima i deterdžentima, priborom za higijenu i uljepšavanje za ljude, odjećom, i to donjim rubljem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nagykereskedelmi és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten is az alábbiakkal: emberi higiéniai készítmények, nem gyógyszeres kozmetikumok és piperecikkek, higiéniai tisztító kesztyűk, nők higiéniai tisztálkodására szolgáló törülközők, illatosított szövetek, tisztítószereket tartalmazó törlőkendők, előre nedvesített kozmetikai törlőkendők, tisztítószerrel impregnált rongyok; Nagykereskedelmi szolgáltatások és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, online is, az alábbiakkal kapcsolatban: higiéniai termékek, intimhigiéniás szerek, menstruációs csészék, nedvszívó termékek személyes higiéniai célra, fertőtlenítőszerrel impregnált tisztító kendők higiéniai célokra, fertőtlenítő szappanok, antibakteriális szappan, gyógyszerek és higiéniai szappanok és mosószerek; Nagykereskedelmi szolgáltatások és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, on-line is, az alábbiakkal kapcsolatban: higiéniás és szépségápoló eszközök emberek számára, fertőtlenítő szappanok, antibakteriális szappan, gyógyszerek és higiéniai szappanok és mosószerek, higiéniai és szépségápoló eszközök emberek számára, ruházat, nevezetesen, jégeralsók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di vendita all'ingrosso e vendita al dettaglio, anche on-line, in relazione ai preparati igienici per la persona, cosmetici non medicati e preparati per la toilette, salviette detergenti per l'igiene, salviette detergenti per l'igiene intima femminile, salviette profumate, salviette contenenti prodotti per la pulizia, salviette cosmetiche preumidificate, strofinacci impregnati con un detergente per pulire; Servizi di vendita all'ingrosso e vendita al dettaglio, anche on-line, riguardo prodotti per l'igiene, prodotti per l'igiene femminile, coppette per mestruazioni, articoli assorbenti per l'igiene personale, panni per la pulizia imbevuti di disinfettante per uso igienico, saponi disinfettanti, sapone antibatterico, medicinali e saponi igienizzanti e detergenti; Servizi di vendita all'ingrosso e vendita al dettaglio, anche on-line, riguardo strumenti di bellezza e per l'igiene della persona, saponi disinfettanti, sapone antibatterico, medicinali e saponi igienizzanti e detergenti, igienico e strumenti di bellezza per esseri umani, prodotti d'abbigliamento, ovvero, biancheria intima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Didmeninės ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, taip pat ir internetu, susijusios su tokiomis prekėmis, kaip higienos preparatai žmonėms, negydomieji kosmetikos ir tualeto reikmenys, higieniniai valymo rankšluosčiai, moteriškos higienos valymo rankšluosčiai, kvepiantys audiniai, servetėlės su valymo preparatais, iš anksto sudrėkintos kosmetinės servetėlės, valymo priemonės, įmirkytos; Didmeninės ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, taip pat ir internetu, susijusios su higienos produktais, moteriškos higienos priemonėmis, menstruacinėmis taurėmis, sugeriančiaisiais asmeninės higienos gaminiais, valymo servetėlėmis, įmirkytomis dezinfekavimo priemonėmis higienos reikmėms, dezinfekavimo muilu, antibakteriniu muilu, gydomuoju ir dezinfekuojamuoju muilu bei plovikliais; Didmeninės ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, taip pat ir internetu, susijusios su žmonių higienos ir grožio prietaisais, dezinfekuojamuoju muilu, antibakteriniu muilu, vaistiniais ir sanitariniais muilais ir plovikliais, higieniniais ir grožio prietaisais žmonėms, drabužiais, būtent apatiniais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, tostarp tiešsaistē, saistībā ar higiēnas līdzekļiem cilvēkiem, kosmētiku un tualetes piederumiem bez ārstniecības līdzekļiem, higiēnas tīrīšanas dvieļiem, sieviešu higiēnas tīrīšanas dvieļiem, aromatizētiem audiem, salvetēm ar tīrīšanas līdzekļiem, iepriekš samitrinātām kosmētikas salvetēm, piesūcinātām drānām ar mazgāšanas līdzekli tīrīšanai; Vairumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, arī tiešsaistē, saistībā ar šīm precēm: higiēnas produkti, intīmās higiēnas līdzekļi, menstruālās piltuves, absorbējošie līdzekļi personīgās higiēnas nolūkiem, tīrīšanas lupatiņas, kas ir piesūcinātas ar dezinfekcijas līdzekļiem, higiēnai, dezinficējošas ziepes, antibakteriālās ziepes, medicīniskas un higiēniskās ziepes un mazgāšanas līdzekļi; Vairumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, arī tiešsaistē, saistībā ar šīm precēm: higiēnas un cilvēkiem paredzētās skaistumkopšanas iekārtas, dezinficējošas ziepes, antibakteriālās ziepes, medicīnisks un higiēniskās ziepes un mazgāšanas līdzekļi, higiēnisks un cilvēkiem paredzētās skaistumkopšanas iekārtas, apģērbi, proti, apakšveļa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-ingrossa u servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut, anke onlajn, b'rabta ma' preparazzjonijiet iġjeniċi għall-bnedmin, kożmetiċi u preparazzjonijiet tat-twaletta mhux medikati, srievet għat-tindif tal-iġjene, srievet għat-tindif tal-iġjene femminili, tixus ifuħu, biċċiet tal-imsiħ li fihom preparazzjonijiet tat-tindif, biċċiet tal-imsiħ kożmetiċi mxarrbin minn qabel, biċċiet tad-drapp imxarrba b'deterġent għat-tindif; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-ingrossa u servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut, anke onlajn, b'rabta ma' prodotti tal-iġjene, prodotti tal-iġjene għall-mara, kontenituri għall-mestruwazzjoni, oġġetti assorbenti għall-iġjene personali, biċċiet tat-tindif imxarrbin b'diżinfettant għal skopijiet iġjeniċi, sapun diżinfettanti, sapun antibatteriku, sapun u deterġenti medikati u diżinfettanti; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-ingrossa u servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut, anke onlajn, b'rabta ma' prodotti iġjeniċi u tas-sbuħija għall-bnedmin, sapun diżinfettanti, sapun antibatteriku, sapun u deterġenti medikati u diżinfettanti, prodotti iġjeniċi u tas-sbuħija għall-bnedmin, ħwejjeġ, jiġifieri, ħwejjeġ ta' taħt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Detail- en groothandel, waaronder online, in hygiënische producten voor mensen, niet-medicinale cosmetische middelen en producten voor de toiletverzorging, hygiënische reinigingsdoekjes, reinigingsdoekjes voor hygiënisch gebruik voor vrouwen, geparfumeerde doekjes, doekjes met reinigingsmiddelen, voorbevochtigde cosmetische doekjes, doekjes, geïmpregneerd met detergentia voor het reinigen; Detail- en groothandel, waaronder online, in hygiënische producten, hygiënische producten voor vrouwen, menstruatiecups, absorberende artikelen voor de persoonlijke hygiëne, reinigingsdoekjes, geïmpregneerd met ontsmettingsmiddelen voor hygiënische doeleinden, desinfecterende zeep, antibacteriële zeep, medicinale en hygiënische zepen en detergentia; Detail- en groothandel, waaronder online, in hygiënische en schoonheidsinstrumenten voor mensen, desinfecterende zeep, antibacteriële zeep, medicinale en hygiënische zepen en detergentia, hygiënische en schoonheidsinstrumenten voor mensen, kledingstukken, te weten ondergoed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi handlu hurtowego i usługi handlu detalicznego, w tym online, w związku z towarami, takimi jak środki sanitarne dla ludzi, nielecznicze kosmetyki i preparaty toaletowe, chusteczki oczyszczające do higieny, chusteczki oczyszczające do higieny intymnej dla kobiet, bibułki perfumowane, chusteczki zawierające preparaty oczyszczające, nawilżane chusteczki kosmetyczne, ściereczki nasączane detergentami do czyszczenia; Usługi handlu hurtowego i usługi handlu detalicznego, w tym online, w związku z towarami, takimi jak produkty sanitarne, produkty higieniczne dla kobiet, kubeczki menstruacyjne, chłonne artykuły do higieny osobistej, oczyszczające ściereczki nasączone preparatem dezynfekcyjnym do celów higienicznych, mydło dezynfekujące, mydło antybakteryjne, mydła lecznicze i higieniczne i detergenty; Usługi handlu hurtowego i usługi handlu detalicznego, w tym online, w związku z towarami, takimi jak przyrządy higieniczne i kosmetyczne dla ludzi, mydło dezynfekujące, mydło antybakteryjne, mydła lecznicze i higieniczne i detergenty, przyrządy higieniczne i kosmetyczne dla ludzi, odzież, mianowicie bielizna.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, incluindo online, de produtos higiénicos para uso humano, preparações cosméticas e de higiene pessoal não medicinais, toalhetes de limpeza para a higiene, toalhetes de limpeza para a higiene feminina, toalhetes perfumados, toalhetes que incorporam produtos de limpeza, toalhetes cosméticos pré-humedecidos, panos de limpeza impregnados com detergente; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, incluindo online, de produtos higiénicos, produtos de higiene feminina, copos menstruais, artigos absorventes para higiene pessoal, panos de limpeza impregnados com desinfetantes para fins de higiene, sabão desinfetante, sabão antibacteriano, sabões e detergentes higiénicos e medicinais; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, incluindo online, de utensílios para os cuidados de higiene e beleza para uso humano, sabão desinfetante, sabão antibacteriano, sabões e detergentes higiénicos e medicinais, utensílios para os cuidados de higiene e beleza para uso humano, vestuário, especificamente roupa interior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de comerț cu ridicata și servicii de comerț cu amănuntul, inclusiv online, în legătură cu preparate igienice pentru oameni, cosmetice și preparate de toaletă nemedicamentoase, șervete de curățare igienice, șervețele pentru curățare utilizate pentru igiena intimă feminină, șervețele parfumate, șervețele impregnate cu preparate de curățare, șervețele cosmetice umezite în prealabil, lavete impregnate cu detergent pentru curățat; Servicii de comerț cu ridicata și servicii de comerț cu amănuntul, inclusiv online, în legătură cu produse de igienă, produse igienice pentru femei, cupe menstruale, articole absorbante pentru igiena personală, lavete de curățare impregnate cu produse dezinfectante de uz igienic, săpunuri dezinfectante, săpun antibacterian, săpunuri medicamentoase și de igienizare și detergenți; Servicii de comerț cu ridicata și servicii de comerț cu amănuntul, inclusiv online, în legătură cu instrumente de igienă și frumusețe pentru oameni, săpun dezinfectant, săpun antibacterian, săpunuri medicamentoase și de igienizare și detergenți, instrumente de igienă și frumusețe pentru oameni, îmbrăcăminte, și anume lenjerie de corp.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, vrátane online, so zameraním na hygienické prípravky pre ľudí, neliečivé kozmetické prípravky a toaletné prípravky, hygienické čistiace obrúsky, čistiace obrúsky na intímnu hygienu, parfumované obrúsky, utierky obsahujúce čistiace prípravky, vlhčené kozmetické utierky, tkaniny napustené čistiacim prípravkom na čistenie; Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, vrátane online, so zameraním na hygienické výrobky, výroky na intímnu hygienu, menštruačné kalíšky, absorpčné výrobky na osobnú hygienu, čistiace tkaniny napustené dezinfekčným prostriedkom na hygienické účely, dezinfekčné mydlá, antibakteriálne mydlá, liečivé a hygienické mydlá a detergenty; Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, vrátane online, so zameraním na hygienické a skrášľovacie potreby pre ľudí, dezinfekčné mydlá, antibakteriálne mydlá, liečivé a hygienické mydlá a detergenty, hygienické a skrášľovacie potreby pre ľudí, odevy, menovite spodnú bielizeň.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve veleprodaje in maloprodaje, tudi prek spleta, v zvezi z izdelki, kot so higienski izdelki za ljudi, kozmetični izdelki brez zdravilnih učinkovin in toaletni pripravki, brisače za higiensko čiščenje, brisače za higiensko čiščenje za ženske, parfumirani robčki, robčki, ki vsebujejo pripravke za čiščenje, vlažni kozmetični robčki, krpe, prepojene z detergentom za čiščenje; Storitve veleprodaje in maloprodaje, tudi prek spleta, v zvezi z izdelki, kot so higienski izdelki, higienski izdelki za ženske, menstrualne skodelice, vpojni izdelki za osebno higieno, krpe za čiščenje, prepojene z dezinfekcijskimi sredstvi za higienske namene, dezinfekcijsko milo, antibakterijsko milo, medicinska in higienska mila in detergenti; Storitve veleprodaje in maloprodaje, tudi prek spleta, v zvezi z izdelki, kot so higienski in lepotilni izdelki za ljudi, dezinfekcijsko milo, antibakterijsko milo, medicinska in higienska mila in detergenti, higienski in lepotilni izdelki za ljudi, oblačila, in sicer spodnje perilo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Grossist- och detaljhandelsförsäljning, inklusive online, av hygienpreparat för människor, icke medicinsk kosmetika och toalettartiklar, hygienrengöringsservetter, rengöringsservetter för kvinnohygien, parfymerade servetter, torkservetter innehållande rengöringsmedel, förfuktade sanitetsservetter, dukar impregnerade med tvättmedel för rengöring; Partihandelstjänster och detaljhandelsförsäljning, inklusive online, av hygienprodukter, hygieniska produkter för kvinnor, menskoppar, absorberande artiklar för personlig hygien, rengöringstrasor impregnerade med desinfektionsmedel för hygieniska ändamål, desinficerande tvål, antibakteriell tvål, medicinska och hygienisk tvål och rengöringsmedel; Partihandelstjänster och detaljhandelsförsäljning, inklusive online, avseende hygien- och skönhetsredskap för människor, desinficerande tvål, antibakteriell tvål, medicinska och hygienisk tvål och rengöringsmedel, hygienisk och skönhetsredskap för människor, kläder, nämligen, underkläder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/096</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081928</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>93931</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003129042</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-08-20</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Identity of marks and G&amp;S
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>GB</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>UK00003479870</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-07</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>UK00003479870</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-10</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>Allmatters</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>GB</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>UK00003479870</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-07</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>UK00003479870</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-10</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>Allmatters</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>51637</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
