<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-10T08:16:27</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228513</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228513</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-08</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-10</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>N&amp;U</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162457355</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/228/018228513/000162457355.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>24.17.97</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.14</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.21</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Лосиони за коса; Тоалетно мляко за почистване; Шампоани; Немедицински препарати за баня; Средства за измиване на лице [козметични]; Душ гелове и душ кремове; Ароматни етерични масла; Вани (Козметични препарати за -); Козметични маски; Козметични комплекти; Козметични средства; Кремове (Козметични -); Парфюмерия; Козметика за грижа за кожата; Лосиони за защита от слънцето; Крем против бръчки; Белила за кожа; Кремове за лице за козметична употреба; Крем против лунички; Козметика за деца.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vlasové vody; Čisticí mléko pro toaletní účely; Šampony; Koupelové přípravky, ne pro léčebné účely; Obličejové mycí přípravky; Tělové šampony; Aromatické esenciální oleje; Koupele (Kosmetické přípravky do -); Kosmetické masky; Kosmetické soupravy; Kosmetické přípravky; Kosmetické krémy; Parfémy; Kosmetické přípravky pro péči o pokožku; Přípravky na ochranu před sluncem; Krém proti vráskám; Krém pro bělení pokožky; Pleťové krémy; Krémy proti pihám; Kosmetické přípravky pro děti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Hårlotions; Rensemælk til toiletbrug; Shampoo; Badepræparater, ikke til medicinsk brug; Rensemidler til ansigtet [kosmetik]; Bodyshampoo; Aromatiske æteriske olier; Badepræparater, kosmetiske; Skønhedsmasker; Necessairer med kosmetik; Kosmetik; Kosmetiske cremer; Parfumer; Kosmetiske præparater til hudpleje; Solcremer; Antirynkecremer; Hudblegende cremer; Ansigtscremer til kosmetisk brug; Cremer mod fregner; Kosmetik til børn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Haarlotionen; Reinigungsmilch für Körper- und Schönheitspflege; Shampoos; Badezusätze, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Gesichtswaschmittel [Kosmetika]; Körpershampoos; Aromastoffe, pflanzliche [ätherische Öle]; Badezusätze, kosmetische; Kosmetische Masken; Kosmetiknecessaires [gefüllt]; Kosmetika; Kosmetische Hautcremes; Parfüms; Hautpflegemittel [kosmetisch]; Sonnenschutzmittel; Faltencremes; Bleichcreme für die Haut; Gesichtscremes für kosmetische Zwecke; Kosmetische Cremes gegen Sommersprossen; Kosmetika für Kinder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Λοσιόν για τα μαλλιά· Γαλακτώματα καλλυντικά· Σαμπουάν· Μη φαρμακευτικά παρασκευάσματα για το μπάνιο· Προϊόντα καθαρισμού προσώπου· Σαμπουάν σώματος· Αρωματικά αιθέρια έλαια· Λουτρό (Παρασκευάσματα καλλυντικά για το -)· Καλλυντικές μάσκες· Καλλυντικά σετ· Καλλυντικά· Κρέμες καλλυντικές· Αρωματισμού (Προϊόντα -)· Δέρματος (Καλλυντικά προϊόντα περιποίησης -)· Λοσιόν για μετά την ηλιοθεραπεία· Αντιρυτιδική κρέμα· Κρέμα για λεύκανση της επιδερμίδας· Κρέμα προσώπου· Κρέμες κατά των φακίδων· Παιδικά καλλυντικά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">hair lotions; cleansing milk for toilet purposes; shampoos; bath preparations, not for medical purposes; facial cleansers; body washes; aromatic essential oils; cosmetic preparations for baths; beauty masks; cosmetic kits; cosmetics; cosmetic creams; perfumes; cosmetic preparations for skin care; sunscreen preparations; anti-wrinkle creams; cream for whitening the skin; face creams; anti-freckle creams; cosmetics for children.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Lociones capilares; Leches limpiadoras de tocador; Champús; Preparaciones para el baño que no sean para uso médico; Limpiadores faciales; Geles para el cuerpo; Aceites esenciales aromáticos; Preparaciones cosméticas para el baño; Mascarillas de belleza; Neceseres de cosmética; Cosméticos; Cremas cosméticas; Perfumes; Productos cosméticos para el cuidado de la piel; Preparaciones con filtro solar; Cremas antiarrugas; Crema para aclarar la piel; Cremas faciales para uso cosmético; Cremas antipecas; Productos cosméticos para niños.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Juukseveed; Puhastuspiim [tualett-tarve]; Šampoonid; Vannipreparaadid, v.a meditsiinilised; Näopuhastusvahendid [kosmeetikatooted]; Dušigeelid; Aromaatsed eeterlikud õlid; Kosmeetilised vannipreparaadid; Kosmeetilised maskid; Kosmeetikakomplektid; Kosmeetikavahendid; Kosmeetilised kreemid; Parfüümid, lõhnaõlid; Nahahoolduskosmeetika; Päikesekaitsevahendid; Kortsudevastane kreem; Kosmeetilised nahapleegituskreemid; Kosmeetilised näokreemid; Tedretähnide vastased kreemid; Lastekosmeetika.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hiusvedet; Puhdistusemulsiot toalettitarkoituksiin; Shampoot; Kylpyvalmisteet (ei-lääkinnälliset); Kasvojenpesuaineet [kosmetiikka]; Vartalosampoot; Aromaattiset aineet [eteeriset öljyt]; Kylvyissä käytettävät kosmeettiset valmisteet; Kosmeettiset naamiot; Kosmetiikkapakkaukset; Kosmetiikka; Voiteet, kosmeettiset; Parfyymit; Ihonhoidossa käytettävät kosmeettiset valmisteet; Aurinkovoiteet; Ryppyvoiteet; Ihonvalkaisuvoiteet; Kasvovoiteet kosmeettiseen käyttöön; Pisamien peitevoiteet; Lasten kosmetiikka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Lotions capillaires; Laits de toilette; Shampooings; Préparations pour le bain, non à usage médical; Nettoyants pour le visage [cosmétiques]; Gels douche pour le corps; Huiles essentielles aromatiques; Préparations cosmétiques pour le bain; Masques cosmétiques; Nécessaires de produits de beauté; Cosmétiques; Crèmes cosmétiques; Parfums; Produits cosmétiques pour les soins de la peau; Produits antisolaires; Crèmes antirides; Crème pour blanchir la peau; Crèmes pour le visage à usage cosmétique; Crèmes contre les taches de rousseur; Produits cosmétiques pour enfants.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Losion za kosu; Toaletno mlijeko; Šamponi; Nemedicinski preparati za kupanje; Sredstva za čišćenje lica [kozmetika]; Šamponi za tijelo; Aromatična esencijalna ulja; Kozmetički pripravci za kupanje; Kozmetičke maske; Neseseri [torbe s kozmetičkim proizvodima]; Kozmetički proizvodi; Kreme za kozmetičke potrebe; Mirisi; Koža (kozmetički proizvodi za njegu kože); Losion za sunčanje; Krema protiv bora; Kreme za izbjeljivanje kože; Kreme za lice za kozmetičku uporabu; Kreme protiv pjega; Kozmetika za djecu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hajápoló folyadékok; Tisztító tejek kozmetikai használatra; Samponok; Nem gyógyhatású fürdőkészítmények; Arclemosók [kozmetikumok]; Tusfürdők; Aromatikus esszencia olajok; Kozmetikai készítmények fürdőkhöz; Kozmetikai maszkok; Kozmetikai készletek; Kozmetikai szerek; Kozmetikai krémek; Illatszer készítmények; Bőrápoló kozmetikumok; Naptejek; Ránctalanító krémek; Bőrfehérítő krémek; Arckrémek kozmetikai használatra; Szeplő elleni krémek; Gyermekkozmetikai cikkek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Lozioni per i capelli; Latte per la toilette; Shampoo; Preparati per il bagno, non per uso medico; Detergenti per il viso [per uso cosmetico]; Shampoo per il corpo; Oli essenziali aromatici; Preparati cosmetici per il bagno; Maschere cosmetiche; Nécessaires di cosmetica; Cosmetici; Creme cosmetiche; Profumo; Prodotti cosmetici per la cura della pelle; Preparati a schermo solare; Creme per le rughe; Creme per sbiancare la pelle; Creme per il viso per uso cosmetico; Creme contro le lentiggini; Cosmetici per bambini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Plaukų losjonai; Tualetinis pienelis; Šampūnai; Vonių preparatai (ne medicinos reikmėms); Veido prausikliai [kosmetiniai]; Kūno prausikliai; Aromatiniai eteriniai aliejai; Vonių kosmetiniai preparatai; Kosmetinės kaukės; Kosmetikos rinkiniai; Kosmetika; Kosmetiniai kremai; Parfumerijos gaminiai; Odos priežiūros kosmetiniai preparatai; Apsaugos nuo saulės preparatai; Kremai nuo raukšlių; Odos balinimo kremai; Veido kremai kosmetikos reikmėms; Kremai nuo pigmentinių dėmių; Vaikiška kosmetika.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Matu kopšanas līdzekļi; Attīroši pieniņi kosmētiskiem nolūkiem; Šampūni; Vannas līdzekļi nemedicīniskiem nolūkiem; Sejas mazgāšanas līdzekļi; Ķermeņa šampūni; Aromātiskās ēteriskās eļļas; Kosmētiskie līdzekļi vannām; Kosmētiskās maskas; Kosmētikas komplekti; Kosmētiskie līdzekļi; Kosmētiskie krēmi; Smaržas; Kosmētiskie līdzekļi ādas kopšanai; Sauļošanās losjoni; Pretgrumbu krēmi; Ādas balināšanas krēmi (kosmētiskie līdzekļi); Sejas krēmi kosmētiskiem nolūkiem; Krēmi pret vasarraibumiem; Bērnu kosmētika.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Lozjonijiet tax-xagħar; Ħalib kosmetiku; Xampù; Preparazzjonijiet għall-banju, mhux medikat; Aġenti tat-tindif għall-wiċċ [kosmetiċi]; Xampus għall-banju; Prodotti aromatiċi [żjut essenzjali]; Banju (Preparazzjonijiet kosmetiċi għall- -); Maskri kosmetiċi; Tagħmir kosmetiku; Kożmetiċi; Kosmetiċi (Kremi -); Prodotti ta' fwejjaħ; Kura tal-ġilda (Preparazzjonijiet kosmetiċi għall- -); Lozjonijiet għal wara li tieħdok ix-xemx; Kremi kontra t-tikmix; Kremi li jbajdu l-ġilda; Kremi għall-wiċċ għall-użu kosmetiku; Kremi għal kontra n-nemex; Kosmetiċi tat-tfal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Haarlotions; Melk voor de toiletverzorging; Shampoo; Badpreparaten, niet voor medisch gebruik; Gezichtsreinigingsmiddelen [cosmetica]; Shampoos voor het lichaam; Aromaten [vluchtige oliën]; Cosmetische preparaten voor het baden; Maskers (cosmetische); Cosmetica-sets [gevuld]; Cosmetica; Cosmetische crèmes; Parfums; Cosmetische producten voor de huidverzorging; Zonnebrandpreparaten; Antirimpelcrèmes; Crème voor het bleekmaken van de huid; Gezichtscrèmes voor cosmetisch gebruik; Anti-sproetencrème; Cosmetica voor kinderen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Płyny do pielęgnacji włosów; Mleczko oczyszczające do celów kosmetycznych; Szampony; Preparaty do kąpieli, nielecznicze; Płyny do mycia twarzy [kosmetyki]; Szampony do ciała; Aromatyczne olejki eteryczne; Preparaty kosmetyczne do kąpieli; Maski kosmetyczne; Zestawy kosmetyków; Kosmetyki; Kremy kosmetyczne; Produkty perfumeryjne; Kosmetyki do pielęgnacji skóry; Preparaty do ochrony przeciwsłonecznej; Krem przeciwzmarszczkowy; Kremy wybielające do skóry; Kremy do twarzy do użytku kosmetycznego; Kremy przeciw piegom; Kosmetyki dla dzieci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Loções capilares; Leite de limpeza para uso em toilette; Champôs; Preparações para o banho, não sendo para fins medicinais; Produtos para lavar o rosto [cosméticos]; Champôs para o corpo; Óleos aromáticos essenciais; Preparações cosméticas para o banho; Máscaras cosméticas; Estojos de cosmética; Cosméticos; Cremes cosméticos; Perfumes; Produtos cosméticos para os cuidados da pele; Preparações de proteção solar; Cremes antirrugas; Creme para branquear a pele; Cremes faciais para uso cosmético; Cremes antissardas; Prdutos cosméticos para crianças.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Loţiuni capilare; Lapte de curăţare de uz cosmetic; Şampoane; Preparate cosmetice pentru baie [nu de uz medical]; Produse cosmetice pentru spălarea feţei; Şampoane pentru corp; Uleiuri esenţiale aromatizate; Baie (Preparate cosmetice pentru -); Măşti de frumuseţe; Trusă pentru cosmetice; Cosmetice; Creme cosmetice; Parfumerie (Produse de -); Produse cosmetice pentru îngrijirea pielii; Produse de protecţie solară; Creme antirid; Albirea pielii (Cremă pentru -); Creme pentru faţă de uz cosmetic; Creme pentru pistrui; Cosmetice pentru copii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vlasové vody; Čistiace toaletné mlieka; Šampóny; Prípravky do kúpeľa (nie na lekárske použitie); Prípravky na čistenie tváre [kozmetika]; Telové šampóny; Aromatické látky [esenciálne oleje]; Kúpeľ (Kozmetické prípravky do -); Skrášľovacie masky (kozmetické prípravky); Kozmetické taštičky; Kozmetické prípravky; Kozmetické krémy; Voňavkárske výrobky; Kozmetické prípravky na starostlivosť o pleť; Ochranné prípravky na opaľovanie; Krémy proti vráskam; Bieliace krémy na pokožku; Krémy na tvár na kozmetické účely; Krémy proti pehám; Detská kozmetika.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Losjoni za lase; Čistilno mleko za toaletne namene; Šamponi; Pripravki za kopanje, ne za medicinske namene; Sredstva za umivanje obraza [kozmetična sredstva]; Šamponi za telo; Aromatična eterična olja; Kozmetični pripravki za kopanje; Kozmetične maske; Kozmetični neseserji; Kozmetični izdelki; Kozmetične kreme; Parfumerijski izdelki; Kozmetični izdelki za nego kože; Losjon za porjavitev na soncu; Krema proti gubam; Kreme za beljenje kože; Kreme za obraz za kozmetično uporabo; Kreme proti pegam; Kozmetična sredstva za otroke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hårlotioner; Rengöringsmjölk för toalettändamål; Schampon; Icke-medicinska badpreparat; Ansiktsrengöringsmedel; Kroppstvål; Aromatiska ämnen [flyktiga oljor]; Kosmetiska preparat för bad; Kosmetiska masker; Kosmetikasatser; Kosmetika; Kosmetiska krämer; Parfymerivaror; Kosmetiska preparat för hudvård; Sollotion; Antirynkkräm; Hudblekningskrämer; Ansiktskrämer för kosmetisk användning; Krämer mot fräknar; Barnkosmetika.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/101</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/173</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081987</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>956</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
