<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T09:40:13</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228498</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228498</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ULIFTUS</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Говорители; Зарядни устройства за коли; Кабели за предаване на данни; Слушалки; Стойки, пригодени за мобилни телефони; Калъфи, пригодени за мобилни телефони; Етернет кабели; Пръчици за селфи, използвани като аксесоари за смартфони; Слънчеви батерии; USB адаптори; Четци на USB карти; USB зарядни устройства; USB хъбове; Видеокабели; Безжични зареждащи устройства; Безжични слушалки; Безжични клавиатури; Безжични тонколони; Кабели за USB устройства; Портативни устройства за измерване на спортна активност; Високоговорителни системи; Слушалки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Reproduktory; Automobilové nabíječky; Kabely na přenos dat; Sluchátka; Držáky na mobilní telefony; Obaly na mobilní telefony; Ethernetové kabely; Teleskopické držáky na selfie používané jako příslušenství k chytrým telefonům; Solární baterie; USB adaptéry; Čtečky karet USB; USB nabíječky; USB huby; Video kabely; Bezdrátové nabíječky; Bezdrátová sluchátka; Bezdrátové klávesnice; Bezdrátové reproduktory; USB kabely; Monitorovací zařízení nošená na těle; Systémy reproduktorů; Sluchátka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Højttalere; Biloplader; Kabler til datatransmission; Høretelefoner; Holdere til mobiltelefoner; Etuier til mobiltelefoner; Ethernet-kabler; Selfiepinde til anvendelse som tilbehør til smartphones; Solbatterier; USB-adaptere; USB-kortlæsere; USB-opladere; USB-hubs; Videokabler; Trådløse opladere; Trådløse hovedtelefoner; Trådløse tastaturer; Trådløse højttalere; USB-kabler; Wearable aktivitetstrackere; Højttalerinstallationer; Hovedtelefoner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Lautsprecher; Autoladegeräte; Kabel für die Datenübertragung; Kopfhörer; Halterungen für Mobiltelefone; Etuis für Mobiltelefone; Ethernetkabel; Selfie-Stangen zur Verwendung als Zubehör für Smartphones; Sonnenbatterien; USB-Adapter; USB-Kartenlesegeräte; USB-Ladegeräte; USB-Hubs; Videokabel; Kabellose Ladegeräte; Kabellose Kopfhörer; Drahtlose Tastaturen; Kabellose Lautsprecher; USB-Kabel; Tragbare Activity Tracker; Lautsprecheranlagen; Kopfhörer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ηχεία· Φορτιστές αυτοκινήτου· Καλώδια μετάδοσης δεδομένων· Ακουστικά· Υποδοχές για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Θήκες για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Καλώδια ethernet· Πτυσσόμενα μπαστούνια κάμερας ως αξεσουάρ για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Συσσωρευτές ηλιακοί· Προσαρμογείς USB (ενιαίος σειριακός δίαυλος)· Αναγνώστες κάρτας USB· Φορτιστές καθολικού σειριακού αγωγού (USB)· Κόμβοι USB· Καλώδια βίντεο· Ασύρματοι φορτιστές· Ασύρματα ακουστικά· Ασύρματα πληκτρολόγια· Ασύρματα ηχεία· Καλώδια καθολικού σειριακού αγωγού (USB)· Φορετοί ανιχνευτές δραστηριότητας· Μεγαφωνικά συστήματα· Ακουστικά κεφαλής με μικρόφωνο.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Audio speakers; Car charger; Data cables; Earphones; Holders adapted for mobile phones; Mobile phone cases; Network cables; Selfie sticks; Solar batteries; USB adapters; USB card readers; USB chargers; USB hubs; Video cables; Wireless chargers; Wireless headphones; Wireless keyboards; Wireless speakers; USB cables; Wearable activity trackers; Loudspeaker systems; Headsets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Altavoces; Cargador de coches; Cables para la transmisión de datos; Auriculares intraurales; Soportes para teléfonos móviles; Estuches adaptados para teléfonos móviles; Cables Ethernet; Palos para selfies utilizados como accesorios de teléfonos inteligentes; Pilas solares; Adaptadores de USB; Lectores de tarjetas USB; Cargadores por USB; Hubs USB; Cables de vídeo; Cargadores inalámbricos; Cascos inalámbricos; Teclados inalámbricos; Altavoces inalámbricos; Cables USB; Monitores de actividad física ponibles; Sistema de altavoces; Cascos con micrófono.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kõlarid, valjuhääldid; Autolaadija; Andmeedastuskaablid; Kõrvaklapid; Mobiiltelefonide jaoks kohandatud hoidikud; Mobiiltelefonivutlarid; Ethernetijuhtmed; Selfipulgad nutitelefoni lisaseadmetena; Päikesepatareid; USB-adapterid; USB-kaardi lugejad; USB-laadurid; USB-jaoturid; Videokaablid; Juhtmeta laadurid; Juhtmeta kõrvaklapid; Juhtmeta klaviatuurid; Juhtmeta kõlarid; USB-kaablid; Kantavad aktiivsusmonitorid; Valjuhääldisüsteemid; Mikrofoniga kõrvaklapid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kaiuttimet; Autolaturit; Tiedonsiirtokaapelit; Kuulokkeet; Matkapuhelimen pitimet; Matkapuhelinkotelot; Ethernet-kaapelit; Selfietikut älypuhelinten lisälaitteina käytettäväksi; Aurinkoparistot; USB-sovittimet; USB-kortinlukijat; USB-laturit; USB-keskittimet; Videokaapelit; Langattomat laturit; Langattomat kuulokkeet; Langattomat näppäimistöt; Langattomat kaiuttimet; USB-kaapelit; Puettavat aktiivisuusmittarit; Kaiutinlaitteistot; Kuulokkeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Haut-parleurs; Chargeurs de voiture; Câbles de transmission de données; Casques d'écoute; Supports spéciaux pour téléphones portables; Étuis pour téléphones portables; Câbles Ethernet; Bâtonnets selfie utilisés comme accessoires de smartphone; Piles solaires; Adaptateurs USB; Lecteurs de cartes USB; Chargeurs USB; Concentrateurs USB; Câbles vidéo; Chargeurs sans fil; Ecouteurs sans fil; Claviers sans fil; Haut-parleurs sans fil; Câbles USB; Capteurs d'activité à porter sur soi; Haut-parleurs; Casques d'écoute.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Zvučnici; Punjač za automobile; Kablovi za prijenos podataka; Slušalice; Držači za mobilne telefone; Futrole prilagođene za mobilne telefone; Ethernet kablovi; Šipke za snimanje autoportreta (selfie) kao dodatna oprema za pametne telefone; Solarne baterije; USB adapteri; Čitači USB kartica; USB punjači; Koncentrator USB; Videokabel; Bežični punjači; Bežične slušalice; Bežične tipkovnice; Bežični zvučnici; USB kablovi; Uređaji za praćenje aktivnosti koji se nose; Sustavi zvučnika; Slušalice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hangszórók, hangosbemondók, megafonok; Autós töltők; Adatátviteli kábelek; Fejhallgatók; Mobiltelefonokhoz kialakított tartók; Mobiltelefonokhoz kialakított tokok; UTP hálózati kábelek; Okostelefonhoz használt szelfi botok; Napelemek, szolár akkumulátorok; USB adapterek; USB-kártya olvasók; USB-töltők; USB-hubok; Videokábelek; Vezeték nélküli töltők; Vezeték nélküli fejhallgatók; Vezeték nélküli billentyűzet; Vezeték nélküli hangszórók; USB kábelek; Viselhető aktivitásészlelők; Hangszóró rendszerek; Fejhallgatók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Altoparlanti; Caricatori da automobile; Cavi per trasmissione di dati; Auricolari; Supporti per telefoni cellulari; Custodie adattate per telefoni cellulari; Cavi Ethernet; Bastoni per gli autoscatti usati come accessori per smartphone; Pile solari; Adattatori USB; Lettori di schede USB; Caricatori USB; Concentratori USB; Cavi video; Caricatori senza filo; Cuffie senza fili; Tastiere senza filo; Altoparlanti senza fili; Cavi USB; Tracciatori di attività fisica indossabili; Sistemi di altoparlanti; Cuffie per la musica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Garsiakalbiai; Automobiliniai įkrovikliai; Duomenų perdavimo kabeliai; Ausinės; Laikikliai, pritaikyti mobiliesiems telefonams; Mobiliesiems telefonams pritaikyti dėklai; Eterneto kabeliai; Teleskopinės lazdos išmaniesiems telefonams; Saulės baterijos; USB adapteriai; USB kortelių skaitytuvai; USB įkrovikliai; USB šakotuvai; Vaizdo kabeliai; Belaidžiai įkrovikliai; Belaidės ausinės; Bevielės klaviatūros; Bevieliai garsiakalbiai; USB kabeliai; Dėvimieji fizinio aktyvumo įrašymo įrenginiai; Garsiakalbių sistemos; Ausinės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Skaļruņi; Automobiļu uzlādes ierīces; Datu pārraides kabeļi; Ieaušu austiņas; Mobilo telefonu turētāji; Mobilo tālruņu futrāļi; Ethernet kabeļi; Selfiju rokas statīvi (nūjas), ko lieto kā viedtālruņu piederumus; Saules baterijas; USB adapteri; USB karšu lasītāji; USB uzlādes ierīces; USB centrmezgli; Video kabeļi; Bezvadu uzlādes ierīces; Bezvadu austiņas; Bezvadu klaviatūras; Bezvadu skaļruņi; Universālo seriālo kopņu (USB) kabeļi; Valkājamas ierīces fiziskās aktivitātes izsekošanai; Skaļruņu sistēmas; Radioaustiņas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Lawdspikers; Ċarġer tal-karozza; Linji għat-trasmissjoni ta' data; Kuffji; Pokits adattati għal telefons ċellulari; Kaxxetti adattati għat-telefowns ċellulari; Kejbils tal-eternet; Stikek tal-istessu użati bħala aċċessorji għall-ismartfowns; Batteriji solari; Adatturi ta' l-USB; Tagħmir li jaqra l-kard USB; Ċarġers tal-USB; USB hubs; Kejbils tal-vidjo; Ċarġers mingħajr fili; Kuffji tar-radju jew tat-telefon għar-ras li huma mingħajr fil; Tastieri mingħajr fili; Spikers mingħajr fili; Kejbil tal-USB; Apparat li jirreġistra l-attività li jista' jinġarr; Sistemi ta' lawdspiker; Kuffji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Luidsprekers; Auto-opladers; Datatransmissiekabels; Oortelefoons; Houders voor mobiele telefoons; Hoesjes voor mobiele telefoons; Ethernetkabels; Selfiestokken als toebehoren voor smartphones; Zonnecellen; USB-adapters; USB-kaartlezers; Usb-laders; USB-hubs; Videokabels; Draadloze opladers; Draadloze hoofdtelefoons; Draadloze toetsenborden; Draadloze luidsprekers; USB kabels; Draagbare activiteitsmeters; Luidsprekersystemen; Hoofdtelefoons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Głośniki; Ładowarki samochodowe; Kable do transmisji danych; Słuchawki [douszne]; Uchwyty przystosowane do telefonów komórkowych; Futerały dopasowane do telefonów komórkowych; Kable wykorzystywane w sieci Ethernet; Kijki do robienia selfie jako akcesoria do smartfonów; Baterie słoneczne; Adaptery USB; Czytniki kart USB; Ładowarki USB; Huby USB; Kable wideo; Ładowarki bezprzewodowe; Słuchawki bezprzewodowe; Klawiatury bezprzewodowe; Głośniki bezprzewodowe; Kable USB; Przyrządy do śledzenia aktywności do noszenia na sobie; Systemy głośnikowe; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Altifalantes; Carregadores para automóveis; Cabos para a transmissão de dados; Auriculares; Suportes ajustados para telemóveis; Bolsas adaptadas para telemóveis; Cabos Ethernet; Braços extensíveis utilizados como acessórios para smartphones; Pilhas solares; Adaptadores USB; Leitores de cartões USB; Carregadores USB; Hubs USB; Cabos de vídeo; Carregadores sem fios; Auscultadores sem fios; Teclados sem fios; Altifalantes (colunas de som) sem fios; Cabos USB; Dispositivos de uso corporal para registo de atividade física; Sistemas de altifalantes; Auriculares.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Difuzoare; Încărcătoare pentru vehicule; Cabluri pentru transmisia de date; Căști auriculare; Suporturi adaptate pentru telefoane mobile; Etuiuri pentru telefoane mobile; Cabluri Ethernet; Suporturi pentru selfie, utilizate ca accesorii pentru telefoane inteligente; Baterii solare; Adaptoare USB; Dispozitive de citire de cartele USB; Încărcătoare USB; USB hub-uri; Cabluri video; Încărcătoare fără fir; Casti fara fir; Tastaturi fara fir; Boxe fara fir; Cabluri USB; Dispozitive portabile de urmărire a activității; Sisteme de difuzoare; Căști.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reproduktory, amplióny; Automobilové nabíjačky; Káble na prenos údajov; Slúchadlá; Držiaky na mobilné telefóny; Puzdrá na mobilné telefóny; Ethernet káble; Teleskopické držiaky na smartfóny; Solárne články; USB adaptéry; Čítačky na USB karty; USB nabíjačky; USB huby; Videokáble; Bezdrôtové nabíjačky; Bezdrôtové slúchadlá; Bezdrôtové klávesnice; Bezdrôtové reproduktory; USB káble; Zariadenia na sledovanie fyzickej aktivity nosené na tele; Reproduktorové systémy; Slúchadlá s mikrofónom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zvočniki; Polnilniki za avtomobile; Kabli za prenos podatkov; Slušalke; Držala, prilagojena za mobilne telefone; Etuiji za mobilne telefone; Ethernet kabli; Podaljšek za fotografiranje samoportretov za uporabo s pametnimi telefoni; Solarne baterije; Adapterji USB; Čitalniki kartic USB; USB polnilci; USB zvezdišča; Video kabli; Brezžični polnilniki; Brezžične slušalke; Brezžične tipkovnice; Brezžični zvočniki; USB kabli; Nosljive naprave za spremljanje aktivnosti; Sistemi zvočnikov; Slušalke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Högtalare; Billaddare; Kablar för dataöverföring; Hörlurar; Mobiltelefonhållare; Fodral anpassade för mobiltelefoner; Ethernetkablar; Selfiepinnar för användning som tillbehör till smartphones; Solbatterier; USB-adaptrar; USB-kortläsare; USB-laddare; USB-hubbar; Videokablar; Trådlösa laddare; Trådlösa hörlurar; Trådlösa tangentbord; Högtalare för trådlös användning; USB-kablar; Bärbara aktivitetsband; Högtalarsystem; Headsets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/080</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/151</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-11</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081946</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>71845</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
