<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-21T11:39:06</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228813</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228813</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-21</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="12" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-21</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>MIYOU YOUMI</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Противозаслепяващи очила; DVD плейъри; Очила за спорт; Ръкавици за защита от злополуки; Ръкавици за защита от рентгенови лъчи за промишлени цели; Очила; Защитни очила; Слънчеви очила; Касетофони; Комутатори; Компактдискове [аудио-видео]; Cd-rom; Електрически звънци за врати; Оптични стоки; Окуляри.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Antireflexní brýle; DVD přehrávače; Ochranné brýle pro sportovní účely; Ochranné rukavice (k ochraně před úrazy a nehodami); Ochranné rukavice proti rentgenovému záření pro použití v průmyslu; Brýle; Bezpečnostní brýle; Sluneční brýle; Kazetové přehrávače; Komutátory; Kompaktní disky [audio-video]; Kompaktní disky [CD ROM - pouze pro čtení]; Elektrické dveřní zvonky; Výrobky oční optiky; Okuláry.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Blændingsforhindrende briller; DVD afspillere; Sportsbriller; Handsker til beskyttelse mod ulykker; Handsker til industriel brug til beskyttelse mod røntgenstråler; Briller; Beskyttelsesbriller; Solbriller; Kassetteafspillere; Kommutatorer; Compactdisks [lyd/billede]; Compactdisks [hukommelseskredsløb]; Elektriske dørklokker; Optikervarer; Okularer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Blendschutzbrillen; DVD-Spieler, DVD-Player; Sportbrillen; Unfallschutzhandschuhe; Schutzhandschuhe gegen Röntgenstrahlen für gewerbliche Zwecke; Brillen; Korbbrille; Sonnenbrillen; Kassettenabspielgeräte; Stromwender; Compact-Disks [Ton, Bild]; Compact-Disks [ROM, Festspeicher]; Elektrische Türklingeln; Brillen und Kontaktlinsen; Okulare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αντιθαμβωτικά γυαλιά· Συσκευές αναπαραγωγής ψηφιακών βιντεοδίσκων· Γυαλιά προστατευτικά για αθλήματα· Γάντια για προστασία από ατυχήματα· Γάντια κατά των ακτίνων Χ βιομηχανικής χρήσης· Διόπτρες· Προστατευτικά γυαλιά· Γυαλιά ηλίου· Κασετόφωνα· Μεταγωγοί· Δίσκοι σύμπυκνοι [ήχου-βίντεο]· Σύμπυκνοι δίσκοι απλής ανάγνωσης (CD-ROM)· Κουδουνάκια για πόρτες ηλεκτρικά· Οπτικά είδη· Φακοί προσοφθάλμιοι.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Anti-glare glasses; DVD players; Goggles for sports; Gloves for protection against accidents; Gloves for protection against X-rays for industrial purposes; Spectacles; Goggles; Sunglasses; Cassette players; Commutators; Compact discs [audio-video]; Compact discs [read-only memory]; Electric door bells; Eyewear; Eyepieces.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Gafas antideslumbrantes; Lectores de DVD; Gafas de deporte; Guantes de protección contra accidentes; Guantes de protección contra los rayos X para uso industrial; Gafas [óptica]; Gafas protectoras; Gafas de sol; Lectores de casetes; Conmutadores; Discos compactos [audio y vídeo]; Discos ópticos compactos; Timbres de puerta eléctricos; Artículos de óptica para la vista; Oculares.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Pimestusvastased prillid; DVD-mängijad; Spordiprillid; Kaitsekindad; Tööstuslikud röntgenikiirgusvastased kindad; Prillid [optika]; Ohutusprillid; Päikeseprillid; Kassetimängijad; Kommutaatorid, ümberlülitid; Kompaktplaadid, laserplaadid, CD-d [audio-video]; Kompaktplaadid, CD-ROMid [püsimälu]; Elektrilised uksekellad; Optikakaubad; Okulaarid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Häikäisysuojalasit; DVD-soittimet; Suojalasit urheilemiseen; Käsineet suojaksi onnettomuuksilta; Käsineet suojaksi röntgensäteiltä teollisuuskäyttöön; Silmälasit; Turvasuojalasit; Aurinkolasit; Kasettisoittimet; Virrankääntimet; CD-levyt (Ääni- ja kuva -); CD-levyt [ROM]; Sähköiset ovikellot; Optikon tuotteet; Okulaarit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Lunettes antiéblouissantes; Lecteurs DVD; Lunettes de sport; Gants pour la protection contre les accidents; Gants de protection contre les rayons X à usage industriel; Lunettes [optique]; Lunettes de protection; Lunettes de soleil; Lecteurs de cassettes; Commutateurs; Disques compacts [audio-vidéo]; Disques optiques compacts; Sonnettes de portes, électriques; Articles de lunetterie; Oculaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Antireflekscijske naočale; DVD plejeri; Sportske zaštitne naočale; Zaštitne rukavice; Rukavice za zaštitu od X-zraka u industriji; Naočale; Zaštitne naočale; Sunčane naočale; Kazetofoni; Komutatori; Kompaktni diskovi [audio i video]; Kompaktni optički diskovi; Električna zvonca za vrata; Optički proizvodi; Okulari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vakításgátló szemüvegek; DVD-lejátszók; Védőszemüvegek sportoláshoz; Balesetek elleni védőkesztyűk; Röntgensugárzás elleni védőkesztyűk ipari célokra; Szemüvegek; Védőszemüvegek; Napszemüvegek; Magnók [kazetták lejátszásához]; Kommutátorok; Kompakt lemezek, CD-k [audio-video]; CD-ROM-ok; Elektromos ajtócsengők; Optikai cikkek; Szemlencsék, okulárok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Occhiali antiabbaglianti; Lettori dvd; Occhiali da sport; Guanti per la protezione contro gli infortuni; Guanti i protezione contro i raggi X per uso industriale; Occhiali [ottica]; Occhiali di protezione; Occhiali da sole; Lettori di cassette; Commutatori; Compact disc [audio-video]; Dischi ottici compatti; Campanelli elettrici per porte; Occhiali; Oculari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Akiniai nuo akinimo; DVD grotuvai; Apsauginiai sportiniai akiniai; Apsauginės pirštinės; Pirštinės nuo rentgeno spinduliuotės (gamyboje); Akiniai; Apsauginiai akiniai; Saulės akiniai; Kasetiniai (garsajuosčių ir vaizdajuosčių) leistuvai; Komutatoriai; Kompaktiniai diskai [audio- ir video-]; Kompaktiniai diskai [pastovioji atmintis]; Elektriniai durų skambučiai; Optikos prekės; Okuliarai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pretapžilbšanas brilles; Ciparvideodisku (DVD) atskaņotāji; Sporta brilles; Cimdi aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem; Cimdi aizsardzībai pret rentgena starojumu rūpnieciskiem nolūkiem; Brilles; Brilles acu aizsardzībai; Saulesbrilles; Kasešu atskaņotāji; Komutatori; Audio un video ierakstu kompaktdiski; Lasāmatmiņas kompaktdiski; Elektriskie durvju zvani; Optikas preces; Okulāri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Nuċċalijiet bi protezzjoni minn dawl qawwi; Plejers (DVD); Nuċċalijiet għall-isport; Ingwanti għall-protezzjoni kontra l-inċidenti; Ingwanti ta' protezzjoni kontra r-raġġi-X għal skopijiet industrijali; Nuċċalijiet; Nuċċalijiet protettivi; Nuċċalijiet tax-xemx; Apparat li jdoqq jew jirrekordja kasett; Kommutaturi; Diski kumpatti (awdjo-vidjo); CD-ROMs; Qniepen tal-bieb tal-elettriku; Prodotti tat-tobba li jieħdu ħsieb il-kura tal-għajnejn; Lenti ta' tromba, ta' teleskopju jew ta' mikroskopju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Antiverblindingsbrillen; Dvd-spelers; Sportbrillen; Handschoenen ter bescherming tegen ongevallen; Beschermende handschoenen tegen röntgenstralen, voor industrieel gebruik; Brillen [optiek]; Beschermende brillen; Zonnebrillen; Cassettespelers; Schakelaars; Compact discs [audio-video]; Cd-rom 's; Deurbellen, elektrisch; Eyewear; Oculairs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Okulary przeciwoślepieniowe; Odtwarzacze płyt DVD; Okulary ochronne do uprawiania sportu; Rękawice do ochrony przed wypadkami; Rękawice do ochrony przed promieniami rentgenowskimi do celów przemysłowych; Okulary; Okulary ochronne; Okulary przeciwsłoneczne; Odtwarzacze kaset; Komutatory; Płyty kompaktowe [audio-wideo]; Dyski kompaktowe [CD-ROM-y]; Elektryczne dzwonki do drzwi; Artykuły optyczne; Zestawy soczewek [wzierniki, okulary].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Óculos antirreflexo; Leitores de dvd; Óculos para desporto; Luvas para proteção contra acidentes; Luvas de proteção contra raios-x para uso industrial; Óculos [ótica]; Óculos de proteção; Óculos de sol; Leitores de cassetes; Comutadores; Discos compactos [áudio e vídeo]; Discos óticos compactos; Campainhas de porta, elétricas; Artigos de ótica; Oculares.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ochelari antireflex; DVD playere; Ochelari de protecție pentru sport; Mănuși de protecție împotriva accidentelor; Mănuși de uz industrial pentru protecție contra razelor X; Ochelari; Ochelari de protecție; Ochelari de soare; Dispozitive de redare pentru casete; Comutatoare; Discuri compacte [audio-video]; Discuri compacte cu lectură laser (CD-ROM-uri); Sonerii de ușă, electrice; Produse de optică; Oculare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Okuliare proti oslepeniu svetlom; DVD prehrávače; Okuliare na športovanie; Ochranné rukavice; Ochranné rukavice proti rtg. lúčom na priemyselné použitie; Okuliare; Bezpečnostné okuliare; Slnečné okuliare; Kazetové prehrávače; Komutátory; Audiovizuálne kompaktné disky; Optické kompaktné disky; Elektrické dverové zvončeky; Výrobky očnej optiky; Okuláre.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Očala proti bleščanju; DVD predvajalniki; Očala za šport; Rokavice za zaščito pred nesrečam; Rokavice za zaščito pred rentgenskimi žarki za industrijske namene; Očala; Zaščitni naočniki; Sončna očala; Predvajalniki kaset; Komutatorji; CD-ji [avdio-video]; CD-ROM-i; Električni hišni zvonci; Proizvodi za optiko; Okularji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bländskyddsglasögon; DVD spelare; Glasögon för sport; Handskar för skydd mot olyckor; Handskar för skydd mot röntgenstrålning för industriella ändamål; Glasögon; Skyddsglasögon; Solglasögon; Kassettdäck; Kommutatorer (el); CD-skivor [audio-video]; Kompaktskivor [rom]; Elektriska dörrklockor; Optikervaror; Okularlinser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Осветителни крушки; Лампи; Осветителни крушки; Лампени шишета; Глобуси за лампи; Електрически лампи; Държачи за абажури за лампи; Фенери за осветление; Електрически кухненски плотове за готвене; Пещи за печене на кафе; Електрически цедки за кафе; Електрически цедки за кафе; Електрически готварски принадлежности; Готварски печки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Žárovky; Svítidla; Elektrické žárovky; Skleněná stínidla do svítidel; Kulovitá stinidla do svítidel; Elektrické světelné zdroje (žárovky, zářivky); Kostry na stínidla lamp; Lucerny; Elektrické varné plotýnky; Zařízení na pražení kávy; Elektrické překapávače na kávu; Elektrické kávovary; Elektrické kuchyňské náčiní; Sporáky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Pærer til belysning; Lamper; Elektriske pærer; 'lampeglas; Lampekupler; Lamper, elektriske; Stel til lampeskærme; Lanterner til belysning; Elektriske kogeplader; Kafferistere; Elektriske kaffepercolatorer; Kaffemaskiner, elektriske; Elektriske redskaber til madlavning; Køkkenkomfurer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Glühbirnen für Beleuchtungszwecke; Beleuchtungslampen; Elektrische Glühbirnen; Lampengläser; Lampenkugeln; Elektrische Lampen; Lampenschirmhalter; Laternen; Elektrische Kochfelder; Kaffeeröstmaschinen; Elektrische Kaffeeperkolatoren; Elektrische Kaffeemaschinen; Elektrische Kochgeräte; Küchenherde.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Λαμπτήρες· Φωτισμός (λαμπτήρες -ού)· Λαμπτήρες· Αγωγοί λυχνιών· Λαμπτήρες λυχνιών· Ηλεκτρικές λυχνίες· Αμπαζουρ (Στήριγμα -)· Φανοί φωτισμού· Ηλεκτρικές κουζίνες· Καβουρδιστήρια για καφέ· Ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες· Ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες· Ηλεκτρικά σκεύη μαγειρέματος· Κουζίνες ηλεκτρικές.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Light bulbs; Lamps; Light bulbs, electric; Lamp glasses; Lamp globes; Electric lamps; Lampshade holders; Lanterns for lighting; Electric cooktops; Coffee roasters; Coffee percolators, electric; Coffee machines, electric; Cooking utensils, electric; Cooking stoves.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bombillas de iluminación; Lámparas [aparatos de iluminación]; Bombillas eléctricas; Cristales de lámparas; Globos de lámparas; Lámparas eléctricas; Portapantallas para lámparas; Faroles de alumbrado; Placas de cocción eléctricas; Torrefactores de café; Cafeteras de filtro eléctricas; Cafeteras eléctricas; Utensilios de cocción eléctricos; Cocinas [aparatos].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Lambipirnid; Lambid [valgustid]; Elektripirnid; Lambiklaasid; Lambikuplid; Elektrilambid; Lambivarjuhoidikud; Valgustuslaternad; Elektrilised pliidiplaadid; Kohviröstrid; Elektrilised kohviperkolaatorid; Elektrilised kohvimasinad, -aparaadid; Toiduainete elektrilised kuumtöötlusnõud; Köögipliidid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hehkulamput; Lamput; Hehkulamput; Lamppujen kuoret; Lampunkuvut; Sähkölamput; Lampunvarjostimen pitimet; Lyhdyt valaistukseen; Sähkökäyttöiset keittotasot; Kahvinpaahtimet; Kahvinkeittimet, sähkökäyttöiset; Kahvinkeittimet, sähkökäyttöiset; Keittovälineet, sähkökäyttöiset; Hellat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Ampoules d'éclairage; Lampes d'éclairage; Ampoules électriques; Verres de lampes; Globes de lampes; Lampes électriques; Porte-abat-jour; Lanternes d'éclairage; Plaques de cuisson électriques; Torréfacteurs à café; Percolateurs à café électriques; Cafetières électriques; Ustensiles de cuisson électriques; Cuisinières.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Rasvjetne žaruljice; Rasvjetne svjetiljke; Rasvjetne žaruljice; Cijevi [tuljci] za svjetiljke; Staklene kugle za svjetiljke; Električne svjetiljke; Stalci za sjenila; Rasvjetni fenjeri; Električne ploče za kuhanje; Kava (strojevi za prženje kave); Perkolatori [električni strojevi za kuhanje kave]; Perkolatori [električni strojevi za kuhanje kave]; Električni pribor za kuhanje; Štednjaci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Villanykörték; Lámpák; Villanykörték; Lámpaüvegek; Gömblámpák; Elektromos lámpák; Lámpaernyőtartó vázak; Lámpások világításra; Elektromos főzőlapok; Kávépörkölő készülékek; Elektromos kávéfőzők; Elektromos kávéfőzők; Elektromos főzőeszközök; Tűzhelyek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Lampadine per illuminazione; Lampade per illuminazione; Lampadine elettriche; Vetri per lampade; Globi per lampade; Lampade elettriche; Portaparalumi; Lanterne per illuminazione; Piastre elettriche; Apparecchi per tostare il caffè; Macchine da caffè elettriche; Caffettiere elettriche; Utensili per la cottura, elettrici; Cucine economiche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Apšvietimo lemputės; Lempos; Elektros lemputės; Lempų stiklai; Lempų stikliniai gaubtai; Elektros lempos; Lempų gaubtų laikikliai; Apšvietimo žibintai; Elektrinės kaitlentės; Kavos pupelių skrudintuvai; Elektriniai kavinukai su koštuvais; Elektriniai kavos aparatai; Elektriniai valgio virimo reikmenys; Viryklės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Spuldzes; Lampas; Elektriskās spuldzes; Spuldžu patronas; Spuldžu patronas; Elektriskās lampas un spuldzes; Abažūru turētāji; Lukturi apgaismošanai; Elektriskās plīts virsmas; Kafijas grauzdēšanas ierīces; Elektriskie kafijas perkulatori; Elektriskie kafijas perkolatori; Elektriskas ierīces ēdienu termiskai apstrādei; Plītis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Bozoz tad-dawl; Lampi; Bozoz tad-dawl; Ċumniji tal-lampi; Tubi tal-lampi; Sistemi għad-dawl elettriku; Ħowlders tal-paralumi; Fanali għad-dawl; Partijiet ta' fuq tal-fran elettriċi; Inkaljaturi tal-kafe; Perkolaturi tal-kafè tal-elettriku; Perkolaturi tal-kafè tal-elettriku; Reċipjenti tat-tisjir tal-elettriku; Kukers u fran kombinati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Gloeilampen; Lampen voor verlichting; Elektrische gloeilampen; Glazen voor lampen; Afschermballons voor lampen; Elektrische lampen; Lampenkaphouders; Lantaarns voor verlichting; Elektrische keukenfornuizen; Koffiebranders; Koffiezetapparaten, elektrisch; Koffiemachines, elektrisch; Kookgerei, elektrisch; Fornuizen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Żarówki oświetleniowe; Lampy oświetleniowe; Żarówki oświetleniowe; Klosze do lamp [kominki]; Kuliste klosze do lamp; Lampy elektryczne; Stelaże do abażurów; Latarnie oświetleniowe; Elektryczne płyty kuchenne; Urządzenia do palenia kawy; Elektryczne zaparzacze do kawy; Elektryczne zaparzacze do kawy; Kuchenny (Sprzęt -) elektryczny; Kuchenki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Lâmpadas de iluminação; Lâmpadas; Lâmpadas de iluminação, elétricas; Vidros de candeeiros; Globos de candeeiros; Lâmpadas elétricas; Suporte para abat-jour; Lanternas de iluminação; Placas elétricas para cozinhar; Torrefadores para café; Percoladores para café elétricos; Cafeteiras elétricas; Utensílios de cozinha elétricos; Fogões de cozinha.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Becuri de iluminat; Lămpi de iluminat; Becuri de iluminat; Sticle de lampă; Globuri de lămpi; Lămpi electrice; Abajururi (Suporturi de -); Lanterne de iluminat; Plăci de gătit electrice; Aparate pentru prăjit cafea; Percolatoare electrice de cafea; Percolatoare electrice de cafea; Ustensile de gătit electrice; Mașini de gătit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Žiarovky; Lampy; Elektrické žiarovky; Cylindre; Lampové banky; Elektrické lampy; Objímky na tienidlá; Lampáše; Elektrické varné dosky; Zariadenia na praženie kávy; Elektrické filtračné alebo extrakčné kávovary; Elektrické kávovary; Elektrické kuchynské potreby na prípravu jedál; Sporáky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Žarnice za razsvetljavo; Svetilke; Žarnice za razsvetljavo; Steklene cevi za luči; Steklene krogle za luči; Električne svetilke; Podstavki za senčnike svetilk; Lanterne za razsvetljavo; Električne kuhalne površine; Stroji za praženje kave; Električni strojčki za kuhanje kave; Električni strojčki za kuhanje kave; Električni pripomočki za kuhanje; Kuhalniki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Glödlampor; Lampor; Glödlampor, elektriska; Lampglas; Lampkupor; Elektriska lampor; Lampskärmshållare; Lanternor för belysning; Elektriska spishällar; Kafferostare; Kaffeperkulatorer, elektriska; Kaffemaskiner, elektriska; Elektriska kokredskap; Köksspisar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<SeniorityDetails>
<Seniority>
<SeniorityCountryCode>GB</SeniorityCountryCode>
<SeniorityApplicationNumber>UK00003341923</SeniorityApplicationNumber>
<SeniorityFilingDate>2018-09-28</SeniorityFilingDate>
<SeniorityRegistrationNumber>UK00003341923</SeniorityRegistrationNumber>
<SeniorityRegistrationDate>2018-12-21</SeniorityRegistrationDate>
<InternationalTradeMarkCode>EU</InternationalTradeMarkCode>
<SeniorityPartialIndicator>false</SeniorityPartialIndicator>
<SeniorityStatusCode>Accepted</SeniorityStatusCode>
</Seniority>
</SeniorityDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/081</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-30</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081986</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>69891</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017927644</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>95836</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-05-27</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018372436</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>69891</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-20</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
