<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-04T08:48:09</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228817</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228817</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-10-30</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>nl</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-11-04</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>VELYON</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>4</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Свещи; Ароматни свещи.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Svíčky; Parfémované svíčky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kærter; Parfumerede lys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kerzen; Duftkerzen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κεριά· Αρωματικά κεριά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Candles; Perfumed candles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Velas [iluminación]; Velas perfumadas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Küünlad; Lõhnaküünlad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kynttilät; Tuoksukynttilät.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bougies [éclairage]; Bougies parfumées.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Svijeće; Mirisne svijeće.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Gyertyák; Illatosított gyertyák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Candele; Candele profumate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Žvakės; Kvepiančios žvakės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Sveces; Sveces (aromatizētas).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Xemgħat; Xemgħat imfewħa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kaarsen; geurkaarsen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Świece; Świece zapachowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Velas, candeias, círios [iluminação]; Velas perfumadas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Lumânări; Lumânări parfumate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Sviečky (na svietenie); Parfumované sviečky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Sveče; Parfumirane sveče.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Ljus; Parfymerade ljus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>8</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Прибори за гасрономията; Ръчно задвижвани инструменти и сечива; Ножарски изделия; Хладни оръжия; Бръсначи.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Jídelní příbory; Ruční nástroje a ruční nářadí; Nožířské výrobky; Bodné a sečné zbraně; Holicí strojky, elektrické i neelektrické.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Bestik til brug i restauranter; Håndværktøj og -redskaber [håndbetjente]; Spisebestik; Sidevåben andre end skydevåben; Barbermaskiner og -knive.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gastronomiebestecke; Handbetätigte Werkzeuge und Geräte; Messerschmiedewaren; Hieb- und Stichwaffen; Rasierapparate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μαχαιροπίρουνα για τον τομέα της γαστρονομίας· Εργαλεία χειρός και οργανα (χειροκίνητα)· Μαχαιροποιίας είδη· Αιχμηρά όπλα· Ξυράφια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Table cutlery; Hand tools and implements [hand-operated]; Cutlery; Side arms, other than firearms; Razors.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cubiertos para gastronomía; Herramientas e instrumentos de mano accionados manualmente; Artículos de cuchillería; Armas blancas; Maquinillas de afeitar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Söögiriistad toitlustusasutustele; Käsitsi käitatavad tööriistad ja vahendid; Söögiriistad (noad, kahvlid, lusikad); Vööl kantavad külmrelvad; Habemenoad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ravintola-aterimet; Käsityökalut ja -välineet; Ruokailuvälineet (aterimet); Sivuaseet; Parranajovälineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Couverts de restauration; Outils et instruments à main entraînés manuellement; Coutellerie; Armes blanches; Rasoirs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pribor za jelo; Ručni alati i oprema [ručno pokretani]; Nožarski proizvodi [pribor za jelo]; Ručno oružje; Britve.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Gasztronómiai étkészletek; Kézzel működtetett kéziszerszámok és eszközök; Evőeszközök; Vágó- és szúrófegyverek; Borotvák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Posate per gastronomia; Utensili e strumenti azionati manualmente; Coltelleria; Armi bianche; Rasoi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Gastronomijos srities įrankiai; Rankiniai įrankiai ir padargai (rankinio valdymo); Peiliai, šakutės ir šaukštai; Ginklai, nešiojami prie diržo (išskyrus šaunamuosius); Skustuvai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Gastronomijas jomas piederumi; Rokas darbarīki un ierīces (ar roku darbināmas); Galda naži, dakšiņas un karotes; Pie jostas nēsājami ieroči, izņemot šaujamieročus; Skuvekļi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pożati għall-gastronomija; Għodda tal-idejn u implimenti (imħaddma bl-idejn); Pożati; Armi tal-ġenb, minbarra armi tan-nar; Magni tal-leħja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Bestek; Handgereedschappen en -instrumenten, met de hand te bedienen; messenmakerswaren, vorken en lepels; blanke wapens; scheerapparaten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Sztućce do gastronomi; Narzędzia i przyrządy ręczne (ręcznie obsługiwane); Sztućce; Broń biała [boczna]; Brzytwy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Talheres; Ferramentas e instrumentos manuais (operados manualmente); Cutelaria; Armas brancas; Lâminas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Tacâmuri destinate gastronomiei; Unelte de mână și instrumente acționate manual; Cuțite, furculițe și linguri; Arme purtate lateral; Lame de ras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Gastronomické príbory; Ručné nástroje a ručné náradia; Nožiarsky tovar; Bodné a sečné zbrane; Britvy, holiace strojčeky (elektrické aj neelektrické).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Gostinski pribor; Ročno orodje in oprema (ročno upravljano); Jedilni pribor; Hladno orožje; Brivniki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Gastronomibestick; Handverktyg och instrument, handmanövrerade; Bestick; Sidovapen, inte skjutvapen; Rakhyvlar och -apparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Осветителни апарати; Уреди за осветление, отопление, парогенериране, готвене, охлаждане, сушене, вентилация, водоснабдяване и за санитарни цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přístroje na osvětlení; Přístroje pro osvětlení, topení, výrobu páry, pro vaření, přístroje chladicí, pro sušení, ventilaci, rozvod vody a sanitární zařízení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Belysningsapparater; Apparater til belysning, opvarmning, dampdannelse, madlavning, køling, tørring, ventilation og vandforsyning, samt til sanitære formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Beleuchtungsgeräte; Beleuchtungs-, Heizungs-, Dampferzeugungs-, Koch-, Kühl-, Trocken-, Lüftungs- und Wasserleitungsgeräte sowie sanitäre Anlagen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μονάδες φωτισμού· Συσκευές και συστήματα φωτισμού, θέρμανσης, παραγωγής ατμού, μαγειρέματος, ψύξης, αποξήρανσης, αερισμού, υδροδότησης και εγκαταστάσεις υγειϊνής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Lighting apparatus; Apparatus for lighting, heating, steam generating, cooking, refrigerating, drying, ventilating, water supply and sanitary purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de iluminación; Aparatos de alumbrado, calefacción, producción de vapor, cocción, refrigeración, secado, ventilación y distribución de agua, así como instalaciones sanitarias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Valgustusaparaadid; Valgustus-, kütteseadmed, aurugeneraatorid, toiduainete kuumtöötlusseadmed, jahutusseadmed, kuivatus-, ventilatsiooni-, veevarustus- ja sanitaarseadmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Valaisinlaitteet; Valaistus-, lämmitys-, höyrynkehitys-, keitto-, jäähdytys-, kuivatus-, ilmastointi-, vesihuolto- ja saniteettilaitteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils d'éclairage; Appareils d'éclairage, de chauffage, de production de vapeur, de cuisson, de réfrigération, de séchage, de ventilation, de distribution d'eau et installations sanitaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Rasvjetni uređaji; Uređaji za rasvjetu, grijanje, proizvodnju pare, kuhanje, hlađenje, sušenje, ventilaciju, vodoopskrbu i sanitarna oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Világítókészülékek; Világító-, fűtő-, gőzfejlesztő, főző-, hűtő-, szárító-, szellőztető-, vízszolgáltató és egészségügyi berendezések.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi per illuminazione; Apparecchi di illuminazione, di riscaldamento, di produzione di vapore, di cottura, di refrigerazione, di essiccamento, di ventilazione, di distribuzione d'acqua e impianti sanitari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Apšvietimo aparatai; Apšvietimo, šildymo, garų gamybos, valgio virimo, šaldymo, džiovinimo, vėdinimo, vandens tiekimo ir sanitariniai įrenginiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apgaismes ķermeņi; Apgaismošanas, apsildes, tvaika ražošanas, ēdiena termiskās apstrādes, dzesēšanas, žāvēšanas, vēdināšanas, ūdensapgādes un sanitārtehniskās ierīces un aparāti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat għat-tidwil; Apparat li jagħti d-dawl, li jsaħħan, li jiġġenera l-fwar, li jsajjar, li jkessaħ, li jnixxef, li jagħti ventilazzjoni, li jipprovdi l-ilma u għal użu sanitarju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verlichting; Verlichtings-, verwarmings-, stoomopwekkings-, kook-, koel-, droog-, ventilatie- en waterleidingsapparaten en sanitaire installaties.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia oświetleniowe; Urządzenia do oświetlania, ogrzewania, wytwarzania pary, gotowania, chłodzenia, suszenia, wentylacji, zaopatrzenia w wodę oraz instalacje sanitarne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos de iluminação; Aparelhos de iluminação, de aquecimento, de produção de vapor, de cozedura, de refrigeração, de secagem, de ventilação, de distribuição de água e instalações sanitárias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate de iluminat; Aparate de iluminat, de incălzit, de producere a vaporilor, de coacere, de refrigerare, de uscare, de ventilare, de distribuire a apei şi instalaţii sanitare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Osvetľovacie prístroje; Zariadenia na osvetľovanie, vykurovanie, parné kotly, zariadenia na varenie, chladenie a sušenie, vetracie, vodárenské a sanitárne zariadenia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Aparati za razsvetljavo; Naprave za osvetljevanje, ogrevanje, proizvodnjo pare, kuhanje, hlajenje, sušenje, prezračevanje, vodovodne in sanitarne instalacije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Apparater för belysning; Apparater för belysning, uppvärmning, ångalstring, kokning, kylning, torkning, ventilation, vattenförsörjning och sanitära ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Плакати; Печатни произведения и изделия; Кутии за съхранение на класьори и фотографии; Хартия, картон; Печатни произведения; Книговезки материали; Фотографии [отпечатани]; Несесери за принадлежности за писане [канцеларски]; Лепила за канцеларски цели и домашна употреба; Материали за художници; Четки за рисуване; Пишещи машини и канцеларско оборудване (с изключение на мебели); Учебни материали [с изключение на апарати]; Пластмасови материали за опаковки (които не са включени в други класове); Печатарски букви; Клишета.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Plakáty; Tiskárenské výrobky; Úložné krabice pro složky a fotografie; Papír, lepenka; Tiskoviny; Potřeby pro vazbu knih; Fotografie [tištěné]; Pouzdra na psací potřeby [papírnické zboží]; Klovatina (lepidlo) pro kancelářské potřeby nebo pro domácnost; Potřeby pro umělce; Štětce; Psací stroje a kancelářské potřeby (vyjímaje nábytek); Učební pomůcky [s výjimkou zařízení]; Plastické obaly (nezařazené do jiných tříd); Tiskařské typy; Štočky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Plakat; Trykkeprodukter; Opbevaringsbokse til akter og fotografier; Papir, pap; Tryksager; Materialer til bogbinding; Fotografier [trykte]; Skrivemapper [kontorartikler]; Gummi [klæbemiddel] til papirvarer og til husholdningsbrug; Materialer til brug for kunstnere; Penselpenne; Skrivemaskiner og kontorartikler (dog ikke møbler); Undervisningsmateriale [undtagen apparater]; Plasticmateriale til emballeringsbrug (ikke indeholdt i andre klasser); Tryktyper; Klichéer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Plakat; Druckereierzeugnisse; Aufbewahrungskisten für Akten und Fotografien; Papier, Pappe; Druckereierzeugnisse; Buchbindeartikel; Fotografien [Abzüge]; Schreibmappen [Papeteriewaren]; Klebstoffe für Papier- und Schreibwaren oder für Haushaltszwecke; Künstlerbedarfsartikel; Pinselstifte; Schreibmaschinen und Büroartikel (ausgenommen Möbel); Lehr- und Unterrichtsmittel [ausgenommen Apparate]; Verpackungsmaterial aus Kunststoff, so weit es nicht in anderen Klassen enthalten ist; Drucktypen; Druckstöcke [Klischees].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αφίσες· Έντυπο υλικό· Κουτιά φύλαξης για ντοσιέ και φωτογραφίες· Χαρτί, χαρτόνι· Έντυπο υλικό· Υλικά βιβλιοδεσίας· Φωτογραφίες [εκτυπωμένες]· Θήκες γραφής [χαρτικά]· Κολλητικές ύλες για γραφική ύλη ή για οικιακούς σκοπούς· Υλικά για καλλιτέχνες· Μαρκαδόροι γραφής· Γραφομηχανές και είδη γραφείου (εκτός των επίπλων)· Υλικό διδασκαλίας και εκπαίδευσης (εκτός συσκευών)· Πλαστικά υλικά συσκευασίας (μη περιλαμβανόμενα σε άλλες κλάσεις)· Τυπογραφικά (- στοιχεία)· Στερεότυπα τυπογραφίας (κλισέ).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Posters; Printed material; Storage boxes for photos and files; Paper, cardboard; Printed matter; Bookbinding material; Photographs [printed]; Writing cases [stationery]; Gums [adhesives] for stationery or household purposes; Artists' materials; Brush pens; Typewriters and office requisites (except furniture); Teaching materials [except apparatus]; Plastic materials for packaging (not included in other classes); Printing type; Printing blocks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Carteles; Productos de imprenta; Cajas de almacenamiento para archivos y fotografías; Papel, cartón; Material impreso; Material de encuadernación; Fotografías [impresas]; Recados de escribir; Gomas [colas] de papelería o para uso doméstico; Material para artistas; Rotuladores con punta de pincel; Máquinas de escribir y artículos de oficina (excepto muebles); Material de instrucción, excepto aparatos; Materias plásticas para embalar (no comprendidas en otras clases); Caracteres de imprenta; Clichés de imprenta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Plakatid; Trükised; Dokumendimappide ja fotode säilituskastid; Paber, papp, kartong; Trükitooted; Raamatuköitematerjalid; Trükitud fotod; Kirjatarvete karbid; Kummiliimid kantseleis või majapidamises kasutamiseks; Kunstnikutarbed; Marker-pintslid (pintsli varres oleva värviga pintslid); Kirjutusmasinad ja kantseleitarbed (v.a mööbel); Õppematerjalid, v.a seadmed; Plastist pakkematerjal, mis ei kuulu teistesse klassidesse; Trükitüübid; Klišeed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Julisteet; Painantaan liittyvät tuotteet; Kansioiden ja valokuvien säilytyslaatikot; Paperi, pahvi; Painotuotteet; Kirjansidontatarvikkeet; Valokuvat [painetut]; Kirjoitusvälinekotelot; Liimat toimisto- ja kotitalouskäyttöön; Taiteilijantarvikkeet; Kynäsiveltimet; Kirjoituskoneet ja toimistotarvikkeet (paitsi huonekalut); Neuvonta- ja opetusmateriaali [paitsi laitteet]; Muoviset pakkaustarvikkeet (jotka eivät sisälly muihin luokkiin); Kirjasimet; Painolaatat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Affiches; Produit de l'imprimerie; Boîtes de rangement pour dossiers et photographies; Papier, carton; Produits de l'imprimerie; Articles pour reliures; Photographies [imprimées]; Nécessaires pour écrire [papeterie]; Gommes [colles] pour la papeterie ou le ménage; Matériel pour artistes; Marqueurs pinceaux; Machines à écrire et articles de bureau (à l'exception des meubles); Matériel d'instruction à l'exception des appareils; Matières plastiques pour l'emballage (non comprises dans d'autres classes); Caractères d'imprimerie; Clichés d'imprimerie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Plakati [posteri]; Tiskarski proizvodi; Kutije za spremanje spisa i fotografija; Papir, karton; Tiskani materijali; Materijali za uvezivanje knjiga; Fotografije [tiskane]; Poslovne mape [uredski materijal]; Ljepila za papirnate proizvode ili kućanske potrebe; Oprema za umjetnike; Olovke s četkicom; Pisaći strojevi i uredski pribor (osim namještaja); Materijal za obuku (osim uređaja); Plastični materijali za ambalažu (koji nisu obuhvaćeni drugim razredima); Slova [tiskarska slova]; Tiskarski klišeji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Plakát; Nyomdaipari termékek; Tároló dobozok mappák és fényképek számára; Papír, karton; Nyomtatványok; Könyvkötészeti cikkek; Fényképek [nyomtatott]; Írókészletek [papíráruk]; Ragasztók irodai és otthoni célokra; Anyagok művészek részére; Ecsettollak; Írógépek és irodai cikkek (bútorok kivételével); Tanítási és oktatási anyagok [kivéve készülékek, berendezések]; Csomagolásra szolgáló műanyagok (amelyek nem tartoznak más osztályokba); Nyomdai betűk; Klisék, nyomódúcok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Manifesti; Materiale stampato; Classificatori e scatole per l'archiviazione di fotografie; Carta, cartone; Stampati; Articoli per rilegature; Fotografie [stampate]; Astucci portapenne [cartoleria]; Adesivi per la cartoleria o per uso domestico; Materiale per artisti; Pennarelli; Macchine da scrivere e articoli per ufficio (esclusi i mobili); Materiale per l'insegnamento esclusi gli apparecchi; Materie plastiche per l'imballaggio (non comprese in altre classi); Caratteri da stampa; Clichés per la tipografia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Plakatas; Spaudiniai; Rinkmenų ir nuotraukų saugojimo dėžutės; Popierius, kartonas; Spaudiniai; Knygų viršelių medžiagos; Fotonuotraukos [spausdintos]; Rašymo reikmeninės [raštinės reikmenys]; Augaliniai klijai (raštinės ar buities reikmėms); Dailininkų reikmenys; Teptukiniai rašikliai; Rašomosios mašinėlės ir biuro reikmenys (išskyrus baldus); Mokymo medžiaga [išskyrus aparatūrą]; Plastikinės pakavimo medžiagos (nepriskirtos prie kitų klasių); Šriftas [poligrafija]; Klišės [poligrafija].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Plakāti; Iespiedmateriāli; Failu un fotoattēlu uzglabāšanas kastes; Papīrs, kartons; Iespiedprodukcija; Grāmatu iesiešanas materiāli; Iespiesti fotoattēli; Piezīmju blociņi (kancelejas preces); Sveķi (līmvielas) kancelejas un mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Materiāli māksliniekiem; Otas; Rakstāmmašīnas un kancelejas preces (izņemot mēbeles); Mācību un uzskates līdzekļi (izņemot aparatūru); Sintētiskie iesaiņojuma materiāli (kas nav ietverti citās klasēs); Tipogrāfijas burti; Klišejas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kartellun; Materjal stampat; Kaxxi għall-ħażna għal fajls u ritratti; Karti, kartunċin; Materjal stampat; Materjal għall-legatura tal-kotba; Ritratti [stampati]; Kaxxetti għal strumenti tal-kitba [kartolerija]; Adeżivi għal skopijiet ta' kartolerija jew domestiku; Materjali tal-artisti; Pniezel taż-żebgħa; Tajprajters u oġġetti neċessarji għall-uffiċċju (minbarra għamara); Materjal istruttiv u għat-tagħlim (minbarra apparat); Materjali tal-plastik għall-ippakkjar (mhux inklużi fi klassijiet oħra); Tipa tal-istampar; Inċiżjonijiet tal-istampar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Posters; gedrukte materialen; opbergdozen voor dossiers en foto's; Papier, karton; drukwerken; boekbinderswaren; foto's; schrijfbehoeften; kleefstoffen voor kantoorgebruik of voor de huishouding; materiaal voor kunstenaars; penselen; schrijfmachines en kantoorartikelen (uitgezonderd meubelen); leermiddelen en onderwijsmateriaal (uitgezonderd toestellen); plastic materialen voor verpakking, voor zover niet begrepen in andere klassen; drukletters; clichés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Plakaty; Druki; Pudełka do przechowywania akt i zdjęć; Papier, karton; Materiały drukowane; Materiały do introligatorstwa; Fotografie [wydrukowane]; Teczki z notatnikiem i przyborami do pisania [artykuły papiernicze]; Kleje do materiałów papierniczych lub do użytku domowego; Materiały przeznaczone dla artystów; Pisaki z końcówką pędzelkową; Maszyny do pisania i sprzęt biurowy (z wyjątkiem mebli); Materiały szkoleniowe i instruktażowe (z wyjątkiem aparatów); Materiały z tworzyw sztucznych do pakowania (nie ujęte w innych klasach); Czcionki drukarskie; Matryce do druku ręcznego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Letreiros; Materiais de impressão; Caixas de armazenamento para dossiers e fotografias; Papel, cartão; Material impresso; Materiais para encadernações; Fotografias impressas; Estojos para escrita [papelaria]; Adesivos para papelaria ou uso doméstico; Materiais para artistas; Canetas pincel; Máquinas de escrever e artigos de escritório (com excepção de móveis); Material de ensino [com exceção dos aparelhos]; Matérias plásticas para embalagem (não incluídas noutras classes); Carateres de tipografia; Clichés de tipografia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Afişe; Produse de imprimerie; Cutii de depozitare pentru dosare și fotografii; Hârtie, carton; Produse de imprimerie; Articole de legătorie; Fotografii imprimate; Mape pentru scris [papetărie]; Adezivi; Materiale pentru artiști plastici; Stilouri pensulă; Maşini de scris şi articole de birou (cu excepţia mobilelor); Material didactic (cu excepția aparatelor); Materiale plastice pentru ambalaj (necuprinse în alte clase); Caractere [cifre și litere]; Clișee tipografice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Plagáty; Tlačoviny; Dózy na ukladanie spisov a fotografií; Papier, kartón; Tlačoviny; Knihárske potreby; Fotografie (tlačoviny); Písacie súpravy (papiernický tovar); Lepiace gumy na kancelárske použitie alebo pre domácnosť; Potreby pre umelcov; Perá s tenkým štetcom; Písacie stroje a kancelárske potreby okrem nábytku; Vyučovacie pomôcky okrem prístrojov a zariadení; Obalové materiály z plastických hmôt, ktoré nie sú zahrnuté v iných triedach; Typy, tlačové písmo; Tlačiarenské štočky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Plakati; Tiskarski izdelki; Škatle za shranjevanje dokumentov in fotografij; Papir, karton; Tiskovine; Knjigovezni materiali; Fotografije [tiskane]; Peresnice za pisala [pisalne potrebščine]; Lepila za pisarniške in gospodinjske namene; Potrebščine za umetnike; Čopiči; Pisalni stroji in pisarniški pribor (razen pohištva); Material za učenje ali poučevanje (razen aparatov); Zavijalni materiali iz umetnih snovi (ki jih ne obsegajo drugi razredi); Tiskarske črke; Klišeji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Affisch; Trycksaker; Förvaringslådor för mappar och fotografier; Papper, papp, kartong; Trycksaker; Bokbinderimaterial; Fotografier [tryckta]; Skrivportföljer [kontorsmaterial]; Gummi [bindemedel] för kontors- eller hushållsändamål; Konstnärsmaterial; Penselpennor; Skrivmaskiner och kontorsförnödenheter (ej möbler); Undervisningsmaterial [inte apparater]; Plastmaterial för emballering (ej ingående i andra klasser); Trycktyper; Klichéer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>18</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Необработени кожи; Животински кожи с косъм; Кожа и имитация на кожа; Куфари и пътни чанти; Чадъри, слънчобрани и бастуни; Камшици, хамути и сарашки стоки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zvířecí kůže; Zvířecí kůže/usně; Kůže a imitace kůže; Kufry a cestovní tašky; Deštníky, slunečníky (velké) a vycházkové hole; Biče, jezdecké postroje a sedla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Skind; Dyrehuder; Læder og læderimitationer; Kufferter og rejsetasker; Paraplyer, paraplyer og parasoller (store) og spadserestokke; Piske, seletøj og sadelmagervarer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Tierhäute; Felle; Leder und Lederimitationen; Reise- und Handkoffer; Regenschirme, Sonnenschirme und Spazierstöcke; Peitschen, Pferdegeschirre und Sattlerwaren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δέρματα· Δέρματα ζώων· Δέρμα και απομιμήσεις δέρματος· Κιβώτια [μπαούλα] και βαλίτσες ταξιδίου· Ομπρέλες, αλεξήλια και ράβδοι περιπάτου· Μαστίγια, ιπποσκευές και είδη σελοποιίας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Animal skins; Animal skins; Leather and imitations of leather; Trunks and suitcases; Umbrellas, big umbrellas and walking sticks; Whips, harness and saddlery.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pieles de animales; Pelajes de animales; Cuero e imitaciones de cuero; Baúles y maletas; Paraguas, sombrillas (grandes) y bastones; Fustas y artículos de guarnicionería.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Loomanahad; Loomanahad; Nahk ja kunstnahk; Reisikohvrid; Päikesevarjud, vihmavarjud (suured) ja jalutuskepid; Piitsad, hobuseriistad ja sadulsepatooted.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Eläinten nahat; Eläinten nahat; Nahat ja nahan jäljitelmät; Matka-arkut ja -laukut; Sateenvarjot, päivänvarjot ja kävelykepit; Piiskat, valjaat ja satulavarusteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Peaux d'animaux; Fourrures; Cuir et imitations cuir; Malles et valises; Parapluies, parasols et cannes; Fouets et sellerie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Životinjske kože pripremljene za izradu krznarskih proizvoda; Životinjske kože; Koža i umjetna koža; Kovčezi i putne torbe; Kišobrani, suncobrani i štapovi za hodanje; Bičevi, hamovi i sedlarski proizvodi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Állatbőrök és irhák; Állatbőrök; Bőrök és műbőrök; Utazótáskák és bőröndök; Esernyők, napernyők és sétapálcák; Ostorok, hámok, nyergek és lószerszámok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pelli d'animali; Peli degli animali; Pelle e finta pelle; Bauli e valigie; Ombrelli, ombrelloni e bastoni da passeggio; Fruste e articoli di selleria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Gyvulių odos; Gyvūnų odos; Oda ir dirbtinė oda; Lagaminai, kelioniniai krepšiai; Skėčiai, (saulės) skėčiai ir lazdelės; Rimbai, botagai, pakinktai ir balnojimo reikmenys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Dzīvnieku ādas; Dzīvnieku ādas; Āda un ādas imitācijas; Ceļasomas un čemodāni; Lietussargi, saulessargi (lieli) un spieķi; Pātagas, zirglietas un seglinieku izstrādājumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ġlud ta' annimali; Ġlud tal-annimali; Ġilda u imitazzjoni tal-ġilda; Bagolli [bagalji]; Umbrelel, parasols (kbar) u kejns; Frosti, xedd ta' żiemel jew ta' bhima oħra u oġġetti tas-sarrâġ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Dierenhuiden; dierenvachten; leder en kunstleder; reiskoffers en koffers; paraplu's, parasols en wandelstokken; zwepen en zadelmakerswaren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Skóry zwierzęce; Futra zwierzęce; Skóra i imitacja skóry; Kufry i walizki; Parasolki, parasole (duże) i laski; Bicze, uprzęże i wyroby rymarskie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Peles de animais; Peles de animais; Couro e imitação de couro; Malas e maletas de viagem; Chapéus-de-chuva, chapéus-de-sol e bengalas; Chicotes e selaria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Piei de animale; Blănuri de animale; Piele sau imitație de piele; Cufere și geamantane; Umbrele, umbrele de soare si bastoane; Bice şi articole de şelărie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zvieracie kože; Zvieracia srsť; Koža a imitácie kože; Cestovné kufre; Dáždniky a vychádzkové palice; Biče, postroje a sedlárske výrobky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Živalske kože; Živalsko krzno; Usnje in imitacije usnja; Veliki potovalni kovčki in potovalne torbe; Dežniki, veliki sončniki in sprehajalne palice; Biči, konjska zaprega in sedlarski izdelki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Djurhudar; Djurpälsar; Läder och läderimitationer; Koffertar och resväskor; Paraplyer, parasoller och promenadkäppar; Piskor, seldon och sadelmakerivaror.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>20</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Мебели; Oгледала (посребрено стъкло); Поставки за списания; Кутии за съхранение; Стойки за дрехи; Дъски за стена; Кошове; Рамки за фотографии; Мебели, огледала, рамки за картини, стоки, които не са включени в други класове от дърво, корк, тръстика, камъш, ракита, рог, кост, слонова кост, китова кост, раковина, кехлибар, седеф, морска пяна и заместители за тях или от пластмаса.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nábytek; Zrcadla; Stojany na časopisy; Úložné krabice; Stojany na šaty; Nástěnné police; Košíky; Rámečky na fotografie; Nábytek, zrcadla, rámy, výrobky nejmenované v jiných třídách ze dřeva, korku, rákosu, vrbového proutí, z rohu, kosti, slonoviny, z kostic, želvoviny, jantaru, perleti, mořské pěny, náhražky všech těchto materiálů nebo náhražky z plastických hmot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Møbler; Spejle (forsølvet glas); Tidsskrifthylder; Bokse til opbevaring; Tøjstandere; Vægkanter; Kurve; Fotorammer; Møbler, spejle, billedrammer, varer (ikke indeholdt i andre klasser) af træ, kork, rør, spanskrør, kurveflet, horn, ben, elfenben, fiskeben, skaller, rav, perlemor, merskum samt af erstatningsstoffer herfor eller af plastic.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Möbel; Spiegel [versilbertes Glas]; Zeitschriftenständer; Aufbewahrungsboxen; Kleiderständer; Wandborde; Körbe; Fotorahmen; Möbel, Spiegel, Bilderrahmen, Waren (soweit sie nicht in anderen Klassen enthalten sind) aus Holz, Kork, Rohr, Binsen, Weide, Horn, Knochen, Elfenbein, Fischbein, Schildpatt, Bernstein, Perlmutter, Meerschaum und deren Ersatzstoffen oder aus Kunststoffen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Έπιπλα· Καθρέπτες (επαργυρωμένο γυαλί)· Ράφια για περιοδικά· Κουτιά φύλαξης· Κρεμάστρες (καλόγεροι)· Επίτοιχα ερμάρια· Καλάθια· Πλαίσια φωτογραφιών· Έπιπλα, καθρέφτες, πλαίσια (κορνίζες), είδη μη περιλαμβανόμενα σε άλλες κλάσεις από ξύλο, φελλό, καλάμι, βρύουλα, λυγαριά, κέρατο, κόκκαλο, ελεφαντοστό, κόκκαλο φάλαινας, ταρταρούγα, ήλεκτρο, μαργαριτάρι, σηπιόλιθο και υποκατάστατα των παραπάνω υλικών, ή από πλαστικό.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Furniture; Mirrors (silvered glass); Magazine stands; Storage tins; Clothes stands; Wall racks; Baskets; Photograph frames; Furniture, mirrors, picture frames, goods not included in other classes, of wood, cork, reed, cane, wicker, horn, bone, ivory, whalebone, shell, amber, mother of pearl, meerschaum, and substitutes for, or plastic.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Muebles; Espejos (vidrio argentado); Revisteros; Cajas de almacenamiento; Colgadores de ropa; Estantes murales; Cestas; Marcos para fotografías; Muebles, espejos, marcos de cuadros, productos que no se incluyan en otras clases de madera, corcho, caña, junco, mimbre, cuerno, hueso, marfil, ballena, concha, ámbar, nácar, espuma de mar, sucedáneos de todas estas materias o materias plásticas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Mööbel; Peeglid (hõbetatud klaas); Ajakirjaalused, ajakirjahoidlid; Ladustuskastid või -karbid; Riidevarnad; Seinariiulid; Korvid; Fotoraamid; Puidust, korgist, roost, bambusest, vitstest, sarvest, luust, elevandiluust, vaalaluust, kilpkonnakilbist, merevaigust, pärlmutrist, sepioliidist ning kõigi nende materjalide aseainetest või plastist valmistatud mööbel, peeglid ja raamid, mis ei kuulu teistesse klassidesse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Huonekalut; Peilit (hopeoitu lasi); Lehtitelineet; Säilytyslaatikot; Vaaterekit; Seinähyllyt; Korit; Valokuvakehykset; Huonekalut, peilit, taulunkehykset, puusta, korkista, ruo'osta, rottingista, pajusta, sarvesta, luusta, norsunluusta, valaanluusta, simpukasta, meripihkasta, helmiäisestä, merenvahasta ja kaikkien näiden aineiden korvikkeista tai muovista tehdyt tavarat, jotka eivät sisälly muihin luokkiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Meubles; Miroirs (verre argenté); Range revues; Boîtes de rangement; Portemanteaux; Étagères murales; Paniers; Cadres pour photographies; Meubles, miroirs, cadres, produits non compris dans d'autres classes, en bois, liège, roseau, jonc, osier, corne, os, ivoire, fanon de baleine, écaille, ambre, nacre, écume de mer et succédanés de toutes ces matières ou en matières plastiques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Namještaj; Ogledala (posrebreno staklo); Stalci za časopise; Spremnici; Stalci za odjeću; Zidne police; Košare; Okviri za fotografije; Namještaj, ogledala, okviri, od drva, pluta, trske, rogoza, šiblja, rožine, kosti, bjelokosti, usovine, kornjačevine, jantara, sedefa, stive i zamjena za sve te materijale ili proizvodi od plastike, koji nisu obuhvaćeni drugim razredima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Bútorok; Tükrök (ezüstözött üveg); Folyóirattartók; Tárolódobozok; Ruhaállványok, ruhafogasok; Fali táblák; Kosarak; Fényképkeretek; Bútorok, tükrök, képkeretek, fából, parafából, nádból, bambusznádból, fűzfavesszőből, szaruból, csontból, elefántcsontból, halcsontból, kagylóhéjból, borostyánból, gyöngyházból, habkőből és mindezek pótanyagaiból vagy műanyagból készült, más osztályokba nem tartozó termékek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Mobilia; Specchi (vetro argentato); Porta-riviste; Scatole per riporre oggetti; Appendiabiti; Mensole a muro; Cestini; Cornici per fotografie; Mobili, specchi, cornici, articoli non compresi in altre classi in legno, sughero, canna, giunco, vimini, corno, osso, avorio, balena, tartaruga, ambra, madreperla, spuma di mare, succedanei di tutte queste materie o in materie plastiche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Baldai; Veidrodžiai; Žurnalų padėklai; Daiktų laikymo dėžutės; Drabužių stovai; Sieniniai bortai; Pintinės; Nuotraukų rėmeliai; Baldai, veidrodžiai, paveikslų rėmai, medžio, kamščio, meldų, nendrių, gluosnių, rago, kaulo, dramblio kaulo, banginio ūsų, vėžlio šarvo, kriauklių, gintaro, jūros putų dirbiniai, šių medžiagų pakaitalų arba plastikų gaminiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mēbeles; Spoguļi; Žurnālu plaukti; Uzglabāšanas kastes; Stieņi apģērbu pakarināšanai; Dēļu plaukti; Grozi; Fotogrāfiju rāmji; Mēbeles, spoguļi, attēlu rāmji, preces, kas nav iekļautas citās klasēs, proti, koka, korķa, niedru, meldru, klūgu, raga, kaula, ziloņkaula, vaļa ragvielas, gliemežvāku, dzintara, perlamutra, jūras putu izstrādājumi, kā arī preces, kas ir izgatavotas no šo materiālu aizstājējiem vai plastmasas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Għamara; Mirja (silvered glass); Xtilliera għall-magazines; Kaxxi għall-preservazzjoni; Stends tal-ħwejjeġ; Xkafef ta' mal-ħajt; Qfief; Gwarniċi għar-ritratti; Għamara, mirja, inkwatri, oġġetti mhux inklużi fi Klassijiet oħra, tal-injam, sufra, qasab, qasab tal-bambù, qasab tal-bxiekel, qrun, għadam, avorju, għadam tal-balena, arzell, ambra, madreperla, meerschaum, u sostituti tagħhom, jew tal-plastik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Meubelen; spiegels; tijdschriftenrekken; opbergdozen; kledingrekken; wandrekken; manden; fotolijsten; meubelen, spiegels, en lijsten van hout, kurk, riet, bies, teen, hoorn, been, ivoor, balein, schildpad, barnsteen, parelmoer, meerschuim, vervangingsmiddelen van al deze stoffen of van plastic vervaardigde producten voor zover niet begrepen in andere klassen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Meble; Lustra (srebrzone szkło); Czasopisma (stojaki na -); Pudełka do przechowywania rzeczy; Wieszaki stojące do ubrań; Półki ścienne; Koszyki; Ramki do zdjęć; Meble, lustra, ramki obrazów, towary nieujęte w innych klasach, z drewna, korka, trzciny, wikliny, rogu, kości, kości słoniowej, fiszbinu, muszli, bursztynu, macicy perłowej, sepiolitu, imitacji tych surowców lub z tworzyw sztucznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Mobiliário; Espelhos (vidro prateado); Porta revistas; Caixas de armazenamento; Cabideiro; Prateleiras de parede; Cestos; Molduras para fotografias; Mobiliário, espelhos, molduras, produtos (não incluídos noutras classes) em madeira, cortiça, cana, junco, vime, chifre, osso, marfim, baleia, tartaruga, âmbar, madrepérola, espuma de mar, sucedâneos de todas estas matérias ou em matérias plásticas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Piese de mobilier; Oglinzi (sticlă argintată); Suporturi de reviste; Cutii de depozitare; Suporturi pentru haine; Plăci de perete; Coşuri; Rame pentru fotografii; Mobile, oglinzi, rame, produse (necuprinse în alte clase) din lemn, plută, trestie, stuf, răchită, corn, os, fildeş, fanoane de balenă, solz, ambră, sidef, spumă de mare, înlocuitori ai tuturor acestor materiale sau din materiale plastice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nábytok; Zrkadlá; Stojany na časopisy; Krabice na uskladňovanie predmetov; Stojany na šaty; Nástenné police; Koše; Rámiky na fotografie; Nábytok, rámy na obrazy, výrobky, nezahrnuté v iných triedach, z dreva, korku, tŕstia, ratanu, prútia, rohoviny, kosti, slonoviny, veľrybích kostíc, korytnačiny, jantáru, perlete, sépiolitu a náhrad týchto materiálov alebo plastov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pohištvo; Ogledala (posrebreno steklo); Stojala za revije; Škatle za shranjevanje; Stojala za obleke; Stenske police; Košare; Okvirji za fotografije; Pohištvo, ogledala, okviri za slike, izdelki, ki jih ne obsegajo drugi razredi, iz lesa, plute, trsa, rogoza, vrbovega protja, roževine, kosti, slonovine, ribje kosti, želvovine, jantarja, biserne matice, morske pene, nadomestkov vseh teh snovi ali iz umetnih snovi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Möbler; Speglar (försilvrat glas); Tidningshyllor; Förvaringsboxar; Klädställ; Vägghyllor; Korgar; Fotoramar; Möbler, speglar, tavelramar, varor ej ingående i andra klasser av trä, kork, vass, rotting, vidjor, horn, ben, elfenben, valfiskben, snäckskal, bärnsten, pärlemor, sjöskum eller av ersättningar för dessa material, eller av plast.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Саксии; Светилници, не от благороден метал; Ветроупорни фенери (поставки за чаени свещи); Подноси за икономи; Сервизи за хранене; Домакински или кухненски прибори и съдове; Гребени и гъби; Четки; Материали за изработване на четки; Изделия за почистване; Домакинска тел за почистване на замърсени повърхности; Необработено или полуобработено стъкло (с изключение на стъкло, използвано в строителството); Стъклария, порцеланови и керамични изделия, които не са включени в други класове.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Květináče; Svícny; Svícny (svícny na čajové svíčky); Odkládací stolky; Stolní náčiní; Pomůcky a nádoby pro domácnost a kuchyň; Hřebeny a mycí houby; Kartáče; Materiály na výrobu kartáčů; Čisticí a úklidové potřeby; Skelná vata; Sklo surové nebo opracované (s výjimkou stavebního skla); Sklo, porcelán a majolika neobsažené v jiných třídách.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Urtepotter; Kandelabre [lysestager]; Fyrfadslys (holdere til fyrfadslys); Bakkeborde [serveringsbakker på ben]; Bordservice; Husholdnings- og køkkenredskaber samt beholdere; Kamme og svampe; Børster; Børstenbindermaterialer; Rengøringsartikler; Ståluld; Uforarbejdet eller halvforarbejdet glas (undtagen glas til bygningsbrug); Glasvarer, porcelæn og keramik, ikke indeholdt i andre klasser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Blumentöpfe; Leuchter; Windlichter (Teelichthalter); Serviertabletts; Geschirr; Geräte und Behälter für Haushalt und Küche; Kämme und Schwämme; Bürsten; Bürstenmachermaterial; Putzgeräte und Putzzeug; Stahlwolle; Rohes oder teilweise bearbeitetes Glas (mit Ausnahme von Bauglas); Glaswaren, Porzellan und Steingut, so weit sie nicht in anderen Klassen enthalten sind.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Γλάστρες· Κηροπήγια [μονά κηροπήγια]· Φαναράκια (βάσεις για ρεσό)· Δίσκοι για αρχιυπηρέτες (μπάτλερ)· Επιτραπέζια σκεύη· Μικρά σκεύη και δοχεία οικιακής και μαγειρικής χρήσης· Χτένια και σφουγγάρια· Βούρτσες· Υλικά κατασκευής βουρτσών· Είδη καθαρισμού· Σύρμα καθαρισμού· Ακατέργαστο ή ημικατεργασμένο γυαλί (εκτός της οικοδομικής υάλου)· Είδη υαλουργίας, πορσελάνη και φαγεντιανά μη περιλαμβανόμενα σε άλλες κλάσεις.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Flower pots; Candlesticks; Hurricane lamps (tea light holders); Butlers' trays; Dinnerware; Household or kitchen utensils and containers; Combs and sponges; Brushes; Material for brush-making; Cleaning articles; Steelwool; Unworked or semi-worked glass (except glass used in building); Glassware, porcelain and earthenware not included in other classes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Macetas [tiestos]; Candeleros; Velas (soportes para velas); Mesa bandeja; Servicios de mesa; Utensilios y recipientes para uso doméstico y culinario; Peines y esponjas; Cepillos; Materiales para fabricar cepillos; Artículos de limpieza; Viruta de acero; Vidrio en bruto o semielaborado (excepto el vidrio de construcción); Artículos de cristalería, porcelana y loza no comprendidos en otras clases.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Lillepotid; Küünlajalad; Teeküünlad (teeküünlahoidikud); Serveerimislauad; Lauanõud; Maja- ja köögitarbed ning mahutid; Kammid ja käsnad; Harjad; Harjamaterjal; Puhastustarbed; Terasvill; Töötlemata või pooltöödeldud klaas (v.a ehitusklaas); Klaas-, portselan- ja savinõud, mis ei kuulu teistesse klassidesse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kukkaruukut; Kynttilänjalat; Lyhdyt (lämpökynttilöiden pidikkeet); Hovimestarin tarjottimet; Pöytäastiat; Talous- ja keittiövälineet ja -astiat; Kammat ja pesusienet; Harjat; Harjanvalmistusaineet; Puhdistusvälineet; Teräsvilla; Raakalasi ja lasi puolivalmisteena (paitsi rakennuslasi); Lasitavarat, posliini ja keramiikka, jotka eivät sisälly muihin luokkiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Pots à fleurs; Chandeliers; Photophores (supports pour bougies chauffe-plat); Plateaux à usage domestique; Vaisselle; Ustensiles et récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine; Peignes et éponges; Brosses; Matériaux pour la brosserie; Articles de nettoyage; Paille de fer; Verre brut ou mi-ouvré (à l'exception du verre de construction); Verrerie, porcelaine et faïence non comprises dans d'autres classes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Lončanice za cvijeće; Svijećnjaci; Svijeće u posudi (držači za dušice); Pladnjevi sa nožicama; Stolno posuđe; Pribor i posuđe za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju; Češljevi i spužve; Četke; Materijali za četke; Artikli za čišćenje; Čelična vuna; Sirovo ili poluobrađeno staklo (osim građevinskog stakla); Stakleni proizvodi, porculansko i keramičko posuđe koje nije obuhvaćeno drugim razredima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Virágcserepek; Gyertyatartók; Viharlámpák (mécsestartók); Felszolgáló asztalok [lábas tálcák]; Evőeszközök; Eszközök, edények és tartályok háztartási és konyhai célokra; Fésűk és szivacsok; Kefék; Kefegyártáshoz használt anyagok; Tisztítóeszközök; Acélgyapot; Nyers vagy félig megmunkált üveg (kivéve az építéshez használt üveget); Üveg-, porcelán- és fajanszáruk, amelyek nem tartoznak más osztályokba.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Vasi da fiori; Candelieri; Lanterne (portacandele); Vassoi da maggiordomo; Servizi da tavola; Utensili e recipienti per uso domestico o di cucina; Pettini e spugne; Spazzole; Materiali per spazzole; Articoli per la pulizia; Lana d'acciaio; Vetro grezzo o semilavorato (eccetto il vetro da costruzione); Vetreria, porcellana e maiolica non comprese in altre classi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vazonai; Kandeliabrai; Vėjo žibintai (arbatos lempučių laikikliai); Padėklai ant stovų; Stalo reikmenys; Namų apyvokos arba virtuvės reikmenys ir indai; Šukos ir kempinės; Šepečiai; Šepečių medžiagos; Valymo reikmenys; Plieniniai šveistukai; Neapdirbtas arba iš dalies apdirbtas stiklas (išskyrus statybinį); Stiklo, porceliano ir keramikos gaminiai, nepriskirti prie kitų klasių.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Puķu podi; Kandelabri (svečturi); Vējlukturi (tējas svecīšu turētāji); Galdiņi-paplātes; Ēdamtrauki un galda piederumi; Mājturības un virtuves piederumi, ierīces, tilpnes un trauki; Ķemmes un sūkļi; Sukas; Materiāli suku izstrādājumiem; Tīrīšanas un apkopšanas rīki un ierīces; Metāla sūkļi; Neapstrādāts vai daļēji apstrādāts stikls (izņemot stiklu celtniecības vajadzībām); Izstrādājumi no stikla, porcelāna, fajansa un keramikas, kas nav ietverti citās klasēs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Qsari; Gandlieri; Mtieħen tar-riħ (ħowlders tax-xemgħat ċatti għat-tisħin tal-ikel); Gabarrejiet tal-maġġordomi; Oġġetti li jintużaw għal fuq il-mejda; Għodda jew reċipjenti u kontenituri għad-dar u għall-kċina; Pettnijiet u sponoż; Pniezel; Materjali biex tagħmel l-ixkupilji u l-pniezel; Oġġetti għat-tindif; Barraxa tal-azzar għat-tindif u l-għerik; Ħġieġ mhux maħdum jew parzjalment maħdum (minbarra ħġieġ użat fil-bini); Oġġetti tal-ħġieġ, porċellana u oġġetti tal-fuħħar mhux inklużi fi klassijiet oħra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Plantenbakken; kaarshouders; windlichten (waxinelichthouders); dienbladen; servies; gerei en vaatwerk voor de huishouding of de keuken; kammen en sponzen; borstels (uitgezonderd penselen); materialen voor de borstelfabricage; reinigingsmateriaal; staalwol; ruw of halfbewerkt glas (uitgezonderd glas voor bouwdoeleinden); glas-, porselein- en aardewerk voor zover niet begrepen in andere klassen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Doniczki na kwiaty; Świeczniki; Świeczki (pojemniki na świeczki); Tace z uchwytami, na składanych nóżkach; Zastawa stołowa; Przybory oraz pojemniki kuchenne i gospodarstwa domowego; Grzebienie i gąbki; Szczotki; Materiały do wyrobu szczotek i pędzli; Sprzęt i artykuły do sprzątania i czyszczenia; Wełna stalowa; Nieprzetworzone lub półprzetworzone szkło (z wyjątkiem szkła stosowanego w budownictwie); Wyroby szklane, porcelanowe i ceramiczne nie ujęte w innych klasach.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vasos para flores; Candelabros [castiçais]; Lanternas (suportes de velas); Mesas tabuleiro; Talheres; Utensílios e recipientes para uso doméstico e na cozinha; Pentes e esponjas; Escovas; Materiais para o fabrico de escovas; Artigos de limpeza; Palha de aço; Vidro em bruto ou semi-acabado (com excepção do vidro de construção); Vidraria, porcelana e faiança não incluídas noutras classes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ghivece de flori; Sfeşnice; Suporturi de lumânări anti-vânt (suporturi de lumânări); Mese cu blat-tavă; Articole de masă; Ustensile şi recipienţi pentru menaj sau bucătărie; Piepteni şi bureţi; Perii; Material pentru perii; Material pentru curățare; Bureți metalici; Sticlă brută sau semiprelucrată (cu excepţia sticlei de construcţie); Sticlărie, porţelan şi faianţă necuprinse în alte clase.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kvetináče; Viacramenné svietniky; Vrtuľky (nádoby na čajové sviečky); Odkladacie stolíky; Kuchynský riad, príbory; Domáce alebo kuchynské potreby a nádoby; Hrebene a špongie; Kefy; Materiál na kefárske výrobky; Predmety na čistenie; Oceľová vlna a drôtenky; Sklo (surovina alebo polotovar), nie pre stavebníctvo; Výrobky zo skla, porcelánu a kameniny, ktoré nie sú zahrnuté v iných triedach.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Lončki za rože; Svečniki; Vetrne luči (stojala za svečke); Pladnji za strežbo; Namizni pribor; Priprave ter posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo; Glavniki in gobe; Krtače; Materiali za izdelavo krtač; Proizvodi za čiščenje; Jeklena volna; Surovo ali delno obdelano steklo (razen stekla za gradbeništvo); Steklenina, porcelan in fajansa, ki jih ne obsegajo drugi razredi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Blomkrukor; Kandelabrar; Vindsnurror (vaxljusstakar); Brickor med fällbara ben [Butlers' trays]; Servis; Redskap och behållare för hushållsändamål samt köksgeråd; Kammar och tvättsvampar; Borstar; Material för borstbinderi; Redskap för rengöringsändamål; Stålull; Obearbetat eller delvis bearbetat glas (ej byggnadsglas); Varor av glas, porslin och keramik, ej ingående i andra klasser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>27</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Тапети; Килими, черги, изтривалки, рогозки, линолеум и други материали за подови покрития; Тапети за стена, не от текстил.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Tapety; Koberce, rohožky, rohože, linoleum a jiné obklady podlah; Netextilní tapety.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tapeter; Gulvtæpper og tæpper, måtter, linoleum og andet belægningsmateriale til eksisterende gulve; Tapeter, ikke af tekstilmaterialer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Papiertapeten; Teppiche, Fußmatten, Matten, Linoleum und andere Bodenbeläge; Tapeten, nicht aus textilem Material.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ταπετσαρίες τοίχου· Τάπητες, ψάθες, χαλάκια, λινοτάπητες και άλλα είδη επίστρωσης δαπέδων· Ταπετσαρίες (μη υφασμάτινες).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Wallpaper; Carpets, rugs, mats and matting, linoleum and other materials for covering existing floors; Non-textile wallpaper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Papel pintado; Alfombras, felpudos, esteras, linóleo y otros revestimientos de suelos; Papel pintado que no sea de materias textiles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tapeet; Vaibad, matid, linoleum ja põrandakatted; Mitte-tekstiilist tapeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tapetit (Paperi -); Matot, korkkimatot ja muut valmiiden lattioiden päällysteet; Muut kuin kankaiset tapetit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Papiers peints; Tapis, paillassons, nattes, linoléum et autres revêtements de sols; Papier mural non textile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Zidne tapete; Sagovi, prostirači, strunjače i otirači, linoleum i ostali pokrivači za podove; Zidne tapete (netekstilne).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tapéta; Szőnyegek, lábtörlők (szalmából), gyékények és nádfonatok, linóleum és más padlóburkolatok; Nem textil tapéták.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Carte da tappezzeria; Tappeti, zerbini, stuoie, linoleum e altri rivestimenti per pavimenti; Carta da parati non in materiali tessili.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Popieriniai sienų apmušalai; Kilimai, kilimėliai, patiesalai, linoleumas ir kitos grindų dangos; Netekstiliniai tapetai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tapetes; Paklāji, grīdsegas, mašas un pīteņi, linolejs un citi grīdu pārklājumu materiāli; Tapetes, kas nav izgatavotas no tekstilmateriāliem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Karta tal-ħajt; Twapet, twapet żgħar u ħsajjar, linolju u materjali oħra biex tiksi art eżistenti; Karta għall-kisi ta' ħitan mhux tat-tessuti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Behangpapier; tapijten, vloermatten, matten, linoleum en andere vloerbedekking; behang, niet van textielmateriaal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Tapeta; Dywany, chodniki (kilimy), maty i słomianki, linoleum i inne materiały do pokrywania podłóg; Tapety nietekstylne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Papel de parede; Tapetes, capachos, esteiras, linóleos e outros artigos de revestimento de soalhos; Papel de parede não em matérias têxteis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Tapet; Covoare, preşuri, rogojini, linoleum şi alte produse pentru acoperirea podelelor; Tapet, nu din material textil.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Papierové tapety; Koberce, predložky, rohože, rohožky, linoleum a iné podlahové krytiny; Netextilné tapety.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Tapete; Preproge, predpražniki, rogoznice, linolej in drugi proizvodi za prekrivanje tal; Netekstilne tapete.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tapeter; Mattor och mattbeläggningar, linoleum och andra material för golvbeläggningar; Icke-textila tapeter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>31</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Стайни растения; Семена, естествени растения и цветя.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pokojové rostliny; Osivo, přírodní rostliny a květiny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Stueplanter; Frø og såsæd, naturlige planter og blomster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Zimmerpflanzen; Sämereien, lebende Pflanzen und natürliche Blumen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Φυτά εσωτερικών χώρων· Σπόροι για σπορά, φυσικά φυτά και άνθη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">House plants; Seeds, natural plants and flowers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Plantas de interior; Semillas, plantas flores naturales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Toataimed; Seemned, looduslikud taimed ja lilled.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Huonekasvit; Siemenet, luonnonkasvit ja -kukat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Plantes d'intérieur; Semences, plantes et fleurs naturelles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kućne biljke; Sjemenje, prirodne biljke i cvijeće.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szobanövények; Magok, élő növények és virágok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Piante da interni; Sementi, piante e fiori naturali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kambariniai augalai; Sėklos, augalai, natūralios gėlės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Telpaugi; Sēklas, dabīgie augi un ziedi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pjanti għad-dar; Żrieragħ, pjanti u fjuri friski.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kamerplanten; zaaizaden, levende planten en bloemen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Rośliny domowe; Ziarna, naturalne rośliny i kwiaty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Plantas de interior; Sementes, plantas e flores naturais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Plante de apartament; Seminte, plante flori naturale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Domáce rastliny; Semená, prírodné rastliny a kvetiny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Hišne rastline; Seme, naravne rastline in rože.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Husväxter; Fröer och utsäden, levande plantor, växter och blommor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/137</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/210</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-11-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>563120</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>31509</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
