<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-05T12:03:38</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228804</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228804</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>it</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="2" status="1">Application under examination</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-04-24</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>CO.V-19</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Дезинфектанти; Санитарни кърпички за еднократна употреба; Дезинфектиращ сапун; Дезинфектанти и антисептици; Дезинфектанти за медицински инструменти; Дезинфектанти за домакинска употреба; Дезинфектанти за хигиенни цели; Дезинфектанти за ветеринарна употреба; Дезинфектанти за медицинска употреба; Препарати за пречистване на въздуха; Дезинфекциращи средства за измиване на ръце; Дезинфектанти за стоматологични апарати и инструменти; Дезинфектанти за медицински апарати и инструменти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Dezinfekční přípravky; Dezinfekční ubrousky; Dezinfekční mýdla; Dezinfekční a antiseptické přípravky; Dezinfekční přípravky na lékařské nástroje; Dezinfekční látky k použití v domácnosti; Dezinfekční prostředky pro hygienické účely; Dezinfekční prostředky k veterinárnímu použití; Dezinfekční přípravky pro lékařské použití; Přípravky na dezinfikování vzduchu; Dezinfekční prostředky na mytí rukou; Dezinfekční přípravky na zubní přístroje a nástroje; Dezinfekční přípravky na lékařské nástroje a přístroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Desinfektionsmidler; Renseservietter; Desinficerende sæbe; Desinficerende og antiseptiske midler; Desinfektionsmidler til medicinske instrumenter; Desinfektionsmidler til husholdningsbrug; Desinfektionsmidler til hygiejniske formål; Desinfektionsmidler til veterinærmedicinske formål; Desinfektionsmidler til medicinske formål; Præparater til luftsterilisering; Desinficerende håndvaskemidler; Desinfektionsmidler til tandlægeapparater og instrumenter; Desinfektionsmidler til medicinske instrumenter og apparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Desinfektionsmittel; Desinfektionstücher für medizinische Zwecke; Desinfizierende Seifen; Desinfektionsmittel und Antiseptika; Desinfektionsmittel für medizinische Instrumente; Desinfektionsmittel für den Haushalt; Desinfektionsmittel für hygienische Zwecke; Desinfektionsmittel für veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Desinfektionsmittel für medizinische Zwecke; Präparate zur Desinfektion der Luft; Desinfizierende Handwaschmittel; Desinfektionsmittel für zahnärztliche Apparate und Instrumente; Desinfektionsmittel für medizinische Geräte und Instrumente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Απολυμαντικά· Μαντιλάκια καθαρισμού· Απολυμαντικά σαπούνια· Απολυμαντικά και αντισηπτικά· Απολυμαντικά για ιατρικά όργανα· Απολυμαντικά για οικιακή χρήση· Απολυμαντικά για υγειονομική χρήση· Απολυμαντικά για κτηνιατρική χρήση· Απολυμαντικά για ιατρικούς σκοπούς· Παρασκευάσματα απολύμανσης αέρα· Απολυμαντικά σαπούνια χεριών· Απολυμαντικά για οδοντιατρικές συσκευές και εργαλεία· Απολυμαντικά προϊόντα για ιατρικά εργαλεία και συσκευές.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Disinfectants; Sanitizing wipes; Disinfectant soap; Disinfectants and antiseptics; Disinfectants for medical instruments; Sanitizers for household use; Disinfectants for hygiene purposes; Disinfectants for veterinary use; Disinfectants for medical use; Air sanitizing preparations; Disinfecting handwash; Disinfectants for dental apparatus and instruments; Disinfectants for medical apparatus and instruments.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Desinfectantes; Paños desinfectantes; Jabones desinfectantes; Desinfectantes y antisépticos; Desinfectantes para instrumentos médicos; Desinfectantes para uso doméstico; Desinfectantes para uso higiénico; Desinfectantes para uso veterinario; Desinfectantes para uso médico; Preparaciones para desinfectar el aire ambiental; Producto desinfectante para lavar las manos; Desinfectantes para equipos e instrumentos odontológicos; Desinfectantes para equipos e instrumentos médicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Desinfektsioonivahendid; Desinfitseerivad lapid; Desinfitseeriv seep; Desinfektsioonivahendid ja antiseptikumid; Arstiriistade desinfitseerimisvahendid; Desinfitseerivad ained majapidamises kasutamiseks; Hügieenilised desinfektsioonivahendid; Veterinaarias kasutatavad desinfitseerimisvahendid; Meditsiinilised desinfektsiooniained; Õhudesinfektsioonipreparaadid; Desinfitseerivad kätepesuvahendid; Hambaraviseadmete ja -riistade desinfektsioonivahendid; Meditsiiniseadmete ja -riistade desinfitseerimisvahendid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Desinfiointiaineet; Desinfiointipyyhkeet; Desinfioiva saippua; Desinfiointiaineet ja antiseptiset aineet; Desinfiointiaineet lääketieteellisiä välineitä varten; Desinfiointiaineet kotitalouskäyttöön; Desinfiointiaineet hygieenisiin tarkoituksiin; Desinfiointiaineet eläinlääkintäkäyttöön; Desinfiointiaineet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Ilmanpuhdistusvalmisteet; Desinfioivat käsihuuhteet; Desinfiointiaineet hammaslääkinnällisiä laitteita ja välineitä varten; Lääketieteellisten välineiden ja laitteiden desinfiointiaineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Désinfectants; Lingettes désinfectantes; Savons désinfectants; Désinfectants et antiseptiques; Désinfectants pour instruments médicaux; Désinfectants à usage ménager; Désinfectants à usage hygiénique; Désinfectants à usage vétérinaire; Désinfectants à usage médical; Préparations pour l’assainissement de l’air; Produit lavant désinfectant pour les mains; Désinfectants pour instruments et appareils dentaires; Désinfectants pour instruments et appareils médicaux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Dezinfekcijska sredstva; Dezinfekcijske maramice; Dezinfekcijski sapuni; Dezinfekcijska i antiseptička sredstva; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za medicinske instrumente; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za kućnu uporabu; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za higijenske namjene; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za veterinarsku uporabu; Dezinficijensi za primjenu u medicini; Preparati za dezinfekciju zraka; Dezinfekcijsko sredstvo za pranje ruku; Sredstva za dezinfekciju dentalnih uređaja i instrumenata; Sredstva za dezinfekciju medicinskih uređaja i instrumenata.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Fertőtlenítőszerek; Fertőtlenítő törlőkendők; Fertőtlenítő szappanok; Fertőtlenítők és fertőzésgátlók; Fertőtlenítőszerek orvosi műszerekhez; Fertőtlenítők háztartási használatra; Fertőtlenítőszerek higiéniai célokra; Fertőtlenítőszerek állatgyógyászati használatra; Fertőtlenítő szerek gyógyászati használatra; Légfertőtlenítő készítmények; Fertőtlenítő kézmosó; Fertőtlenítőszerek fogorvosi készülékekhez és műszerekhez; Fertőtlenítőszerek orvosi műszerekhez és készülékekhez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Disinfettanti; Salviette disinfettanti; Saponi disinfettanti; Disinfettanti ed antisettici; Disinfettanti per strumenti medici; Disinfettanti per uso domestico; Disinfettanti per uso igienico; Disinfettanti per uso veterinario; Disinfettanti per uso medico; Preparati disinfettanti per l'aria; Disinfettanti per il lavaggio delle mani; Disinfettanti per apparati e strumenti odontotecnici; Disinfettanti per apparati e strumenti medici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Dezinfekantai; Dezinfekuojamosios šluostės; Dezinfekcinis muilas; Dezinfekantai ir antiseptikai; Medicinos instrumentų dezinfekavimo priemonės; Buitiniai dezinfektantai; Dezinfekavimo priemonės (higienos reikmėms); Dezinfekavimo priemonės veterinarijos reikmėms; Dezinfekavimo preparatai medicinos reikmėms; Oro sanitarijos preparatai; Dezinfekuojantys rankų plovikliai; Odontologijos aparatų ir instrumentų dezinfekavimo preparatai; Medicininių aparatų ir instrumentų dezinfekavimo preparatai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi; Dezinfekcijas drāniņas; Dezinficējošās ziepes; Dezinfekcijas un antiseptiskie līdzekļi; Medicīnas instrumentu dezinfekcijas līdzekļi; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi higiēniskiem nolūkiem; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi veterināriem nolūkiem; Dezinficējoši līdzekļi medicīniskai izmantošanai; Gaisa dezinfekcijas līdzekļi; Dezinficējoši roku mazgāšanas līdzekļi; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi zobārstniecības aparātiem un ierīcēm; Dezinfektanti medicīniskiem instrumentiem un iekārtām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Diżinfettanti; Biċċiet tal-imsiħ għal skop ta' iġjene; Sapun diżinfettanti; Diżinfettanti u antisettiċi; Diżinfettanti għal strumenti mediċi; Materjal biex itejjeb l-iġjene għall-użu domestiku; Diżinfettanti għal skopijiet ta' iġjene; Diżinfettanti għall-użu fil-qasam veterinarju; Diżinfettanti għal skopijiet mediċi; Preparazzjonijiet tas-sanitizzazzjoni tal-arja; Sapun likwidu tal-idejn diżinfettanti; Diżinfettanti għal apparat u strumenti tas-snien; Diżinfettanti għal strumenti u apparat mediku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Desinfectiemiddelen; Hygiënische doekjes; Desinfecterende zeep; Ontsmettingsmiddelen en antiseptica; Ontsmettingsmiddelen voor medische instrumenten; Sanitaire doekjes voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Desinfecterende middelen voor hygiënisch gebruik; Desinfecterende middelen voor diergeneeskundig gebruik; Ontsmettingsmiddelen voor medische doeleinden; Luchtzuiveringspreparaten; Handreinigingsmiddelen (Desinfecterende -); Ontsmettingsmiddelen voor tandheelkundige apparaten en instrumenten; Ontsmettingsmiddelen voor medische apparaten en instrumenten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Środki odkażające; Chusteczki odkażające; Mydła dezynfekujące; Środki dezynfekcyjne i antyseptyczne; Środki dezynfekcyjne do przyrządów medycznych; Środki odkażające do użytku domowego; Środki dezynfekcyjne do celów higienicznych; Środki dezynfekujące do użytku weterynaryjnego; Środki dezynfekcyjne do celów medycznych; Preparaty do dezynfekcji powietrza; Odkażający preparat do mycia rąk; Środki dezynfekujące do aparatury i przyrządów stomatologicznych; Środki odkażające do przyrządów i aparatury medycznej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Desinfetantes; Toalhetes higiénicos; Sabão desinfetante; Desinfetantes e antissépticos; Desinfetantes para instrumentos médicos; Soluções desinfetantes para uso doméstico; Desinfetantes para uso higiénico; Desinfetantes para uso veterinário; Desinfetantes para uso médico; Produtos para higienização do ar; Desinfetante para lavar as mãos; Desinfetantes para aparelhos e instrumentos dentários; Desinfetantes para aparelhos e instrumentos médicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Dezinfectante; Șervețele dezinfectante; Săpunuri dezinfectante; Dezinfectanți și antiseptice; Dezinfectante pentru instrumente medicale; Produse dezinfectante de uz menajer; Dezinfectante folosite pentru igienă; Dezinfectante de uz veterinar; Dezinfectanți de uz medical; Preparate pentru igienizarea aerului; Produse dezinfectante pentru spălarea mâinilor; Dezinfectanți pentru aparate și instrumente dentare; Dezinfectanți pentru instrumente și aparate medicale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Dezinfekčné prípravky; Dezinfekčné utierky; Dezinfekčné mydlá; Dezinfekčné a antiseptické prípravky; Dezinfekčné prípravky pre lekárske nástroje; Dezinfekčné látky na domáce účely; Dezinfekčné prípravky na hygienické použitie; Dezinfekčné prípravky pre veterinárne účely; Dezinfekčné prípravky na lekárske účely; Prípravky na dezinfekciu vzduchu; Dezinfekčný prípravok na umývanie rúk; Dezinfekčné prostriedky pre zubárske prístroje a nástroje; Dezinfekčné prostriedky na lekárske nástroje a prístroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Razkužila; Dezinfekcijski robčki; Dezinfekcijsko milo; Dezinfekcijska in antiseptična sredstva; Razkužila za medicinske instrumente; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za gospodinjsko uporabo; Razkužila za higienske namene; Razkužila za veterinarsko uporabo; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za medicinsko uporabo; Pripravki za razkuževanje zraka; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za umivanje rok; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za zobne aparate in instrumente; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za medicinske aparate in instrumente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Desinfektionsmedel; Steriliserande torkservetter; Desinficerande tvål; Desinfektions- och antiseptiska medel; Desinfektionsmedel för medicinska instrument; Steriliseringspreparat för hushållsändamål; Desinfektionsmedel för hygieniska ändamål; Desinfektionsmedel för veterinärt bruk; Desinfektionsmedel för medicinskt bruk; Preparat för luftsterilisering; Desinficerande handtvätt; Desinfektionsmedel för odontologiska apparater och instrument; Desinfektionsmedel för medicinska instrument och apparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1128600</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
