<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-12T08:41:04</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018228511</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018228511</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-11</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-12</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Schnekon</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>7</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Автоматични конвейрни инсталации; Серводвигатели; Серводвигатели за променлив ток; Сервомеханизми; Промишлени роботи; Задвижващи устройства за машини; Двигатели за макети на превозни средства; Двигатели, с изключение на такива за сухопътни превозни средства; Електрически мотори за машини.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Automatická dopravníková zařízení; Servomotory; Servomotory na střídavý proud; Servomechanismy; Průmysloví roboti; Hnací zařízení pro stroje; Motory pro modely vozidel; Motory, jiné než pro pozemní vozidla; Elektrické hnací motory pro stroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Automatiske transportøranlæg; Servomotorer; Servomotorer med vekselstrøm; Servomekanismer; Industrirobotter; Drev til maskiner; Motorer til modelkøretøj; Motorer, ikke til køretøjer til brug på land; Elektriske drivmotorer til maskiner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Automatische Förderanlagen; Servomotoren; Wechselstrom-Servomotoren; Servomechanismen, ausgenommen für Landfahrzeuge; Industrieroboter; Motoren für Maschinen; Motoren für Fahrzeugmodelle; Motoren, ausgenommen für Landfahrzeuge; Elektromotoren für Maschinen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αυτόματες εγκαταστάσεις μεταφορέων· Σερβοκινητήρες· Σερβοκινητήρες εναλλασσόμενου ρεύματος· Σερβομηχανισμοί· Βιομηχανικά ρομπότ· Διατάξεις οδήγησης για μηχανές· Κινητήρες για μοντέλα οχημάτων· Κινητήρες πλην των χερσαίων οχημάτων· Ηλεκτροκινητήρες για μηχανήματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Automatic conveyor installations; Servomotors; Alternating current servo motors; Servo-mechanisms; Industrial robots; Driving devices for machines; Engines for model vehicles; Motors, other than for land vehicles; Electric driving motors for machines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Instalaciones transportadoras automáticas; Servomotores; Servomotores de corriente alterna; Servomecanismos; Robots industriales; Dispositivos impulsores para máquinas; Motores para maquetas de vehículos; Motores que no sean para vehículos terrestres; Motores eléctricos de accionamiento para máquinas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Automatiseeritud konveierseadmed; Servomootorid; Vahelduvvoolu-servomootorid; Servomehhanismid; Tööstusrobotid; Masinate ajamiseadmed; Mudelsõidukite mootorid; Mootorid, v.a maismaasõidukite; Masinate elektrilised veomootorid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Automaattiset kuljetuslaitteistot; Servomoottorit; Vaihtovirtaservomoottorit; Servomekanismit; Teollisuusrobotit; Käyttökoneet; Ajoneuvojen pienoismallien moottorit; Moottorit, paitsi maa-ajoneuvoihin; Koneiden sähkömoottorit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Convoyeurs automatiques; Servomoteurs; Servomoteurs à courant alternatif; Servocommandes [parties de machines]; Robots industriels; Dispositifs d'entraînement pour machines; Moteurs pour modèles réduits de véhicules; Moteurs autres que pour véhicules terrestres; Moteurs électriques pour machines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Automatske instalacije transportnih traka; Servo motori; Servo motori s izmjeničnom strujom; Servo mehanizmi; Industrijski roboti; Pogoni za strojeve; Motori za makete vozila; Motori [osim za kopnena vozila]; Električni motori za strojeve.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Automata szállítószalagos berendezések; Szervomotorok; Váltóáramú szervomotorok; Szervomechanizmusok; Ipari robotok; Hajtóeszközök gépekhez; Motorok járműmodellekhez; Motorok, nem szárazföldi járművekhez; Villanymotorok gépekhez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Impianti trasportatori automatici; Servomotori; Servomotori a corrente alternata; Servomeccanismi; Robot industriali; Dispositivi di comando per macchine; Motori per modellini; Motori diversi da quelli per veicoli terrestri; Motrici elettriche per macchine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Automatinių konvejerių įrengimai; Vykdomieji varikliai; Kintamosios srovės servovarikliai; Vykdomieji mechanizmai; Pramoniniai robotai; Mašinų varomieji įrenginiai; Transporto priemonių modelių varikliai; Ne antžeminio transporto priemonių varikliai; Elektriniai mašinų pavarų varikliai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Automātiskie konveijeri; Servomotori; Maiņstrāvas servomotori; Servomehānismi; Rūpnieciskie roboti (iekārtas); Piedziņas ierīces mašīnām; Transportlīdzekļu modeļu dzinēji; Motori un dzinēji (izņemot sauszemes transporta līdzekļiem paredzētos); Piedziņas elektromotori mašīnām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Sistemi ta' konvejers awtomatiċi; Servomuturi; Servomutur li jieħu kurrent li jalterna; Servo-mekkaniżmi; Robots industrijali; Apparat tat-trasmissjoni għal-magni; Magni għall-mudelli ta' vetturi; Muturi u magni (minbarra għal vetturi ta' fuq l-art); Muturi tal-elettriku għall-magni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Transportinstallaties (Automatische -); Servomotoren; Servomotoren met wisselstroom; Servomechanismen; Industriële robots; Aandrijvingen voor machines; Motoren voor modelvoertuigen; Motoren, anders dan voor landvoertuigen; Elektrische motoren voor machines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Automatyczne instalacje przenośnikowe; Serwomotory; Serwomotory prądu zmiennego; Serwomechanizmy; Roboty przemysłowe; Urządzenia napędowe do maszyn; Silniki do modeli pojazdów; Silniki, inne niż do pojazdów lądowych; Elektryczne silniki napędowe do maszyn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Instalações de transporte automático; Servomotores; Servomotores de corrente alterna; Servomecanismos; Robots industriais; Dispositivos de acionamento para máquinas; Motores para veículos em miniatura; Motores, não sendo para veículos terrestres; Motores impulsionadores elétricos para máquinas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Instalații de conveiere automate; Servomotoare; Servomotoare de curent alternativ; Servomecanisme; Roboți industriali; Dispozitive de acționare pentru mașini; Motoare pentru modele de vehicule; Motoare, altele decât cele pentru vehicule terestre; Motoare de acționare electrice pentru mașini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Automatické dopravníkové zariadenia; Servomotory; Servomotory na striedavý prúd; Servomechanizmy; Priemyselné roboty; Pohonné zariadenia pre stroje; Motory automobilových modelov; Motory (nie do pozemných vozidiel); Elektrické hnacie motory pre stroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Instalacije avtomatskih transportnih trakov; Servomotorji; Servomotorji na izmenični tok; Servo mehanizmi; Industrijski roboti; Pogonske naprave za stroje; Motorji za modele vozil; Motorji, razen za kopenska vozila; Električni pogonski motorji za stroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Automatiska transportörsinstallationer; Servomotorer; Servomotorer för växelström; Servomekanismer; Industrirobotar; Drivanordningar för maskiner; Motorer till modellfordon; Motorer, andra än för landfordon; Elektriska motorer till maskiner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Автоматични апарати за набиране; Автоматични трансферни превключватели; Фотоапарати [фотография]; Дигитални камери; Екшън камери; Устройства за монтиране на камери; Видеокамери; Промишлен софтуер; Контролери за промишлена автоматизация; Софтуер за автоматизация на промишленото производство; Релета, електрически; Фасонки за релета; Светлочувствителни релета; Уред за измерване на течения; Електричен амперметър; Измервателни уреди за електричество; Амперметри; Уреди за отчитане; Цифрови измервателни апарати; Електронни измервателни уреди; Оптични уреди за измерване; Уреди за измерване акустиката.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Automatické vytáčecí přístroje; Automatické přenosové přepojovače; Fotoaparáty; Digitální kamery/fotoaparáty; Akční kamery; Montážní zařízení pro kamery; Videokamery; Software pro průmyslové využití; Průmyslové automatizační ovladače; Software pro průmyslovou automatizaci; Elektrická relé; Relé zásuvky; Relé citlivá na světlo; Měřiče proudu; Měřiče elektrického proudu; Přístroje na měření elektřiny; Ampérmetry; Měřící nástroje a zařízení; Digitální měřicí přístroje; Elektronické měřiče; Optické měřicí přístroje; Akustické měřicí zařízení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Automatiske opkaldeapparater; Automatisk omkoblingskontakter; Kameraer [fotografiske]; Digitale kameraer; Actionkameraer; Monteringsanordninger til kameraer; Camcordere; Software til industrien; Automatiske kontrolenheder til industrielle formål; Software til industriel automatisering; Relæer, elektriske; Relækontakter; Lysfølsomme relæer; Strømmålere; Apparater til måling af elektrisk strøm; Elektricitetsmålende instrumenter; Amperemetre; Måleapparater; Digitale måleapparater; Elektroniske målere; Optiske måleapparater; Akustiske målere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Automatische Wählapparate; Automatische Transferschalter; Kameras; Digitale Kameras; Action-Kameras; Halterungen für Kameras; Videokameras; Industriesoftware; Industrielle Automatisierungssteuerungen; Software für die industrielle Automatisierung; Elektrische Relais; Relaisfassungen; Lichtempfindliche Relais; Elektronische Relais; Strommessgeräte; Elektrische Strommessgeräte; Stromzähler; Stromstärkemesser; Amperemeter [Stromstärkemesser]; Messgeräte; Digitale Messgeräte; Elektronische Messgeräte; Optische Messgeräte; Akustische Messgeräte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αυτόματες συσκευές επιλογής (κλήσης)· Αυτόματοι διακόπτες μεταφοράς· Φωτογραφικές μηχανές· Ψηφιακές μηχανές λήψης· Κάμερες δράσης· Διατάξεις στερέωσης για κάμερες· Κάμερες βίντεο· Βιομηχανικό λογισμικό· Όργανα ελέγχου βιομηχανικών αυτοματισμών· Λογισμικό βιομηχανικού αυτοματισμού· Ηλεκτρικός (Ηλεκτρονόμος -)· Υποδοχές ηλεκτρονόμων· Φωτοευαίσθητοι ηλεκτρονόμοι· Μετρητές ρεύματος· Μετρητές ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος· Όργανα ηλεκτρικής μέτρησης· Αμπερόμετρα· Μέτρηση (όργανα -ης)· Ψηφιακές συσκευές μέτρησης· Ηλεκτρονικοί μετρητές· Εξοπλισμός οπτικών μετρήσεων· Ακουστικοί μετρητές.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Automatic dialling apparatus; Automatic transfer switches; Cameras [photography]; Digital cameras; Action cameras; Mounting devices for cameras; Camcorders; Industrial software; Industrial automation controls; Industrial automation software; Relays, electric; Relay sockets; Light sensitive relays; Current-meters; Electric current meters; Electricity measuring instruments; Ammeters; Measuring apparatus; Digital measuring apparatus; Electronic meters; Optical measurement apparatus; Acoustic meters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de marcado automático; Conmutadores automáticos de transferencia; Cámaras fotográficas; Cámaras digitales; Cámaras de acción; Dispositivos de montaje para cámaras; Cámaras de vídeo; Software industrial; Controles de automatización industrial; Software para la automatización industrial; Relés eléctricos; Enchufes de relés; Relés fotosensibles; Medidores de corriente; Contadores de corriente eléctrica; Instrumentos para medir la electricidad; Amperímetros; Aparatos de medición; Aparatos de medida digitales; Contadores electrónicos; Aparatos de medida ópticos; Medidores acústicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Automaatsed numbrivalimisseadmed; Automaatülekandelülitid; Fotokaamerad, fotoaparaadid; Digitaalkaamerad; Action-kaamerad; Kaamerate paigaldusseadmed; Taasestavad videokaamerad; Tööstustarkvara; Tööstusautomaatika juhtimisseadised; Tööstusautomaatika tarkvara; Elektrireleed; Releepistikud; Valgustundlikud releed; Voolumõõtjad; Elektrivoolumõõtjad; Elektrimõõturid; Ampermeetrid; Mõõteaparaadid, mõõteseadmed; Digitaalmõõteseadmed; Elektroonilised mõõturid; Optilised mõõteseadmed; Akustilised mõõteriistad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Automaattiset numeronvalintalaitteet; Automaattiset siirtokytkimet; Kamerat; Digitaalikamerat; Toimintakamerat; Kameroiden jalustat; Videokamerat; Teollisuusohjelmistot; Teollisuudessa käytettävät automaattiset ohjaimet; Ohjelmistot teollisuuden automaatiota varten; Releet (Sähkö -); Relekannat; Valoherkät releet; Virtamittarit; Sähkövirtamittarit; Sähkönmittausvälineet; Ampeerimittarit; Mittalaitteet; Digitaaliset mittauslaitteet; Elektroniset mittarit; Optiset mittauslaitteet; Akustiset mittarit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils de numérotation automatique; Commutateurs de transferts automatiques; Appareils photographiques; Appareils photographiques numériques; Caméras d'action; Dispositifs de support pour caméras; Caméras vidéo; Logiciel industriel; Contrôles de productique; Logiciels pour l’automatisation industrielle; Relais électriques; Supports de relais; Relais sensibles à la lumière; Appareils de mesure de courant électrique; Ampèremètres électriques; Instruments de mesure de l'électricité; Ampèremètres; Mesureurs; Appareils de mesure numériques; Compteurs électroniques; Appareils optiques de mesure; Appareils de mesure acoustique.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Uređaji za automatsko biranje; Automatski prekidači za prijenos; Fotoaparati; Digitalne kamere [fotoaparati]; Akcijske kamere; Stalci za kamere; Videokamere; Industrijski softver; Upravljački elementi za industrijsku automatizaciju; Softver za industrijsku automatizaciju; Električni releji; Relejne utičnice; Releji osjetljivi na svjetlost; Mjerači struje; Mjerači električne struje; Instrumenti za mjerenje električne struje; Ampermetri; Mjerni instrumenti; Uređaji za digitalno mjerenje; Elektronički metri; Optički uređaji za mjerenje; Mjerači zvuka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Automatikus tárcsázó berendezések; Automatikus tranzitkapcsolók; Fényképezőgépek, kamerák; Digitális kamerák, fényképezőgépek; Akciókamerák; Eszközök kamerák, fényképezőgépek felszereléséhez; Videokamerák; Ipari szoftverek; Ipari automatizálási vezérlők; Ipari automatizálási szoftverek; Relék, elektromos; Relé foglalatok; Fényérzékeny relék; Árammérők, árammérő eszközök; Elektromos árammérők; Elektromosságmérő berendezések; Árammérők, ampermérők; Mérőműszerek; Digitális mérőberendezések; Elektronikus mérőműszerek, mérőeszközök; Optikai mérőberendezések; Akusztikai mérőműszerek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi di selezione telefonica automatica; Commutatori di trasferimento; Apparecchi fotografici; Apparecchi fotografici digitali; Telecamere sportive; Dispositivi di supporto per macchine fotografiche; Videocamere; Software industriale; Comandi di automazione industriale; Software per automazione industriale; Relè elettrici; Prese di relè; Relè sensibili alla luce; Misuratori di corrente; Contatori per corrente elettrica; Strumenti per misurare l'elettricità; Amperometri; Misuratori; Apparecchi di misurazione digitali; Contatori elettronici; Apparecchi per la misurazione ottica; Misuratori acustici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Automatinio numerio rinkimo aparatai; Automatiniai perdavimo jungikliai; Fotoaparatai; Skaitmeniniai fotoaparatai; Veiksmo filmavimo kameros; Kamerų tvirtinimo įtaisai; Videokameros; Pramonės programinė įranga; Pramoninės automatikos valdikliai; Pramonės automatizavimo programinė įranga; Elektrinės relės; Relių lizdai; Šviesai jautrios relės; Srovės matuokliai; Elektros srovės matuokliai; Elektros matavimo prietaisai; Ampermetrai; Matavimo aparatai; Skaitmeniniai matavimo aparatai; Elektroniniai skaitikliai; Optiniai matavimo aparatai; Garso matavimo prietaisai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Automātiski numura sastādīšanas aparāti; Automātiski ieslēgšanas slēdži; Fotokameras; Digitālās kameras; Videokameras izmantošanai aktīvajā atpūtā; Kameru montāžas ierīces; Videokameras; Rūpniecības programmatūra; Rūpnieciskās automatizācijas kontrolierīces; Ražošanas automatizācijas programmatūra; Elektriskie releji; Releju ligzdas; Gaismjutīgi releji; Strāvas mērīšanas ierīces; Elektriskās strāvas mērīšanas iekārtas; Elektriskās strāvas mērinstrumenti; Ampērmetri; Mēraparatūra; Ciparu mērīšanas ierīces; Elektroniskie skaitītāji; Optiskas mērīšanas ierīces; Akustikas mērītāji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat għall-iddajljar awtomatiku; Swiċis ta' trasferiment awtomatiku; Kameras; Kameras diġitali; Kameras tal-azzjoni; Tagħmir biex jitwaħħlu mal-kameras; Kamera tal-vidjos; Softwer tal-industrija; Kontrolli ta' awtomazzjoni industrijali; Softwer ta' awtomazzjoni industrijali; Tagħmir elettriku li jirċievi u li jittrasmetti; Sokits tar-rilej; Rilejs sensittivi għad-dawl; Strumenti għall-kejl tal-kurrent; Strumenti għall-kejl tal-kurrent elettriku; Strumenti għall-kejl tal-elettriku; Ammetri; Strumenti tal-kejl; Apparat diġitali tal-kejl; Miters elettriċi; Apparat ottiku għall-kejl; Miters akustiċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Automatische kiesapparaten; Automatische omzetschakelaars; Fototoestellen; Digitale camera's; Actiecamera's; Bevestigingen voor camera's; Camcorders; Industriële software; Industriële automatiseringsbesturingen; Software voor industriële automatisering; Elektrische relais; Relaisvoeten; Relais (Lichtgevoelige -); Stroommeters; Elektrische stroommeters; Instrumenten voor elektrische meting; Ampèremeters; Meetapparaten; Meetapparatuur (Digitale -); Elektronische meters; Meetapparaten (Optische -); Akoestische meters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Automatyczne urządzenia do wybierania numeru; Automatyczne przełączniki między obwodami; Aparaty fotograficzne; Aparaty fotograficzne cyfrowe; Kamery akcji; Urządzenia do montowania kamer; Kamery wideo; Oprogramowanie przemysłowe; Sterowniki automatyki przemysłowej; Oprogramowanie do automatyzacji przemysłowej; Przekaźniki elektryczne; Gniazda przekaźnikowe; Przekaźniki wrażliwe na światło; Mierniki prądu; Liczniki prądu elektrycznego; Przyrządy do pomiaru energii elektrycznej; Amperomierze; Przyrządy pomiarowe; Cyfrowe urządzenia pomiarowe; Mierniki elektroniczne; Optyczne urządzenia pomiarowe; Mierniki akustyczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos automáticos de marcação telefónica; Comutadores de transferência automáticos; Câmaras fotográficas; Câmaras digitais; Câmaras de ação; Dispositivos de montagem para câmaras; Câmaras de vídeo; Software industrial; Controlos de automação industrial; Software para automação industrial; Relés elétricos; Tomadas de relés; Relés sensíveis à luz; Medidores de corrente; Medidores de corrente elétrica; Instrumentos de medição elétrica; Amperímetros; Aparelhos de medição; Dispositivos de medida digitais; Contadores eletrónicos; Equipamento de medição ótica; Aparelhos de medição acústica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate de apelare automată; Comutatoare automate de transfer; Aparate de fotografiat; Aparate de fotografiat digitale; Aparate foto de acțiune; Dispozitive de montare pentru camere; Camere video portabile; Software industrial; Comenzi de automatizare industrială; Software pentru automatizare industrială; Relee electrice; Prize de relee; Relee sensibile la lumină; Aparate de măsurat curentul; Aparate pentru măsurarea curentului electric; Instrumente pentru măsurarea electricității; Ampermetre; Instrumente de măsurare; Aparate de măsurat digitale; Contoare electronice; Instrumente optice de măsurare; Aparate de măsurat acustice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Automatické vytáčacie zariadenia; Automatické prenosové spínače; Fotoaparáty; Digitálne fotoaparáty; Akčné kamery; Montážne a upevňovacie prvky pre kamery; Videokamery; Priemyselný softvér; Ovládače priemyselnej automatizácie; Softvér pre priemyselnú automatizáciu; Elektrické relé; Zásuvky na relé; Svetlocitlivé relé; Merače prúdu; Merače elektrického prúdu; Nástroje na meranie elektriny; Ampérmetre; Meracie prístroje; Digitálne meracie zariadenia; Elektronické merače; Optické meracie prístroje; Akustické meracie zariadenia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Avtomatski klicni aparati; Avtomatska preklopna stikala; Fotoaparati; Digitalni fotoaparati; Akcijske kamere; Naprave za postavitev kamer; Video kamere (kamkorderji); Industrijska programska oprema; Krmilniki za industrijsko avtomatizacijo; Programska oprema za industrijsko avtomatizacijo; Releji, električni; Vtičnice relejev; Svetlobno občutljivi releji; Merilniki toka; Merilniki za električni tok; Električni merilni instrumenti; Ampermetri; Merilni instrumenti; Digitalni merilni aparati; Elektronski števci; Optični merilni aparati; Merilci zvoka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Apparater för automatisk uppringning; Automatiska överföringsomkopplare; Kameror; Digitala kameror; Actionkameror; Monteringsanordningar för kameror; Camcorders; Programvaror för industrin; Industriella automatiseringskontroller; Programvara för industriautomation; Elektriska reläer; Reläsocklar; Ljuskänsliga reläer; Strömmätare; Mätare av elektrisk ström; Mätinstrument avseende elektricitet; Amperemätare; Mätapparater; Digitala mätapparater; Elektroniska mätare; Optiska mätinstrument; Akustiska mätare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Агенции за внос и износ; Услуги на агенции за внос.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zprostředkování dovozu a vývozu; Služby dovozní agentury.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Import- og eksportagenturer; Importagenturer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Import-/Exportagenturdienste; Dienstleistungen einer Importagentur.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Πρακτορεία εισαγωγών-εξαγωγών· Υπηρεσίες γραφείων εισαγωγών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Import-export agency services; Import agency services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de agencias de importación-exportación; Servicios de agencia de importación.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ekspordi- ja impordiagentuuride teenused; Impordiagentuuride teenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tuonti- ja vientiagentuuripalvelut; Tuontiagentuuripalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d'agences d'import-export; Services d'agences d'importation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Agencije za uvoz-izvoz; Usluge agencija za uvoz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Import-export ügynökségek; Import ügynökségek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di agenzie per l'importazione e l'esportazione; Servizi di agenzia di importazione.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Importo ir eksporto agentūrų paslaugos; Importo agentūrų paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Importa-eksporta aģentūru pakalpojumi; Importa aģentūru pakalpojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-importazzjoni u esportazzjoni; Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-importazzjoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diensten van import- en exportagentschappen; Import agentschappen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi agencji importowo-eksportowych; Usługi agencji importowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de agências de importação-exportação; Serviços de agências de importação.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Agenții de import-export; Servicii ale agențiilor de import.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kancelárie zaoberajúce sa dovozom a vývozom; Služby agentúr zaoberajúcich sa dovozom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Uvozno - izvozne agencije; Storitve uvozne agencije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Import-exportagenturer; Importagenturtjänster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/082</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/152</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-12</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>952045</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
