<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-28T10:35:19</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018223371</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018223371</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>es</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-10</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>La Rocca Serving coffe since 1985</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162203571</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/223/018223371/000162203571.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>06.01.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.02</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.05</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.06</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.08</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>29.01.04</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>7</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Машини за извличане на кафе; Електрически кафе машини; Електрически кафе машини; Електрически миксери за кафе; Мелнички за кафе, с изключение на ръчни; Мелнички за кафе, с изключение на ръчни.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Stroje na extrahování kávy; Elektrické mlýnky na kávu; Elektrické mlýnky na kávu; Elektrické pěniče mléka do kávy; Mlýnky na kávu, jiné než na ruční pohon; Mlýnky na kávu, jiné než na ruční pohon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Maskiner til udvinding af kaffe; Eldrevne kaffemøller; Eldrevne kaffemøller; Elektriske kaffeskummere; Kaffekværne, undtagen manuelle; Kaffekværne, undtagen manuelle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Maschinen zur Herstellung von Kaffeeextrakten; Elektrische Kaffeemühlen; Elektrische Kaffeemühlen; Elektrische Kaffeeaufschäumer; Nicht handbetriebene Kaffeemühlen; Nicht handbetriebene Kaffeemühlen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μηχανές εξαγωγής καφέ· Ηλεκτροκίνητοι μύλοι του καφέ· Ηλεκτροκίνητοι μύλοι του καφέ· Ηλεκτρικές συσκευές αφρίσματος του καφέ· Καφέ (Μύλοι για -) όχι χειροκίνητοι· Καφέ (Μύλοι για -) όχι χειροκίνητοι.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Coffee extracting machines; Power-operated coffee grinders; Power-operated coffee grinders; Electric coffee frothers; Coffee grinders, other than hand-operated; Coffee grinders, other than hand-operated.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Máquinas extractoras de café; Molinillos de café eléctricos; Molinillos eléctricos de café; Batidoras eléctricas de café; Molinillos de café [no manuales]; Molinillos de café que no sean accionados manualmente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kohviekstraheerimismasinad; Kohviveskid (elektrilised); Kohviveskid (elektrilised); Elektrilised piimavahustid; Kohviveskid, v.a käsitsi käitatavad; Kohviveskid, v.a käsitsi käitatavad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kahvinuuttokoneet; Sähkökäyttöiset kahvimyllyt; Sähkökäyttöiset kahvimyllyt; Sähkökäyttöiset kahvinvaahdottimet; Kahvimyllyt, muut kuin käsikäyttöiset; Kahvimyllyt, muut kuin käsikäyttöiset.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Machines pour l'extraction du café; Moulins à café électriques; Moulins à café électriques; Fouets à café électriques; Moulins à café autres qu'à main; Moulins à café autres qu'à main.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Strojevi za ekstrakciju kave; Električni mlinci za kavu; Električni mlinci za kavu; Električni uređaji za pjenjenje kave; Uređaji za mljevenje kave, osim ručnih; Uređaji za mljevenje kave, osim ručnih.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kávé kivonatoló gépek; Elektromos kávédarálók; Elektromos kávédarálók; Elektromos kávéhabosítók; Kávédarálók, nem kézzel működtetett; Kávédarálók, nem kézzel működtetett.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Macchine per l'estrazione del caffè; Macinini per il caffè elettrici; Macinini per il caffè elettrici; Schiumatori elettrici per caffè; Macinini da caffè non manuali; Macinini da caffè non manuali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kavos ištraukimo mašinos; Elektrinės kavamalės; Elektrinės kavamalės; Elektriniai kavos plakikliai; Kavamalės (išskyrus rankines); Kavamalės (išskyrus rankines).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kafijas ekstrakcijas mašīnas; Elektriskās kafijas dzirnaviņas; Elektriskās kafijas dzirnaviņas; Elektriskie kafijas putotāji; Kafijas dzirnaviņas, izņemot ar roku darbināmās; Kafijas dzirnaviņas, izņemot ar roku darbināmās.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Magni għall-estrazzjoni tal-kafè; Imtieħen tal-kafè li jitħaddmu bl-elettriku; Imtieħen tal-kafè li jitħaddmu bl-elettriku; Magni elettriċi tal-kafè li jagħmlulu r-rawgħa; Magni li jitħnu l-kafè, minbarra dawk li jinħadmu bl-idejn; Magni li jitħnu l-kafè, minbarra dawk li jinħadmu bl-idejn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Winnen van koffie (Machines voor het -); Koffiemolens (Elektrische -); Koffiemolens (Elektrische -); Elektrische koffie-opschuimers; Koffiemolens, anders dan handbediend; Koffiemolens, anders dan handbediend.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Maszyny do wyciskania kawy; Elektryczne młynki do kawy; Elektryczne młynki do kawy; Elektryczne spieniacze mleka do kawy; Młynki do kawy, inne niż obsługiwane ręcznie; Młynki do kawy, inne niż obsługiwane ręcznie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máquinas para extrair café; Moedores de café acionados eletricamente; Moedores de café acionados eletricamente; Batedores elétricos para fazer espuma para o café; Moinhos de café, não sendo manuais; Moinhos de café, não sendo manuais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Maşini pentru extracţia cafelei; Râşniţe de cafea electrice; Râşniţe de cafea electrice; Mixere electrice pentru cafea; Cafea (râşniţe de -, cu excepţia celor manuale); Cafea (râşniţe de -, cu excepţia celor manuale).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Stroje na extrahovanie kávy; Elektricky poháňané kávové mlynčeky; Elektricky poháňané kávové mlynčeky; Elektrické peniče kávy; Kávové mlynčeky okrem ručných; Kávové mlynčeky okrem ručných.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Stroji za ekstrakcijo kave; Električni mlinčki za kavo; Električni mlinčki za kavo; Električni aparati za penjenje kave; Mlinčki za kavo, razen na ročni pogon; Mlinčki za kavo, razen na ročni pogon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kaffeextraheringsmaskiner; Elektriska kaffekvarnar; Elektriska kaffekvarnar; Elektriska kaffeskummare; Kaffekvarnar, inte handdrivna; Kaffekvarnar, inte handdrivna.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Кафе (Пещи за печене на -); Електрически цедки за кафе; Кафе (Пещи за печене на -); Кафе (Пещи за печене на -); Кафе (Пещи за печене на -); Електрически безжични кафеварки; Електрически кафеварки; Електрически пещи за кафе; Електрически филтри за кафе; Електрически филтри за кафе; Кафе (Пещи за печене на -); Кафе (Пещи за печене на -); Машини за кафе еспресо; Електрически кафеварки с вградени мелачки; Цедки за кафе, електрически; Автоматични инсталации за направата на кафе; Електрически машини за еспресо; Електрически кафемашини за домакински цели; Кафемашини, електрически; Електрически филтри за кафе; Домашни цедки за кафе [електрически]; Електрически готварски принадлежности; Електрически чайници; Капсули за кафе за многократна употреба.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zařízení na pražení kávy; Kávovary elektrické; Zařízení na pražení kávy; Zařízení na pražení kávy; Zařízení na pražení kávy; Elektrické bezdrátové konvice na kávu; Elektrické nádoby na kávu; Elektrické přístroje na pražení kávy; Elektrické kávové filtry; Elektrické kávové filtry; Zařízení na pražení kávy; Zařízení na pražení kávy; Kávovary na espreso; Elektrické kávovary s filtrem; Elektrické překapávače na kávu; Automatická zařízení na přípravu kávy; Elektrické kávovary na espreso; Elektrické kávovary pro domácnost; Elektrické přístroje na přípravu kávy; Elektrické kávové filtry; Domácí kávovary (elektrické); Elektrické kuchyňské náčiní; Elektrické konvice; Plnitelné kávové kapsle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kaffebrændere; Elektriske kaffekander; Kaffebrændere; Kaffebrændere; Kaffebrændere; Trådløse elektriske kaffekander; Elektriske kaffekogere (kaffeperkolator - hvor kogende vand presses op gennem kaffebønner); Elektriske kafferistere; Kaffefiltreringsapparater, elektriske; Kaffefiltreringsapparater, elektriske; Kaffebrændere; Kaffebrændere; Espressomaskiner; Elektriske kaffekander med indbygget perkolator; Elektriske kaffepercolatorer; Automatiske installationer til kaffebrygning; Elektriske espressomaskiner; Elektriske kaffemaskiner til husholdningsbrug; Elektriske kaffemaskiner; Kaffefiltreringsapparater, elektriske; Kaffeperkolatorer til brug i hjemmet [elektriske]; Elektriske redskaber til madlavning; Kedler, elektriske; Genopfyldelige kaffekapsler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kaffeeröstmaschinen; Kaffeemaschinen, elektrisch; Kaffeeröstmaschinen; Kaffeeröstmaschinen; Kaffeeröstmaschinen; Elektrische kabellose Kaffeekocher; Elektrische Kaffeekessel; Elektrische Kaffeeröster; Elektrische Filtergeräte für Kaffee; Elektrische Filtergeräte für Kaffee; Kaffeeröstmaschinen; Kaffeeröstmaschinen; Espressomaschinen; Elektrische Kaffeekannen mit Perkolator; Kaffeeperkolatoren, elektrisch; Automatische Kaffeezubereitungsanlagen; Elektrische Espressomaschinen; Elektrische Kaffeemaschinen für Haushaltszwecke; Kaffeemaschinen; Elektrische Filtergeräte für Kaffee; Kaffeeperkolatoren für den Haushalt [elektrisch]; Kochgeräte, elektrisch; Elektrische Wasserkessel; Nachfüllbare Kaffeekapseln.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καβουρδιστήρια για καφέ· Ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες· Καβουρδιστήρια για καφέ· Καβουρδιστήρια για καφέ· Καβουρδιστήρια για καφέ· Ασύρματες ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες· Ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες· Συσκευές καβουρντίσματος του καφέ, ηλεκτρικές· Ηλεκτρικά φίλτρα καφέ· Ηλεκτρικά φίλτρα καφέ· Καβουρδιστήρια για καφέ· Καβουρδιστήρια για καφέ· Καφετιέρες για εσπρέσο· Ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες με ενσωματωμένο διηθητήρα· Ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες· Αυτόματες εγκαταστάσεις παρασκευής καφέ· Ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες, ακόμα και μηχανές παρασκευής καφέ τύπου εσπρέσο· Φορητές ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες για οικιακή χρήση· Ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες· Ηλεκτρικά φίλτρα καφέ· Οικιακές καφετιέρες φίλτρου [ηλεκτρικά]· Ηλεκτρικά σκεύη μαγειρέματος· Ηλεκτρικοί βραστήρες· Επαναγεμιζόμενες κάψουλες καφέ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Coffee roasters; Electric coffeepots; Coffee roasters; Coffee roasters; Coffee roasters; Electric wireless coffeepots; Electric coffee urns; Electric coffee roasters; Electric coffee filters; Electric coffee filters; Coffee roasters; Coffee roasters; Expresso coffee machines; Electrical coffee pots incorporating percolators; Electric coffee percolators; Automatic installations for making coffee; Electric espresso machines; Electric coffee makers for household use; Electric coffee brewers; Electric coffee filters; Domestic coffee percolators [electric]; Cooking utensils, electric; Electric kettles; Refillable coffee capsules.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Torrefactores de café; Cafeteras eléctricas; Tostadores de café; Café (Torrefactores de -); Café (Tostadoras de -); Cafeteras eléctricas inalámbricas; Cafeteras dispensadoras eléctricas; Tostadoras de café eléctricas; Café (Filtros de -) eléctricos; Filtros de café eléctricos; Hornos para tostar café; Máquinas para tostar café; Máquinas de café expreso; Cafeteras eléctricas con percolador; Cafeteras de filtro eléctricas; Instalaciones automáticas para hacer café; Máquinas de café expreso eléctricas; Cafeteras eléctricas para uso doméstico; Aparatos eléctricos para preparar café; Aparatos eléctricos para filtrar el café; Percoladores eléctricos de café para uso doméstico; utensilios de cocina eléctricos; Hervidores eléctricos; Cápsulas de café recargables.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kohviröstrid; Elektrilised kohvimasinad, -aparaadid; Kohviröstrid; Kohviröstrid; Kohviröstrid; Elektrilised juhtmeta kohvikannud; Elektrilised kraaniga kohvikeetmisnõud; Elektrilised kohviröstrid; Elektrilised kohvifiltrid; Elektrilised kohvifiltrid; Kohviröstrid; Kohviröstrid; Espressomasinad; Perkolaatoreid sisaldavad elektrilised kohvikeedunõud; Elektrilised kohviperkolaatorid; Automaatseadmed kohvi valmistamiseks; Elektrilised espressomasinad; Elektrikohvikannud majapidamisotstarbeks; Kohvikeetlid, kohvimasinad (Elektrilised); Elektrilised kohvifiltrid; Elektrilised kohviperkolaatorid majapidamises kasutamiseks; Toiduainete elektrilised kuumtöötlusnõud; Elektrikannud; Taastäidetavad kohvikapslid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kahvinpaahtimet; Kahvinkeittimet, sähkökäyttöiset; Kahvinpaahtimet; Kahvinpaahtimet; Kahvinpaahtimet; Sähkökäyttöiset johdottomat kahvipannut; Sähkökäyttöiset kahvinkeittimet; Sähköiset kahvinpaahtimet; Kahvinsuodattimet, sähkökäyttöiset; Kahvinsuodattimet, sähkökäyttöiset; Kahvinpaahtimet; Kahvinpaahtimet; Espressokahvinkeittimet; Sähkökäyttöiset kahvipannut, joihin kuuluu perkolaattoreita; Kahvinkeittimet, sähkökäyttöiset; Automaattiset kahvinkeittolaitteistot; Sähkötoimiset espressokoneet; Kannettavat kahvinkeittimet kotitalouskäyttöön; Sähköiset kahvinkeittimet; Kahvinsuodattimet, sähkökäyttöiset; Kodin aromikahvinkeittimet [sähkökäyttöiset]; Keittovälineet, sähkökäyttöiset; Vedenkeittimet, sähkökäyttöiset; Uudelleen täytettävät kahvikapselit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Torréfacteurs à café; Cafetières électriques; Torréfacteurs à café; Torréfacteurs à café; Torréfacteurs à café; Cafetières électriques sans fil; Cafetières électriques; Torréfacteurs à café électriques; Filtres à café électriques; Filtres à café électriques; Torréfacteurs à café; Torréfacteurs à café; Machines à expresso; Cafetières électriques équipées de percolateurs; Percolateurs électriques; Installations automatiques pour faire du café; Machines à expresso électriques; Cafetières électriques à usage domestique; Infuseurs à café électriques; Filtres à café électriques; Percolateurs à café électriques à usage domestique; Ustensiles de cuisson électriques; Bouilloires électriques; Capsules de café rechargeables.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kava (strojevi za prženje kave); Perkolatori [električni strojevi za kuhanje kave]; Kava (strojevi za prženje kave); Kava (strojevi za prženje kave); Kava (strojevi za prženje kave); Električni bežični aparati za kavu; Električne posude za pripremu kave; Električni aparati za prženje kave; Električni filtri za kavu; Električni filtri za kavu; Kava (strojevi za prženje kave); Kava (strojevi za prženje kave); Aparati za expresso kavu; Električni aparati za kavu s ugrađenim filtrima; Perkolatori [električni strojevi za kuhanje kave]; Automatske instalacije za pripremu kave; Električni aparati za espresso kavu; Električni aparati za kavu za kućanstvo; Električni aparati za kuhanje kave; Električni filtri za kavu; Kafetjere za kućanstvo [električne]; Električni pribor za kuhanje; Električni čajnici [kuhala za vodu]; Punjive kapsule za kavu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kávépörkölő készülékek; Elektromos kávéfőzők; Kávépörkölő készülékek; Kávépörkölő készülékek; Kávépörkölő készülékek; Vezeték nélküli elektromos kávéfőzők; Elektromos kávékannák; Elektromos kávépörkölők; Elektromos kávéfilterek; Elektromos kávéfilterek; Kávépörkölő készülékek; Kávépörkölő készülékek; Presszó kávéfőzők; Perkolátorral felszerelt elektromos kávéfőzők; Elektromos kávéfőzők; Automata kávéfőző készülékek; Elektromos presszógépek; Elektromos kávéfőzők háztartási használatra; Kávéfőzőgépek, elektromos; Elektromos kávéfilterek; Háztartási kávéfőzők [elektromos]; Elektromos főzőeszközök; Elektromos vízforraló kannák; Utántölthető kávékapszulák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi per tostare il caffè; Caffettiere elettriche; Apparecchi per tostare il caffè; Apparecchi per tostare il caffè; Apparecchi per tostare il caffè; Caffettiere elettriche senza filo; Caffettiere elettriche; Tostacaffè elettrici; Filtri per il caffé, elettrici; Filtri per il caffé, elettrici; Apparecchi per tostare il caffè; Apparecchi per tostare il caffè; Macchine per caffè espresso; Caffettiere elettriche con filtro; Macchine da caffè elettriche; Impianti automatici per fare il caffè; Macchine elettriche per caffè espresso; Macchine da caffè elettriche per uso domestico; Macchine per il caffè elettriche; Filtri per il caffé, elettrici; Macchine per il caffè per uso domestico [elettriche]; Utensili per la cottura, elettrici; Bollitori elettrici; Capsule di caffè ricaricabili.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kavos pupelių skrudintuvai; Elektrinės kavavirės su sieteliais; Kavos pupelių skrudintuvai; Kavos pupelių skrudintuvai; Kavos pupelių skrudintuvai; Elektriniai belaidžiai kavinukai; Elektriniai kavos virduliai; Elektriniai kavos skrudintuvai; Elektriniai kavos filtrai; Elektriniai kavos filtrai; Kavos pupelių skrudintuvai; Kavos pupelių skrudintuvai; Espreso kavos aparatai; Elektriniai kavinukai su filtrais; Elektrinės kavavirės su sieteliais; Automatiniai kavos ruošimo įrengimai; Elektriniai espreso kavos aparatai; Elektrinės kavavirės buities reikmėms; Kavos virimo aparatai; Elektriniai kavos filtrai; Buitiniai kavos aparatai su sieteliais [elektriniai]; Elektriniai valgio virimo reikmenys; Virduliai (Elektriniai -); Pakartotinio užpildymo kavos kapsulės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kafijas grauzdēšanas ierīces; Kafijas vārāmās ierīces; Kafijas grauzdēšanas ierīces; Kafijas grauzdēšanas ierīces; Kafijas grauzdēšanas ierīces; Bezvadu elektriskās kafijas kannas; Elektriskas kafijas kannas; Elektriski kafijas grauzdētāji; Elektriskie kafijas filtri; Elektriskie kafijas filtri; Kafijas grauzdēšanas ierīces; Kafijas grauzdēšanas ierīces; Espresso kafijas automāti; Elektriskās kafijas kannas ar perkolatoriem; Kafijas vārāmās ierīces; Kafijas automāti; Elektriski espresso automāti; Elektriski kafijas aparāti mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Elektriskie kafijas aparāti; Elektriskie kafijas filtri; Elektriskie kafijas perkolatori mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Elektriskās ierīces ēdiena gatavošanai; Elektriskās tējkannas; Atkārtoti uzpildāmas kafijas kapsulas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Inkaljaturi tal-kafe; Perkolaturi tal-kafè tal-elettriku; Inkaljaturi tal-kafe; Inkaljaturi tal-kafe; Inkaljaturi tal-kafe; Buqari tal-kafè tal-elettriku mingħajr fili; Kafettieri elettriċi; Inkaljaturi elettriċi tal-kafè; Kafè (Filtri tal- -), tal-elettriku; Kafè (Filtri tal- -), tal-elettriku; Inkaljaturi tal-kafe; Inkaljaturi tal-kafe; Magni tal-kafè espresso; Kafettieri elettriċi li jinkorporaw stanjati; Perkolaturi tal-kafè tal-elettriku; Sistemi awtomatiċi għat-tħejjija tal-kafè; Magni elettriċi tal-kafè espresso; Perkolaturi tal-kafè li jinġarru elettriċi għall-użu domestiku; Magni tal-kafe, tal-elettriku; Kafè (Filtri tal- -), tal-elettriku; Perkolaturi tal-kafè tad-djar (elettriku); Reċipjenti tat-tisjir tal-elettriku; Ktieli tal-elettriku; Kapsuli tal-kafè li jimtlew.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Koffiebranders; Koffiemachines, elektrisch; Koffiebranders; Koffiebranders; Koffiebranders; Elektrische en draadloze koffieapparaten; Elektrische koffiekannen; Elektrische koffiebranders; Koffiefilters, elektrisch; Koffiefilters, elektrisch; Koffiebranders; Koffiebranders; Espressomachines; Elektrische koffiepotten met ingebouwde percolator; Koffiezetapparaten, elektrisch; Installaties (Automatische -) voor het zetten van koffie; Elektrische espressoapparaten; Elektrische koffiezetters voor huishoudelijke doeleinden; Elektrische koffiepotten; Koffiefilters, elektrisch; Koffiezetapparaten voor huishoudelijk gebruik [elektrisch]; Kookgerei, elektrisch; Waterketels, elektrisch; Hervulbare koffiecapsules.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia do palenia kawy; Elektryczne zaparzacze do kawy; Urządzenia do palenia kawy; Urządzenia do palenia kawy; Urządzenia do palenia kawy; Elektryczne bezprzewodowe zaparzacze do kawy; Elektryczne warniki do kawy; Elektryczne urządzenia do palenia kawy; Elektryczne filtry do kawy; Elektryczne filtry do kawy; Urządzenia do palenia kawy; Urządzenia do palenia kawy; Ekspresy do kawy espresso; Elektryczne dzbanki do kawy wyposażone w zaparzacz; Elektryczne zaparzacze do kawy; Instalacje automatyczne do przyrządzania kawy; Elektryczne automaty do espresso; Kawiarki elektryczne do celów domowych; Ekspresy do kawy (Elektryczne -); Elektryczne filtry do kawy; Domowe ekspresy do kawy [elektryczne]; Kuchenny (Sprzęt -) elektryczny; Czajniki elektryczne; Kapsułki na kawę do ponownego napełniania.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Torrefatores para café; Cafeteiras elétricas; Torrefatores para café; Torrefatores para café; Torrefatores para café; Cafeteiras elétricas sem fios; Cafeteiras eléctricas; Torradores de café elétricos; Filtros para café elétricos; Filtros para café elétricos; Torrefatores para café; Torrefatores para café; Máquinas de café expresso; Cafeteiras elétricas com percoladores incorporados; Percoladores para café elétricos; Instalações automáticas para fazer café; Máquinas de café expresso elétricas; Máquinas de café elétricas para uso doméstico; Cafeteiras (jarros para café) elétricas; Filtros para café elétricos; Máquinas elétricas de fazer café para uso doméstico; Utensílios de cozinha elétricos; Chaleiras elétricas; Cápsulas de café recarregáveis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate pentru prăjit cafea; Percolatoare electrice de cafea; Aparate pentru prăjit cafea; Aparate pentru prăjit cafea; Aparate pentru prăjit cafea; Ibrice de cafea electrice, fără fir; Cafetiere electrice; Aparate electrice de prăjit cafea; Filtre electrice de cafea; Filtre electrice de cafea; Aparate pentru prăjit cafea; Aparate pentru prăjit cafea; Maşini de cafea espresso; Cafetiere electrice prevăzute cu filtru; Percolatoare electrice de cafea; Instalaţii automate pentru prepararea cafelei; Maşini electrice de cafea espresso; Maşini electrice de făcut cafea, de uz casnic; Filtre de cafea electrice; Filtre electrice de cafea; Percolatoare de cafea pentru uz casnic [electrice]; Ustensile de gătit electrice; Fierbătoare electrice; Capsule de cafea reîncărcabile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zariadenia na praženie kávy; Elektrické kávovary; Zariadenia na praženie kávy; Zariadenia na praženie kávy; Zariadenia na praženie kávy; Elektrické bezdrôtové konvice; Elektrické kávové kanvice; Elektrické pražiče kávy; Elektrické kávové filtre; Elektrické kávové filtre; Zariadenia na praženie kávy; Zariadenia na praženie kávy; Espresso kávovary; Elektrické kávovary s perkolátorom; Elektrické filtračné alebo extrakčné kávovary; Automatické zariadenia na výrobu kávy; Elektrické kávovary na prípravu espressa; Elektrické kávovary na použitie v domácnosti; Elektrické kanvice na kávu; Elektrické kávové filtre; Domáce elektrické kávovary [perkolátory]; Elektrické kuchynské potreby na prípravu jedál; Elektrické kanvice; Plniteľné kávové kapsuly.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Stroji za praženje kave; Električni strojčki za kuhanje kave; Stroji za praženje kave; Stroji za praženje kave; Stroji za praženje kave; Brezžični električni aparati za kavo; Električne ročke za kavo; Električni pražilniki kave; Električni aparati za kuhanje kave, s filtrom; Električni aparati za kuhanje kave, s filtrom; Stroji za praženje kave; Stroji za praženje kave; Avtomati za espresso kavo; Električna kavna ročka, ki vsebuje filter; Električni aparati za kuhanje kave; Avtomatske inštalacije za pripravo kave; Električni espresso avtomati; Električni kavni aparati za gospodinjsko uporabo; Električni kavni avtomati; Električni aparati za kuhanje kave, s filtrom; Naprave za kuhanje kave, za gospodinjstvo [električne]; Električni pripomočki za kuhanje; Kotlički za gretje vode, električni; Kavne kapsule za ponovno polnjenje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kafferostare; Elektriska kaffeautomater; Kafferostare; Kafferostare; Kafferostare; Elektriska sladdlösa kaffekannor; Elektriska kaffekokare; Elektriska kafferostare; Elektriska kaffefiltrerare; Elektriska kaffefiltrerare; Kafferostare; Kafferostare; Espressomaskiner; Elektriska kaffepannor med filtreringsapparat; Elektriska kaffeautomater; Automatiska installationer för tillagning av kaffe; Elektriska espressomaskiner; Elektriska kaffemaskiner för hushållsbruk; Elektriska kaffebryggare; Elektriska kaffefiltrerare; Elektriska kaffebryggare för hushållsbruk; Elektriska kokredskap; Elektriska vattenkokare; Påfyllningsbara kaffekapslar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Джезвета; Чаши за кафе; Кафемелачки; Бъркалки за кафе; Сервизи за кафе, не от благороден метал; Съдове за сервиране на кафе, неелектрически; Вакуумни кафеварки; Мелнички за кафе, ръчни; Дозиращи лъжички за кафе; Сервизи за кафе, не от благороден метал; Не електрически мелнички за кафе; Мелнички за кафе, ръчни; Мелнички за кафе, ръчни; Филтри за кафе, неелектрически; Филтри за кафе, неелектрически; Сервизи за кафе от порцелан; Сервизи за кафе от керамика; Неелектрически миксери за кафе; Неелектрически машини за кафе; Цедки за кафе, неелектрически; Цедки за кафе, неелектрически; Съдове за сервиране на кафе, неелектрически; Неелектрически кафеварки с бутало; Неелектрически филтърни машини за приготвяне на кафе; Сервизи за кафе от благороден метал; Кани за сервиране на кафе, неелектрически, от благороден метал; Кафеварки, не от благороден метал; Филтри за кафе, неелектрически; Комплекти за кафе, състоящи се от чашки и чинийки; Сервизи за кафе, не от благороден метал.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kávové konvice; Šálky na kávu; Mlýnky na kávu; Míchátka na kávu; Kávové servisy [stolní nádobí]; Konvice na kávu, ne elektrické; Vakuové kávovary; Ruční mlýnky na kávu; Naběračky na kávu; Kávové servisy [stolní nádobí]; Neelektrické mlýnky na kávu; Ruční mlýnky na kávu; Ruční mlýnky na kávu; Filtry na kávu, ne elektrické; Filtry na kávu, ne elektrické; Kávové servisy z porcelánu; Keramické kávové servisy; Neelektrické pěniče mléka do kávy; Kávovary neelektrické; Překapávače na kávu, ne elektrické; Překapávače na kávu, ne elektrické; Konvice na kávu, ne elektrické; Neelektrické konvice s filtrem na přípravu kávy; Neelektrické překapávače na přípravu kávy; Kávové servisy z drahých kovů; Neelektrické kávové konvice z vzácných kovů; Konvice na kávu, jiné než z drahých kovů; Filtry na kávu, ne elektrické; Sady malých kávových šálků sestávající z šálků a podšálků; Kávové soupravy, s výjimkou souprav z drahých kovů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kaffekander; Kaffekrus; Kaffemøller; Rørepinde til kaffe; Kaffeservicer [bordservice]; Kaffekander, ikke elektriske; Vakuumkaffemaskiner; Kaffekværne, hånddrevne; Kaffemåleskeer; Kaffeservicer [bordservice]; Ikke-elektriske kaffekværne; Kaffekværne, hånddrevne; Kaffekværne, hånddrevne; Kaffefiltreringsapparater, ikke elektriske; Kaffefiltreringsapparater, ikke elektriske; Kaffeservice af porcelæn; Kaffeservice af keramik; Ikke-elektriske kaffeskummere; Ikke-elektriske kaffemaskiner; Kaffepercolatorer, ikke elektriske; Kaffepercolatorer, ikke elektriske; Kaffekander, ikke elektriske; Ikke-elektriske stempelkander til brygning af kaffe; Ikke-elektriske kaffetragte til kaffebrygning; Kaffestel af ædelmetal; Kaffekander af ædelmetal, ikke elektriske; Kaffekander, ikke af ædelmetal; Kaffefiltreringsapparater, ikke elektriske; Kaffesæt bestående af kopper og underkopper; Kaffeservice, ikke af ædelmetal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kaffeekannen; Kaffeebecher; Kaffeemühlen; Kaffeerührer; Kaffeeservice [Tafelgeschirr]; Nicht elektrische Kaffeekocher; Vakuum-Kaffeebereiter; Kaffeemühlen, handbetrieben; Kaffeemaßlöffel; Kaffeeservice [Tafelgeschirr]; Nicht elektrische Kaffeemühlen; Kaffeemühlen, handbetrieben; Kaffeemühlen, handbetrieben; Nicht elektrische Kaffeefiltergeräte; Nicht elektrische Kaffeefiltergeräte; Kaffeeservice aus Feinporzellan; Kaffeeservice aus Keramik; Nicht elektrische Kaffeeaufschäumer; Kaffeeperkolatoren (nicht elektrisch); Kaffeeperkolatoren, nicht elektrisch; Kaffeeperkolatoren, nicht elektrisch; Nicht elektrische Kaffeekocher; Nicht elektrische Kaffeemaschinen mit Pressfilter; Nichtelektrische Kaffeefiltergeräte zum Aufbrühen von Kaffee; Kaffeeservices aus Edelmetall; Kaffeespender aus Edelmetall, nicht elektrisch; Kaffeekannen, nicht aus Edelmetall; Nicht elektrische Kaffeefiltergeräte; Mokkasets, bestehend aus Mokkatassen und -untertassen; Kaffeeservices, nicht aus Edelmetall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καφετιέρες (δοχεία)· Κούπες του καφέ· Μύλοι του καφέ· Αναδευτήρες του καφέ· Σερβίτσια καφέ [επιτραπέζια σκεύη]· Καφετιέρες σερβιρίσματος, μη ηλεκτρικές· Καφετιέρες που λειτουργούν με πίεση ατμού· Καφέ (Μύλοι για -) χειροκίνητοι· Κουτάλια για τον καφέ· Σερβίτσια καφέ [επιτραπέζια σκεύη]· Μη ηλεκτρικοί μύλοι του καφέ· Καφέ (Μύλοι για -) χειροκίνητοι· Καφέ (Μύλοι για -) χειροκίνητοι· Καφέ (Φίλτρα για -) μη ηλεκτρικά· Καφέ (Φίλτρα για -) μη ηλεκτρικά· Σερβίτσια του καφέ από πορσελάνη· Σερβίτσια του καφέ από κεραμικό υλικό· Χειροκίνητοι αναδευτήρες καφέ· Μη ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες· Διηθητήρες για καφέ μη ηλεκτρικοί· Διηθητήρες για καφέ μη ηλεκτρικοί· Καφετιέρες σερβιρίσματος, μη ηλεκτρικές· Μη ηλεκτρικές καφετέριες με έμβολο· Μη ηλεκτρικές συσκευές παρασκευής καφέ στάγδην· Σερβίτσια καφέ από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Μη ηλεκτρικά σκεύη για το σερβίρισμα καφέ από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Καφετιέρες, όχι από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Καφέ (Φίλτρα για -) μη ηλεκτρικά· Σετ για καφέ αποτελούμενα από φλιτζάνια και πιατάκια· Σερβίτσια του καφέ, όχι από πολύτιμα μέταλλα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Coffee pots; Coffee mugs; Coffee grinders; Coffee stirrers; Coffee services [tableware]; Coffeepots, non-electric; Vacuum coffee makers; Coffee grinders, hand-operated; Coffee scoops; Coffee services [tableware]; Non-electrical coffee grinders; Coffee grinders, hand-operated; Coffee grinders, hand-operated; Coffee filters, non-electric; Coffee filters, non-electric; Coffee services of china; Coffee services of ceramic; Non-electric coffee frothers; Non-electric coffee machines; Coffee percolators, non-electric; Coffee percolators, non-electric; Coffeepots, non-electric; Non-electric plunger style coffee makers; Non-electric coffee drippers for brewing coffee; Coffee services of precious metal; Non-electric coffee servers of precious metal; Coffee pots not of precious metal; Coffee filters, non-electric; Demitasse sets comprised of cups and saucers; Coffee services, not of precious metal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cafeteras; Tazas de café; Molinillos de café; Agitadores de café; Servicios de café; Cafeteras no eléctricas; Cafeteras de vacío; Molinillos de café manuales; Cucharas medidoras de café; Servicios de café [vajilla]; Molinillos de café no eléctricos; Café (Molinillos de -) accionados manualmente; Molinillos de café accionados manualmente; Café (Filtros de -) no eléctricos; Filtros de café no eléctricos; Servicios de café de porcelana; Servicios de café de cerámica; Espumadores de café no eléctricos; Máquinas de café no eléctricas; Cafeteras de filtro no eléctricas; Filtro (Cafeteras de -) no eléctricas; Cafeteras [que no sean eléctricas]; Cafeteras de émbolo no eléctricas; Cafeteras por goteo no eléctricas; Juegos de café de metales preciosos; Cafeteras no eléctricas de metales preciosos; Cafeteras que no sean de metales preciosos; Filtros de café que no sean de papel, en cuanto partes de cafeteras no eléctricas; Juegos de café formados por tazas y platos; Servicios de café [vajilla] que no sean de metales preciosos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kohvikannud; Kohvikruusid; Kohviveskid; Kohvisegamispulgad; Kohviserviisid [lauanõud]; Kohvikeedukannud, v.a elektrilised; Vaakum-kohvikeetlid; Käsitsi käitatavad kohviveskid; Kohvimõõdulusikad; Kohviserviisid [lauanõud]; Mitteelektrilised kohviveskid; Käsitsi käitatavad kohviveskid; Käsitsi käitatavad kohviveskid; Kohvifiltrid, v.a elektrilised; Kohvifiltrid, v.a elektrilised; Portselanist kohviserviisid; Keraamilised kohviserviisid; Kohvipiimavahustid, v.a elektrilised; Mitteelektrilised kohvikeetlid; Kohvikeetlid, v.a elektrilised; Kohvikeetlid, v.a elektrilised; Kohvikeedukannud, v.a elektrilised; Presskannud; Kohvi valmistamisel kasutatavad kohvifiltrialused, v.a elektrilised; Väärismetallist kohviserviisid; Mitteelektrilised väärismetallist kohvikannud; Kohvikannud [välja arvatud väärismetallist]; Kohvifiltrid, v.a elektrilised; Väikeste tassidega kohviserviisid, mis koosnevad tassidest ja alustassidest; Mitteväärismetallist kohviserviisid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kahvipannut; Kahvimukit; Kahvijauhimet; Kahvinsekoittimet; Kahviastiastot; Kahvipannut, ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Vakuumikahvinkeittimet; Kahvimyllyt, käsikäyttöiset; Kahvimitat; Kahviastiastot; Ei-sähkökäyttöiset kahvimyllyt; Kahvimyllyt, käsikäyttöiset; Kahvimyllyt, käsikäyttöiset; Kahvinsuodattimet, ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Kahvinsuodattimet, ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Kahviastiastot posliinista; Keraamiset kahviastiastot; Muut kuin sähkökäyttöiset kahvinvaahdottimet; Muut kuin sähkökäyttöiset kahvinkeittimet; Kahvinkeittimet, ei-sähkökäyttöiset (perkolaattori); Kahvinkeittimet, ei-sähkökäyttöiset (perkolaattori); Kahvipannut, ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Muut kuin sähkökäyttöiset kahviperkolaattorit; Muut kuin sähkökäyttöiset kahvinsuodattimet; Jalometalliset kahviastiastot; Muut kuin sähkökäyttöiset jalometalliset kahvintarjoilukannut; Kahvipannut, muut kuin jalometalliset; Kahvinsuodattimet, ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Mokkakupit ja lautaset; Kahviastiastot, ei-jalometalliset.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Cafetières; Tasses [mugs] à café; Moulins à café; Touillettes à café; Services à café; Cafetières non électriques; Cafetières à siphon; Moulins à café à main; Cuillers à café; Services à café; Moulins à café non électriques; Moulins à café à main; Moulins à café à main; Filtres à café non électriques; Filtres à café non électriques; Services à café en porcelaine de chine; Services à café en céramique; Fouets à café non électriques; Machines à café non électriques; Percolateurs à café non électriques; Percolateurs à café non électriques; Cafetières non électriques; Cafetières à piston non électriques; Percolateurs non électriques pour infuser le café; Services à café en métaux précieux; Verseuses à café non électriques en métaux précieux; Cafetières non en métaux précieux; Filtres à café non électriques; Services comprenant tasses et soucoupes; Services à café non en métaux précieux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kafetijere; Šalice za kavu; Mlinci za kavu; Miješalice za kavu; Servisi za kavu [stolno posuđe]; Neelektrične posude za kuhanje kave; Vakuumski aparati za kavu; Ručni mlinci za kavu; Mjerne žličice za kavu; Servisi za kavu [stolno posuđe]; Neelektrični mlinci za kavu; Ručni mlinci za kavu; Ručni mlinci za kavu; Filtri za kavu, neelektrični; Filtri za kavu, neelektrični; Servisi za kavu od kineskog porculana; Servisi za kavu od keramike; Ne-električni uređaji za pjenjenje kave; Neelektrični aparati za kavu; Neelektrične kafetjere; Neelektrične kafetjere; Neelektrične posude za kuhanje kave; Neelektrične posude za pripremanje kave [French press]; Neelektrične kapaljke za kuhanje kave; Servisi za kavu od plemenitih metala; Neelektrične posude za posluživanje kave, od plemenitih metala; Kafetijere od neplemenitih metala; Filtri za kavu, neelektrični; Setovi za kavu koji se sastoje od šalica i tanjurića; Servisi za kavu, nisu od plemenitih metala.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kávéskannák; Kávésbögrék; Kávédarálók; Kávékeverők; Kávéskészletek; Kávéskannák, nem elektromos; Vákuumos kávéfőzők; Kávédarálók, (Kézi -); Kávéadagoló kanalak; Kávéskészletek; Kávédarálók, nem elektromos; Kávédarálók, (Kézi -); Kávédarálók, (Kézi -); Kávéfilterek, nem elektromos; Kávéfilterek, nem elektromos; Porcelán kávéskészletek; Kerámia kávéskészletek; Nem elektromos kávéhabosítók; Nem elektromos kávéfőzők; Kávéfőzők, nem elektromos; Kávéfőzők, nem elektromos; Kávéskannák, nem elektromos; Nem elektromos dugattyús kávéfőzők; Nem elektromos kávé csepegtető kávékészítéshez; Nemesfémből készült kávéskészletek; Nemesfémből készült, nem elektromos kávéskannák; Nem nemesfémből készült kávéskannák; Kávéfilterek, nem elektromos; Csészékből és csészealjakból álló eszpresszós készletek; Nem nemesfémből készült kávéskészletek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Caffettiere; Tazzine da caffè; Macinacaffè; Agitatori per caffè; Servizi da caffè; Caffettiere non elettriche; Macchine da caffè a depressione; Macinini per il caffè a mano; Cucchiaini da caffè; Servizi da caffè; Macinacaffè non elettrici; Macinini per il caffè a mano; Macinini per il caffè a mano; Filtri per il caffè non elettrici; Filtri per il caffè non elettrici; Servizi da caffè in porcellana; Servizi da caffè in ceramica; Schiumatori non elettrici per caffè; Macchine non-elettriche per caffè; Macchine da caffè non elettriche; Macchine da caffè non elettriche; Caffettiere non elettriche; Macchine da caffè a leva non elettriche; Filtri non elettrici per preparare il caffè; Servizi da caffè in metallo prezioso; Caffettiere non elettriche in metallo prezioso; Caffettiere non in metallo prezioso; Filtri per il caffè non elettrici; Servizi da caffè costituiti da tazzine e piattini; Servizi da caffè non in metalli preziosi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kavinukai; Kavos puodeliai; Kavamalės; Kavos maišymo lazdelės; Kavos servizai [valgomieji reikmenys]; Kavinukai (Ne elektriniai -); Vakuuminės kavavirės; Kavamalės (Rankinės -); Kavos samteliai; Kavos servizai [valgomieji reikmenys]; Ne elektriniai kavos malūnėliai; Kavamalės (Rankinės -); Kavamalės (Rankinės -); Ne elektriniai kavos filtrai; Ne elektriniai kavos filtrai; Porcelianiniai kavos servizai; Keraminiai kavos servizai; Neelektriniai kavos plikymo aparatai; Neelektriniai kavos aparatai; Ne elektriniai kavinukai su sieteliais; Ne elektriniai kavinukai su sieteliais; Kavinukai (Ne elektriniai -); Ne elektriniai stūmokliniai kavos ruošimo aparatai; Ne elektriniai kavos ruošimo koštuvai; Kavos servizai iš brangiųjų metalų; Ne elektriniai kavinukai iš brangiųjų metalų; Kavinukai ne iš brangiųjų metalų; Ne elektriniai kavos filtrai; Mažų puodelių servizai, sudaryti iš puodelių ir lėkštelių; Kavos servizai [ne brangiųjų metalų].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kafijas kannas; Kafijas krūzes; Kafijas dzirnaviņas; Kafijas maisītāji; Kafijas servīzes [galda piederumi]; Neelektriskas kafijas kannas; Vakuuma kafijas automāti; Ar roku darbināmas kafijas dzirnaviņas; Kafijas karotes; Kafijas servīzes [galda piederumi]; Neelektriskas kafijas dzirnaviņas; Ar roku darbināmas kafijas dzirnaviņas; Ar roku darbināmas kafijas dzirnaviņas; Neelektriski kafijas filtri; Neelektriski kafijas filtri; Kafijas servīzes no porcelāna; Kafijas servīzes no keramikas; Neelektriskie kafijas putotāji; Neelektriski kafijas automāti; Kafijas perkolatori, neelektriski; Kafijas perkolatori, neelektriski; Neelektriskas kafijas kannas; Neelektriskas kafijas kannas ar nospiežamo filtru; Neelektriski kafijas filtri kafijas pagatavošanai; Dārgmetāla kafijas servīzes; Neelektriskas kafijas krūkas no dārgmetāla; Kafijas kannas, kas nav no dārgmetāla; Neelektriski kafijas filtri; Kafijas tasīšu komplekti, kuros ir tasītes un apakštasītes; Kafijas servīzes, kas nav no dārgmetāla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kafettieri; Maggijiet għall-kafè; Inkaljaturi tal-kafè; Oġġetti biex iħawdu l-kafè; Servizzi tal-kafè [oġġetti tal-mejda]; Kafettieri, mhux tal-elettriku; Magni tal-kafè bil-vakwu; Imtieħen tal-kafè, li jinħadmu bl-idejn; Sassli tal-kafè; Servizzi tal-kafè [oġġetti tal-mejda]; Magni li jitħnu l-kafè, mhux tal-elettriku; Imtieħen tal-kafè, li jinħadmu bl-idejn; Imtieħen tal-kafè, li jinħadmu bl-idejn; Filtri tal-kafè, mhux tal-elettriku; Filtri tal-kafè, mhux tal-elettriku; Servizzi tal-kafè tal-kina; Oġġetti għas-servizzi tal-kafè taċ-ċeramika; Magni tal-kafè mhux elettriċi li jagħmlulu r-rawgħa; Magni mhux elettriċi tal-kafè; Filtri tal-kafè (mhux ta' l-elettriku); Filtri tal-kafè (mhux ta' l-elettriku); Kafettieri, mhux tal-elettriku; Magni tal-kafè mhux elettriċi tat-tip li jitilgħu u jinżlu; Dripers tal-kafè mhux elettriċi għat-tisjir tal-kafè; Servizzi tal-kafè tal-metall prezzjuż; Tagħmir biex isservi l-kafè, mhux tal-elettriku, tal-metall prezzjuż; Buqari tal-kafè mhux tal-metall prezzjuż; Filtri tal-kafè, mhux tal-elettriku; Settijiet ta' kikkri u plattini żgħar [demitasse]; Settijiet tal-kafè, mhux tal-metall prezzjuż.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Koffiepotten; Koffiekopjes; Koffiemolens; Roerstaafjes; Koffieserviezen; Koffiepotten, niet elektrisch; Koffiezetters met isoleerkan; Koffiemolens, met de hand te bedienen; Koffiemaatschepjes; Koffieserviezen; Niet-elektrische koffiemolens; Koffiemolens, met de hand te bedienen; Koffiemolens, met de hand te bedienen; Koffiefilters, niet elektrisch; Koffiefilters, niet elektrisch; Koffieserviezen van porselein; Koffieserviezen van keramiek; Niet-elektrische koffie-opschuimers; Niet-elektrische koffiezetapparaten; Koffiepercolators, niet elektrisch; Koffiepercolators, niet elektrisch; Koffiepotten, niet elektrisch; Niet-elektrische koffiezetapparaten met plunjer/perspomp; Niet-elektrische filterkoffiezetapparaten; Koffieserviezen van edele metalen; Serveerkannen voor koffie, niet-elektrisch, van edele metalen; Koffiepotten, niet van edele metalen; Koffiefilters, niet elektrisch; Espressosets bestaande uit kopjes en schotels; Koffieserviezen, niet van edele metalen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dzbanki do kawy; Kubki do kawy; Młynki do kawy; Mieszadełka do kawy; Serwisy do kawy [zastawa stołowa]; Dzbanki do kawy, nieelektryczne; Ciśnieniowe ekspresy do kawy; Ręczne młynki do kawy; Miarki do kawy; Serwisy do kawy [zastawa stołowa]; Nieelektryczne młynki do kawy; Ręczne młynki do kawy; Ręczne młynki do kawy; Filtry do kawy nieelektryczne; Filtry do kawy nieelektryczne; Serwisy do kawy z porcelany; Ceramiczne serwisy do kawy; Nieelektryczne spieniacze mleka do kawy; Maszynki nieelektryczne do kawy; Dzbanki do parzenia kawy nieelektryczne; Dzbanki do parzenia kawy nieelektryczne; Dzbanki do kawy, nieelektryczne; Nieelektryczne zaparzacze do kawy z tłokiem; Filtry [dripy] nieelektryczne do parzenia kawy; Serwisy do kawy z metali szlachetnych; Dzbanki do kawy z metali szlachetnych, inne niż elektryczne; Dzbanki do kawy nie z metali szlachetnych; Filtry do kawy nieelektryczne; Zestawy filiżanek do kawy składające się z małych filiżanek i spodków; Serwisy do kawy nie z metali szlachetnych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cafeteiras; Canecas para café; Moinhos de café; Varetas para agitar o café; Serviços de café [louça de mesa]; Cafeteiras, não elétricas; Cafeteiras de vácuo; Moinhos de café manuais; Medidores de café; Serviços de café [louça de mesa]; Moinhos de café não elétricos; Moinhos de café manuais; Moinhos de café manuais; Filtros de café, não elétricos; Filtros de café, não elétricos; Serviços de café em louça chinesa; Serviços de café em cerâmica; Batedores manuais para fazer espuma para o café; Máquinas de café não eléctricas; Coadores de café, não elétricos; Coadores de café, não elétricos; Cafeteiras, não elétricas; Cafeteiras de êmbolo não elétricas; Gotejadores de café não elétricos para fazer café; Serviços de café em metais preciosos; Cafeteiras de serviço, não elétricas, em metais preciosos; Cafeteiras não em metais preciosos; Filtros de café, não elétricos; Conjuntos de chávenas de café compostos por chávenas e pires; Serviços de café, não em metais preciosos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cafetiere; Căni de cafea; Râşniţe de cafea; Agitatoare de cafea; Servicii de cafea [veselă]; Cafetiere neelectrice; Cafetiere cu vaccum; Cafea (râşniţe de - manuale); Linguri de cafea; Servicii de cafea [veselă]; Râşniţe neelectrice pentru cafea; Cafea (râşniţe de - manuale); Cafea (râşniţe de - manuale); Filtre de cafea neelectrice; Filtre de cafea neelectrice; Servicii de cafea din porţelan; Servicii de cafea de ceramică; Mixere neelectrice pentru cafea; Maşini neelectrice pentru cafea; Filtre mari de cafea, neelectrice; Filtre mari de cafea, neelectrice; Cafetiere neelectrice; Cafetiere neelectrice cu piston; Filtre non-electrice pentru fierberea cafelei; Servicii de cafea din metale preţioase; Vase non-electrice pentru servirea cafelei, din metale preţioase; Ibrice de cafea, nu din metale preţioase; Filtre de cafea neelectrice; Seturi de cafea formate din ceşti şi farfurii; Servicii de cafea, nu din metale preţioase.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kanvice na kávu; Šálky na kávu; Mlynčeky na kávu; Tyčinky na miešanie kávy; Kávové súpravy (stolový riad); Kanvice na kávu (nie elektrické); Vákuové kávovary; Ručné kávové mlynčeky; Naberačky na kávu; Kávové súpravy (stolový riad); Neelektrické kávové mlynčeky; Ručné kávové mlynčeky; Ručné kávové mlynčeky; Kávové filtre (nie elektrické); Kávové filtre (nie elektrické); Kávové súpravy z porcelánu; Keramické kávové servisy; Neelektrické šľahače mlieka do kávy; Neelektrické kávovary; Kávovary (nie elektrické); Kávovary (nie elektrické); Kanvice na kávu (nie elektrické); Neelektrické sklenené kanvice s filtrom na prípravu kávy; Neelektrické kávové prekvapkávače s filtrom na varenie kávy; Kávové súpravy z drahých kovov; Neelektrické kanvice na kávu z drahých kovov; Kanvice na kávu s výnimkou kanvíc z drahých kovov; Kávové filtre (nie elektrické); Mokka súpravy pozostávajúce zo šálok a tanierikov pod šálku; Kávové súpravy nie z drahých kovov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kafetiere; Skodelice za kavo; Mlinčki za kavo; Palčke za mešanje kave; Kavni servisi; Aparati za kavo (neelektrični); Vakuumski aparati za pripravo kave; Mlinčki za kavo, ročni; Zajemalke za kavo; Kavni servisi; Neelektrični mlinčki za kavo; Mlinčki za kavo, ročni; Mlinčki za kavo, ročni; Kavni filtri, ne električni; Kavni filtri, ne električni; Kavni servisi iz porcelana; Kavni servisi iz keramike; Neelektrični aparati za penjenje kave; Neelektrični stroji za kuhanje kave; Aparati za filtriranje kave, neelektrični; Aparati za filtriranje kave, neelektrični; Aparati za kavo (neelektrični); Neelektrični potopni lončki za kuhanje kave; Neelektrični kapljalniki za pripravo kave; Kavni servisi iz žlahtnih kovin; Neelektrične posode za serviranje kave, iz žlahtnih kovin; Kavne ročke, ne iz žlahtnih kovin; Kavni filtri, ne električni; Servisi za črno kavo, sestavljeni iz skodelic in krožničkov; Kavni servisi, ne iz plemenitih kovin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kaffekannor; Kaffemuggar; Kaffekvarnar; Omrörare för kaffe; Kaffeserviser [bordsserviser]; Icke-elektriska kaffekannor; Vakuumkaffebryggare; Handdrivna kaffekvarnar; Kaffemått; Kaffeserviser [bordsserviser]; Icke-elektriska kaffekvarnar; Handdrivna kaffekvarnar; Handdrivna kaffekvarnar; Icke-elektriska kaffefiltrerare; Icke-elektriska kaffefiltrerare; Kaffeserviser av porslin; Kaffeserviser av keramik; Icke-elektriska kaffeskummare; Icke-elektriska kaffebryggare; Icke-elektriska kaffebryggare; Icke-elektriska kaffebryggare; Icke-elektriska kaffekannor; Icke-elektriska kaffebryggare med nedtryckningsbar kolv; Icke-elektriska kaffefiltreringsanordningar för kaffebryggning; Kaffeserviser av ädelmetall; Icke-elektriska kaffekannor av ädelmetall; Kaffekannor, inte av ädelmetall; Icke-elektriska kaffefiltrerare; Mockakoppsserviser bestående av koppar och tefat; Kaffeserviser, inte av ädelmetall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>30</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Заместители на кафе; Какао; Кафе; Чай; Ориз; Тапиока; Саго; Брашно; Преподготвени продукти от зърнени растения; Хляб; Смес за сладкиши; Сладкарски изделия; Сладоледи и сладоледени кремове; Захар, мед, меласа; Мая; Бакпулвер; Сол; Горчица; Оцет; Сосове [подправки за ястия]; Подправки; Лед.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Náhražky kávy; Kakao; Káva; Čaj; Rýže; Tapioka; Ságo; Mouka; Přípravky vyrobené z obilnin; Chléb; Cukrářské výrobky; Cukrovinky; Produkty určené ke konzumaci v mraženém stavu; Cukr, med, melasa; Droždí; Kypřící prášek do pečiva; Sůl; Hořčice; Ocet; Omáčky [dochucovadla]; Koření; Led pro osvěžení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kaffeerstatning; Kakao; Kaffe; Te; Ris; Tapioka; Sago; Mel; Præparater lavet af kornsorter; Brød; Konditorivarer; Konfekturevarer; Spiseis; Sukker, honning, sirup; Gær; Bagepulver; Salt; Sennep; Eddike; Kryddersaucer; Krydderier; Råis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kaffee-Ersatz; Kakao; Kaffee; Tee; Reis; Tapioca; Sago; Mehl; Getreidezubereitungen; Brot; Backwaren [fein]; Zuckerwaren, Konfekt; Speiseeis; Zucker, Honig, Melassesirup; Hefe; Backpulver; Salz; Senf; Essig; Soßen [Würzen]; Gewürze; Kühleis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υποκατάστατα καφέ· Κακάο· Καφές· Τσάι· Ρύζι· Ταπιόκα· Σαγού· Αλεύρι· Παρασκευάσματα φτιαγμένα από δημητριακά· Άρτος· Γλυκά· Ζαχαρώδη· Προϊόντα παγωτού διαφόρων τύπων [γρανίτες, πολτοί φρούτων παγωμένοι, παγωτά με γάλα, κρεμώδη παγωμένα ροφήματα, κλπ]· Ζάχαρη, μέλι, σιρόπι μελάσας· Μαγιά· Ζυμωτική σκόνη· Αλάτι· Μουστάρδα· Ξύδι· Σάλτσες [καρυκεύματα]· Μπαχαρικά· Πάγος.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Artificial coffee; Cocoa; Coffee; Tea; Rice; Tapioca; Sago; Flour; Preparations made from cereals; Bread; Pastries; Confectionery; Ices; Sugar, honey, treacle; Yeast; Baking powder; Salt; Mustard; Vinegar; Sauces [condiments]; Spices; Ice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Sucedáneos del café; Cacao; Café; Té; arroz; Tapioca; Sagú; Harinas; Preparados a base de cereales; Pan; Productos de pastelería; Productos de confitería; helados; azúcar, miel, jarabe de melaza; Levadura; Polvos de hornear; sal; mostaza; Vinagre; Salsas [condimentos]; especias; hielo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kohvi aseained; Kakao; Kohv; Tee; Riis; Tapiokk, maniokitärklis; Saago, saagotangud; Jahu; Teraviljadest valmissegud; Leib, sai; Kondiitritooted; Maiustused; Jäätised; Suhkur, mesi, siirup; Pärm; Küpsetuspulber; Sool; Sinep; Äädikas; Maitsekastmed; Vürtsid; Jää.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kahvinkorvike; Kaakao; Kahvi; Tee; Riisi; Tapioka; Saagosuurimot; Jauhot; Viljoista valmistetut tuotteet; Leipä; Leivonnaiset; Sokerimakeiset; Jäätelöt; Sokeri, hunaja, siirappi; Hiiva; Leivinjauhe; Suola; Sinappi; Etikka; Kastikkeet (Mauste -); Mausteet; Jää.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Succédanés du café; Cacao; Café; Thé; Riz; Tapioca; Sagou; Farine; Préparations à base de céréales; Pain; Pâtisserie; Confiserie; Glaces comestibles; Sucre, miel, sirop de mélasse; Levure; Poudre à lever; Sel; Moutarde; Vinaigres; Sauces [condiments]; Épices; Glace à rafraîchir.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Nadomjesci kave; Kakao; Kava; Čaj; Riža; Tapioka; Sago [škrob iz jezgre palme sago]; Brašno; Pripravci od žitarica; Kruh; Tijesto za kolače; Slastice; Sladoledi; Šećer, med, sirup od melase; Pjenica [kvasac]; Prašak za dizanje; Sol; Senf; Ocat; Umaci (začinski); Začini; Led.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Pótkávé; Kakaó; Kávé; Tea; Rizs; Tápióka; Szágó; Liszt; Gabonafélékből előállított készítmények; Kenyér; Süteménytészta; Kandiscukor; Fagylaltok és jégkrémek; Cukor, méz, melaszszirup; Élesztő; Sütőpor; Só; Mustár; Ecet; Szószok [ízesítőszerek, fűszeres mártások]; Fűszerek; Jég.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Succedanei del caffè; Cacao; Caffè; Tè; Riso; Tapioca; Sago; Farine alimentari; Preparati a base di cereali; Pane; Pasticceria; Confetteria; Gelati commestibili; Zucchero, miele, sciroppo di melassa; Lievito; Lievito in polvere; Sale; Senape; Aceto; Salse salate; Spezie; Ghiaccio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kavos pakaitalai; Kakava; Kava; Arbata; Ryžiai; Tapijoka; Sago kruopos; Miltai; Grūdų ruošiniai; Duona; Miltiniai konditerijos gaminiai; Konditerijos gaminiai; Ledai ir pieniniai ledai; Cukrus, medus, sirupas; Mielės; Kepimo milteliai; Druska; Garstyčios; Actas; Padažai [uždarai]; Prieskoniai; Ledas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kafijas aizstājēji; Kakao; Kafija; Tēja; Rīsi; Tapioka; Sāgo; Milti; Graudaugu izstrādājumi; Maize; Toršu mīkla; Konditorejas izstrādājumi; Pārtikas ledus (atspirdzinājumam); Cukurs, medus, melases sīrups; Raugs; Cepamais pulveris; Sāls; Sinepes; Etiķis; Mērces [garšvielu mērces]; Garšvielas; Pārtikas ledus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kafè artifiċjali; Kawkaw; Kafè; Tè; Ross; Tapjoka; Sagu; Dqiq; Preparazzjonijiet magħmulin minn ċereali; Ħobż; Għaġina tal-kejk; Ħelu; Silġijiet u ġelati; Zokkor, għasel, għasel iswed; Ħmira; Trab tal-ħami; Melħ; Mustarda; Ħall; Zlazi [kondimenti]; Ħwawar; Silġ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Koffiesurrogaten; Cacao; Koffie; Thee; Rijst; Tapioca; Sago; Meel; Producten gemaakt van granen; Brood; Banketbakkerswaren; Suikergoed; Consumptie-ijs; Suiker, honing, melassestroop; Gist; Bakpoeder; Zout; Mosterd; Azijn; Kruidensausen; Specerijen; Ijs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kawa nienaturalna; Kakao; Kawa; Herbata; Ryż; Tapioka; Sago; Mąka; Preparaty zbożowe; Chleb; Ciasto na wypieki; Wyroby cukiernicze; Lody; Cukier, miód, melasa (syropy); Drożdże; Proszek do pieczenia; Sól; Musztarda; Ocet; Sosy [przyprawy]; Przyprawy; Lód.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Sucedâneos do café; Cacau; Café; Chá; Arroz; Tapioca; Sagú; Farinhas alimentares; Preparações à base de cereais; Pão; Produtos de pastelaria; Produtos de confeitaria; Gelados; Açucar, mel e xarope de melaço; Levedura; Fermento em pó; Sal; Mostarda; Vinagres; Molhos [condimentos]; Especiarias; Gelo para refrescar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Înlocuitori de cafea; Cacao; Cafea; Ceai; Orez; Tapioca; Sago; Făină; Preparate pe bază de cereale; Pâine; Torturi; Dulciuri; Îngheţată; Zahăr, miere, sirop de melasă; Drojdie; Praf de copt; Sare; Muştar; Oţet; Sosuri [condimente]; Mirodenii; Gheaţă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kávové náhradky; Kakao; Káva; Čaj; Ryža; Tapioka; Ságo; Múka; Prípravky vyrobené z obilnín; Chlieb; Jemné pečivárske výrobky; Cukrovinky; Zmrzliny; Cukor, med, melasový sirup; Droždie; Práškové droždie; Soľ; Horčica; Ocot; Omáčky (chuťové prísady); Korenie; Ľad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kavni nadomestki; Kakav; Kava; Čaj; Riž; Tapioka; Sago (škrobna moka iz stržena sagove palme); Moka; Pripravki, narejeni iz žitaric; Kruh; Testo za torte; Slaščice; Sladoledi na vodni osnovi; Sladkor, med, melasni sirup; Kvas; Pecilni praški; Sol; Gorčica; Kis; Omake [začimbe]; Začimbe; Led.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kaffeersättning; Kakao; Kaffe; Te; Ris; Tapioka; Sagogryn; Mjöl; Preparat tillverkade av säd; Bröd; Kakdeg; Konfekt; Isglassar; Socker, honung, sirap; Jäst; Bakpulver; Salt; Senap; Vinäger; Såser [smaktillsatser]; Kryddor; Is.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/091</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-15</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>964690</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>13708</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003127940</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-08-10</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Identity of marks and G&amp;S
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>SK</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>68577</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>1992-05-15</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>176118</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>1995-11-15</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>ROCCA</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>SK</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>68577</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>1992-05-15</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>176118</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>1995-11-15</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>ROCCA</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>CZ</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>68577</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>1992-05-15</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>178590</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>1994-07-29</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>ROCCA</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>CZ</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>68577</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>1992-05-15</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>178590</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>1994-07-29</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>ROCCA</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>494399</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>11068</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
