<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:46</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018223368</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018223368</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Sweet Carefor</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162195546</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/223/018223368/000162195546.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.01</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Памучни тампони за козметични цели; Козметични маски; Памучна вата за козметични цели; Препарат за полиране на кожа; Кърпички за еднократна употреба, напоени с козметични лосиони; Кърпички, напоени с препарати за сваляне на грим; Препарати за слънчев загар [козметични средства]; Дезодоранти за лична употреба; Импрегнирани с почистващ препарат кърпички за почистване; Декоративни лепенки за нокти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vatové tampóny pro kosmetické účely; Kosmetické masky; Vata pro kosmetické účely; Přípravky na leštění kůže; Ubrousky napuštěné pleťovou vodou; Ubrousky napuštěné přípravky na odličování; Přípravky na opalování [kosmetické přípravky]; Deodoranty pro lidskou potřebu nebo pro zvířata; Utěrky napuštěné čisticím prostředkem pro čištění; Ozdobné nálepky na nehty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Vatpinde til kosmetiske formål; Skønhedsmasker; Vat til kosmetisk brug; Pudsemidler til læder; Servietter imprægneret med kosmetiske cremer; Servietter imprægneret med makeupfjernerpræparater; Solbrunende præparater [kosmetiske]; Dedoranter til mennesker eller til dyr; Klude imprægneret med rengøringsmiddel til rengøring; Nail art stickere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wattestäbchen für kosmetische Zwecke; Schönheitsmasken; Watte für kosmetische Zwecke; Lederpolituren; Mit kosmetischen Lotionen getränkte Tücher; Mit Abschminkmitteln getränkte Tücher; Sonnenschutzmittel [kosmetische Mittel zur Hautbräunung]; Deodorants für Menschen oder für Tiere; Mit einem Reinigungsmittel imprägnierte Putztücher; Nagelaufkleber.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ωτογλυφίδες (μπατονέτες) για καλλυντική χρήση· Καλλυντικές μάσκες· Φαρμακευτικό βαμβάκι για καλλυντική χρήση· Στιλβωτικά δέρματος· Μαντηλάκια εμβαπτισμένα με λοσιόν καλλυντική· Μαντιλάκια εμποτισμένα με παρασκευάσματα αφαίρεσης μακιγιάζ· Καλλυντικά προϊόντα για μαύρισμα από τον ήλιο· Αποσμητικά για ανθρώπους ή ζώα· Πανάκια καθαρισμού εμποτισμένα με καθαριστικό· Αυτοκόλλητα για διακόσμηση νυχιών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">cotton swabs for cosmetic purposes; beauty masks; cotton wool for cosmetic purposes; leather polishes; tissues impregnated with cosmetic lotions; tissues impregnated with make-up removing preparations; sun-tanning preparations [cosmetics]; deodorants for human beings or for animals; cloths impregnated with a detergent for cleaning; Decalcomanias for fingernails.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bastoncillos de algodón para uso cosmético; Mascarillas de belleza; Algodón para uso cosmético; Pulimento para cuero; Toallitas impregnadas de lociones cosméticas; Toallitas impregnadas de preparaciones desmaquillantes; Preparaciones cosméticas para el bronceado de la piel; Desodorantes para personas o animales [productos de perfumería]; Paños de limpieza impregnados con detergente; Pegatinas decorativas para uñas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Vatipulgad [tualett-tarbed]; Kosmeetilised maskid; Kosmeetiline vatt; Naha poleerimisained; Tualettveega immutatud salvrätid; Meigieemaldusvahendiga immutatud salvrätid; Kosmeetilised päevitusvahendid; Deodorandid inimestele või loomadele; Puhastusvahendiga immutatud lapid; Küünekleebised.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vanupuikot kosmeettisiin tarkoituksiin; Kosmeettiset naamiot; Pumpuli kosmeettisiin tarkoituksiin; Nahankiillotusaineet; Kosmeettisilla aineilla kyllästetyt kasvopyyhkeet; Meikinpoistoaineilla kostutetut pyyhkeet; Aurinkosuojavalmisteet [kosmeettiset]; Deodorantit ihmisille tai eläimille; Rievut (pesuaineilla kyllästetyt); Kynsitarrat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bâtonnets ouatés à usage cosmétique; Masques de beauté; Ouate à usage cosmétique; Produits lustrants pour le cuir; Serviettes imprégnées de lotions cosmétiques; Lingettes imprégnées de préparations démaquillantes; Préparations cosmétiques pour le bronzage de la peau; Déodorants [parfumerie]; Torchons imprégnés d'un détergent pour le nettoyage; Autocollants de stylisme ongulaire.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Vateni štapići za kozmetičke potrebe; Kozmetičke maske; Vata za kozmetičke svrhe; Sredstva za poliranje kožnih proizvoda; Maramice namočene u kozmetičke losione; Maramice natopljene pripravcima za uklanjanje šminke; Sunčanje [kozmetički preparati za sunčanje]; Dezodoransi za ljude ili za životinje; Krpe namočene deterdžentom za čišćenje; Ukrasne naljepnice za nokte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vattapálcikák kozmetikai célokra; Kozmetikai maszkok; Vatta kozmetikai használatra; Bőrfényező, bőrfényesítő szerek; Kozmetikai folyadékokkal átitatott kendők; Sminkeltávolító készítményekkel átitatott kendők; Napvédő, napozó készítmények [kozmetikumok]; Dezodorok emberi használatra vagy állatoknak; Mosószerrel impregnált ruhák tisztításra; Körömdíszítő matricák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Bastoncini ovattati per uso cosmetico; Maschere di bellezza; Ovatta per uso cosmetico; Lucidi per cuoio; Tovaglioli imbevuti di lozioni cosmetiche; Salviette impregnate struccanti; Preparati abbronzanti [cosmetici]; Deodoranti per uso umano o animale [profumeria]; Strofinacci impregnati con un detergente per pulire; Adesivi decorativi per unghie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vatos krapštukai (kosmetikos reikmėms); Kosmetinės kaukės; Vata (kosmetikos reikmėms); Odų blizgikliai; Popierinės servetėlės, įmirkytos kosmetiniais losjonais; Makiažo valymo preparatais įmirkytos servetėlės; Įdegio preparatai [kosmetika]; Žmonių ar gyvūnų dezodorantai; Valikliais impregnuotas audeklas; Nagų dekoravimo lipdukai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vates irbuļi kosmētiskiem nolūkiem; Kosmētiskās maskas; Vate kosmētiskiem nolūkiem; Ādas izstrādājumu pulēšanas līdzekļi; Ar kosmētiskiem losjoniem piesūcinātas salvetes; Ar dekoratīvās kosmētikas noņemšanas līdzekļiem piesūcinātas salvetes; Kosmētikas līdzekļi sauļošanās nolūkiem; Dezodoranti cilvēkam un dzīvniekiem; Ar tīrīšanas līdzekļiem piesūcinātas lupatiņas; Dekoratīvas nagu uzlīmes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tampuni tal-qoton għal skopijiet kożmetiċi; Maskri kosmetiċi; Tajjar għal skopijiet kosmetiċi; Lostru għall-ġilda; Tessuti mgħammra b'lozjonijiet kosmetiċi; Tessuti mxappin bil-preparazzjonijiet għat-tneħħija tal-mejkapp; Preparazzjonijiet biex tismar [kosmetiċi]; Deodoranti għall-bnedmin jew għall-annimali; Ċraret mgħammra b'diterġent għat-tindif; Stikers tal-arti għad-difrejn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Wattenstaafjes voor cosmetisch gebruik; Schoonheidsmaskers; Watten voor cosmetisch gebruik; Lederpoetsmiddelen; Doekjes geïmpregneerd met cosmetische lotions; Doekjes geïmpregneerd met middelen voor het verwijderen van make-up; Cosmetische preparaten voor het bruinen van de huid; Deodorantia voor mens of dier; Doeken geïmpregneerd met een reinigingsmiddel; Nagelstickertjes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Waciki do celów kosmetycznych; Maski kosmetyczne; Wata do celów kosmetycznych; Środki do polerowania skóry; Chusteczki nasączane płynami kosmetycznymi; Chusteczki nasączone preparatami do usuwania makijażu; Preparaty do samoopalania [kosmetyki]; Dezodoranty dla ludzi i zwierząt; Ściereczki nasączane detergentami, do czyszczenia; Naklejane ozdoby do paznokci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cotonetes algodoados para uso cosmético; Máscaras de beleza; Algodão para uso cosmético; Produtos para polir couro; Lenços impregnados de loções cosméticas; Lenços impregnados com preparações para remover maquilhagem; Preparações para bronzear [cosméticos]; Desodorizantes [perfumaria]; Panos de limpeza impregnados com detergente; Autocolantes para arte de unhas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Bețișoare de bumbac pentru uz cosmetic; Măști de frumusețe; Vată de uz cosmetic; Produse pentru lustruirea articolelor din piele; Șervețele impregnate cu loțiuni cosmetice; Șervețele impregnate cu preparate pentru demachiere; Produse pentru bronzare [cosmetice]; Deodorante pentru oameni sau pentru animale; Pânză îmbibată cu detergent, pentru curățat; Abțibilduri pentru decorarea unghiilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vatové tyčinky na kozmetické použitie; Skrášľovacie masky (kozmetické prípravky); Vata na kozmetické použitie; Prípravky na leštenie kože; Obrúsky napustené pleťovými vodami; Obrúsky napustené odličovacími prípravkami; Kozmetické prípravky na opaľovanie; Dezodoranty (parfuméria); Tkaniny impregnované čistiacimi prípravkami; Ozdobné nálepky na nechty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Vatirane palčke za kozmetične namene; Kozmetične maske; Vata za kozmetične namene; Loščila za usnje; Robčki, prepojeni s kozmetičnimi losjoni; Robčki, prepojeni s sredstvi za odstranjevanje ličil; Pripravki za sončenje [kozmetični izdelki]; Dezodoranti za ljudi ali za živali; Krpe prepojene s čistilnim sredstvom; Okrasne nalepke za nohte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bomullstoppar för kosmetiska ändamål; Kosmetiska masker; Bomull för kosmetiska ändamål; Läderpolish; Servetter impregnerade med kosmetiska lotioner; Servetter impregnerade med avsminkningspreparat; Brun-utan-sol-preparat; Deodoranter för människor eller för djur; Dukar impregnerade med tvättmedel för rengöring; Självhäftande stickers för nagelkonst.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Реактивна хартия за медицински цели; Лаксативи [разхлабителни средства]; Антисептичен памук; Дамски превръзки; Антибактериални кърпички; Импрегнирани антисептични кърпички; Дезинфектанти за хигиенни цели; Тъкани, импрегнирани с фармацевтични лосиони; Хигиенни мъжки гащи; Хартия за ловене на летящи насекоми.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Reagenční papírky pro léčebné účely; Přípravky na pročištění; Antiseptická vata; Hygienické vložky; Antibakteriální ubrousky; Napuštěné dezinfekční ubrousky; Dezinfekční prostředky pro hygienické účely; Ubrousky napuštěné farmaceutickými lotiony; Hygienické kalhotky; Mucholapky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Reagenspapir til medicinsk brug; Udtømningsmidler; Antiseptisk vat; Hygiejnebind; Antibakterielle servietter; Imprægnerede antiseptiske servietter; Desinfektionsmidler til hygiejniske formål; Servietter imprægneret med farmaceutiske lotioner; Hygiejnebenklæder; Fluefangere af papir.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Reagenzpapier für medizinische Zwecke; Blutreinigende Mittel; Antiseptische Baumwolle; Damenbinden; Antibakterielle Tücher; Imprägnierte antiseptische Wischtücher; Desinfektionsmittel für hygienische Zwecke; Mit pharmazeutischen Lotionen getränkte Tücher; Monatshöschen; Fliegenfänger [Klebstreifen].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αντιδραστήριο χαρτί για ιατρικούς σκοπούς· Καθαρτικά· Αντισηπτικό βαμβάκι· Σερβιέτες υγιεινής· Αντιβακτηριδιακά μαντιλάκια· Εμποτισμένα αντισηπτικά μαντηλάκια· Απολυμαντικά για υγειονομική χρήση· Μαντηλάκια εμποτισμένα με λοσιόν φαρμακευτική· Κυλότες υγιεινής· Μυγοπαγίδες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">reagent paper for medical purposes; depuratives; antiseptic cotton; sanitary towels; Antibacterial wipes; Impregnated antiseptic wipes; disinfectants for hygiene purposes; tissues impregnated with pharmaceutical lotions; sanitary panties; fly catching paper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Papel reactivo para uso médico; Depurativos; Algodón antiséptico; Compresas higiénicas; Toallitas antibacterianas; Toallitas impregnadas antisépticas; Desinfectantes para uso higiénico; Toallitas impregnadas de lociones farmacéuticas; Bragas higiénicas; Papel atrapamoscas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meditsiiniline reaktiivpaber; Verepuhastid; Antiseptiline vatt; Hügieenisidemed; Antibakteriaalsed lapid; Immutatud antiseptilised lapid; Hügieenilised desinfektsioonivahendid; Farmatseutiliste vedelikega immutatud salvrätid; Hügieenipüksikud; Kärbsepaber.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Reagenssipaperi lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Ulostusaineet; Antiseptinen vanu; Terveyssiteet; Antibakteeriset kosteuspyyhkeet; Kyllästetyt antiseptiset pyyhkeet; Desinfiointiaineet hygieenisiin tarkoituksiin; Ihopyyhkeet, farmaseuttisilla aineilla kyllästetyt; Hygieniasuojat; Kärpäspaperi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Papier réactif à usage médical; Dépuratifs; Coton antiseptique; Serviettes hygiéniques; Lingettes antibactériennes; Lingettes imprégnées antiseptiques; Désinfectants à usage hygiénique; Serviettes imprégnées de lotions pharmaceutiques; Culottes hygiéniques; Attrape-mouches.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Indikator papir za medicinske potrebe; Čišćenje (sredstva za čišćenje) [laksativi]; Antiseptička vata; Higijenski ulošci; Antibakterijske maramice; Impregnirane antiseptičke maramice; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za higijenske namjene; Ubrusiči natopljeni farmaceutskim losionom; Higijenske gaćice; Muholovke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Lakmuszpapírok orvosi célokra; Hashajtók; Antiszeptikus vatta; Menstruációs betétek; Antibakteriális kendők; Impregnált antiszeptikus kendők; Fertőtlenítőszerek higiéniai célokra; Kendők gyógyszeres folyadékokkal átitatva; Egészségügyi fehérneműk; Légyfogó papír.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Carta reattiva per scopi medici; Depurativi; Cotone antisettico; Assorbenti igienici; Salviette antibatteriche; Salviette imbevute antisettiche; Disinfettanti per uso igienico; Tovaglioli imbevuti di lozioni farmaceutiche; Mutandine igieniche; Acchiappa-mosche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Indikatorinis popierius (medicinos reikmėms); Vidurius valantys vaistai; Antiseptinė vata; Higieniniai rankšluostukai; Antibakterinės servetėlės; Įmirkytos antiseptinės servetėlės; Dezinfekavimo priemonės (higienos reikmėms); Farmaciniais losjonais įmirkytos servetėlės; Higieninės vaikiškos kelnaitės; Musgaudžių popierius.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reaģentu papīrs medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Caureju veicinoši līdzekļi; Antiseptiskā vate; Sieviešu higiēniskās paketes; Antibakteriālās salvetes; Piesūcinātas antiseptiskas drāniņas; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi higiēniskiem nolūkiem; Ar farmaceitiskiem losjoniem piesūcinātas salvetes; Apakšbikses higiēniskiem nolūkiem; Mušpapīrs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Karta reaġenti għal skopijiet mediċi; Purganti; Qoton antisettiku; Faxex tal-mestrwazzjoni; Karti tal-imsiħ antibatteriċi; Karti tal-imsiħ imxarrbin antisettiċi; Diżinfettanti għal skopijiet ta' iġjene; Tíxus mgħammra b'lozjonijiet farmaċewtiċi; Qliezet ta' taħt sanitarji; Karta li taqbad id-dubbien.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reageerpapier voor medische doeleinden; Bloedzuiverende middelen; Antiseptisch katoen; Maandverband; Antibacteriële doekjes; Antiseptische geïmpregneerde doekjes; Desinfecterende middelen voor hygiënisch gebruik; Doekjes geïmpregneerd met farmaceutische lotions; Menstruatieslips; Vliegenvangers [kleefstroken].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Papier odczynnikowy do celów medycznych; Środki przeczyszczające; Wata antyseptyczna; Podpaski higieniczne; Chusteczki antybakteryjne; Nasączane chusteczki antyseptyczne; Środki dezynfekcyjne do celów higienicznych; Chusteczki nasączane płynami farmaceutycznymi; Majtki higieniczne; Lep na muchy [taśmy].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Papel reagente para fins medicinais; Depurativos; Algodão antissético; Toalhas higiénicas; Toalhetes antibacterianos; Toalhetes impregnados antissépticos; Desinfetantes para uso higiénico; Lenços impregnados de loções farmacêuticas; Cuecas higiénicas para a menstruação; Papel apanha-moscas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Hârtie de turnesol de uz medical; Laxative; Tampoane de vată antiseptice; Prosoape sanitare; Șervețele antibacteriene; Șervețele antiseptice impregnate; Dezinfectante folosite pentru igienă; Șervețele impregnate cu loțiuni farmaceutice; Chiloți igienici; Hârtie pentru prins muște.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reagenčný papier na lekárske použitie; Preháňadlá; Antiseptická vata; Hygienické obrúsky; Antibakteriálne utierky; Impregnované dezinfekčné utierky; Dezinfekčné prípravky na hygienické použitie; Obrúsky napustené farmaceutickými pleťovými vodami; Hygienické nohavičky; Lepkavé pásky na chytanie múch.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Reagenčni papir za medicinske namene; Laksativi; Antiseptični bombaž; Menstruacijski vložki; Antibakterijski robčki; Impregnirane brisačke z antiseptikom; Razkužila za higienske namene; Robčki, prepojeni s farmacevtskimi losjoni; Sanitarne hlačke; Papir za lovljenje muh.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Reagenspapper för medicinska ändamål; Renande laxermedel; Antiseptisk bomull; Dambindor; Bakteriedödande servetter; Impregnerade antiseptiska servetter; Desinfektionsmedel för hygieniska ändamål; Servetter impregnerade med farmaceutiska lotioner; Sanitetsbyxor; Flugpapper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Медицински апарати и инструменти; Хирургически стерилни покривки за операции; Термометри за медицински цели; Хирургически маски; Ръкавици за медицински цели; Маски за медицински персонал; Дезинфекциращи [опушващи] апарати за медицински цели; Стоматологично оборудване; Оборудване за физиотерапия; Защитно облекло за медицински цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Lékařské přístroje a nástroje; Operační roušky; Teploměry pro lékařské účely; Chirurgické masky; Rukavice pro lékařské účely; Roušky pro lékařský personál; Fumigační přístroje pro lékařské účely; Zařízení pro zubní lékařství; Fyzioterapeutické přístroje; Ochranné oděvy pro lékařské účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Medicinske apparater og instrumenter; Kirurgiske afdækningsstykker; Termometre til medicinsk brug; Operationsmasker; Handsker til medicinske formål; Masker til brug for medicinsk personel; Røgfrembringelsesapparater til medicinsk brug; Tandlægeapparater og -instrumenter; Udstyr til fysisk terapi; Beskyttelsesbeklædning til medicinske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Medizinische Apparate und Instrumente; Operationstücher; Thermometer für medizinische Zwecke; Chirurgischer Mundschutz; Handschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Masken für medizinisches Personal; Räucherapparate für medizinische Zwecke; Zahnärztliche Apparate und Instrumente; Geräte für physikalische Therapie; Schutzbekleidung für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ιατρικά (Συσκευές και όργανα -)· Σεντόνια χειρουργικά· Θερμόμετρα ιατρικά· Χειρουργικές μάσκες· Γάντια ιατρικής χρήσης· Μάσκες για το ιατρικό προσωπικό· Καπνού εκπομπή (συσκευές ατμοθεραπείας) ιατρικής χρήσης· Οδοντιατρικός εξοπλισμός· Εξοπλισμός φυσικοθεραπείας· Προστατευτικά ενδύματα για ιατρική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">medical apparatus and instruments; surgical drapes; thermometers for medical purposes; surgical masks; gloves for medical purposes; masks for use by medical personnel; fumigation apparatus for medical purposes; dental apparatus and instruments; physiotherapy apparatus; Protective clothing for medical purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos e instrumentos médicos; Sábanas quirúrgicas; Termómetros para uso médico; Mascarillas quirúrgicas; Guantes para uso médico; Mascarillas para personal médico; Aparatos de fumigación para uso médico; Aparatos e instrumentos odontológicos; Equipos de terapia física; Ropa protectora para fines médicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meditsiiniseadmed ja -riistad; Kirurgilised steriilsed riided; Meditsiinilised termomeetrid; Kirurgimaskid; Meditsiinilised kindad; Maskid meditsiinipersonalile; Meditsiinilised suitsutusaparaadid; Hambaraviseadmed ja -riistad; Füsioteraapiaseadmed; Meditsiinis kasutatavad kaitserõivad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Leikkausliinat; Kuumemittarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Kirurgin naamarit; Käsineet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Suojanaamarit lääkintähenkilökuntaa varten; Kaasun tai höyryn sisäänhengityslaitteet lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Hammaslääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Fysioterapiassa käytettävät välineet; Suojavaatteet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils et instruments médicaux; Draps chirurgicaux; Thermomètres à usage médical; Masques chirurgicaux; Gants à usage médical; Masques utilisés par le personnel médical; Appareils pour fumigations à usage médical; Appareils et instruments dentaires; Équipement de thérapie physique; Vêtements de protection à usage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Medicinski uređaji i instrumenti; Plahte za kirurške potrebe; Toplomjeri za medicinske potrebe; Kirurške maske; Rukavice za medicinsku uporabu; Maske za medicinsko osoblje; Uređaji za dimljenje za medicinske potrebe; Stomatološka oprema; Oprema za fizikalnu terapiju; Zaštitna odjeća za medicinske namjene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Gyógyászati készülékek és eszközök; Sebészeti lepedők; Hőmérők gyógyászati célokra; Sebészeti maszkok; Kesztyűk gyógyászati használatra; Maszkok egészségügyi személyzet általi használatra; Fertőtlenítő készülékek gyógyászati használatra; Fogászati berendezések; Fizikoterápiás készülékek; Védőruházat orvosi célokra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi e strumenti medici; Lenzuola chirurgiche; Termometri per uso medico; Mascherine chirurgiche; Guanti per uso medico; Maschere utilizzate dal personale medico; Apparecchi per fumigazioni per uso medico; Apparecchi e strumenti dentari; Attrezzatura per terapie fisiche; Abbigliamento protettivo per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Medicinos aparatai ir instrumentai; Chirurginiai drabužiai; Medicininiai termometrai; Chirurginės kaukės; Pirštinės (medicinos reikmėms); Kaukės medicinos personalui; Smilkymo prietaisai (medicinos reikmėms); Odontologijos aparatūra ir instrumentai; Fizioterapijos įranga; Apsauginiai drabužiai medicininėms reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Medicīniskā aparatūra un instrumenti; Ķirurģiskie pārklāji; Medicīniskie termometri; Ķirurģiskās maskas; Cimdi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Medicīnas personālam paredzētās maskas; Fumigācijas ierīces medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Zobārstniecības ierīces un instrumenti; Fizikālās terapijas iekārtas; Aizsargtērpi medicīniskām vajadzībām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat u strumenti mediċi; Lożor bħala għata għal waqt operazzjonijiet kirurġiċi; Termometri għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri kirurġiċi; Ingwanti għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri għal personal mediku; Apparat ta' fumigazzjoni għal skopijiet mediċi; Tagħmir dentali; Tagħmir għat-terapija fiżika; Ħwejjeġ protettivi għall-użu mediku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Medische apparaten en instrumenten; Chirurgische lakens; Thermometers voor medisch gebruik; Maskers voor chirurgisch gebruik; Handschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Maskers te gebruiken door medisch personeel; Berokingsapparaten voor medisch gebruik; Tandheelkundige apparaten en instrumenten; Fysiotherapeutische apparatuur; Beschermende kledingstukken voor medische doeleinden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia i instrumenty medyczne; Okrycia chirurgiczne; Termometry do celów medycznych; Maski chirurgiczne; Rękawice do celów medycznych; Maski stosowane przez personel medyczny; Urządzenia do fumigacji do celów medycznych; Przyrządy i przybory dentystyczne; Urządzenia i przyrządy do fizjoterapii; Odzież ochronna do celów medycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos e instrumentos médicos; Lençóis para cirurgia; Termómetros para uso médico; Máscaras cirúrgicas; Luvas para uso médico; Máscaras para pessoal médico; Aparelhos de fumigação, para uso médico; Aparelhos e instrumentos dentários; Equipamento de fisioterapia; Vestuário de proteção para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate și instrumente medicale; Cearceafuri chirurgicale; Termometre de uz medical; Măști chirurgicale; Mănuși de uz medical; Măști utilizate de personalul medical; Aparate de fumigație pentru uz medical; Echipament stomatologic; Echipament pentru exerciții fizice; Îmbrăcăminte de protecție de uz medical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Lekárske prístroje a nástroje; Chirurgické plachty; Lekárske teplomery; Chirurgické masky; Rukavice na lekárske použitie; Rúška (pre nemocničný personál); Inhalačné prístroje na lekárske použitie; Zubárske prístroje a nástroje; Fyzioterapeutické zariadenia; Ochranné odevy na lekárske účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Medicinski aparati in instrumenti; Kirurške rjuhe; Termometri za medicinske namene; Kirurške maske; Rokavice za medicinske namene; Maske za medicinsko osebje; Aparati za razkuževanje za medicinsko uporabo; Zobozdravstveni aparati in instrumenti; Naprave za fizikalno terapijo; Zaščitna oblačila za medicinske namene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Medicinska apparater och instrument; Kirurgiska skynken; Termometrar för medicinska ändamål; Operationsmasker; Handskar för medicinska ändamål; Munskydd för medicinsk personal; Apparater för inandning av gas eller ånga för medicinska ändamål; Dentala apparater och instrument; Utrustning för fysioterapi; Skyddskläder för medicinska ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Тоалетна хартия; Салфетки от хартия за маса; Салфетки хартия за почистване на грим; Кърпи от хартия; Кърпи от хартия за лице; Лигавници от хартия; Хартиени кърпи за почистване; Хартиени носни кърпички; Кухненски ролки [хартия].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Toaletní papír; Papírové stolní ubrousky; Papírové odličovací ubrousky; Papírové ručníky; Papírové ručníky na obličej; Papírové bryndáčky; Čisticí papírové utěrky; Papírové kapesníky; Kuchyňský papír v rolích.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">WC-papir; Bordservietter af papir; Papirservietter til fjernelse af make-up; Håndklæder af papir; Ansigtsservietter af papir; Hagesmække af papir; Papirservietter til rengøringsformål; Papirlommetørklæder; Køkkenruller [papir].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Toilettenpapier; Papierservietten; Abschminktücher aus Papier; Papierhandtücher; Papiergesichtstücher; Lätzchen aus Papier; Papiertücher für Reinigungszwecke; Papiertaschentücher; Küchenrollen aus Papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υγείας (Χαρτί -)· Χαρτοπετσέτες· Χαρτομάντιλα για την αφαίρεση του μακιγιάζ· Πετσέτες χεριών από χαρτί· Πετσέτες τουαλέτας [από χαρτί]· Σαλιάρες χάρτινες· Χαρτοπετσέτες καθαρισμού· Χαρτομάντιλα· Ρολά κουζίνας (χαρτί).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">toilet paper; table napkins of paper; Napkins of paper for removing make-up; tissues of paper for removing make-up; towels of paper; face towels of paper; bibs of paper; Paper wipes for cleaning; handkerchiefs of paper; Kitchen paper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Papel higiénico; Servilletas de papel; Toallitas de papel para desmaquillar; Toallas de papel; Toallitas de tocador de papel; Baberos de papel; Toallas de papel para limpieza; Pañuelos de bolsillo de papel; Rollos de papel de cocina.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tualettpaber; Paberist lauasalvrätikud; Paberist salvrätikud meigi eemaldamiseks; Paberkäterätid; Paberist näokuivatusrätikud; Paberist pudipõlled; Paberrätid puhastamiseks; Pabertaskurätikud; Köögipaberirullid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Wc-paperi; Lautasliinat (Paperi -); Paperipyyhkeet ehostusaineiden poistamiseen; Pyyhkeet (Paperi -); Kasvopyyhkeet, paperia; Leukalaput, paperia; Paperipyyhkeet puhdistustarkoituksiin; Paperipyyhkeet; Talouspaperirullat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Papier hygiénique; Serviettes de table en papier; Lingettes en papier pour le démaquillage; Essuie-mains en papier; Serviettes de toilette en papier; Bavoirs en papier; Chiffonnettes en papier pour le nettoyage; Mouchoirs de poche en papier; Rouleaux d'essuie-tout.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Papir (Toaletni -); Papirnati stolni ubrusi; Ubrusi od papira za skidanje šminke; Papirnati ručnici za ruke; Papirnati ručnici za lice; Papirnati podbradnjaci; Papirnati ručnici za čišćenje; Ubrusi od papira; Kuhinjske role [papir].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Egészségügyi papír, WC-papír; Papírszalvéták; Sminkeltávolító papírkendők; Papírtörölközők; Toalettkendők papírból; Előkék papírból; Papírtörlők tisztítási célokra; Papírzsebkendők, papírtörlők; Konyhai papírtörlők [tekercsek].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Carta igienica; Tovaglioli di carta; Tovagliolini per struccare di carta; Asciugamani di carta; Salviette di carta per il viso; Bavaglini di carta; Tovaglioli di carta per pulizia; Fazzoletti di carta; Rotoli da cucina [carta].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Higieninis popierius; Popierinės servetėlės; Popierinės servetėlės (grimui valytis); Popieriniai rankšluosčiai; Popierinės servetėlės (veidui šluostytis); Popieriniai seilinukai; Popierinės valymo šluostės; Popierinės nosinės; Virtuvinio popieriaus ritiniai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tualetes papīrs; Galda salvetes no papīra; Papīra salvetes dekoratīvās kosmētikas noņemšanai; Papīra dvieļi; Sejas dvieļi no papīra; Papīra krūšautiņi; Papīra salvetes tīrīšanai; Zīdpapīrs; Virtuves papīra dvielis, ruļļos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Karta iġjenika; Srievet tal-karti għal fuq il-mejda; Karta tat-tixù, għat-tneħħija tal-mejkapp; Xugamani tal-karti; Xugamani tal-wiċċ tal-karti; Bavalori tal-karti; Xugamani tal-karti għal skopijiet ta' tindif; Karta tat-tixù; Rollijiet tal-kċina (tal-karta).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Toiletpapier; Tafelservetten van papier; Afschminkdoekjes van papier; Handdoeken van papier; Handdoekjes van papier, voor het gezicht; Slabbetjes van papier; Papieren handdoeken voor reinigingsdoeleinden; Zakdoeken van papier; Rollen keukenpapier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Papier higieniczny; Serwetki stołowe papierowe; Chusteczki papierowe do usuwania makijażu; Ręczniki papierowe; Ręczniki do twarzy papierowe; Śliniaki papierowe; Ręczniki papierowe do czyszczenia; Chusteczki do nosa [papierowe]; Papier kuchenny w rolkach.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Papel higiénico; Guardanapos de mesa em papel; Lenços de papel para remover maquilhagem; Toalhas em papel; Toalhas de rosto em papel; Babetes em papel; Toalhas de papel para limpeza; Lenços de bolso [em papel]; Rolos de papel para cozinha.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Hârtie igienică; Șervețele de masă din hârtie; Șervețele pentru demachiat, din hârtie; Prosoape din hârtie; Șervețele de toaletă din hârtie; Bavete din hârtie; Prosoape de hârtie utilizate la curățenie; Șervețele de hârtie; Role de bucătărie [hârtie].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Toaletný papier; Papierové servítky; Odličovacie papierové obrúsky; Papierové utierky; Papierové utierky na tvár; Papierové podbradníky; Čistiace papierové utierky; Papierové vreckovky; Kotúče kuchynského papieru.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Higienski papir; Namizne serviete iz papirja; Robčki iz papirja za odstranjevanje make-upa; Brisače iz papirja; Brisače za obraz iz papirja; Slinčki iz papirja; Papirnate brisačke za čiščenje; Papirnati robčki; Kuhinjske papirnate brisače v roli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Toalettpapper; Bordsservetter av papper; Pappersservetter för avsminkning; Pappershanddukar; Ansiktshanddukar av papper; Haklappar av papper; Rengöringsdukar av papper; Näsdukar av papper; Hushållspappersrullar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079036</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>38810</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
