<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-31T08:41:00</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229247</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229247</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-28</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-31</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>PD</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162457388</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229247/000162457388.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>14.01.13</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.22</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.04</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.16</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Химически почистващи препарати за домакински цели; Етерични масла; Парфюмерия; Козметични средства; Моливи за вежди; Козметични маски; Гланц за устни; Памучна вата за козметични цели; Козметика за деца; Козметични средства за животни.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Chemické čisticí přípravky pro použití v domácnosti; Éterické oleje; Parfémy; Kosmetické přípravky; Tužky na obočí; Kosmetické masky; Lesky na rty; Vata pro kosmetické účely; Kosmetické přípravky pro děti; Kosmetické přípravky pro zvířata.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kemiske rengøringsmidler til husholdningsbrug; Æteriske olier; Parfumer; Kosmetik; Kosmetiske stifter; Skønhedsmasker; Lipgloss; Vat til kosmetisk brug; Kosmetik til børn; Kosmetik til dyr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Chemische Reinigungsmittel für Haushaltszwecke; Ätherische Öle; Parfüms; Kosmetika; Kosmetikstifte; Kosmetische Masken; Lipgloss; Watte für kosmetische Zwecke; Kosmetika für Kinder; Tierkosmetika.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Χημικά παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού για οικιακή χρήση· Αιθέρια (Έλαια -)· Αρωματισμού (Προϊόντα -)· Καλλυντικά· Μολύβια για φρύδια· Καλλυντικές μάσκες· Γυαλιστικά για τα χείλη (lip gloss)· Φαρμακευτικό βαμβάκι για καλλυντική χρήση· Παιδικά καλλυντικά· Καλλυντικά για ζώα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Chemical cleaning preparations for household purposes; essential oils; perfume; cosmetics; pencils for cosmetic use; beauty masks; lip gloss; cotton for cosmetic purposes; cosmetics for children; cosmetics for animals.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Preparaciones químicas de limpieza para uso doméstico; Aceites esenciales; Perfumes; Cosméticos; Lápices para uso cosmético; Mascarillas cosméticas; Brillos de labios; Algodón para uso cosmético; Productos cosméticos para niños; Cosméticos para animales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Keemilised puhastuspreparaadid kodumajapidamises kasutamiseks; Eeterlikud õlid; Parfüümid, lõhnaõlid; Kosmeetikavahendid; Jumestuspliiatsid; Kosmeetilised maskid; Huuleläiked; Vatt (Kosmeetiline); Lastekosmeetika; Loomakosmeetikavahendid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kemialliset puhdistusvalmisteet kotitalouskäyttöön; Eteeriset öljyt; Parfyymit; Kosmetiikka; Kulmakarvakynät; Kosmeettiset naamiot; Huulikiilteet; Pumpuli kosmeettisiin tarkoituksiin; Lasten kosmetiikka; Eläinten kosmeettiset tuotteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits chimiques de nettoyage à usage domestique; Huiles essentielles; Parfums; Cosmétiques; Crayons à usage cosmétique; Masques cosmétiques; Brillant à lèvres; Coton à usage cosmétique; Produits cosmétiques pour enfants; Cosmétiques pour animaux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kemijski pripravci za čišćenje u kućanstvu; Esencijalna ulja; Mirisi; Kozmetički proizvodi; Olovke za obrve; Kozmetičke maske; Sjajila za usne; Vata za kozmetičke svrhe; Kozmetika za djecu; Kozmetika za životinje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vegyi tisztítókészítmények háztartási célokra; Esszenciális olajok; Illatszer készítmények; Kozmetikai szerek; Szemöldökceruzák; Kozmetikai maszkok; Ajakfények; Vatta kozmetikai használatra; Gyermekkozmetikai cikkek; Kozmetikai szerek állatok számára.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Preparati chimici per la pulizia per uso domestico; Oli essenziali; Profumo; Cosmetici; Matite per uso cosmetico; Maschere cosmetiche; Lucidanti per labbra; Ovatta per uso cosmetico; Cosmetici per bambini; Cosmetici per animali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Cheminiai valymo preparatai (buities reikmėms); Eteriniai aliejai; Parfumerijos gaminiai; Kosmetika; Antakių pieštukai; Kosmetinės kaukės; Lūpų blizgiai; Vata (kosmetikos reikmėms); Vaikiška kosmetika; Gyvulių kosmetika.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ķīmiskie tīrīšanas līdzekļi mājsaimniecībām; Ēteriskās eļļas; Smaržas; Kosmētiskie līdzekļi; Kosmētiskie zīmuļi; Kosmētiskās maskas; Lūpu spīdums; Vate kosmētiskiem nolūkiem; Bērnu kosmētika; Kosmētiskie līdzekļi dzīvniekiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Preparazzjonijiet kimiċi tat-tindif għal skopijiet domestiċi; Żjut meħudin minn pjanti; Prodotti ta' fwejjaħ; Kożmetiċi; Lapsijiet tal-ħuġbejn; Maskri kosmetiċi; Lostru tax-xofftejn; Tajjar għal skopijiet kosmetiċi; Kosmetiċi tat-tfal; Kosmetiċi għall-annimali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Chemische reinigingsmiddelen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Etherische oliën; Parfums; Cosmetica; Potloden voor cosmetisch gebruik; Maskers (cosmetische); Lippengloss; Watten voor cosmetisch gebruik; Cosmetica voor kinderen; Cosmetica voor dieren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Preparaty chemiczne do czyszczenia do użytku domowego; Olejki eteryczne; Produkty perfumeryjne; Kosmetyki; Ołówki do brwi; Maski kosmetyczne; Błyszczyki do ust; Wata do celów kosmetycznych; Kosmetyki dla dzieci; Kosmetyki dla zwierząt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Produtos quimicos de limpeza para uso doméstico; Óleos essenciais; Perfumes; Cosméticos; Lápis para uso cosmético; Máscaras cosméticas; Glosses para os lábios; Algodão para uso cosmético; Prdutos cosméticos para crianças; Cosméticos para animais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Preparate chimice de curăţare pentru uz casnic; Uleiuri eterice; Parfumerie (Produse de -); Cosmetice; Creioane pentru sprâncene; Măşti de frumuseţe; Luciu de buze; Vată de uz cosmetic; Cosmetice pentru copii; Produse cosmetice pentru animale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Chemické čistiace prípravky do domácnosti; Esenciálne (éterické) oleje; Voňavkárske výrobky; Kozmetické prípravky; Ceruzky na očné linky; Skrášľovacie masky (kozmetické prípravky); Lesky na pery; Vata na kozmetické použitie; Detská kozmetika; Kozmetické prípravky pre zvieratá.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kemični čistilni pripravki za gospodinjske namene; Eterična olja; Parfumerijski izdelki; Kozmetični izdelki; Kozmetični svinčniki; Kozmetične maske; Bleščilo za ustnice (lip gloss); Vata za kozmetične namene; Kozmetična sredstva za otroke; Kozmetični izdelki za živali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kemiska rengöringspreparat för hushållsändamål; Flyktiga oljor; Parfymerivaror; Kosmetika; Kosmetiska pennor; Kosmetiska masker; Läppglans; Bomull för kosmetiska ändamål; Barnkosmetika; Kosmetika för djur.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Препарати за грижа за кожата [медицински]; Препарати за баня за медицински цели; Антисептици; Разтвори за контактни лещи; Капки за очи; Диетични вещества за медицински цели; Дамски превръзки; Хигиенни меки подложки; Памук за медицински цели; Зъболекарски лак.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přípravky pro péči o pleť [léčivé]; Přípravky do koupelí pro léčebné účely; Antiseptika; Roztoky na kontaktní čočky; Oční kapky; Dietetické látky pro léčebné účely; Hygienické tampóny; Hygienické vložky; Bavlna pro zdravotnické účely; Laky na zuby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Præparater til hudpleje (medicinske); Badepræparater til medicinsk brug; Antiseptiske midler; Opløsninger til brug med kontaktlinser; Øjendråber; Diætetiske substanser tilpasset medicinsk brug; Menstruationstamponer; Hygiejnebind; Bomuld til medicinske formål; Dentallak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Hautpflegemittel (medizinische ); Badezusätze für medizinische Zwecke; Antiseptika; Lösungen für Kontaktlinsen; Augentropfen; Diätische Substanzen für medizinische Zwecke; Tampons für hygienische Zwecke; Damenbinden; Baumwolle für medizinische Zwecke; Zahnlacke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παρασκευάσματα περιποίησης του δέρματος [φαρμακευτικά]· Παρασκευάσματα για το μπάνιο για ιατρική χρήση· Αντισηπτικά· Διαλύματα για φακούς επαφής· Κολλύρια· Διαιτητικές ουσίες προσαρμοσμένες για ιατρικές χρήσεις· Ταμπόν για χρήσεις υγιεινής· Σερβιέτες υγιεινής· Βαμβάκι για ιατρική χρήση· Οδοντικό βερνίκι.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Skin care preparations (medicated); medicated bath preparations; antiseptics; solutions for contact lenses; eye drops; dietetic substances adapted for medical use; sanitary tampons; sanitary pads; cotton for medical purposes; dental lacquer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Preparados para el cuidado de la piel [medicinales]; Preparaciones de baño para uso médico; Antisépticos; Soluciones para lentillas; Gotas para los ojos; Sustancias dietéticas para uso médico; Tampones; Compresas higiénicas; Algodón para uso médico; Lacas dentales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Nahahooldustooted (ravitoimega); Meditsiinilised vannipreparaadid; Antiseptikumid; Kontaktläätsevedelikud; Silmatilgad; Meditsiinilised dieetained; Tampoonid; Hügieenisidemed; Meditsiiniline vatt; Hambalakk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ihonhoitovalmisteet (lääkeaineita sisältävät); Kylpyvalmisteet lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Antiseptiset aineet; Nesteet piilolinssejä varten; Silmätipat; Dieettivalmisteet lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Kuukautistamponit; Terveyssiteet; Vanu lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Hammaslakka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits pour le soin de la peau [médicinaux]; Préparations pour le bain à usage médical; Antiseptiques; Solutions pour verres de contact; Collyre; Substances diététiques à usage médical; Tampons hygiéniques; Serviettes hygiéniques; Coton à usage médical; Laque dentaire.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pripravci za njegu kože [medicinski]; Pripravci za kupanje za medicinske svrhe; Antiseptici; Otopine za kontaktne leće; Kapi za oči; Dijetne tvari za medicinske potrebe; Higijenski taponi; Higijenski ulošci; Pamuk za medicinske potrebe; Zubarski lak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Bőrápoló készítmények (gyógyhatású); Fürdőkészítmények gyógyászati használatra; Fertőtlenítőszerek, antiszeptikus készítmények; Oldatok kontaktlencsékhez; Szemcseppek; Diétás anyagok gyógyászati használatra; Tamponok; Menstruációs betétek; Vatta gyógyászati célokra; Fogászati lakkok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Preparati (medicinali) per la cura della pelle; Preparati per il bagno ad uso medico; Antisettici; Soluzioni per lenti a contatto; Gocce oculari; Sostanze dietetiche per uso medico; Tamponi per la mestruazione; Assorbenti igienici; Cotone per uso medico; Lacche dentarie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Odos priežiūros preparatai [gydomieji]; Vonių preparatai (medicinos reikmėms); Antiseptikai [vaistai nuo pūlinės infekcijos]; Glaustinių [kontaktinių] lęšių tirpalai; Akių lašai; Dietinės medžiagos (medicinos reikmėms); Higieniniai tamponai; Higieniniai rankšluostukai; Medvilnė (medicinos reikmėms); Dantų lakas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ādas kopšanas līdzekļi [medicīniski]; Medicīniski vannas līdzekļi; Antiseptiskie līdzekļi; Šķīdumi kontaktlēcām; Acu pilieni; Diētiskas vielas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Higiēniskie tamponi; Higiēniskās paketes; Vate medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Zobu laka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Preparazzjonijiet għall-kura tal-ġilda [immedikati]; Preparazzjonijiet tal-banju għal finijiet mediċi; Antisettiċi; Soluzzjonijiet għal-lenti tal-kuntatt; Qtar tal-għajnejn; Sustanzi djetetiċi addattati għall-użu mediku; Tampuni; Xugamani sanitarji; Tajjar għal skopijiet mediċi; Verniċ għas-snien.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Huidverzorgingspreparaten [medicinaal]; Badpreparaten voor medisch gebruik; Antiseptische middelen; Contactlensvloeistoffen; Oogdruppels; Diëtische substanties voor medisch gebruik; Tampons voor de menstruatie; Maandverband; Katoen voor geneeskundig gebruik; Lak voor de tanden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Lecznicze produkty ochronne do skóry; Preparaty do kąpieli do celów medycznych; Antyseptyki; Roztwory do szkieł kontaktowych; Krople do oczu; Dietetyczne substancje przystosowane do celów medycznych; Tampony; Podpaski higieniczne; Wata do celów medycznych; Lakier dentystyczny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Preparações [medicinais] para os cuidados da pele; Preparações de banho com fins medicinais; Antisséticos; Soluções para lentes de contacto; Colírio; Substâncias dietéticas para uso medicinal; Tampões; Toalhas higiénicas; Algodão para uso medicinal; Lacas dentárias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Preparate [medicinale] pentru ingrijirea pielii; Preparate pentru baie de uz medical; Antiseptice; Contact (Soluţii pentru lentile de -); Picături de ochi; Dietetice (substanţe - de uz medical); Tampoane pentru menstruaţie; Absorbante menstruale; Bumbac de uz medical; Lacuri dentare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Výrobky na ošetrovanie pleti (liečivé); Prípravky do kúpeľa na lekárske použitie; Antiseptické prípravky, dezinfekčné prípravky; Roztoky na kontaktné šošovky; Očné kvapky; Diétne látky na lekárske použitie; Hygienické tampóny; Hygienické obrúsky; Vata na lekárske použitie; Zubné laky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Proizvodi za nego kože (z zdravilnimi učinkovinami); Pripravki za kopanje za medicinske namene; Antiseptiki; Raztopine za kontaktne leče; Kapljice za oči; Dietetične snovi za medicinsko uporabo; Tamponi; Menstruacijski vložki; Bombaž za medicinske namene; Dentalni lak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hudvårdspreparat (medicinska); Badpreparat för medicinska ändamål; Antiseptiska medel; Lösningar för kontaktlinser; Ögondroppar; Dietiska ämnen för medicinska ändamål; Menstruationskompresser; Dambindor; Bomull för medicinska ändamål; Tandlack.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Апарати за микродермабразио; Стоматологично оборудване; Естетически апарати за масажиране; Галванични терапевтични прибори; Слухови апарати; Апарати за защита на слуха; Приспивателна възглавница против безсъние; Бебешки шишета; Презервативи; Протези за коса.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přístroje pro mikrodermabrazi; Zařízení pro zubní lékařství; Přístroje pro estetickou masáž; Galvanické terapeutické přístroje; Naslouchátka; Prostředky na ochranu sluchu; Uspávací polštářky pro případy nespavosti; Dětské láhve; Kondomy; Vlasové protézy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Apparater til microdermabrasion; Tandlægeapparater og -instrumenter; Apparater til skønhedsmassage; Galvaniske terapeutiske apparater; Hjælpemidler for hørelsen; Udstyr til beskyttelse af hørelsen; Hovedpuder til modvirkning af søvnløshed; Sutteflasker; Kondomer; Hårkarstransplantater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Apparate zur Mikrodermabrasion; Zahnärztliche Apparate und Instrumente; Massagegeräte für die Schönheitspflege; Galvanische Therapiegeräte; Hörgeräte; Gehörschutzgeräte; Kopfkissen gegen Schlaflosigkeit; Babyflaschen; Präservative [Kondome]; Haarprothesen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές μικροδερμοαπόξεσης· Οδοντιατρικός εξοπλισμός· Αισθητική (συσκευές για μαλάξεις -ής)· Γαλβανικές (- θεραπευτικές συσκευές)· Βοηθήματα ακοής· Συσκευές προστασίας ακοής· Προσκέφαλα κατά της αϋπνίας· Υποδοχείς για θήλαστρα· Προφυλακτικά· Προσθετικά μαλλιών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Microdermabrasion apparatus; dental apparatus and instruments; esthetic massage apparatus; galvanic therapeutic appliances; hearing aids; hearing protectors; soporific pillows for insomnia; baby bottles; condoms; hair prostheses.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de microdermoabrasión; Aparatos e instrumentos odontológicos; Aparatos para masajes estéticos; Aparatos galvánicos para uso terapéutico; Audífonos de corrección auditiva; Dispositivos de protección auditiva; Almohadas contra el insomnio; Recipientes para biberones; Preservativos; Prótesis capilares.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Naha mikrolihvimise aparatuur; Hambaraviseadmed ja -riistad; Kosmeetilise massaaži seadmed, aparaadid; Galvanoteraapiaseadmed; Kuuldeaparaadid; Kuulmist kaitsvad seadmed; Uinutuspadjad; Lutipudelid; Kondoomid, preservatiivid; Tehisjuuksed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mikrohiontalaitteet; Hammaslääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Kauneudenhoidossa käytettävät hierontalaitteet; Galvanoterapeuttiset laitteet; Kuulolaitteet; Kuulosuojaimet; Unettomuuden hoitoon tarkoitetut tyynyt; Tuttipullojen säilytysastiat; Kondomit; Hiussiirteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils de microdermabrasion; Appareils et instruments dentaires; Appareils pour massages esthétiques; Appareils thérapeutiques galvaniques; Appareils auditifs; Dispositifs de protection acoustique; Oreillers contre l'insomnie; Supports pour biberons; Préservatifs; Prothèses capillaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Uređaji za mikrodermoabraziju; Stomatološka oprema; Estetska masaža (uređaji za estetsku masažu); Galvanski terapeutski uređaji; Slušna pomagala; Naprave za zaštitu sluha; Jastuci protiv nesanice; Spremnici dječjih bočica; Kondomi; Kapilarne proteze.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Mikrodermabráziós készülékek; Fogászati berendezések; Esztétikai masszírozó készülékek; Galvánterápiás készülékek; Hallókészülékek; Hallásvédő eszközök; Altató hatású fejpárnák álmatlanság ellen; Cumisüvegtartók; Óvszerek; Hajprotézisek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi per microdermoabrasione; Apparecchi e strumenti dentari; Apparecchi per massaggi estetici; Apparecchi terapeutici galvanici; Sussidi per l'udito; Dispositivi per la protezione dell'udito; Guanciali contro l'insonnia; Recipienti per biberon; Preservativi; Protesi capillari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Odos šlifavimo labai mažais kristalais aparatai; Odontologijos aparatūra ir instrumentai; Kosmetinio masažo aparatai; Galvanoterapijos aparatūra; Klausos aparatai; Klausos apsaugos aparatai; Migdomosios pagalvės; Žindymo buteliukai; Prezervatyvai; Dirbtiniai plaukai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mikrodermabrāzijas iekārta; Zobārstniecības iekārtas; Skaistumkopšanai paredzētās masāžas ierīces; Galvaniskās terapeitiskās ierīces; Dzirdes aparāti; Dzirdes aizsardzības ierīces; Spilveni pret bezmiegu; Barošanas pudelīšu turētāji; Prezervatīvi; Matu protēzes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat ta' mikrodermabrazzjoni; Tagħmir dentali; Tagħmir għal massaġġi estetiċi; Tagħmir terapewtiku galvaniku; Mezzi għall-għajnuna fis-smigħ; Mezzi għall-protezzjoni tas-smigħ; Mħaded soporifiċi għall-insomnja; Reċipjenti bħala fliexken għat-tmigħ tat-trabi; Kondoms; Protesi tax-xagħar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Apparaten voor microhuidafschaving; Tandheelkundige apparaten en instrumenten; Schoonheidsmassage-apparaten; Galvanische apparaten voor therapeutisch gebruik; Hoorapparaten; Gehoorbeschermers; Hoofdkussens tegen slapeloosheid; Reservoirs voor zuigflessen; Voorbehoedmiddelen; Haarprotheses.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Aparatura do mikrodermabrazji; Przyrządy i przybory dentystyczne; Przyrządy do masażu estetycznego; Galwaniczna aparatura terapeutyczna; Aparaty słuchowe; Aparaty do ochrony słuchu; Poduszki przeciw bezsenności; Pojemniki na butelki do karmienia; Prezerwatywy; Włosy (Sztuczne -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos de microdermoabrasão; Aparelhos e instrumentos dentários; Aparelhos para massagens estéticas; Aparelhos terapêuticos galvânicos; Auxiliares auditivos; Dispositivos para proteção auditiva; Almofadas contra a insónia; Biberons [biberões]; Preservativos; Próteses capilares.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate pentru microdermoabraziune; Echipament stomatologic; Aparate pentru masaje estetice; Aparate pentru terapie galvanică; Dispozitive auditive; Dispozitive pentru protecţia auzului; Perne contra insomniei; Recipiente pentru biberoane; Prezervative; Proteze capilare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Prístroje na mikrodermabráziu; Zubárske prístroje a nástroje; Zariadenia na estetickú masáž; Galvanické terapeutické zariadenia; Načúvacie pomôcky; Chrániče sluchu; Vankúše proti nespavosti; Detské fľaše; Kondómy, prezervatívy; Vlasové protézy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Aparati za mikrodermoabrazijo; Zobozdravstveni aparati in instrumenti; Masažni aparati za estetske učinke; Terapevtske naprave z galvanskim tokom; Slušni pripomočki; Naprave za zaščito sluha; Uspavalne blazine za nespečnost; Posodice za stekleničke za hranjenje; Kondomi; Lasni vstavki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hudslipningsapparater; Dentala utrustningar; Massageapparater för skönhetsvård; Galvaniska terapiapparater; Hörselhjälpmedel; Hörselskyddsanordningar; Sömngivande kuddar mot sömnlöshet; Nappflaskor; Kondomer; Hårimplantat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Произведения на изкуството от порцелан, теракота или стъкло; Гребени за коса; Четки за мигли; Тоалетни чанти; Несесери за козметични принадлежности; Пухчета за пудра; Приспособления за отстраняване на грим; Разделители от пяна, за пръсти на крака, за употреба при педикюр; Козметични четки; Механични инструменти (неелектрически) за почистване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Umělecká díla z porcelánu, keramiky, kameniny nebo skla; Hřebeny na vlasy; Kartáčky na řasy; Toaletní taštičky; Pouzdra na kosmetické potřeby; Labutěnky na pudrování; Zařízení na odličování; Pěnové pedikérní separátory prstů; Štětce na nanášení líčidel; Mechanické nástroje (neelektrické) pro čištění.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kunstgenstande af porcelæn, keramik, lertøj, terrakotta eller glas; Hårkamme; Øjenvippebørster; Rejsenecessaire; Æsker tilpasset til kosmetikredskaber; Pudderkvaster; Make-up fjerneapparater; Tåskillere af skum til brug ved pedicure; Kosmetikbørster; Mekaniske instrumenter (ikke-elektriske) til rengøringsformål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kunstgegenstände aus Porzellan, Keramik, Steingut, Terrakotta oder Glas; Haarkämme; Wimpernbürsten; Toilettenecessaires; Etuis für kosmetische Geräte; Puderquasten; Abschminkgeräte; Zehentrenner aus Schaumstoff für die Pediküre; Kosmetikpinsel; Mechanische Instrumente (nicht elektrisch) für Reinigungszwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Έργα τέχνης από πορσελάνη, κεραμικό, πηλό, ή γυαλί· Χτένες για τα μαλλιά· Βουρτσάκια για τις βλεφαρίδες· Σετ τουαλέτας σε τσαντάκι· Θήκες προσαρμοσμένες για σύνεργα καλλωπισμού· Σφουγγαράκια πουδραρίσματος· Συσκευές αφαίρεσης μακιγιάζ· Διαχωριστικά για τα δάχτυλα των ποδιών από αφρώδες υλικό για χρήση στην ποδοκομία (πεντικιούρ)· Καλλυντικές βούρτσες· Μηχανικά όργανα καθαρισμού (μη ηλεκτρικά).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Works of art of porcelain, ceramic, earthenware, terra-cotta or glass; hair combs; eyelash brushes; toiletry cases; cases adapted for cosmetic utensils; powder puffs; make-up removing appliances; foam toe separators for use in pedicures; cosmetics brushes; mechanical instruments (non electric) for cleaning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Objetos de arte de porcelana, cerámica, loza, barro cocido o vidrio; Peines para el cabello; Cepillos para pestañas; Neceseres de tocador; Neceseres para utensilios cosméticos; Borlas de polvera; Aparatos para desmaquillar; Separadores interdigitales de espuma para la pedicura; Cepillos para uso cosmético; Instrumentos mecánicos (no eléctricos) para limpieza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Portselanist, savist, keraamilistest materjalidest, terrakotast või klaasist kunstiteosed, taiesed; Juuksekammid; Ripsmepintslid; Tualett-tarvete kotid; Kosmeetikatarvetekotid; Puudritupsud; Meigieemaldustarvikud; Vahtplastist varbavahekud pediküüris kasutamiseks; Kosmeetikaharjad; Mitteelektrilised mehaanilised puhastusseadmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Taide-esineet posliinia, keramiikkaa, savea, terrakottaa tai lasia; Hiuskammat; Silmäripsiharjat; Toalettilaukut; Kotelot kosmetiikkavälineille; Puuterihuiskut; Ehostuksen poistovälineet; Jalkahoidossa käytettävät vaahtomuoviset varpaanerottelijat; Harjat kosmeettisiin tarkoituksiin; Mekaaniset puhdistusvälineet (muut kuin sähkökäyttöiset).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Objets d'art en porcelaine, en céramique, en faïence, en terre cuite ou en verre; Peignes à cheveux; Brosses à cils; Nécessaires de toilette; Boîtes pour ustensiles cosmétiques; Houppes à poudrer; Appareils pour le démaquillage; Séparateurs d'orteils en mousse pour soins de pédicurie; Pinceaux de maquillage; Instruments mécaniques (non électriques) pour le nettoyage.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Umjetnički predmeti od porculana, terakote ili od stakla; Češljevi za kosu; Četkice za trepavice; Toaletni neseseri; Torbice za kozmetički pribor; Jastučići za nanošenje pudera; Pribor za skidanje šminke; Separatori nožnih prstiju od pjene za uporabu u pedikuri; Kozmetičke četke; Mehanički instrumenti (neelektrični) za čišćenje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Műtárgyak porcelánból, kerámiából, agyagból vagy üvegből; Hajfésűk; Szempilla kefék; Piperetáskák, neszesszerek; Tokok kozmetikai eszközökhöz; Púderpamacsok; Sminkeltávolító termékek; Szivacsos lábujjszétválasztók pedikűrözéshez; Kozmetikai ecsetek, pipere ecsetek; Mechanikus műszerek (nem elektromos) tisztításhoz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Oggetti d'arte in porcellana, in ceramica, in terracotta o in vetro; Pettini per capelli; Spazzole per le ciglia; Nécessaire per la toilette; Astucci per utensili cosmetici; Piumino della cipria; Apparecchi elettrici per togliere il trucco; Separatori per le dita dei piedi per pedicure; Spazzole per usi cosmetici; Strumenti meccanici (non elettrici) per pulizia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Porceliano, keramikos, molio ar stiklo meno dirbiniai; Plaukų šukos; Blakstienų šepetėliai; Tualeto reikmeninės; Kosmetikos reikmenų dėklai; Pudrinukai; Grimo valymo reikmenys; Putplasčio kojų pirštų skirtukai (pedikiūro reikmėms); Kosmetiniai šepetėliai; Mechaniniai valymo instrumentai (ne elektriniai).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mākslas darbi no porcelāna, terakotas vai stikla; Matu ķemmes; Skropstu birstītes; Tualetes maciņi; Ietvari, kas pielāgoti kosmētikas piederumiem; Pūdera spilventiņi; Piederumi dekoratīvās kosmētikas noņemšanai; Putu materiāla ieliktņi pirkstu atdalīšanai, paredzēti izmantošanai pedikīrā; Kosmētikas otiņas; Mehāniskie instrumenti [nav elektriski] tīrīšanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Oġġetti artistiċi tal-porċellana, tat-terrakotta u tal-ħġieġ; Pettnijiet għax-xagħar; Pniezel tax-xagħar ta' xfar l-għajnejn; Kaxxi fejn jitpoġġew l-oġġetti tat-twaletta; Kaxxetti adattati għal għodod kożmetiċi; Peds għat-terra; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tneħħija tal-irtokk; Separaturi tal-fowm għas-subgħajn tas-saqajn għall-użu fil-pedikjur; Pniezel kożmetiċi; Strumenti mekkaniċi (mhux elettriċi) tat-tindif.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kunstvoorwerpen van porselein, keramiek, aardwerk of glas; Haarkammen; Borstels voor de oogwimpers; Toiletnecessaires; Etuis voor cosmetisch gerei; Poederkwasten; Elektrische apparaten voor het verwijderen van make-up; Schuimvormen voor het uit elkaar houden van de tenen voor gebruik bij voetverzorging; Borstels voor cosmetische doeleinden; Mechanische instrumenten (niet-elektrische) voor reiniging.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dzieła sztuki z porcelany, ceramiki, gliny, terakoty i szkła; Grzebienie do włosów; Szczoteczki do rzęs; Kosmetyczki na przybory toaletowe; Futerały dopasowane do przyborów kosmetycznych; Puszki do pudru; Przyrządy do demakijażu; Separatory piankowe do palców stóp do użytku podczas pedicure; Pędzle kosmetyczne; Przyrządy mechaniczne (nieelektryczne) do czyszczenia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Objetos de arte em porcelana, cerâmica, barro, terracota ou vidro; Pentes para os cabelos; Escovas para pestanas; Bolsas de toucador; Estojos concebidos para utensílios cosméticos; Esponjas de pó-de-arroz; Aparelhos para remover maquilhagem; Esponjas para separar dedos dos pés, para uso em pedicura; Escovas para fins cosméticos; Instrumentos mecânicos (não elétricos) para limpeza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Lucrări de artă din porţelan, teracotă sau sticlă; Pieptene; Periuţe pentru gene; Truse de toaletă; Cutii adaptate pentru ustensile cosmetice; Pămătufuri pentru pudrat; Dispozitive de demachiere; Separatoare din spumă pentru degetele de la picioare folosite în pedichiură; Pensule de uz cosmetic; Instrumente mecanice (neelectrice) pentru curățat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Porcelánové, keramické, kameninové alebo sklenené umelecké predmety; Hrebene na vlasy; Kefky na očné riasy; Tašky alebo kufríky na toaletné potreby; Puzdrá pre kozmetické potreby; Labutienky; Odličovacie pomôcky; Penové oddeľovače prstov na nohách (pedikérske potreby); Kozmetické štetce; Mechanické nástroje (neelektrické) na čistenie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Umetniška dela iz porcelana, terakote ali stekla; Glavniki za lase; Ščetke za trepalnice; Toaletne torbice; Torbice, prirejene za kozmetične potrebščine; Pudrne blazinice; Aparati za odstranjevanje ličil; Razdelilci iz penaste gume za uporabo v pedikuri; Čopiči za kozmetične namene; Mehanski instrumenti (neelektrični) za čiščenje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Konstföremål av porslin, keramik, lergods, terrakotta eller glas; Hårkammar; Borstar för ögonfransar; Resenecessärer (inredda); Fodral anpassade till kosmetiska redskap; Pudervippor; Redskap för sminkborttagning; Tåseparatorer av skum för användning i pedikyr; Sminkborstar; Mekaniska instrument (ej elektriska) för rengöring.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Реклама; Администрация на бизнес дела за франчайзинг; Поместване на реклами за трети лица; Осигуряване на онлайн пазар за покупко-продажби на стоки и услуги; Агенции за внос и износ; Представяне на стоки с цел продажаба на дребно чрез всички средства за комуникация; Систематизиране на информация в компютърни бази данни; Бизнес одити; Консултантски услуги в областта на човешките ресурси; Търговия на дребно и едро с фармацевтични, ветеринарни, санитарни и медицински препарати.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Propagační činnost, reklama; Správa obchodních věcí v oblasti franšíz; Umisťování reklam pro třetí osoby; Provozování online trhu pro kupující a prodejce výrobků a služeb; Služby agentury zaměřené na export a import; Prezentace výrobků v komunikačních médiích pro účely maloobchodu; Systematizace údajů do počítačových databází; Provádění podnikových auditů; Poradenství v oblasti řízení lidských zdrojů; Služby pro maloobchod nebo velkoobchod s farmaceutickými, veterinárními a sanitárními přípravky a zdravotnickým materiálem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed; Administration af forretningsanliggender i forbindelse med franchisevirksomhed; Placering af reklamer og annoncer for andre; Tilvejebringelse af en onlinemarkedsplads til købere og sælgere af varer og tjenesteydelser; Import- og eksportagenturer; Præsentation af varer på kommunikationsmedier til detailhandelsmæssige formål; Sortering og redigering af informationer computerdatabaser; Virksomhedsrevision; Rådgivning vedrørende personaleledelse; Detailhandel med farmaceutiske, veterinære og sanitære præparater samt medicinske artikler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werbung; Verwaltung der geschäftlichen Angelegenheiten von Franchise-Unternehmen; Platzierung von Anzeigen für Dritte; Bereitstellen eines Online-Marktplatzes für Käufer und Verkäufer von Waren und Dienstleistungen; Dienstleistungen einer Im- und Exportagentur; Präsentation von Waren in Kommunikations-Medien für den Einzelhandel; Systematisierung von Daten in Computerdatenbanken; Prüfen von Geschäftsabläufen; Beratung in Fragen des Personalwesens; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf pharmazeutische, medizinische und veterinärmedizinische Artikel sowie Hygienepräparate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαφήμιση· Διοίκηση των επιχειρηματικών υποθέσεων αλυσίδων δικαιόχρησης· Καταχώριση διαφημίσεων για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Παροχή χώρων αγορών επί γραμμής για αγοραστές και πωλητές προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών· Πρακτορεία εισαγωγών-εξαγωγών· Παρουσίαση αγαθών σε μέσα επικοινωνίας με σκοπό τη λιανική πώληση· Συστηματοποίηση δεδομένων σε βάσεις δεδομένων· Λογιστικός έλεγχος επιχειρήσεων· Συμβουλευτική για θέματα διοίκησης προσωπικού· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής ή χονδρικής για προμήθειες φαρμακευτικών, κτηνιατικών, ιατρικών και ειδών υγιεινής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Advertising; administration of the business affairs of franchises; placing advertisements (for others); provision of an online marketplace for buyers and sellers of goods and services; import-export agencies; presentation of goods on communication media, for retail purposes; systemization of information into computer databases; business auditing; personnel management consultancy; retail services for pharmaceutical, veterinary and sanitary preparations and medical supplies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicidad; Administración de asuntos de negocios de franquicias; Colocación de anuncios para terceros; Suministro de espacios de venta en línea para vendedores y compradores de productos y servicios; Servicios de agencias de importación-exportación; Presentación de productos en cualquier medio de comunicación para su venta minorista; Sistematización de información en bases de datos informáticas; Auditoría empresarial; Consultoría en gestión de personal; Servicios de venta minorista de preparaciones farmacéuticas, veterinarias y sanitarias, así como de suministros médicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reklaam; Frantsiisidega seotud äritegevuse juhtimine; Kuulutuste ülespanemisteenused teistele; Veebipõhise müügikeskkonna pakkumine kaupade ja teenuste ostjatele ning müüjatele; Ekspordi- ja impordiagentuuride teenused; Kaupade jaemüügi reklaam meediakanalites; Info süstematiseerimine arvuti andmebaasides; Äri auditeerimine; Personalijuhtimisalane nõustamine; Farmaatsia- ja veterinaariapreparaatide ning hügieeni- ja meditsiinitarvete jae- ja hulgimüük.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mainonta; Franchising-liiketoiminnan hallinnointi; Mainosten sijoittelu muiden lukuun; Online-markkinapaikan tarjoaminen tavaroiden ja palvelujen ostajille ja myyjille; Tuonti- ja vientiagentuuripalvelut; Tavaraesittely tiedotusvälineissä vähittäismyyntiä varten; Tietokantatietojen systematisointi; Yritysten tilintarkastus; Henkilöstöhallintakonsultointi; Farmaseuttisten ja eläinlääkinnällisten valmisteiden, saniteettivalmisteiden sekä lääkintätarvikkeiden vähittäiskauppapalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publicité; Services administratifs relatifs aux affaires commerciales de franchises; Emplacement de publicités pour des tiers; Mise à disposition d'espaces de vente en ligne pour acheteurs et vendeurs de produits et services; Services d'agences d'import-export; Présentation de produits sur tout moyen de communication pour la vente au détail; Systématisation des données dans des bases de données informatiques; Audits d'entreprises [analyses commerciales]; Consultation pour les questions de personnel; Services de vente au détail de préparations pharmaceutiques, vétérinaires et hygiéniques ainsi que de fournitures médicales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Oglašavanje; Upravljanje poslovnim aktivnostima franšiza; Postavljanje reklama za druge; Pružanje internetskog tržišnog prostora za kupce i prodavatelje proizvoda i usluga; Agencije za uvoz-izvoz; Prezentacija robe putem komunikacijskih medija, u maloprodajne svrhe; Sistematiziranje podataka za središnju kartoteku; Vođenje knjiga; Savjetovanje o osoblju; Usluge maloprodaje ili veleprodaje za farmaceutske, veterinarske i sanitarne pripravke i za medicinske potrepštine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Reklámozás; Franchise-zal kapcsolatos üzleti ügyek adminisztrációja; Szolgáltatás reklámok elhelyezésére; Online piactér biztosítása áruk és szolgáltatások eladói és vásárlói részére; Import-export ügynökségek; Áruk bemutatása kommunikációs médiában, kiskereskedelmi célokból; Információk számítógépes adatbázisokba való rendezése; Üzleti könyvvizsgálat; Konzultáció személyzeti kérdésekben; Gyógyszerészeti, állatgyógyászati és higiéniai készítmények valamint gyógyászati eszközök kis- és nagykereskedelme.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicità; Amministrazione degli affari commerciali di affiliati; Collocazione di annunci pubblicitari per conto terzi; Fornitura su mercato on-line di beni e servizi per acquirenti e venditori; Servizi di agenzie per l'importazione e l'esportazione; Presentazione di prodotti con mezzi di comunicazione per la vendita al dettaglio; Sistemazione di informazioni in banche dati informatiche; Verifica di conti; Consulenza in materia di gestione del personale; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio di preparati farmaceutici, veterinari e sanitari e di forniture mediche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Reklama; Verslo reikalų, susijusių su franšize, administravimas; Reklamos kitiems skelbimas; Interneto prekyviečių teikimas prekių ir paslaugų pardavėjams bei pirkėjams; Importo ir eksporto agentūrų paslaugos; Prekių pateikimas žiniasklaidoje pardavimo reikmėms; Informacijos sisteminimas į kompiuterines duomenų bazes; Verslo auditas; Personalo vadybos konsultacijos; Mažmeninė ar didmeninė prekyba farmacijos, veterinarijos ir higienos preparatais bei medicinos reikmenimis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reklāma; Uzņēmējdarbības franšīzu administrēšana; Reklāmas izvietošana citu personu interesēs; Tiešsaistes tirgus nodrošināšana preču un pakalpojumu pārdevējiem un pircējiem; Importa-eksporta aģentūru pakalpojumi; Preču demonstrēšana komunikācijas līdzekļos mazumtirdzniecības vajadzībām; Informācijas sistematizēšana datoru datu bāzēs; Audita pakalpojumi; Konsultāciju sniegšana personālvadībā; Farmaceitisko, veterināro un higiēnas preparātu un medicīnisko preču mazumtirdzniecība un vairumtirdzniecība.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reklamar; Amministrazzjoni tal-affarijiet tan-negozju ta' frankiġji; It-tpoġġija ta' reklami għal oħrajn; Forniment ta' suq onlajn għal xerrejja u bejjiegħa ta' prodotti u servizzi; Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-importazzjoni u esportazzjoni; Il-preżentazzjoni ta' oġġetti fuq mezzi tal-komunikazzjoni, għal skopijiet ta' bejgħ bl-imnut; Is-sistematizzazzjoni ta' informazzjoni f'dejtabejżis tal-kompjuter; Awditjar għan-negozji; Konsulenza dwar il-ġestjoni tal-personàl; Servizzi kemm bl-imnut jew bl-ingrossa għall-forniment ta' oġġetti farmaċewtiċi, veterinarji, medikali u preparazzjonijiet sanitarji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reclame; Administratieve diensten inzake de commerciële zaken van franchiseondernemingen; Het plaatsen van advertenties voor derden; Ter beschikking stellen van online verkoopplaats voor kopers en verkopers van goederen en diensten; Import- en exportagentschappen; Presentatie van goederen op communicatiemedia, voor verkoopdoeleinden; Systematisering van gegevens in een centraal bestand; Zakelijke analyse van bedrijven [auditing]; Advisering met betrekking tot personeel; Detailhandels- of groothandelsdiensten in farmaceutische, veterinaire en hygiënische preparaten en medische hulpmiddelen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Reklama; Administrowanie działalnością gospodarczą w zakresie franchisingu; Zamieszczanie ogłoszeń dla osób trzecich; Zapewnianie platformy internetowej dla nabywców i sprzedawców towarów i usług; Usługi agencji importowo-eksportowych; Prezentowanie produktów w mediach dla celów sprzedaży detalicznej; Systematyzacja danych w komputerowych bazach danych; Audyt przedsiębiorstw; Doradztwo w zakresie zarządzania personelem; Sprzedaż detaliczna środków farmaceutycznych, weterynaryjnych i sanitarnych oraz zaopatrzenia medycznego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicidade; Administração de assuntos de negócios de franquias; Colocação de anúncios para terceiros; Disponibilização de um espaço de mercado on-line para compradores e vendedores de produtos e serviços; Agências de importação-exportação; Apresentação de produtos nos meios de comunicação, para fins de venda a retalho; Sistematização de dados em bases de dados informáticas; Auditorias de empresas; Consultadoria de gestão de pessoal; Serviços de venda a retalho de preparações farmacêuticas, veterinárias e higiénicas e provisões médicas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicitate; Administrarea afacerilor în sistem de franciză; Plasarea de anunţuri publicitare pentru terţi; Furnizarea unei pieţe online pentru cumpărătorii şi vânzătorii de bunuri şi servicii; Agenţii de import-export; Prezentarea produselor prin toate mijloacele de comunicare pentru vânzarea cu amănuntul; Sistematizarea informaţiilor în fişiere electronice; Contabilitate; Consultanţă în gestiune de personal; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul sau en-gros pentru preparate farmaceutice, veterinare şi sanitare şi produse medicale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reklamné služby; Správa obchodných záležitostí franchisingových podnikov; Umiestňovanie reklám pre iné firmy a osoby; Online poskytovanie obchodného priestoru pre nákupcov a predajcov tovarov a služieb; Kancelárie zaoberajúce sa dovozom a vývozom; Prezentácia výrobkov v komunikačných médiách pre maloobchod; Zoraďovanie údajov v počítačových databázach; Účtovníctvo; Personálne poradenstvo; Maloobchodné alebo veľkoobchodné služby s farmaceutickými, zverolekárskymi a zdravotníckymi prípravkami a s lekárskymi potrebami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oglasna dejavnost; Administracija poslovnih zadev franšiz; Nameščanje oglasov za druge; Zagotavljanje spletnega trga za kupce in prodajalce blaga in storitev; Uvozno - izvozne agencije; Predstavitev blaga v komunikacijskih medijih (prodaja na drobno); Sistematizacija informacij v računalniške baze podatkov; Poslovno revidiranje; Svetovanje pri kadrovanju; Maloprodajne ali veleprodajne storitve za farmacevtske, veterinarske in sanitarne proizvode in medicinske potrebščine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Annons- och reklamverksamhet; Administration av affärsverksamhet för franchiseföretag; Placering av annonser för andras räkning; Tillhandahållande av en marknadsplats on-line för köpare och säljare av varor och tjänster; Import-exportagenturer; Presentation av varor på kommersiella media, för försäljningsändamål; Systematisering av information i databaser; Företagsrevision; Konsultationer avseende personaladministration; Återförsäljning eller detaljhandelstjänster för farmaceutiska, veterinära och sanitära preparat och medicinska varor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>44</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Медицински клиники; Пластична хирургия; Медицински спа услуги; Консултантски услуги, свързани със здравето; Ароматотерапия; Фризьорски услуги; Козметични гримьорски услуги; Епилиране с восък; Услуги за грижа за тоалета на животни; Оптометрични услуги.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zdravotnická střediska; Plastická chirurgie; Lékařské lázeňské služby; Zdravotní poradenství; Aromaterapie; Kadeřnictví; Kosmetické služby týkající se líčení; Depilace voskem; Péče o vzhled domácích zvířat; Služby v oblasti optometrie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tjenester ydet af medicinske klinikker; Plastikkirurgi; Medicinsk spavirksomhed; Rådgivning om sundhed; Aromaterapi; Klipning og styling af hår; Tjenester inden for kosmetisk makeup; Hårfjernende voksbehandling; Soignering af dyr; Optometriske tjenesteydelser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Dienstleistungen von Kliniken [Ambulanzen]; Plastische und Schönheitschirurgie; Betrieb von medizinischen Heilbädern; Beratungsdienste in Bezug auf Gesundheit; Aromatherapie-Dienste; Dienstleistungen eines Friseursalons; Kosmetische Make-up-Behandlungen; Haarentfernung mit Wachs; Kosmetische Pflege von Haustieren; Optometrische Dienste.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες ιατρικής κλινικής· Πλαστική χειρουργική· Υπηρεσίες ιατρικών ιαματικών λουτρών· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σε θέματα υγείας· Αρωματοθεραπεία (Υπηρεσίες -)· Υπηρεσίες κομμωτικής· Υπηρεσίες καλλυντικού μακιγιάζ· Αποτρίχωση με κερί· Υπηρεσίες καλλωπισμού ζώων· Υπηρεσίες οπτομετρίας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Medical clinic services; plastic surgery; medical spa services; advisory services relating to health; aromatherapy services; hairdressing; cosmetic make-up services; depilatory waxing; pet grooming; optometry.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de clínicas médicas; Cirugía plástica; Servicios de balneario médico; Consultoría en materia de salud; Servicios de aromaterapia; Peluquería; Servicios de maquillaje cosmético; Depilación con cera; Servicios de peluquería para animales domésticos; Servicios de optometría.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kliinikute, kliiniliste haiglate meditsiiniteenused; Plastiline kirurgia; Ravispaa-teenused; Tervisealased nõustamisteenused; Aroomiteraapiateenused; Juuksuritööd; Kosmeetilised jumestusteenused; Vahatamine karvade eemaldamiseks, depileerimine; Loomahooldusteenused; Optomeetriateenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lääkintäklinikoiden palvelut; Plastiikkakirurgia; Lääketieteelliset kylpyläpalvelut; Terveysneuvonta; Aromaterapiapalvelut; Kampaamot; Kosmeettiset meikkauspalvelut; Ihokarvojen poisto vahaamalla; Lemmikkieläinten siistimispalvelut; Näönhuoltopalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de clinique médicale; Chirurgie plastique; Services de cures thermales médicalisées; Conseils en matière de santé; Services d'aromathérapie; Coiffure; Services de maquillage [cosmétique]; Épilation à la cire; Toilettage d'animaux de compagnie; Services d'optométrie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Medicinske kliničke usluge; Estetska kirurgija; Medicinske usluge toplica; Savjetodavne usluge u svezi sa zdravljem; Usluge aromaterapije; Frizerske usluge; Usluge kozmetičkog šminkanja; Depilacija voskom; Usluge njege životinja; Optometrijske usluge.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Klinikák, orvos rendelők szolgáltatásai; Plasztikai sebészet; Gyógyfürdő szolgáltatások; Egészséggel kapcsolatos tanácsadó szolgáltatások; Aromaterápiás szolgáltatások; Fodrászat; Kozmetikai sminkelési szolgáltatások; Gyantás szőrtelenítés; Állatápolási szolgáltatások; Optometriai szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cliniche (mediche); Chirurgia plastica; Servizi offerti da centri medico-termali; Servizi di consulenza in materia di salute; Servizi di aromaterapia; Servizi di saloni di parrucchiere; Servizi cosmetici di truccatura; Depilazione con cera; Toelettatura di animali da compagnia; Servizi offerti da optometristi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Medicinos klinikų paslaugos; Plastinė chirurgija; Medicininių SPA centrų paslaugos; Sveikatos konsultacijos; Aromaterapijos paslaugos; Plaukų stilistų ir kirpėjų paslaugos; Kosmetinio makiažo paslaugos; Depiliacija vašku; Gyvūnų higieninės ir grožio priežiūros paslaugos; Optometrijos paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Medicīnisko klīniku pakalpojumi; Plastiskā ķirurģija; Medicīniski spa pakalpojumi; Konsultācijas veselības jautājumos; Aromterapijas pakalpojumi; Frizētavu pakalpojumi; Dekoratīvās kosmētikas uzklāšanas pakalpojumi; Vaksācija depilācijas nolūkiem; Dzīvnieku kopšana; Optometrijas pakalpojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' klinika medika; Kirurġija plastika; Servizzi ta' spa mediku; Servizzi ta' pariri relatati mas-saħħa; Servizzi ta' aromaterapija; Servizzi għall-irranġar jew għall-qtugħ tax-xagħar; Servizzi ta' mejkapp kosmetiku; Xemgħa depilatorja; Servizzi għas-sbuħija tal-annimali; Servizzi ottometriċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diensten van medische klinieken; Plastische chirurgie; Medische kuuroorden; Gezondheid (Advisering op het gebied van -); Aromatherapie; Kappersdiensten; Cosmetische make-up diensten; Epileren met hars; Dierenverzorging; Optometrische diensten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi klinik medycznych; Chirurgia plastyczna; Usługi spa medycznych; Usługi doradcze w zakresie zdrowia; Aromaterapia; Fryzjerstwo; Usługi kosmetyczne w zakresie wykonywania makijażu; Depilacja woskiem; Usługi w zakresie pielęgnacji zwierząt; Usługi optometryczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de clínicas médicas; Cirurgia plástica; Serviços médico-termais; Serviços de assessoria relacionados com saúde; Serviços de aromaterapia; Cabeleireiros; Serviços de maquilhagem cosmética; Depilação a cera; Serviços de tratamento e beleza animal; Serviços de optometria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii ale clinicilor medicale; Chirurgie estetică; Servicii medicale de staţiuni balneare; Consiliere în materie de sănătate; Servicii de aromaterapie; Servicii de coafare a părului; Servicii de machiaj cosmetic; Epilat cu ceară; Servicii de îngrijire a animalelor; Servicii de optometrie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zdravotné strediská (služby); Plastická chirurgia; Lekárske kúpeľné služby; Zdravotné poradenstvo; Aromaterapeutické služby; Kadernícke salóny; Kozmetické služby líčenia tváre; Depilácia voskom; Starostlivosť o vzhľad zvierat; Optometrické služby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve zdravstvenih klinik; Plastična kirurgija; Medicinske zdraviliške storitve; Zdravstveno svetovanje; Storitve aromaterapije; Frizerstvo; Storitve kozmetičnega ličenja; Depilacijsko voskanje; Živalska oskrba (nega); Storitve optometrije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Medicinska kliniktjänster; Plastikkirurgi; Medicinska hälsobadstjänster; Rådgivningstjänster avseende hälsa; Aromterapitjänster; Hårfrisering; Kosmetiska sminktjänster; Hårborttagning med vax; Djurtrimningstjänster; Optometriska tjänster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/094</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-20</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/165</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-31</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1035187</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>28510</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
