<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T11:10:29</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229009</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229009</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>TankerStreet</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Щипки за пране; Четина (Животинска -) [четкарска]; Найлонови ръкавици за домакински цели; Изтъркващи гъбички с метални влакна за домакински цели; Четки за нокти; Поставки за четки за зъби; Контейнери за козметика; Несесери за козметика [окомплектовани]; Празни бутилки за пръскане; Почистващи гъби за лице; Поставки за сапун; Поставки за тоалетна хартия; Пластмасови пръскателни дюзи; Съдове за пресаждане за растения; Сламки за напитки; Форми за кекс; Вилици за сервиране; Лъжици за оформяне на топки [домакински или кухненски прибори]; Подложки за предпазване на повърхността на масата, не от хартия или текстил; Сервизи и прибори за маса [с изключение на ножове, вилици и лъжици], не от благороден метал; Тави за приготвяне на кейкове.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kolíčky na prádlo; Zvířecí štětiny [kartáčnické zboží]; Plastové domácí rukavice; Drátěnky pro domácnost; Kartáčky na nehty; Držáky na zubní kartáčky; Nádoby na kosmetiku; Kosmetické taštičky (vybavené); Prázdné rozprašovací láhve; Mycí houby na čištění obličeje; Stojany na mýdlo; Držáky na toaletní papír; Plastové rozprašovací trysky; Nádoby na přesazování rostlin; Brčka na pití; Formy na dorty; Servírovací vidličky; Servírovací lopatky [domácí nebo kuchyňské náčiní]; Podložky pod (horké) nádobí, ne papírové nebo textilní; Stolní nádobí, nikoliv nože, vidličky a lžíce; Formy na koláče a dorty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tøjklemmer; Børstehår [animalske]; Plastikhandsker til husholdningsbrug; Grydesvampe til husholdningsbrug; Neglebørster; Tandbørsteholdere; Beholdere til kosmetik; Kosmetiktasker [tilpassede]; Tomme sprayflasker; Rensesvampe til ansigtet; Sæbeholdere; Toiletpapirholdere; Spraydyser af plastik; Beholdere til ompotning af planter; Sugerør; Kageforme; Anrettergafler; Serveringsskeer [husholdnings- og køkkenredskaber]; Bordskånere, ikke af papir eller tekstiler; Bordservice, undtagen knive, gafler og skeer; Kageforme i letmetal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wäscheklammern; Tierborsten [Bürsten- und Pinselwaren]; Kunststoffhandschuhe für Haushaltszwecke; Putzkissen für Haushaltszwecke; Nagelbürsten; Zahnbürstenhalter; Aufbewahrungsbehälter für Kosmetika [nicht angepasst]; An kosmetische Geräte angepasste Taschen; Leere Sprayflaschen; Gesichtsreinigungsschwämme; Seifenschalen; Toilettenpapierhalter; Zerstäuberdüse aus Kunststoff für Beregnungsgeräte; Behälter zum Umtopfen von Pflanzen; Trinkhalme; Kuchenformen; Serviergabeln; Portionierer [Haushalts- oder Küchenutensilien]; Nicht aus Papier oder Stoff bestehende Tischdeckchen; Tafelgeschirr; Kuchenbackformen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μανταλάκια λευκών ειδών· Ζώων (τρίχωμα -) [βούρτσες και πινέλα]· Πλαστικά γάντια για οικιακή χρήση· Συρμάτινα σφουγγαράκια καθαρισμού για οικιακή χρήση· Βούρτσες μαλλιών, νυχιών και οδοντόβουρτσες· Υποδοχές για οδοντόβουρτσες· Δοχεία για καλλυντικά· Τσαντάκια καλλυντικών [με χωρίσματα]· Άδειες φιάλες ψεκασμού· Σπόγγοι καθαρισμού προσώπου· Σχάρες για σαπούνια· Θήκες χαρτιού τουαλέτας· Πλαστικά ακροφύσια ψεκασμού· Δοχεία για μεταφύτευση φυτών· Καλαμάκια· Γλυκίσματα (Φόρμες για -)· Πιρούνες σερβιρίσματος· Κουτάλες σερβιρίσματος [μικρά σκεύη οικιακής και μαγειρικής χρήσης]· Επιτραπέζιες προστατευτικές βάσεις σερβίτσιων, όχι από χαρτί ή ύφασμα· Επιτραπέζια σκεύη, εκτός από μαχαίρια, πιρούνια και κουτάλια· Φόρμες για κέικ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Clothes-pegs; Animal bristles [brushware]; Household plastic gloves; Household scouring pads; Nail brushes; Toothbrush holders; Containers for cosmetics; Cosmetic bags [fitted]; Empty spray bottles; Facial cleansing sponges; Soap racks; Toilet paper holders; Plastic spray nozzles; Repotting containers for plants; Straws for drinking; Cake moulds; Serving forks; Serving scoops [household or kitchen utensil]; Tablemats, not of paper or textile; Tableware, other than knives, forks and spoons; Cake tins.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pinzas para la ropa; Cerdas de animales [cepillos y pinceles]; Guantes domésticos de plástico; Estropajos metálicos de uso doméstico para limpiar; Cepillos de uñas; Soportes para cepillos de dientes; Recipientes para cosméticos; Bolsas para cosméticos [equipadas]; Botellas de aerosol vacías; Esponjas limpiadoras faciales; Jaboneras; Portarrollos de papel higiénico; Toberas pulverizadoras de plástico; Recipientes de trasplante para plantas; Pajillas para beber; Moldes para pasteles; Tenedores de servir; Cucharas para servir alimentos sólidos [utensilios para el hogar o la cocina]; Salvamanteles que no sean de papel ni de materias textiles; Vajilla; Moldes de repostería.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Pesupulgad; Jõhvharjad; Majapidamise plastkindad; Küürimisnuustikud kodumajapidamistele; Küüneharjad; Hambaharjahoidjad; Kosmeetikavahendite anumad; Kosmeetikakotid [komplekteeritud]; Tühjad pihustuspudelid; Näopuhastuskäsnad; Seebialused; Tualettpaberihoidlid; Plastist pihustusotsikud; Taimede ümberistutusmahutid; Joogikõrred; Koogivormid; Serveerimiskahvlid; Serveerimislusikad [majapidamis- või köögitarbed]; Lauamatid, v.a paberist või tekstiilist; Lauanõud, v.a noad, kahvlid ja lusikad; Koogivormid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Pyykkipojat; Harjas (eläin -) [harjanvalmistusaineena]; Muoviset kotitalouskäsineet; Hankaustyynyt kotitalouskäyttöön; Kynsiharjat; Hammasharjatelineet; Kosmetiikkatuotteiden säilytysastiat; Kosmetiikkalaukut (varustetut); Tyhjät suihkepullot; Kasvojen puhdistussienet; Saippuatelineet; Pidikkeet WC-paperirullille; Muoviset sumutussuuttimet; Istutusruukut kasveille; Juomapillit; Kakkuvuoat; Tarjoiluhaarukat; Annostelukauhat [kotitalous- tai keittiövälineet]; Tabletit, ei paperia eikä tekstiiliä; Pöytätarvikkeet, muut kuin veitset, haarukat ja lusikat; Kakkumuotit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Pinces à linge; Soies d'animaux [brosserie et pinceaux]; Gants ménagers en plastique; Tampons à récurer pour le ménage; Brosses à ongles; Supports pour brosses à dents; Récipients pour cosmétiques; Trousses de toilette [garnies]; Flacons vaporisateurs vides; Éponges pour le nettoyage du visage; Porte-savons; Porte-rouleaux pour papier hygiénique; Ajutages de pulvérisateurs en matières plastiques; Récipients de rempotage pour plantes; Pailles pour la dégustation des boissons; Moules à gâteaux; Fourchettes de service; Louches pour le service de la nourriture [ustensile ménager ou de cuisine]; Ronds de table, ni en papier ni en matières textiles; Vaisselle; Moules à gâteaux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kvačice za rublje; Dlaka, životinjska za četkarstvo; Plastične rukavice za kućanstvo; Spužve za ribanje, za uporabu u kućanstvu; Četke za nokte; Držači za četkice za zube; Posude za kozmetiku; Kozmetičke torbice [opremljene]; Prazne boce za raspršivanje; Spužve za čišćenje lica; Držači za sapun; Držači higijenskog papira [napravice]; Plastični raspršivači; Posude za presađivanje biljaka; Slamke za pića; Kolači [kalupi za kolače]; Vilice za posluživanje; Žlice za serviranje [kućanski ili kuhinjski pribor]; Podmetači za stolove, osim od papira i tekstila; Stolni predmeti, osim noževa, vilica i žlica; Kalupi za pečenje kolača.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ruhacsipeszek; Állatsörték [kefeáruk és ecsetek]; Műanyag kesztyűk háztartási célokra; Súrolószivacsok háztartási célokra; Körömkefék; Fogkefetartók; Tárolók, tartók kozmetikumoknak; Kozmetikai táskák [felszerelt]; Üres spriccelő palackok, flakonok; Arctisztító szivacsok; Szappantartók; Toalettpapír-tartók; Permetezőfejek műanyagból; Átültető tartályok növényekhez; Szívószálak; Süteményformák; Tálaló villák; Adagolókanalak [háztartási vagy konyhai eszköz]; Asztali alátétek, nem papírból vagy textilből; Étkészlet, a kések, villák és kanalak kivételével; Tortaformák, sütőformák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Mollette per bucato; Setole d'animali [spazzole e pennelli]; Guanti di plastica per la casa; Pagliette per la casa; Spazzolini per unghie; Portaspazzolini da denti; Recipienti per prodotti per la toilette; Borse per cosmetici [accessoriate]; Flaconi spray [vuoti]; Spugne per la pulizia del viso; Ripiani per il sapone; Portarotoli per carta igienica; Ugelli di spruzzo in plastica; Contenitori per rinvaso di piante; Cannucce per bibite; Stampe per dolci; Forchette per servire; Mestoli per servire [domestici o attrezzi da cucina]; Centrini per tavoli, non di carta o di tessuto; Vasellame; Forme per torte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Baltinių spaustukai; Šeriai [šepečiams]; Buitinės plastikinės pirštinės; Buitiniai šveistukai; Nagų šepetukai; Dantų šepetėlių laikikliai; Kosmetikos talpyklos; Kosmetikos krepšeliai [pritaikyti]; Tušti purškikliai; Veido valymo kempinėlės; Muilinės; Tualetinio popieriaus laikikliai; Plastikiniai purkštukai; Augalų persodinimo tara; Geriamieji šiaudeliai; Konditerijos gaminių kepimo formos; Serviravimo šakutės; Serviravimo samteliai (namų apyvokos ar virtuvės reikmenys); Ne popieriniai ir ne tekstiliniai stalo aptiesalai; Valgomieji reikmenys [išskyrus peilius, šakutes ir šaukštus]; Pyrago kepimo formos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Veļas knaģi; Dzīvnieku saru sukas un otas; Mājsaimniecībā izmantojamie plastmasas cimdi; Beršanas sūkļi mājsaimniecības vajadzībām; Nagu birstītes; Zobu suku turētāji; Tvertnes kosmētikai; Kosmētikas somiņas [pielāgotas]; Tukši pulverizatori; Sūkļi sejas tīrīšanai; Ziepju plaukti; Tualetes papīra turētāji; Izsmidzināšanas uzgaļi no plastmasas; Augu pārstādīšanas konteineri; Salmiņi dzērieniem; Kūku formiņas; Servēšanas dakšiņas; Servēšanas kausi [mājsaimniecības vai virtuves piederumi]; Galda sedziņas, izņemot galda sedziņas no papīra un tekstilmateriāliem; Galda piederumi, izņemot nažus, dakšiņas un karotes; Kūku formiņas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Labar tal-inxir; Xagħar tal-annimali [pniezel]; Ingwanti tal-plastik għall-użu domestiku; Kuxxinetti li jgħorku għad-dar; Xkupilji tad-dwiefer; Ħowlders għall-ixkupilji tas-snien; Kontenituri tal-kosmetiċi; Basktijiet tal-kosmetiċi [mgħammra]; Fliexken vojta biex tisprejja; Sponoż għat-tindif tal-wiċċ; Xkafef għas-sapun; Distributuri tat-toilet paper; Żennuni tal-plastik għall-isprej; Kontenituri għaż-żrigħ mill-ġdid tal-pjanti; Stros għax-xorb; Forom tal-kejkijiet; Frieket biex isservi bihom; Skuwps biex isservi [xogħol fid-dar jew għodda tal-kċina]; Matts ta' fuq il-mejda, mhux tal-karta jew tat-tessut; Tagħmir ta' fuq il-mejda, minbarra skieken, frieket u mgħaref; Laned għall-kejkijiet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Wasknijpers; Dierlijk borstelhaar; Plastic handschoenen voor huishoudelijke doeleinden; Schuursponsjes voor huishoudelijke doeleinden; Nagelborstels; Houders voor tandenborstels; Houders voor cosmetische middelen; Toilettassen [aangepast]; Lege sproeiflacons; Gezichtsreinigingssponzen; Zeeprekjes; Toiletrolhouders; Sproeikoppen (Plastic -); Houders voor het verpotten van planten; Drinkrietjes; Taartvormen; Serveervorken; Scheplepels [gerei voor de huishouding of de keuken]; Tafelmatjes, niet van papier of textiel; Vaatwerk; Cakevormen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Klamerki do wieszania ubrań na sznurze; Szczecina zwierzęca [szczotkarstwo]; Rękawice do prac domowych z tworzyw sztucznych; Zmywaki do szorowania, do użytku domowego; Szczoteczki do paznokci; Uchwyty na szczoteczki do zębów; Pojemniki na kosmetyki; Kosmetyczki [wyposażone]; Puste pojemniki-rozpylacze; Gąbki do oczyszczania twarzy; Mydelniczki; Dozowniki papieru toaletowego; Dysze rozpylające z tworzyw sztucznych; Pojemniki do przesadzania roślin; Słomki do picia; Formy do ciast i ciastek; Widelce do podawania; Łyżki do serwowania (przybory kuchenne lub gospodarstwa domowego); Podkładki na stół, nie z papieru ani materiałów tekstylnych; Zastawa stołowa, inna niż noże, widelce i łyżki; Formy do ciast.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Molas para roupa; Cerdas de animais [escovas e pincéis]; Luvas de plástico para uso doméstico; Esfregões para uso doméstico; Escovas para unhas; Suportes para escovas de dentes; Recipientes para cosméticos; Bolsas para cosméticos [guarnecidos]; Frascos pulverizadores vazios; Esponjas de limpeza facial; Saboneteiras; Suportes para papel higiénico; Agulhetas de pulverização plásticas; Recipientes para reenvasar plantas; Palhinhas para bebidas; Formas para bolos; Garfos para servir; Conchas [utensílos para uso doméstico ou para a cozinha]; Toalhas de mesa, não sendo em papel ou têxteis; Serviços de mesa, exceto facas, garfos e colheres; Moldes para bolos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cârlige de rufe; Păr de animale [perii și pensule]; Mănuși din plastic de uz casnic; Bureți de curățat de uz casnic; Unghii (Perii de -); Suporturi pentru periuțe de dinți; Recipiente pentru cosmetice; Portfarduri [accesorizate]; Sticle goale pentru pulverizare; Bureți pentru curățarea feței; Savoniere; Suporturi pentru role de hârtie igienică; Duze din plastic pentru pulverizare; Recipiente pentru reamenajarea plantelor; Paie de băut; Forme pentru prăjituri; Furculițe de servit; Polonice [ustensile de menaj sau de bucătărie]; Șervete de masă, nu din hârtie sau material textil; Veselă, altele decât cuțite, furculițe și linguri; Forme de copt pentru prăjituri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Štipce na bielizeň; Kefy na zvieratá; Plastové rukavice do domácnosti; Drôtenky pre domácnosť; Kefky na nechty; Stojany na zubné kefky; Nádoby na kozmetiku; Vybavené kozmetické taštičky; Prázdne sprejové fľaše; Špongie na čistenie pleti na tvári; Držiaky na mydlo; Zásobníky na kotúčový toaletný papier; Plastové rozprašovacie trysky; Nádoby na presádzanie rastlín; Slamky na pitie; Formy na zákusky a koláče; Servírovacie vidličky; Servírovacie naberačky (domáce alebo kuchynské náradie); Podložky na stôl (anglické prestieranie) okrem textilných a papierových; Kuchynský riad (okrem príborov); Formy na koláče a torty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Ščipalke za perilo; Živalske ščetine [ščetkarstvo in čopičarstvo]; Rokavice iz plastike za gospodinjske namene; Abrazivne čistilne gobice za gospodinjske namene; Krtačke za nohte; Držala za zobne ščetke; Posode za kozmetiko; Kozmetične torbice [opremljene]; Prazne stekleničke razpršilcev; Gobe za čiščenje obraza; Posodice za milo; Nosilci za WC papir; Plastične pršilne šobe; Posode za presajanje rastlin; Slamice za pitje; Modeli za torte; Servirne vilice; Servirne žlice [priprave za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo]; Namizni pogrinjki, ne iz papirja ali blaga; Namizna posoda (razen nožev, vilic in žlic); Modeli za peko kolačev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Klädnypor; Djurborst [borstbinderivaror]; Plasthandskar för hushållsändamål; Skurdynor för hushållsändamål; Nagelborstar; Tandborsthållare; Behållare för kosmetika; Sminkväskor [inredda]; Tomma sprayflaskor; Tvättsvampar för ansiktsrengöring; Tvålställ; Hållare för toalettpapper; Spraymunstycken av plast; Omplanteringsbehållare för växter; Sugrör; Kakformar; Serveringsgafflar; Serveringsskopor [hushålls- och köksredskap]; Bordsunderlägg, inte av papper eller textil; Bordserviser (inte knivar, gafflar och skedar); Kakformar i lättmetall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/081</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-30</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/150</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081927</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>22168</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017764245</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>22168</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-04-24</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
