<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-22T00:39:24</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229614</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229614</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="1" status="6">Application filed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-04-27</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>LEITNER REISEN</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162504434</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229614/000162504434.JPG</MarkImageURI>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>39</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Пътнически резервации; Услуги на круизни кораби; Провеждане на туристически обиколки; Организиране на екскурзии; Организиране на пътувания; Уреждане на туристически обиколки; Организиране на ваканционни пътувания; Транспортни резервации; Услуги свързани с пътнически резервации за пътуване по въздух; Резервационни услуги за пътувания по море; Организиране и уреждане на пътувания; Услуги за организиране и резервиране на пътувания; Планиране, организиране и резервиране на пътувания; Организиране и резервиране на пътувания за пакетни ваканции; Координиране на пътувания за отделни лица и групи; Туроператорски услуги за резервиране на пътувания.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Rezervace dopravy; Služby okružních plaveb; Vedení zájezdů; Pořádání zájezdů; Organizování cest; Organizování zájezdů; Organizování prázdninových cest; Rezervace dopravy; Rezervační služby týkající se cestování letadlem; Rezervační služby týkající se cestování po moři; Organizování a zprostředkování zájezdů; Organizování a rezervace cest; Plánování, organizování a rezervování cest; Organizování a rezervace cest pro organizované zájezdy; Koordinování cestovních příprav pro jednotlivce a skupiny; Služby tour operátora týkající se rezervace cest.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Rejsereservation; Arrangering af rejsekrydstogter (transport); Ledelse af ture; Arrangering af transport til rejseudflugter; Organisering af rejser; Turledelse; Organisering af ferierejser; Transportreservation; Reservation af flyrejser; Reservationstjenester til rejser ad søvejen; Organisering og arrangering af rejser; Tjenester vedrørende organisering af rejser og rejsereservationer; Planlægning, arrangering og reservation af rejser; Organisering og reservation af pakkerejser; Koordinering af rejsearrangementer for enkeltpersoner og grupper; Rejseledervirksomhed i forbindelse med bestilling af rejser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Reservierungsdienste [Reisen]; Kreuzfahrtdienste [Reisen]; Durchführung von Reisen; Veranstaltung von Reisen; Organisieren von Reisen; Organisation von Reisen; Durchführen von Reisen; Organisation von Reisen zu Urlaubszwecken; Reservierungsdienste [Transportwesen]; Reservierungsdienste für Flugreisen; Reservierungsdienste für Seereisen; Veranstaltung von Reisen und Ausflugsfahrten; Veranstaltung und Vermittlung von Reisen; Veranstaltung und Reservierung von Reisen; Planung, Buchung und Veranstaltung von Reisen; Veranstaltung und Buchung von Reisen für Pauschalurlaubsreisen; Organisation von Ferienreisen; Organisation von Reiseveranstaltungen für Einzelpersonen und Gruppen; Reiseveranstaltungsdienste für die Buchung von Reisen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κρατήσεις ταξιδιών· Υπηρεσίες κρουαζιερόπλοιων· Διεξαγωγή περιηγήσεων· Διοργάνωση εκδρομών· Οργάνωση ταξιδίων· Διαχείριση εκδρομών· Οργάνωση ταξιδιωτικών διακοπών· Κρατήσεις θέσεων για μεταφορά· Υπηρεσίες κρατήσεων για αεροπορικά ταξίδια· Υπηρεσίες κρατήσεων για θαλάσσια ταξίδια· Οργάνωση και διεκπεραίωση ταξιδιών· Υπηρεσίες οργάνωσης και κρατήσεων σε σχέση με ταξίδια· Σχεδιασμός, οργάνωση και κρατήσεις για ταξίδια· Οργάνωση και ταξιδιωτικές κρατήσεις για πακέτα διακοπών· Συντονισμός οργάνωσης ταξιδιών για μεμονωμένα άτομα και ομάδες· Υπηρεσίες ταξιδιωτικού πράκτορα για την κράτηση ταξιδίων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Travel reservation; Cruise ship services; Tour conducting; Arranging of transportation for travel tours; Travel arrangement; Operating of tours; Organisation of holiday travel; Transport reservation; Reservation services for airline travel; Reservation services for travel by sea; Organizing and arranging travel; Travel arrangement and reservation services; Planning, arranging and booking of travel; Arranging and booking of travel for package holidays; Coordinating travel arrangements for individuals and for groups; Tour operator services for the booking of travel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Reservas de viajes; Servicios de viajes en cruceros; Servicios de guía de viajes organizados; Organización de transporte para circuitos turísticos; Organización de viajes; Organización de tours; Organización de viajes de vacaciones; Reservas de transporte; Servicios de reservas para viajes en líneas aéreas; Servicios de reservas de viajes por mar; Organización y mediación de viajes; Servicios de organización y reserva de viajes; Planificación, organización y reserva de viajes; Organización y reserva de viajes en el marco de paquetes de vacaciones; Coordinación de planes de viajes para particulares y para grupos; Servicios de turoperadores para reservas de viajes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reiside reserveerimine, ettetellimine; Kruiisilaevade teenused; Turismireiside korraldamine; Huvireiside transpordi korraldamine; Reiside korraldamine; Reisioperaatoriteenused; Puhkereiside korraldamine; Transpordi, sõidukite ettetellimine, reserveerimine; Lennureisi reserveerimise teenused; Merereiside reserveerimise teenused; Reiside korraldamine; Reisikorraldamine ja -broneerimine; Reiside planeerimine, korraldamine ja broneerimine; Paketina müüdavate puhkusereiside korraldamine ja broneerimine; Reisikorralduse koordineerimine üksikisikutele ja rühmadele; Reisioperaatori teenused reiside broneerimiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Matkojen varaaminen; Laivaristeilypalvelut; Kiertomatkojen ohjaaminen; Kuljetuksen järjestäminen kiertomatkoille; Matkojen järjestäminen; Kiertomatkojen järjestäminen; Lomamatkojen järjestäminen; Kuljetusvaraus; Lentomatkojen varauspalvelut; Merimatkojen varauspalvelut; Matkojen järjestäminen ja välittäminen; Matkojen järjestämis- ja varauspalvelut; Matkojen suunnittelu, järjestäminen ja varaus; Pakettilomamatkojen järjestäminen ja varaus; Yksityisten ihmisten ja ryhmien matkajärjestelyjen koordinointi; Matkanjärjestäjäpalvelut matkojen varaamiseen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Réservations pour les voyages; Services de croisières; Encadrement d'excursions, de visites touristiques et de voyages; Organisation de transports dans le cadre de circuits touristiques; Organisation de voyages; Organisation d'excursions, de visites touristiques et de voyages; Organisation de voyages de vacances; Réservations pour le transport; Services de réservation de voyages en avion; Services de réservation de voyages en mer; Voyages organisés; Services d'organisation et de réservation de voyages; Planification, préparation et réservation de voyages; Préparation et réservation de voyages organisés; Coordination de préparatifs de voyages individuels et de groupe; Services de tour-opérateurs pour la réservation de voyages.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Putovanja (rezervacije za putovanja); Usluge krstarenja brodom; Usluge turističkog vođenja; Organiziranje ekskurzija; Organiziranje putovanja; Vođenje izleta; Organiziranje turističkih putovanja; Prijevoz (rezervacije za prijevoz); Usluge rezervacija za putovanja zrakoplovom; Usluge rezervacija za putovanje morem; Organiziranje i pripremanje putovanja; Usluge planiranja putovanja i rezervacija; Planiranje, organizacija i rezervacija putovanja; Organizacija i rezervacija putovanja u aranžmanima; Koordiniranje putnih aranžmana za pojedince i za grupe; Usluge turoperatora za rezervacije putovanja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Helyfoglalás utazással kapcsolatban; Tengeri hajóút szolgáltatások; Idegenvezetés; Kirándulások, túrák, társasutazások szervezése; Utazásszervezés, kirándulásszervezés; Körutak, túrák lebonyolítása; Utazás- és nyaralásszervezés; Helyfoglalás szállítással kapcsolatban; Helyfoglalási szolgáltatások légi utazásokhoz; Helyfoglalási szolgáltatások tengeri utazáshoz; Utazások szervezése és lebonyolítása; Utazásszervezési és utazási helyfoglalási szolgáltatások; Utazás tervezése, megszervezése és lefoglalása; Társasutazások szervezése és lefoglalása; Utazás koordinálása egyének és csoportok számára; Utazásszervezői szolgáltatások utazások foglalásához.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Prenotazioni per i viaggi; Servizi di navi da crociera; Conduzione di viaggi turistici; Organizzazione di trasporti per giri turistici; Organizzazione di viaggi; Organizzazione di tour; Organizzazione di viaggi di vacanza; Prenotazioni per il trasporto; Servizi di prenotazione di viaggi aerei; Servizi di prenotazione per trasporti marittimi; Organizzazione e mediazione di viaggi; Servizi di organizzazione e prenotazione viaggi; Pianificazione, programmazione e prenotazione di viaggi; Organizzazione e prenotazione di viaggi per pacchetti vacanze; Coordinamento dell'organizzazione di viaggi per singoli e gruppi; Servizi di operatore turistico per prenotazione di viaggi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kelionių užsakymai; Kruizinių laivų paslaugos; Turų vedimas; Transporto parūpinimas turistinėms kelionėms; Kelionių organizavimas; Kelionių (ekskursijų) rengimas; Atostogų kelionių organizavimas; Vežiojimų užsakymas; Kelionių oro linijomis užsakymo paslaugos; Kelionių jūra užsakymo paslaugos; Kelionių organizavimas ir rengimas; Kelionių rengimo ir užsakymo paslaugos; Kelionių planavimas, rengimas ir užsakymas; Poilsinių kelionių organizavimas ir užsakymas; Individualių ir grupių kelionių rengimo koordinavimas; Kelionių organizatorių teikiamos kelionės užsakymo paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ceļojumu rezervēšana; Izpriecu ceļojumu kuģu pakalpojumi; Ceļojumu vadīšana; Transporta pakalpojumu nodrošināšana ekskursantiem; Ceļojumu organizēšana; Tūrisma braucienu nodrošināšana; Brīvdienu ceļojumu organizēšana; Transportlīdzekļu rezervēšana; Rezervēšanas pakalpojumi ceļojumiem pa gaisu; Rezervēšanas pakalpojumi ceļojumiem pa ūdeni; Ceļojumu organizēšana un sagatavošana; Ceļojumu sagatavošanas un rezervācijas pakalpojumi; Ceļojumu plānošana, organizēšana un rezervēšana; Ceļojumu sagatavošana un iepriekš rezervēšana pakešu tipa brīvdienām; Ceļojumu organizēšanas koordinēšana indivīdiem un grupām; Tūrisma operatoru pakalpojumi ceļojumu rezervēšanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reservazzjoni ta' l-ivvjaġġar; Servizzi ta' vapur tal-kruċieri; Tmexxija ta' ġiti; L-organizzazzjoni ta' eskursjonijiet; Arranġamenti għall-ivvjaġġar; Tmexxija ta' turs; L-organizzazzjoni tas-safar fuq vaganza; Riservazzjoni ta' trasport; Servizzi ta' riservazzjoni għall-ivvjaġġar bl-ajru; Servizzi ta' riservazzjoni għall-ivvjaġġar bil-baħar; L-organizzazzjoni u l-arranġament tal-ivvjaġġar; Servizzi ta' arranġament u prenotazzjoni għall-ivvjaġġar; Ippjanar, organizzazzjoni u bbukkjar ta' vjaġġi; Organizzazzjoni u bbukkjar ta' vjaġġar għal pakketti ta' vaganzi; Koordinazzjoni ta' arranġamenti għall-ivvjaġġar għal individwi u għal gruppi; Servizzi ta' operatur tal-vjaġġi għar-riservazzjoni tal-ivvjaġġar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reisreservering; Diensten op het gebied van cruiseschepen; Het begeleiden van rondreizen; Organisatie van georganiseerde reizen; Organisatie van reizen; Organisatie van reizen; Organisatie van vakantiereizen; Transportreservering; Reservering van vliegreizen; Reserveringen van reizen over zee; Organisatie van en bemiddeling bij reizen; Organisatie en reservering van reizen; Plannen, organiseren en boeken van reizen; Organisatie en boeking van pakketreizen; Het coördineren van reisarrangementen voor individuele personen en groepen; Diensten van touroperators voor het boeken van reizen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Rezerwacja miejsc na podróż; Usługi w zakresie rejsów statkami wycieczkowymi; Oprowadzanie wycieczek; Usługi w zakresie organizowania transportu dla wycieczek; Organizowanie podróży; Prowadzenie wycieczek; Organizowanie wczasów; Rezerwacja transportu; Usługi rezerwacji podróży lotniczych; Usługi rezerwacji w zakresie podróży drogą morską; Planowanie i organizowanie podróży; Usługi z zakresu organizacji i rezerwacji podróży; Planowanie, organizowanie i rezerwacja podróży; Organizowanie i rezerwowanie podróży w ramach wakacji zorganizowanych; Koordynowanie planów podróży dla osób prywatnych i grup; Usługi biura turystycznego w celu rezerwacji podróży.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Reservas para viagens; Serviços de viagens em navios; Realização de excursões; Organização de transporte para passeios turísticos; Organização de viagens; Organização de visitas turísticas; Organização de viagens de férias; Reservas para transporte; Serviços de reserva para viagens de transporte aéreo; Serviços de reservas para viagens marítimas; Organização e mediação de viagens; Serviços de organização e reserva de viagens; Planificação, organização e reserva de viagens; Organização e reserva de viagens para pacotes de férias; Coordenação da organização de viagens para indivíduos e grupos; Serviços de operadores turísticos para reserva de viagens.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Călătorii (Rezervări pentru -); Servicii de croaziere; Coordonare de tururi turistice; Organizare de excursii; Organizarea de călătorii; Organizare de tururi; Organizare de călătorii de vacanță; Transport (Rezervări pentru -); Servicii de rezervare pentru transport aerian; Servicii de rezervări pentru călătorii maritime; Organizare și intermediere de călătorii; Organizare de călătorii și servicii de rezervare; Planificare, organizare și rezervare de călătorii; Organizare și rezervare de călătorii pentru pachete de vacanță; Coordonarea organizării de călătorii individuale și de grup; Servicii de touroperatori pentru rezervarea de călătorii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Rezervácie zájazdov; Služby okružnej cesty loďou; Vedenie zájazdov; Organizovanie turistickej dopravy; Zabezpečovanie cestovania; Organizovanie turistickej dopravy; Organizovanie dovolenkových ciest; Rezervácie dopravy; Služby rezervácie leteckej dopravy; Služby v oblasti rezervovania námornej dopravy; Organizovanie a zabezpečovanie cestovania; Služby v oblasti zabezpečovania a rezervovania cestovania; Plánovanie, organizovanie a rezervovanie cestovania; Zabezpečovanie a rezervovanie cestovania pre dovolenkové balíky; Koordinovanie cestovných plánov pre jednotlivcov a skupiny; Služby tour operátora v oblasti rezervácie ciest.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Potovalne rezervacije; Storitve ladijskih križarjenj; Izvajanje potovanj; Organizacija ekskurzij; Organizacija potovanj; Organiziranje potovanj; Organizacija počitniških potovanj; Transportne rezervacije; Storitve rezervacij za letalsko potovanje; Storitve rezervacij za potovanje po morju; Organizacija in urejanje potovanj; Organizacija potovanj in storitve rezervacij; Načrtovanje, organizacija in rezervacija potovanj; Organizacija in rezervacija potovanja za počitniške pakete; Koordiniranje potovalnih aranžmajev za posameznike in skupine; Storitve organizatorjev potovanj v zvezi z rezervacijo potovanj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bokning av resor; Kryssningsfartygstjänster; Ledning av rundturer; Anordnande av transporter vid resor; Researrangemang; Organisering av rundresor; Anordnande av semesterresor; Bokning av transporter; Bokning av flygresor; Bokningstjänster avseende resor till sjöss; Anordnande och förmedling av resor; Tjänster avseende arrangemang och reservation av resor; Planering, anordnande och bokning av resor; Anordnande och bokning av resor för semesterpaket; Samordning av researrangemang för individer och grupper; Researrangörstjänster för bokning av resor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги, свързани с продажба на билети и резервации за събития.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby rezervace a vydávání vstupenek na akce.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Billetudstedelse og eventbooking.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Eintrittskartenvorverkauf und Buchungsdienstleistungen für Veranstaltungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες έκδοσης εισιτηρίων και κρατήσεων για εκδηλώσεις.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Ticketing and event booking services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de emisión y reserva de localidades para eventos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Piletite tellimine ja kohtade broneerimine üritustele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Pääsylippujen ja tapahtumien varauspalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de billetterie et de réservation pour évènements.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge u svezi s nabavom ulaznica i predbilježbom za događanja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Jegyrendelési és jegyfoglalási szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di prenotazione ed emissione di biglietti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Bilietų išdavimo ir renginių užsakymo paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Biļešu un pasākumu rezervēšanas pakalpojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' prenotazzjoni ta' eventi u biljetti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reservering van plaatsbewijzen en boeking voor evenementen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi w zakresie dystrybucji i rezerwacji biletów na imprezy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de reservas e emissão de bilhetes para eventos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de rezervare și vânzare de bilete pentru evenimente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Služby v oblasti predaja a rezervácie lístkov na rôzne predstavenia a udalosti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Prodaja vstopnic in rezervacije za dogodke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bokningstjänster avseende biljetter och evenemang.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>43</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Извършване на резервации за хотелско настаняване; Услуги за настаняване в хотел; Уреждане на хотелски стаи за туристи; Услуги на агенция за резервации свързани с настаняване в хотели; Извършване на резервации и запазване на места за ресторанти и ястия.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Hotely (Rezervace -); Poskytování hotelového ubytování; Rezervace hotelových pokojů pro turisty; Služby agentur pro rezervaci hotelového ubytování; Rezervování a objednávání restaurací a jídel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Reservation af hotelværelser; Tilvejebringelse af hotelindkvartering; Reservation af hotelværelser for rejsende; Bookningsvirksomhed i forbindelse med indkvartering i hotelværelser; Udførelse af reservationer og bookninger til restauranter og måltider.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Reservierungsdienste für Hotelzimmer; Vermittlung von Hotelzimmern; Buchungsservice für Hotelzimmer; Reservierung von Hotelzimmern; Buchung von Hotelzimmern für Reisende; Agenturdienste zur Buchung von Hotelzimmern; Dienstleistungen einer Buchungsagentur für Hotelzimmer; Reservierung und Buchung von Restaurants und Mahlzeiten; Reservierungs- und Buchungsdienstleistungen für Restaurants und Verpflegung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες κρατήσεων για διαμονή σε ξενοδοχείο· Παροχή καταλυμάτων (ξενοδοχείων)· Κρατήσεις δωματίων ξενοδοχείων για ταξιδιώτες· Υπηρεσίες πρακτορείου κρατήσεων ξενοδοχειακού καταλύματος· Κρατήσεις σε εστιατόρια και για γεύματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Booking of hotel accommodation; Provision of hotel accommodation; Booking of hotel rooms for travellers; Booking agency services for hotel accommodation; Making reservations and bookings for restaurants and meals.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Reserva de alojamiento en hoteles; Facilitación de alojamiento en hoteles; Reservas de habitaciones de hotel para viajeros; Servicios de agencias de reservas para alojamiento en hoteles; Reservas de restaurantes y de comidas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hotellimajutuse broneerimine; Hotellimajutus; Hotellitubade broneerimine reisijatele; Hotellimajutuse broneerimine broneerimisagentuuri kaudu; Restoranide ja toitlustuse reserveerimine ja broneerimine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hotellivarauspalvelut; Hotellimajoituksen tarjoaminen; Hotellihuoneiden varaus matkailijoille; Hotellimajoituksen varauspalvelut; Ravintola- ja ateriavarausten ja -tilausten tekeminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Réservation d'hébergement dans des hôtels; Mise à disposition de chambres d'hôtel; Réservation de chambres d'hôtel pour voyageurs; Services d'agence pour la réservation hôtelière; Réservation de restaurants et de repas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Rezervacija hotelskog smještaja; Pružanje hotelskog smještaja; Rezerviranje hotelskih soba za putnike; Usluge agencije za rezerviranje hotelskog smještaja; Usluge rezervacija i predbilježbi za restorane i obroke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Helyfoglalás szállodákban; Szállodai szállásbiztosítás; Szállodai szobák lefoglalása utazók számára; Foglalási ügynökségek szolgáltatásai szállodai elhelyezéshez; Éttermi foglalások és ételek megrendelése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Prenotazione di sistemazione alberghiera; Fornitura di alloggio in alberghi; Prenotazione di camere d'albergo per viaggiatori; Servizi di agenzia per prenotazioni alberghiere; Servizi di prenotazione di ristoranti e pasti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Viešbučių užsakymo paslaugos; Laikinas apgyvendinimas viešbučiuose; Viešbučių kambarių rezervavimas keliautojams; Viešbučių užsakymo agentūrų paslaugos; Vietų restorane rezervavimas ir patiekalų užsakymas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Viesnīcu numuru rezervēšana; Izmitināšanas pakalpojumi viesnīcās; Viesnīcu numuru rezervēšana ceļotājiem; Rezervēšanas aģentūru pakalpojumi saistībā ar izmitināšanu viesnīcās; Restorānu un ēdienu rezervēšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Il-prenotazzjoni ta' akkomodazzjoni f'lukandi; Il-provvista ta' akkomodazzjoni f'lukanda; Il-prenotazzjoni ta' kmamar ta' lukandi għal vjaġġaturi; Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-prenotazzjoni għal akkomodazzjonijiet f'lukanda; Riservazzjonijiet u prenotazzjonijiet għal ristoranti u ikliet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reservering van hotelaccommodatie; Verschaffen van hotelaccommodaties; Hotelkamers voor reizigers (Het boeken van -); Reserveren van hotelaccommodaties (Agentschappen voor het -); Doen van reserveringen en boekingen voor restaurants en maaltijden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi w zakresie rezerwacji zakwaterowania w hotelach; Zapewnianie zakwaterowania w hotelach; Rezerwacja pokojów hotelowych dla podróżnych; Usługi agencji w zakresie rezerwacji zakwaterowania w hotelach; Dokonywanie rezerwacji restauracji i posiłków.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Reserva de alojamentos em hotéis; Fornecimento de alojamento em hotéis; Reservas de quartos de hotel para viajantes; Serviços de agência de marcação de alojamento em hotéis; Realização de reservas e marcações para restaurantes e refeições.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Rezervare de cazare la hotel; Furnizare de locuri de cazare la hoteluri; Rezervare de camere de hotel pentru călători; Servicii prestate de agenții pentru rezervări la hotel; Rezervări pentru restaurante și mese.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Rezervovanie hotelového ubytovania (Služby -); Poskytovanie hotelového ubytovania; Rezervovanie hotelových izieb pre cestovateľov; Agentúrne služby rezervácie hotelového ubytovania; Rezervovanie a objednávanie reštaurácií a jedál.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Rezervacija hotelskih nastanitev; Nudenje hotelskih nastanitev; Rezervacije hotelskih sob za popotnike; Storitve agencij za rezerviranje hotelskih nastanitev; Storitve rezervacij in prijav za restavracije in obroke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bokning av hotellogi; Upplåtande av kortvarigt boende (hotell); Bokning av hotellrum för resenärer; Byråer för bokning av hotell; Reservationer och bokningar av restauranger och måltider.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
