<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-21T11:40:03</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229272</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229272</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>fi</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-19</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>RIMITA</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ароматни масла за вана и тяло; Препарати за ароматерапия; Дезодоранти и препарати против изпотяване; Етерични масла и ароматни екстракти; Парфюмерия и ароматизатори; Products for hair care и hair treatment; Препарати за грижа за кожата, очите и ноктите; Кремове за лице и за тяло; Козметични средства; Органична козметика; Козметични тоалетни препарати; Грим; Почистващи и ароматизиращи препарати; Сапуни и гелове; Шампоани; Препарати за почистване на тялото и за грижа за красотата.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Aromatické oleje do koupele a na tělo; Aromaterapeutické přípravky; Deodoranty a antiperspiranty; Vonné oleje a aromatické výtažky; Parfumerie a vonné přípravky; Výrobky k péči o vlasy a jejich ošetřování; Přípravky pro péči o pleť, oči a nehty; Pleťové a tělové krémy; Kosmetické přípravky; Organická kosmetika; Toaletní přípravky; Přípravky na líčení; Čistící prostředky a vonné přípravky; Mýdla a gely; Šampony; Přípravky pro osobní hygienu a kosmetické přípravky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Aromatiske bade- og kropsolier; Aromaterapipræparater; Deodoranter og antiperspiranter; Æteriske olier og aromatiske udtræk; Parfumer og dufte; Præparater til hårpleje og hårbehandling; Præparater til hud-, øjen- og neglepleje; Ansigts- og kropscremer; Kosmetik; Økologisk kosmetik; Toiletartikler; Sminkeprodukter; Rengørings- og duftpræparater; Sæber og geler; Shampoo; Præparater til rengøring af kroppen og skønhedspleje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Aromatische Bade- und Körperöle; Aromatherapiepräparate; Deodorants und Antitranspirantien; Ätherische Öle und aromatische Extrakte; Parfümeriewaren und Duftstoffe; Mittel zur Haarpflege und Haarbehandlung; Haut-, Augen- und Nagelpflegemittel; Cremes für die Gesichts- und Körperpflege; Kosmetika; Bio-Kosmetika; Körperpflegemittel; Make-up; Reinigungs- und Duftpräparate; Seifen und Gele; Shampoos; Körperreinigungs- und Körperpflegepräparate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αρωματικά έλαια μπάνιου και σώματος· Παρασκευάσματα αρωματοθεραπείας· Αποσμητικά και αντι-ιδρωτικά· Αιθέρια έλαια και αρωματικά εκχυλίσματα· Είδη αρωματοποιίας και αρώματα· Προϊόντα για την περιποίηση και την θεραπεία των μαλλιών· Παρασκευάσματα για την περιποίηση του δέρματος, των ματιών και των νυχιών· Κρέμες για το πρόσωπο και το σώμα· Καλλυντικά· Οργανικά καλλυντικά· Καλλυντικά παρασκευάσματα· Μακιγιάζ· Καθαριστικά και αρωματικά παρασκευάσματα· Σαπούνια και τζέλ· Σαμπουάν· Παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού σώματος και φροντίδας ομορφιάς.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Aromatic bath and body oils; Aromatherapy preparations; Deodorants and antiperspirants; Essential oils and aromatic extracts; Perfumery and fragrances; hair care and hair treatment products; Skin, eye and nail care preparations; Face and body creams; Cosmetics; Organic cosmetics; Toiletries; Make-up preparations; Cleaning and fragrance preparations; Soaps and gels; Shampoos; Body cleaning and beauty care preparations.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aceites aromáticos de baño y corporales; Preparaciones de aromatoterapia; Desodorantes y antitranspirantes; Aceites esenciales y extractos aromáticos; Perfumería y fragancias; Productos para el cuidado del cabello y el tratamiento del cabello; Productos para el cuidado de la piel, los ojos y las uñas; Cremas faciales y corporales; Cosméticos; Cosméticos orgánicos; Preparaciones de tocador; Productos de maquillaje; Preparaciones para limpiar y aromatizar; Jabones y geles; Champús; Preparaciones para la limpieza y cuidado del cuerpo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Aromaatsed kümblus- ja kehaõlid; Aroomiteraapia preparaadid; Deodorandid ja higistusvastased vahendid; Eeterlikud õlid ja aroomiekstraktid; Parfüümid ja lõhnaained; Juuksehooldus- ja juukseravitooted; Naha-, silma- ja küünehoolduspreparaadid; Näo- ja kehakreemid; Kosmeetikavahendid; Orgaanilised kosmeetikatooted; Tualettpreparaadid; Meigivahendid, jumestusvahendid; Puhastus- ja lõhnastusained; Seebid ja geelid; Šampoonid; Puhastus- ja iluhooldustooted kehale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Aromaattiset kylpy- ja vartaloöljyt; aromaterapiavalmisteet; deodorantit ja antiperspirantit; eteeriset öljyt ja aromaattiset uutteet; hajuvedet ja hajusteet; hiustenhoito ja -käsittelyvalmisteet; ihon-, silmien- ja kynsienhoitovalmisteet; kasvo- ja vartalovoiteet; kosmetiikka; luonnonmukainen kosmetiikka; kosmeettiset- ja peseytymisvalmisteet; meikkivalmisteet; puhdistus- ja raikastusvalmisteet; saippuat ja puhdistusgeelit; shampoot; vartalon puhdistus- ja kauneudenhoitovalmisteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Huiles aromatiques pour le bain et le corps; Préparations d'aromathérapie; Déodorants et antiperspirants; Huiles essentielles et extraits aromatiques; Produits de parfumerie et parfums; Produits pour le soin et le traitement des cheveux; Produits pour le soin de la peau, des yeux et des ongles; Crèmes pour le visage et le corps; Cosmétiques; Cosmétiques organiques; Préparations de toilette; Produits de maquillage; Préparations nettoyantes et parfumantes; Savons et gels; Shampooings; Préparations de nettoyage corporel et de soins de beauté.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Aromatska ulja za kupanje i tijelo; Aromaterapijski pripravci; Dezodoransi i antiperspiranti; Esencijalna ulja i aromatični ekstrakti; Mirisi i parfimerijski proizvodi; Proizvodi za njegu i tretiranje kose; Preparati za njegu kože, očiju i noktiju; Kreme za lice i tijelo; Kozmetički proizvodi; Organska kozmetika; Toaletni pripravci; Šminka; Pripravci za čišćenje i osvježivanje prostora; Sapuni i gelovi; Šamponi; Pripravci za čišćenje i njegu tijela.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Aromás fürdő- és testolajok; Aromaterápiás készítmények; Dezodorok és izzadásgátlók; Olajesszenciák és aromakivonatok; Parfümök és illatanyagok; Hajápolásra és hajkezelésre szolgáló termékek; Bőr-, szem- és körömápoló készítmények; Arc- és testkrémek; Kozmetikai szerek; Natúrkozmetikumok; Kozmetikai, szépségápolási készítmények; Smink; Tisztító és illatosító készítmények; Szappanok és gélek; Samponok; Testápolási és szépségápolási készitmények.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Oli aromatici per il bagno e per il corpo; Preparati per l'aromaterapia; Deodoranti e antitraspiranti; Olii essenziali ed estratti aromatici; Profumeria e fragranze; Prodotti per cura e trattamento dei capelli; Prodotti per la pelle, gli occhi e la cura delle unghie; Creme per il viso e per il corpo; Cosmetici; Cosmetici organici; Preparati per la toilette; Make-up; Preparati per pulire e profumare; Saponi e gel; Shampoo; Preparati per la pulizia del corpo e per la cura della bellezza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Aromatiniai vonių ir kūno aliejai; Aromaterapijos preparatai; Dezodorantai ir preparatai nuo prakaitavimo; Eteriniai aliejai ir aromatiniai ekstraktai; Parfumerija ir kvepalai; Kosmetika, išskyrus plaukų priežiūros ir plaukų gydymo produktus; Odos, akių ir nagų priežiūros preparatai; Veido ir kūno kremai; Kosmetika; Organinė kosmetika; Tualetiniai preparatai; Grimas; Valymo ir kvėpinimo preparatai; Muilas ir geliai; Šampūnai; Kūno valomieji ir grožio priežiūros preparatai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Aromātiskas vannas un ķermeņa eļļas; Aromterapijas preparāti; Ķermeņa dezodoranti un pretsviedru līdzekļi; Ēteriskās eļļas un aromātiskie ekstrakti; Parfimērijas izstrādājumi un smaržas; Matu kopšanas un matu aprūpes līdzekļi; Ādas, acu un nagu kopšanas līdzekļi; Sejas un ķermeņa krēmi; Kosmētiskie līdzekļi; Kosmētika no dabīgām izejvielām; Personiskās tualetes līdzekļi; Dekoratīvā kosmētika; Tīrīšanas un aromatizēšanas līdzekļi; Ziepes un želejas; Šampūni; Ķermeņa kopšanas un skaistumkopšanas līdzekļi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Żjut aromatiċi tal-banju u tal-ġisem; Preparazzjonijiet tal-aromaterapija; Deodoranti u antiperspiranti; Żjut essenzjali u estratti aromatiċi; Fwejjaħ u fwejjaħ; Prodotti għall-kura tax-xagħar u t-trattament tax-xagħar; Preparazzjonijiet tal-ġilda, tal-għajnejn u tad-dwiefer; Kremi għall-wiċċ u għall-ġisem; Kożmetiċi; Kosmetiċi organiċi; Preparazzjonijiet tat-twaletta; Mejkapp; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif u għal riħa tfuħ; Sapun u ġellijiet; Xampù; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif tal-ġisem u għall-kura tas-sbuħija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Aromatische olie voor in bad en voor het lichaam; Producten voor aromatherapie; Deodorants en antitranspiratiemiddelen; Essentiële oliën en aromatische extracten; Parfumerieën en geuren; Producten voor de verzorging en behandeling van het haar; Huid-, oog- en nagelverzorgingsproducten; Gezichts-en lichaamscrèmes; Cosmetica; Biologische cosmetica; Preparaten voor de toiletverzorging; Make-up; Reinigingsproducten en geurproducten; Zepen en gels; Shampoo; Reinigings- en schoonheidspreparaten voor het lichaam.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Olejki aromatyczne do ciała i kąpieli; Preparaty aromaterapeutyczne; Dezodoranty i antyperspiranty; Olejki esencjonalne i ekstrakty aromatyczne; Środki perfumeryjne i zapachowe; Produkty do pielęgnacji włosów oraz produkty odżywiające włosy; Preparaty do pielęgnacji skóry, oczu i paznokci; Kremy do twarzy i ciała; Kosmetyki; Kosmetyki organiczne; Preparaty toaletowe; Kosmetyki do makijażu; Preparaty do czyszczenia i odświeżania; Mydła i żele; Szampony; Preparaty do mycia i pielęgnacji ciała.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Óleos aromáticos para o banho e para o corpo; Preparações de aromaterapia; Desodorizantes e antitranspirantes; Óleos essenciais e extratos aromáticos; Perfumaria e fragrâncias; Produtos para os cuidados do cabelo e o tratamento do cabelo; Produtos para os cuidados da pele, dos olhos e das unhas; Cremes para o rosto e para o corpo; Cosméticos; Cosméticos biológicos; Artigos de higiene pessoal; Maquilhagem; Produtos para limpar e perfumar; Sabonetes e géis; Champôs; Produtos para limpeza corporal e cuidados de beleza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Uleiuri aromatice pentru baie și corp; Preparate pentru aromoterapie; Deodorante şi antiperspirante; Uleiuri esenţiale şi extracte aromatice; Articole de parfumerie şi odorizante; Produse pentru ingrijirea parului si tratamente de par; Preparate pentru îngrijirea pielii, a ochilor şi a unghiilor; Creme de faţă şi de corp; Cosmetice; Produse cosmetice organice; Produse de toaletă; Farduri; Preparate pentru curăţare şi odorizante; Săpunuri şi geluri; Şampoane; Preparate pentru curăţarea şi îngrijirea corpului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Aromatické kúpeľové a telové oleje; Arómoterapeutické prípravky; Dezodoranty a prípravky proti poteniu (antiperspiranty); Éterické oleje a aromatické výťažky; Parfumérske a vonné výrobky; Výrobky na ošetrovanie vlasov; Prípravky na starostlivosť o pleť, oči a nechty; Krémy na tvár a telové krémy; Kozmetické prípravky; Organická kozmetika; Toaletné prípravky; Prípravky na líčenie; Čistiace a vonné prípravky; Mydlá a gély; Šampóny; Telové čistiace prípravky a skrášľovacie prípravky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Aromatična olja za kopanje in telo; Pripravki za aromaterapijo; Deodoranti in sredstva proti potenju; Eterična olja in aromatični ekstrakti; Parfumerijski izdelki in dišave; Izdelki za nego las in obdelavo las; Pripravki za nego kože, oči in nohtov; Kreme za obraz in telo; Kozmetični izdelki; Organska kozmetična sredstva; Toaletna sredstva; Ličila; Preparati za čiščenje in odišavljanje; Mila in tekoča mila; Šamponi; Preparati za čiščenje telesa in lepotilno nego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Aromatiska bad- och kroppsoljor; Aromterapipreparat; Deodoranter och antiperspiranter; Eteriska oljor och aromatiska extrakt; Parfymer och dofter; Produkter för hårbehandling och hårvård; Hud-, ögon- och nagelvårdspreparat; Krämer för ansikte och kropp; Kosmetika; Ekologisk kosmetika; Toalettartiklar; Make-up preparat; Rengöringsmedel och välluktande preparat; Tvål och gel; Schampon; Preparat för kroppsrengöring och skönhetsvård.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за търговия на дребно, услуги за препродажба на дребно и услуги за търговия на едро с козметика, органична козметика, препарати за кожата, ноктите и тялото, кремове за лице и тяло, почистващи и ароматизиращи препарати, козметични препарати, почистващи препарати за тяло и козметични препарати; Услуги за продажби, предоставяни чрез компютърни мрежи и електронна търговия във връзка с козметика, органична козметика, препарати за кожата, ноктите и тялото, кремове за лице и тяло, почистващи и ароматизиращи препарати, козметични препарати, почистващи препарати за тяло и козметични препарати.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Maloobchodní služby, přeprodávání a velkoobchodní služby pro kosmetiku, organickou kosmetiku, přípravky na pleť, nehty a tělo, obličejové a tělové krémy, čisticí a vonné přípravky, kosmetické přípravky, čisticí přípravky na tělo a zkrášlující přípravky; Prodejní služby poskytované prostřednictvím počítačových sítí a elektronického obchodování ve vztahu ke kosmetice, organické kosmetice, přípravkům na pleť, nehty a tělo, obličejovým a tělovým krémům, čisticím a vonným přípravkům, kosmetickým přípravkům, čisticím přípravkům na tělo a zkrášlujícím přípravkům.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Detailvirksomhed, videresalg og engroshandel i forbindelse med kosmetiske præparater, organiske kosmetiske præparater, hudpræparater til hud, negle og kroppen, ansigtscremer og hudcremer, rengørings- og duftpræparater, kosmetiske præparater, præparater til rensning af kroppen og præparater til skønhedspleje; Detailsalg udbudt via computernetværk og elektronisk handel med kosmetiske præparater, organiske kosmetiske præparater, hudpræparater til hud, negle og kroppen, ansigtscremer og hudcremer, rengørings- og duftpræparater, kosmetiske præparater, præparater til rensning af kroppen og præparater til skønhedspleje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen, Weiterverkauf und Großhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Kosmetika, Bio-Kosmetika, Präparate für Haut, Nägel und Körper, Gesichts- und Körpercremes, Reinigungs- und Duftpräparate, Kosmetika, Körperreinigungspräparate und Schönheitspräparate; Verkaufsdienstleistungen über Computernetze und elektronischer Handel in Bezug auf Kosmetika, Bio-Kosmetika, Präparate für Haut, Nägel und Körper, Gesichts- und Körpercremes, Reinigungs- und Duftpräparate, Kosmetika, Körperreinigungspräparate und Schönheitspräparate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης, υπηρεσίες μεταπώλησης και υπηρεσίες χονδρικής πώλησης σε σχέση με καλλυντικά, οργανικά καλλυντικά, παρασκευάσματα για το δέρμα, τα νύχια και το σώμα, κρέμες προσώπου και σώματος, παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού και αρωματικά, καλλυντικά παρασκευάσματα, παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού για το σώμα και παρασκευάσματα καλλωπισμού· Υπηρεσίες πώλησης παρεχόμενες μέσω δικτύων ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών και ηλεκτρονικού εμπορίου σε σχέση με καλλυντικά, οργανικά καλλυντικά, παρασκευάσματα για το δέρμα, τα νύχια και το σώμα, κρέμες προσώπου και σώματος, παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού και αρωματικά, καλλυντικά παρασκευάσματα, παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού για το σώμα και παρασκευάσματα καλλωπισμού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Retail services, resale services and wholesale services for cosmetics, organic cosmetics, preparations for the skin, nails and body, facial and body creams, cleaning and fragrancing preparations, cosmetic preparations, cleaning preparations for body and beauty preparations; Sales services provided via computer networks and electronic commerce in relation to cosmetics, organic cosmetics, preparations for the skin, nails and body, facial and body creams, cleaning and fragrancing preparations, cosmetic preparations, cleaning preparations for body and beauty preparations.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de venta al por menor, servicios de reventa y servicios de venta al por mayor de cosméticos, cosméticos orgánicos, preparaciones para la piel, las uñas y el cuerpo, cremas faciales y corporales, productos de limpieza y aromatizantes, productos cosméticos, productos de limpieza para el cuerpo y preparados de belleza; Servicios de ventas prestados a través de redes informáticas y comercio electrónico en relación con cosméticos, cosméticos orgánicos, preparaciones para la piel, las uñas y el cuerpo, cremas faciales y corporales, productos de limpieza y aromatizantes, productos cosméticos, productos de limpieza para el cuerpo y preparados de belleza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Järgmiste kaupade jaemüük, edasimüük ja hulgimüük: kosmeetikatooted, orgaanilised kosmeetikatooted, naha-, küünte- ja kehahooldusvahendid, näo- ja kehakreemid, puhastus- ja lõhnapreparaadid, kosmeetikavahendid, kehapuhastusvahendid ja ilutooted; Järgmiste kaupade müük arvutivõrkude ja elektronkaubanduse kaudu: kosmeetikatooted, orgaanilised kosmeetikatooted, naha-, küünte- ja kehahooldusvahendid, näo- ja kehakreemid, puhastus- ja lõhnapreparaadid, kosmeetikavahendid, kehapuhastusvahendid ja ilutooted.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kosmetiikan, luonnonmukaisen kosmetiikan, ihon-, silmien-, ja kynsienhoitovalmisteiden, kasvo- ja vartalovoiden, puhdistus- ja raikastusvalmisteiden, kosmeettisten valmisteiden ja vartalon puhdistus- ja kauneudenhoitovalmisteiden vähittäis-, jälleen- ja tukkumyyntipalvelut; kosmetiikan, luonnonmukaisen kosmetiikan, ihon-, silmien-, ja kynsienhoitovalmisteiden, kasvo- ja vartalovoiden, puhdistus- ja raikastusvalmisteiden, kosmeettisten valmisteiden ja vartalon puhdistus- ja kauneudenhoitovalmisteiden liittyvät tietoverkossa tapahtuvat vähittäismyyntipalvelut ja verkkokauppa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de vente au détail, services de revente et services de vente en gros de cosmétiques, cosmétiques biologiques, préparations pour la peau, les ongles et le corps, crèmes pour le visage et le corps, préparations nettoyantes et parfumantes, préparations cosmétiques, préparations nettoyantes pour le corps et produits de beauté; Services de vente fournis par le biais de réseaux informatiques et du commerce électronique en lien avec des cosmétiques, cosmétiques biologiques, préparations pour la peau, les ongles et le corps, crèmes pour le visage et le corps, préparations nettoyantes et parfumantes, préparations cosmétiques, préparations nettoyantes pour le corps et produits de beauté.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge maloprodaje, usluge preprodaje i usluge veleprodaje koje se odnose na kozmetičke proizvode, organske kozmetičke proizvode, pripravke za kožu, nokte i tijelo, kreme za lice i tijelo, pripravke za čišćenje i mirisne pripravke, kozmetičke pripravke, pripravke za čišćenje tijela i pripravke za uljepšavanje; Usluge prodaje pružene putem računalnih mreža i elektroničke trgovine koje se odnose na kozmetičke proizvode, organske kozmetičke proizvode, pripravke za kožu, nokte i tijelo, kreme za lice i tijelo, pripravke za čišćenje i mirisne pripravke, kozmetičke pripravke, pripravke za čišćenje tijela i pripravke za uljepšavanje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, újraértékesítési szolgáltatások és nagykereskedelmi szolgáltatások az alábbiakhoz kapcsolódóan: kozmetikumok, szerves kozmetikumok, bőrre való készítmények, arc- és testkrémek, tisztítószerek és illatszer-készítmények, kozmetikai készítmények, testtisztító készítmények és szépítkezőszerek; Számítógépes hálózatokon és elektronikus kereskedelemben nyújtott értékesítési szolgáltatások kozmetikumokkal, bio kozmetikumokkal, bőr-, köröm- és testkészítményekkel, arc- és testkrémekkel, tisztító és illatosító készítményekkel, kozmetikai készítményekkel, testtisztító és szépségápoló készítményekkel kapcsolatban.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di vendita al dettaglio, servizi di rivendita e servizi di vendita all'ingrosso di cosmetici, cosmetici organici, prodotti per la pelle, le unghie e il corpo, creme per il viso e il corpo, prodotti per la pulizia e la profumazione, prodotti cosmetici, prodotti per la pulizia del corpo e prodotti di bellezza; Servizi di vendita tramite reti informatiche e commercio elettronico in relazione a cosmetici, cosmetici organici, prodotti per la pelle, le unghie e il corpo, creme per il viso e il corpo, prodotti per la pulizia e la profumazione, prodotti cosmetici, prodotti per la pulizia del corpo e prodotti di bellezza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kosmetikos, organinės kosmetikos, odos, nagų ir kūno priežiūros priemonių, veido ir kūno kremų, valymo ir kvapiųjų preparatų, kosmetikos, kūno ir grožio preparatų mažmeninės prekybos, perpardavimo ir didmeninės prekybos paslaugos; Pardavimų paslaugos, teikiamos per kompiuterinius tinklus ir elektroninę komerciją, susijusios su kosmetika, ekologiška kosmetika, odos, nagų ir kūno preparatais, veido ir kūno kremais, valymo ir kvapiųjų medžiagų preparatais, kosmetikos preparatais, kūno ir grožio priemonių valymo preparatais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kosmētikas, organiskās kosmētikas, ādas, nagu un ķermeņa kopšanas līdzekļu, sejas un ķermeņa krēmu, tīrīšanas un smaržvielu, kosmētisko līdzekļu, ķermeņa tīrīšanas līdzekļu un skaistumkopšanas līdzekļu mazumtirdzniecības, vairumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi; Pārdošanas pakalpojumi, kas tiek sniegti, izmantojot datortīklus un elektronisko tirdzniecību, saistībā ar kosmētiku, organisko kosmētiku, ādas, nagu un ķermeņa kopšanas līdzekļiem, sejas un ķermeņa krēmiem, tīrīšanas un aromātiskiem līdzekļiem, kosmētiskiem līdzekļiem, ķermeņa tīrīšanas un skaistumkopšanas līdzekļiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut, servizzi ta' bejgħ mill-ġdid u servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-ingrossa għal kożmetiċi, kożmetiċi organiċi, preparazzjonijiet għall-ġilda, għad-dwiefer u għall-ġisem, kremi tal-wiċċ u tal-ġisem, preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif u għat-tfewwiħ, preparazzjonijiet kożmetiċi, preparazzjonijiet tat-tindif għall-ġisem u preparazzjonijiet tas-sbuħija; Servizzi ta' bejgħ ipprovduti permezz ta' netwerks tal-kompjuter u kummerċ elettroniku relatat ma' kożmetiċi, kożmetiċi organiċi, preparazzjonijiet għall-ġilda, għad-dwiefer u għall-ġisem, kremi tal-wiċċ u tal-ġisem, preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif u għat-tfewwiħ, preparazzjonijiet kożmetiċi, preparazzjonijiet tat-tindif għall-ġisem u preparazzjonijiet tas-sbuħija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Detailhandel in, wederverkoop van en groothandel in cosmetische middelen, organisch-biologische cosmetica, middelen voor de huid, nagels en het lichaam, crèmes voor het gezicht en lichaam, zuiverende en geurende preparaten, cosmetische middelen, reinigingsmiddelen voor het lichaam en schoonheidsproducten; Verkoopdiensten geleverd via computernetwerken en elektronische handel in cosmetische middelen, organisch-biologische cosmetica, middelen voor de huid, nagels en het lichaam, crèmes voor het gezicht en lichaam, zuiverende en geurende preparaten, cosmetische middelen, reinigingsmiddelen voor het lichaam en schoonheidsproducten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi handlu detalicznego, usługi odsprzedaży i usługi handlu hurtowego w zakresie kosmetyków, kosmetyków organicznych, preparatów do skóry, paznokci i ciała, kremów do twarzy i ciała, preparatów oczyszczających i zapachowych, preparatów kosmetycznych, preparatów oczyszczających do ciała i preparatów kosmetycznych; Usługi sprzedaży za pośrednictwem sieci komputerowych i handlu elektronicznego w zakresie kosmetyków, kosmetyków organicznych, preparatów do skóry, paznokci i ciała, kremów do twarzy i ciała, preparatów oczyszczających i zapachowych, preparatów kosmetycznych, preparatów oczyszczających do ciała i preparatów kosmetycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de venda a retalho, serviços de revenda e serviços de venda por grosso de cosméticos, cosméticos biológicos, produtos para a pele, as unhas e o corpo, cremes para o rosto e o corpo, produtos de limpeza e perfumados, produtos cosméticos, produtos de limpeza para o corpo e produtos de beleza; Serviços de vendas prestados através de redes informáticas e de comércio eletrónico relacionados com cosméticos, cosméticos biológicos, produtos para a pele, as unhas e o corpo, cremes para o rosto e o corpo, produtos de limpeza e perfumados, produtos cosméticos, produtos de limpeza para o corpo e produtos de beleza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de comerț cu amănuntul, servicii de distribuție și servicii de comerț cu ridicata cu cosmetice, produse cosmetice organice, produse pentru piele, unghii și corp, creme pentru față și corp, preparate de curățat și de parfumat, preparate cosmetice, preparate de curățat pentru corp și preparate pentru frumusețe; Servicii de vânzări furnizate prin rețele de calculatoare și comerț electronic în legătură cu cosmetice, produse cosmetice organice, produse pentru piele, unghii și corp, creme pentru față și corp, preparate de curățat și de parfumat, preparate cosmetice, preparate de curățat pentru corp și preparate pentru frumusețe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Maloobchodné služby, služby ďalšieho predaja a veľkoobchodné služby v oblasti tovaru, akým sú kozmetické prípravky, organická kozmetika, prípravky na pleť, nechty a telo, pleťové a telové krémy, čistenie a vonné prípravky, kozmetické prípravky, prípravky na čistenie tela a kozmetické prípravky; Služby v oblasti predaja poskytované prostredníctvom počítačových sietí a elektronického obchodu v tovaru, akým sú kozmetické prípravky, organická kozmetika, prípravky na pleť, nechty a telo, pleťové a telové krémy, čistenie a vonné prípravky, kozmetické prípravky, prípravky na čistenie tela a kozmetické prípravky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve maloprodaje, preprodaje in veleprodaje za izdelke, kot so kozmetični izdelki, organski kozmetični izdelki, izdelki za kožo, nohte in telo, kreme za obraz in telo, izdelki za čiščenje in odišavljanje, kozmetični izdelki, izdelki za čiščenje telesa in lepotilni izdelki; Storitve prodaje, nudenje prek računalniških omrežij in elektronskega poslovanja v zvezi z izdelki, kot so kozmetični izdelki, organski kozmetični izdelki, izdelki za kožo, nohte in telo, kreme za obraz in telo, izdelki za čiščenje in odišavljanje, kozmetični izdelki, izdelki za čiščenje telesa in lepotilni izdelki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Detaljhandelsförsäljning, återförsäljartjänster och grossistförsäljning av kosmetika, ekologisk kosmetika, preparat för huden, spikar och kropp, ansikts- och kroppskrämer, rengöring och doftpreparat, kosmetiska preparat, kroppsrengöringsmedel och skönhetspreparat; Försäljning tillhandahållen via datornät och elektronisk handel av kosmetika, ekologisk kosmetika, preparat för huden, spikar och kropp, ansikts- och kroppskrämer, rengöring och doftpreparat, kosmetiska preparat, kroppsrengöringsmedel och skönhetspreparat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/091</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-15</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082025</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>10880</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003128958</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-08-13</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>015758303</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2016-08-19</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>015758303</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2016-12-02</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>Remitan</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>806285</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>10004</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
