<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-18T14:29:17</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229802</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229802</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-26</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-14</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-26</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-18</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Behendigkeit</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Записано медийно съдържание.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Obsah médií.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Medieindhold.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bespielte Medien.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Περιεχόμενο πολυμέσων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Media content.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Contenidos multimedia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meediasisu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mediatallenteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Contenu de médias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Medijski sadržaj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Média tartalmak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Contenuti per mezzi di comunicazione.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Masinės Informacijos priemonių turinys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Audio, video un multivides materiāli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kontenut tal-midja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Media content.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Muzyka, filmy i inne rodzaje elektronicznych publikacji tekstowych i obrazowych utrwalone na nośnikach.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Conteúdos de média.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Conținut media.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Záznamy na nosičoch.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Medijske posnete vsebine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Medieinnehåll.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Консултации относно бизнес управление в сферата на развитието на изпълнителните органи и ръководството; Съвети по мениджмънт; Бизнес консултантски услуги; Консултация по бизнес управление; Консултации, свързани с бизнес организация; Услуги за бизнес управление и консултации; Консултации в областта на търговското ръководство и организация; Управление на бизнес проекти; Бизнес консултации, свързани с поизводството на продукти; Стопанско управление.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Poradenství pro obchodní management v oboru rozvoje řízení a vedení; Poradenství v oblasti managementu; Obchodní konzultační služby; Poradenství v oblasti řízení obchodní činnosti; Poradenství v oblasti organizace podniku; Poradenské služby a služby v oblasti obchodního managementu; Poradenství v oblasti řízení a organizace podniku; Management obchodních projektů; Obchodní poradenské služby vztahující se k výrobním odvětvím; Služby v oblasti obchodního managementu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Konsulentbistand vedrørende virksomhedsledelse inden for lederskabsudvikling; Rådgivning vedrørende ledelse; Forretningsmæssig rådgivningsvirksomhed; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsledelse; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsorganisation; Forretningsledelse og -rådgivning; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsledelse og organisation; Administration af erhvervsprojekter; Virksomhedsrådgivning i forbindelse med produktfremstilling; Forretningsledelse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Beratung zu Fragen der Geschäftsführung auf dem Gebiet der Entwicklung von Führungs- und Leitungskräften; Beratung zur Geschäftsführung; Unternehmensberatungsdienste; Beratung in Fragen der Geschäftsführung; Organisationsberatung in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Geschäftsführung und Unternehmensberatungsdienste; Beratung bei der Organisation und Führung von Unternehmen; Kaufmännisches Projektmanagement; Unternehmensberatung in Bezug auf die Herstellung von Produkten; Geschäftsführung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παροχή συμβουλών για διαχείριση επιχειρήσεων στον τομέα της ανάπτυξης διοικητικών στελεχών και ηγετικών ικανοτήτων· Παροχή συμβουλών σε θέματα διαχείρισης· Υπηρεσίες συμβουλευτικής επιχειρήσεων· Παροχή επιχειρηματικών συμβουλών· Συμβουλευτική σε θέματα οργάνωσης επιχειρήσεων· Υπηρεσίες επιχειρηματικής διαχείρισης και συμβουλευτικής· Επιχειρήσεων (Συμβουλές για οργάνωση και διεύθυνση -)· Διαχείριση επιχειρηματικών έργων· Υπηρεσίες παροχής επιχειρηματικών συμβουλών σχετικά με την κατασκευή προϊόντων· Διοίκηση επιχειρήσεων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Business management consultancy in the field of executive and leadership development; Management consulting; Business consulting; Business management consulting; Business organisation consulting; Business management and consulting; Business organisation and management consulting services; Consulting services in business organization and management; Business project management; Business advisory services relating to product manufacturing; Business management.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Consultoría de gestión empresarial en el ámbito del desarrollo de liderazgo y ejecutivo; Asesoría en materia de gestión; Consultoría comercial; Consultoría sobre dirección de negocios; Consultoría sobre organización de negocios; Servicios de consultoría de gestión empresarial; Consultoría sobre organización y dirección de negocios; Gestión de proyectos empresariales; Servicios de asesoramiento de empresas sobre la fabricación de productos; Gestión de empresas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ärijuhtimiskonsultatsioonid täidesaatmis- ja juhtimisoskuse arendamise valdkonnas; Juhtimiskonsultatsioonid; Ärialane nõustamine; Äritegevuse juhtimise konsultatsioonid; Äritegevuse korraldamise konsultatsioonid; Ärijuhtimis- ja konsultatsiooniteenused; Äritegevuse juhtimise ja korraldamise konsultatsioonid; Äriprojektide juhtimine; Toodete tootmisega seotud ärinõustamisteenused; Ärijuhtimine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Liikkeenjohtoon liittyvä konsultointi yrityksen hallitus- ja johtoportaan kehittämisen alalla; Johtamisen neuvonta; Yrityskonsultointipalvelut; Liikkeenhoidon konsultointi; Liiketoiminnan järjestämiseen liittyvä konsultointi; Liikkeenjohto- ja yrityskonsultointipalvelut; Liikkeenhoitoon ja organisaatioon liittyvä konsultointi; Liiketoimintaprojektien hallinta; Tuotteiden valmistukseen liittyvät yritysneuvontapalvelut; Liikkeenjohto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Consultation en gestion commerciale dans le domaine du développement des cadres et de la direction; Conseils en gestion des affaires; Services de conseillers d'affaires; Consultation pour la direction des affaires; Conseils en organisation des affaires; Services de conseillers et gestion d'affaires commerciales; Conseils en organisation et direction des affaires; Gestion de projets commerciaux; Services de conseils commerciaux relatifs à la fabrication de produits; Services de gestion commerciale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Savjetovanje o poslovnom upravljanju u području razvoja izvršnog upravljanja i vodstva; Savjetodavanje za upravljanje; Poslovno savjetovanje; Konzultacije u svezi vođenje poslova; Savjetovanje u svezi poslovne organizacije; Usluge poslovnog upravljanja i konzultacija; Savjeti o organizaciji i vođenju poslova; Upravljanje poslovnim projektima; Poslovne savjetodavne usluge u svezi procesa proizvodnje; Poslovno upravljanje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Üzleti menedzsment tanácsadás az igazgatói és cégvezetési fejlesztéssel kapcsolatban; Menedzsment tanácsadás; Üzleti konzultációs szolgáltatások; Üzletvezetési konzultáció; Üzletszervezéssel kapcsolatos konzultáció; Üzletvezetési és konzultációs szolgáltatások; Üzletszervezési és üzletvezetési tanácsadás; Üzleti projektmenedzsment; Termékgyártással kapcsolatos üzleti tanácsadási szolgáltatások; Üzleti menedzsment.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Consulenza relativa a gestione aziendale in materia di formazione di dirigenti e leadership; Consulenza gestionale; Servizi di consulenza aziendale; Consulenza per la gestione degli affari; Servizi di consulenza per l'organizzazione degli affari; Servizi di gestione aziendale e consulenza; Servizi di consulenza per l'organizzazione e la gestione degli affari; Gestione di progetti aziendali; Servizi di consulenza aziendale in materia di fabbricazione di prodotti; Gestione aziendale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Verslo vadybos konsultacijos vadovaujančiųjų darbuotojų ir vadovybės veiklos gerinimo srityje; Vadybos konsultacijos; Verslo konsultacijos; Verslo vadybos konsultacijos; Verslo organizavimo konsultacijos; Verslo vadybos ir konsultavimo paslaugos; Verslo vadybos ir organizavimo konsultacijos; Verslo projektų vadyba; Produktų gamybos verslo konsultavimo paslaugos; Verslo vadyba.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Biznesa vadības konsultācijas izpildīšanas un vadīšanas attīstības jomā; Vadības konsultācijas; Konsultāciju sniegšana darījumu jomā; Konsultāciju sniegšana uzņēmējdarbības vadībā; Konsultāciju sniegšana par uzņēmējdarbības organizēšanu; Uzņēmējdarbības pārvaldības un konsultāciju pakalpojumi; Konsultāciju sniegšana darījumu vadīšanā un organizēšanā; Uzņēmējdarbības projektu pārvaldība; Uzņēmējdarbības konsultāciju pakalpojumi saistībā ar produktu ražošanu; Uzņēmējdarbības vadības pakalpojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Konsulenza fuq il-ġestjoni tan-negozju fil-qasam ta' l-iżvilupp eżekuttiv u d-direzzjoni; Pariri dwar il-ġestjoni; Konsulenza dwar negozju; Konsulenza fil-ġestjoni ta' negozju; Konsulenza dwar l-organizzazzjoni ta' negozju; Servizzi ta' konsulenza dwar ġestjoni għan-negozji; Konsulenza dwar il-ġestjoni u l-organizzazzjoni ta' negozju; Il-ġestjoni ta' proġetti tan-negozju; Servizzi ta' pariri għan-negozji dwar il-manifattura ta' prodotti; Il-ġestjoni ta' negozju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Consultancy over beheer van commerciële zaken op het gebied van ontwikkeling van leidinggevend personeel en leiderschap; Managementadvies; Zakelijke consultancy; Advisering inzake bedrijfsvoering; Advisering over bedrijfsorganisatie; Commercieel-zakelijke bedrijfsvoering en consultancy; Bedrijfsorganisatorische en -bestuurlijke advisering; Zakelijk projectmanagement; Bedrijfsorganisatorische advisering met betrekking tot productfabricage; Diensten op het gebied van bedrijfsvoering.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Konsultacje w zakresie zarządzania firmą w dziedzinie rozwoju kadry kierowniczej i przywódców; Doradztwo związane z zarządzaniem; Doradztwo biznesowe; Doradztwo w zakresie zarządzania biznesem; Doradztwo w zakresie organizacji działalności gospodarczej; Usługi doradcze w zakresie działalności gospodarczej i usługi zarządzania działalnością gospodarczą; Doradztwo w zakresie organizowania i prowadzenia działalności gospodarczej; Zarządzanie projektami z zakresu działalności gospodarczej; Doradztwo w zakresie działalności gospodarczej dotyczące wytwarzania produktów; Zarządzanie działalnością gospodarczą.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Consultoria em gestão comercial na área de desenvolvimento de executivos e de líderes; Assessoria de gestão; Consultoria empresarial; Consultadoria para direção de negócios comerciais; Consultoria em organização de negócios comerciais; Serviços de gestão de negócios e de consultadoria; Consultadoria em organização e direção de negócios comerciais; Gestão de projetos empresariais; Serviços de assessoria de negócios na área do fabrico de produtos; Gestão de empresas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Consultanță în administrarea afacerilor, în domeniul dezvoltării directorilor și personalului de conducere; Consultanță în materie de management; Consultanță în afaceri; Consultanță pentru conducerea afacerilor; Consultanță privind organizarea afacerii; Servicii de consultanță și de management al afacerilor; Consultanță în managementul și organizarea afacerilor; Managementul proiectelor de afaceri; Servicii de consultanță comercială cu privire la fabricarea de produse; Administrare de afaceri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Obchodné manažérske poradenstvo v oblasti rozvoja výkonných a vedúcich zamestnancov; Poradenstvo v oblasti manažmentu; Obchodné poradenstvo; Poradenstvo pri riadení podnikov; Poradenstvo pri organizovaní obchodnej činnosti; Poradenské služby a služby v oblasti podnikateľského manažmentu; Poradenstvo pri organizovaní a riadení obchodnej činnosti; Riadenie obchodných projektov; Obchodené poradenské služby vo výrobných odvetviach; Obchodný manažment.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Svetovanje pri poslovnem vodenju na področju izvršilne in vodstvene sposobnosti; Svetovanje pri upravljanju; Storitve poslovnega svetovanja; Poslovodno svetovanje; Svetovanje v zvezi s poslovno organizacijo; Storitve poslovnega vodenja in svetovanja; Poslovodno in organizacijsko svetovanje; Upravljanje poslovnih projektov; Poslovno svetovalne storitve v zvezi s proizvodnjo izdelkov; Poslovno upravljanje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Företagsledningskonsultationer avseende chefs- och ledarskapsutveckling; Rådgivning vid företagsledning; Företagskonsultation; Konsulttjänster avseende management; Företagsorganisationskonsultationer; Företagsledning och konsultationer därtill; Konsultationer avseende företagsledning och -organisation; Affärsmässig projektledning; Företagsrådgivningstjänster relaterade till produkttillverkning; Företagsledning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Създаване [писане] на подкастове; Услуги за видео, аудио и мултимедийни цифрови публикации за развлечение; Трениране; Курсове за обучение (предоставяне); Услуги по бизнес обучение; Управление на услуги в областта на образованието; Продуциране на тренировъчни видеокасети; Обучение, ръководене на семинари; Обучение в бизнес управлението; Образование и обучение; Организиране и провеждане на практически семинари [обучение]; Провеждане на курсове, семинар и обучения; Уреждане, провеждане и организиране на конференции; Услуги за образование и обучение.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Tvorba [psaní] podcastů; Digitální video, audio a multimediální zábavní vydavatelské služby; Koučování; Vzdělávací kurzy; Obchodní vzdělávání; Vzdělávací služby týkající se managementu; Výroba naučných videí; Vedení výukových seminářů; Školení podnikového managementu; Vzdělávací a školicí služby; Pořádání a vedení workshopů [školení]; Vedení kurzů, seminářů a workshopů; Pořádání, vedení a organizování konferencí; Vzdělávací a školicí služby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Udarbejdelse [skrivning] af podcasts; Udsendelsestjenester vedrørende digital video-, lyd- og multimedieunderholdning; Coaching; Kursusvirksomhed; Uddannelsesvirksomhed vedrørende handel; Uddannelse i virksomhedsledelse; Produktion af undervisningsvideoer; Organisering af uddannelsesseminarer; Undervisning i forretningsledelse; Uddannelses og undervisningsvirksomhed; Arrangering og ledelse af workshops [uddannelse]; Afholdelse af kurser, seminarer og workshopper; Arrangering, ledelse og organisering af konferencer; Uddannelses- og undervisningsvirksomhed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Erstellung [Verfassen] von Podcasts; Veröffentlichung von digitaler Video-, Audio- und Multimediaunterhaltung; Coaching; Schulung; Betriebliche Ausbildung; Managementausbildung; Aufzeichnungen von Lehrvideos; Organisation von Bildungsseminaren; Betriebswirtschaftliche Ausbildung; Bildung, Erziehung und Unterricht; Veranstaltung und Durchführung von Workshops [Ausbildung]; Durchführung von Kursen, Seminaren und Workshops; Vorbereitung, Durchführung und Organisation von Konferenzen; Bildung, Erziehung und Unterricht.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δημιουργία (συγγραφή) βιντεομηνυμάτων (podcasts)· Υπηρεσίες ψυχαγωγικών εκδόσεων ψηφιακού βίντεο, ήχου και πολυμέσων· Προπόνηση· Παροχή επιμορφωτικών μαθημάτων· Υπηρεσίες επιχειρηματικής κατάρτισης· Υπηρεσίες εκπαίδευσης στον τομέα της διαχείρισης· Παραγωγή εκπαιδευτικών βίντεο· Οργάνωση εκπαιδευτικών σεμιναρίων σε σχέση με· Επιμόρφωση σε θέματα διοίκησης επιχειρήσεων· Εκπαιδευση και Διδασκαλία· Οργάνωση και διεξαγωγή επιμορφωτικών σεμιναρίων· Διεξαγωγή μαθημάτων, σεμιναρίων και εργαστηρίων· Συντονισμός, διοργάνωση και διεξαγωγή συνεδρίων· Υπηρεσίες εκπαίδευσης και διδασκαλίας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Creation [writing] of podcasts; Digital video, audio and multimedia entertainment publishing services; Coaching; Training courses; Business training; Management training services; Production of training videos; Organisation of training seminars; Training in business management; Educational and training services; Arranging and conducting workshops; Conducting courses, seminars and workshops; Arranging, conducting and organisation of conferences; Education and instruction services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Creación [escritura] de archivos de audio portátitles [podcasts]; Servicios de publicación de contenidos de entretenimiento multimedia, de audio y de vídeo digital; Servicios de entrenamiento; Prestación de cursos de formación; Servicios de formación empresarial; Servicios de formación en materia de gestión; Producción de vídeos formativos; Organización de seminarios de formación; Formación en gestión de negocios; Educación e instrucción; Organización y dirección de talleres de formación; Dirección de cursos, seminarios y talleres; Preparación, celebración y organización de conferencias; Servicios de educación e instrucción.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Netisaadete loomine [kirjutamine]; Digitaalsed video-, audio- ja multimeediameelelahutuse avaldamisteenused; Juhendamine, treenimine; Koolituskursuste pakkumine; Ärikoolitusteenused; Juhtimiskoolitus; Õppevideote produtseerimine; Õppeseminaride korraldamine; Ärijuhtimiskoolitus; Haridus ja juhendamine; Õpitubade korraldamine ja läbiviimine [koolitus]; Kursuste, seminaride ja töötubade juhendamine; Konverentside korraldamine, läbiviimine ja organiseerimine; Haridus- ja õpetusteenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Podcastien luominen [kirjoittaminen]; Digitaalisen video-, ääni- ja multimediaviihteen julkaisupalvelut; Valmennuspalvelut; Koulutuskurssien tarjoaminen; Liiketoimintaan liittyvä koulutus; Johtamiskoulutuspalvelut; Koulutusvideoiden tuottaminen; Koulutusseminaarien pitäminen; Liikkeenjohtamisen koulutus; Koulutus ja ohjaus; Työpajojen järjestäminen [koulutus]; Kurssien, seminaarien ja työpajojen pitäminen; Konferenssien järjestäminen, pitäminen ja organisoiminen; Koulutus- ja opetuspalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Création [rédaction] de podcasts; Services d'édition de divertissement multimédia, audio et vidéo numérique; Formation; Offre de cours de formation; Services de formation commerciale; Services de formation en gestion; Production de vidéos de formation; Organisation de séminaires éducatifs; Formation en gestion d'entreprises; Éducation et instruction; Organisation et conduite d'ateliers de formation; Organisation de cours, de séminaires et d'ateliers; Préparation, coordination et organisation de conférences; Services d’éducation et d’instruction.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sastavljanje [pisanje] podcastova; Izdavačke usluge za digitalnu, audio i multimedijsku zabavu; Treniranje; Pružanje tečajeva osposobljavanja; Poslovno usavršavanje; Usluge obuke u svezi s rukovodstvom; Proizvodnja video materijala za poduku; Vođenje seminara osposobljavanja; Osposobljavanje iz poslovnog upravljanja; Obrazovanje i poduka; Organiziranje i vođenje radionica; Vođenje tečajeva, seminara i radionica; Dogovaranje, izvođenje i organizacija konferencija; Usluge obrazovanja i podučavanja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Podcastok létrehozása [írása]; Digitális videó, audió és multimédia kiadási szolgáltatások; Coaching; Tanfolyamok, kurzusok biztosítása; Üzleti képzés; Menedzser oktatási szolgáltatások; Oktatóvideók készítése; Oktatási szemináriumok tartása; Üzletvezetői képzés; Oktatás és tanítás; Alkotóműhelyek szervezése és lebonyolítása [képzés]; Tanfolyamok, szemináriumok és műhelyek lebonyolítása; Konferenciák szervezése, lebonyolítása és rendezése; Oktatási és képzési szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Creazione [redazione] di podcast; Servizi di pubblicazione di contenuti ricreativi multimediali e di audio e video digitali; Assistenza professionale (coaching); Corsi di formazione; Formazione aziendale; Istruzione in materia di gestione; Produzione di video di formazione; Realizzazione di seminari di formazione; Formazione in gestione aziendale; Educazione e formazione; Organizzazione e gestione di laboratori di formazione [workshop]; Conduzione di corsi, seminari e workshop; Organizzazione, preparazione e realizzazione di conferenze; Servizi relativi a educazione e istruzione.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Tinklalaidžių kūrimas [rašymas]; Skaitmeninės vaizdo, garso ir pramoginės multimedijos leidybos paslaugos; Treniravimas; Mokymo kursų rengimas; Verslo mokymo paslaugos; Vadovų mokymo paslaugos; Mokomųjų vaizdo įrašų kūrimas; Mokomųjų seminarų vedimas; Verslo vadybos mokymas; Švietimas ir instruktavimas; Profesinis mokymas ir rengimas; Kursų, seminarų ir praktinių seminarų vedimas; Konferencijų rengimas, vedimas ir organizavimas; Švietimo ir instruktavimo paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Aplādes datņu izveide (rakstīšana); Digitālās video, audio un multivides izklaides publicēšanas pakalpojumi; Trenēšana; Apmācības kursu pakalpojumi; Apmācība uzņēmējdarbības jomā; Vadītāju apmācības pakalpojumi; Mācību video producēšana; Apmācības semināru vadīšana; Apmācība uzņēmējdarbības vadībā; Audzināšana un apmācība; Praktisko nodarbību rīkošana un vadīšana; Kursu, semināru un darbsemināru vadīšana; Konferenču sagatavošana, vadīšana un organizēšana; Izglītības un instruēšanas pakalpojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ħolqien [kitba] ta' podkasts; Servizzi ta' pubblikazzjoni ta' vidjo diġitali, ta' awdjo u ta' divertiment multimedjali; Taħriġ/ikkowċjar; Il-provvista ta' korsijiet tat-taħriġ; Servizzi ta' taħriġ relatati man-negozju; Servizzi ta' edukazzjoni relatati mal-ġestjoni; Produzzjoni ta' vidjows għat-taħriġ; Tmexxija ta' seminars ta' taħriġ; Taħriġ dwar il-ġestjoni tan-negozju; Edukazzjoni u istruzzjoni; L-arranġament u t-tmexxija ta' werkxops [taħriġ]; It-tmexxija ta' korsijiet, seminars u werkxops; Arranġament, tmexxija u organizzazzjoni ta' konferenzi; Servizzi ta' edukazzjoni u ta' tagħlim.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Het creëren [schrijven] van podcasts; Uitgeven van digitale video-, audio- en multimedia entertainment; Coaching (training); Instructiecursussen (Het geven van -); Bedrijfsopleiding; Diensten inzake managementopleiding; Productie van opleidingsvideo's; Instructieve seminars; Trainingen in beheer van commerciële zaken; Opvoeding, onderwijs en training; Het organiseren en houden van workshops; Het houden van cursussen, seminars en workshops; Voorbereiding, uitvoering en organisatie van conferenties; Diensten met betrekking tot opvoeding en opleiding.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Tworzenie [opracowywanie] podcastów; Usługi publikowania cyfrowych materiałów wideo, audio i rozrywki multimedialnej; Trenowanie; Usługi w zakresie zapewniania kursów szkoleniowych; Szkolenia biznesowe; Usługi edukacyjne w zakresie zarządzania; Produkcja szkoleniowych filmów wideo; Prowadzenie seminariów szkoleniowych; Szkolenia w zakresie zarządzania działalnością gospodarczą; Nauczanie i szkolenia; Organizowanie i prowadzenie warsztatów [szkolenie]; Prowadzenie kursów, seminariów i warsztatów; Przygotowywanie, organizowanie i prowadzenie konferencji; Usługi edukacyjne i instruktażowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Criação [escrita] de podcasts; Serviços de publicação de conteúdos de entretenimento de vídeo, áudio e multimédia; Acompanhamento técnico; Fornecimento de cursos de formação; Serviços de formação em negócios; Serviços de formação em matéria de gestão; Produção de vídeos de formação; Direção de seminários de instrução; Formação em gestão empresarial; Educação e Formação; Organização e realização de workshops; Direção de cursos, seminários e workshops; Preparação, direção e organização de conferências; Serviços de educação e formação.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Creare [redactare] de podcast-uri; Servicii de publicare de divertisment video digital, audio și multimedia; Asistență profesională individualizată [coaching]; Furnizare de cursuri de instruire; Servicii de instruire în domeniul afacerilor; Servicii de formare în management; Producție de materiale video formative; Organizare de seminarii educative; Instruire în domeniul administrării afacerilor; Educație și instruire; Organizarea și conducerea de workshop-uri; Coordonare de cursuri, seminarii și ateliere de lucru; Realizare, coordonare și organizare de conferințe; Servicii educative și de instruire.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Tvorba [písanie] podcastov; Služby vydávania digitálnych videozáznamov, audiozáznamov a multimediálnej zábavy; Trénovanie; Vzdelávacie kurzy; Školiace služby v oblasti podnikania a obchodu; Služby týkajúce sa vzdelávania v oblasti manažmentu; Výroba školiacich videozáznamov; Vedenie inštruktážnych seminárov; Školenia zamerané na podnikový manažment; Výchovné a vzdelávacie služby; Organizovanie a vedenie tvorivých dielní (výučba); Vedenie kurzov, seminárov a workshopov; Usporiadanie, vedenie a organizovanie konferencií; Výchovné a vzdelávacie služby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Izdelava [pisanje] poddaj; Digitalne video, avdio in multimedijske razvedrilne založniške storitve; Trenerstvo; Nudenje tečajev usposabljanja; Poslovno usposabljanje; Izobraževalne storitve na področju poslovodstva; Produkcija videov za usposabljanje; Izvajanje izobraževalnih seminarjev; Usposabljanje na področju poslovnega upravljanja; Izobraževanje in poučevanje; Organiziranje in vodenje učnih delavnic [šolanje]; Vodenje tečajev, seminarjev in delavnic; Prirejanje, vodenje in organizacija konferenc; Storitve izobraževanja in poučevanja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Skapande av poddsändningar [textförfattande]; Publiceringstjänster avseende digital video-, ljud- och multimedieunderhållning; Handledning och instruktion, nämligen idrottscoaching; Anordnande av handledning/instruktion och kurser; Affärsutbildning; Undervisning/utbildning i företagsledning; Produktion av utbildningsvideor; Organisering av utbildningsseminarier; Utbildning med inriktning på affärsledning; Utbildning och instruktion; Anordnande och genomförande av workshopar; Genomförande av kurser, seminarier och workshopar; Anordnande, genomförande och organisation av konferenser; Utbildnings- och undervisningstjänster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Консултации в областта на информационните технологии; Компютърни софтуерни консултации; IT управление на проекти; Разработване на продукти; Консултации, свързани с разработване на продукти; Разработване на софтуер; Продуктов дизайн.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Poradenství v oblasti informačních technologií; Poradenství v oblasti počítačového softwaru; Správa projektů v oblasti informačních technologií; Vývoj výrobků; Konzultace v oblasti vývoje výrobků; Vývoj softwaru; Navrhování výrobků.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Rådgivning vedrørende informationsteknologi; Rådgivning vedrørende computer software; It-projektstyring; Produktudvikling; Rådgivning vedrørende produktudvikling; Softwareudvikling; Produktdesign.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Beratung auf den Gebieten Informationstechnologie; Computersoftwareberatung; IT-Projektmanagement; Produktentwicklung; Produktentwicklungsberatung; Softwareentwicklung; Produktdesign.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παροχή συμβουλών στον τομέα της τεχνολογίας της πληροφορίας· Παροχή συμβουλών σε σχέση με λογισμικό ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Διαχείριση έργων τεχνολογίας πληροφοριών· Ανάπτυξη προϊόντων· Παροχή συμβουλών σχετικά με την ανάπτυξη προϊόντων· Ανάπτυξη λογισμικού για ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Σχεδιασμός προϊόντων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Information technology consulting; Software consulting services; IT project management; Product development; Product development consultation; Software development services; Software development; Product design.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Consultoría en materia de tecnología de la información; Consultoría sobre software; Gestión de proyectos de TI; Desarrollo de productos; Consultas sobre desarrollo de productos; Desarrollo de software; Diseño de productos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Infotehnoloogiakonsultatsioonid; Arvutitarkvarakonsultatsioonid; IT-projektijuhtimine; Tootearendus; Tootearendusalased konsultatsioonid; Tarkvara arendamine; Tootedisain.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Konsultointi tietotekniikan alalla; Konsultointi liittyen tietokoneohjelmistoihin; Tietotekniikkaan liittyvä hankkeenjohtaminen; Tuotekehittely; Tuotekehitykseen liittyvä konsultointi; Ohjelmistokehitys; Tuotesuunnittelu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de conseils en technologie de l'information; Consultation en matière de logiciels; Gestion de projets dans le domaine des technologies de l'information; Développement de produits; Conseils en matière de développement de produits; Développement de logiciels; Conception de produits.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Konzultacije u području informacijske tehnologije; Konzultantske usluge u svezi s računalnim softverom; Upravljanje informatičkim projektima; Razvoj proizvoda; Savjetovanje u svezi sa razvojem proizvoda; Razvoj softvera; Dizajn proizvoda.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Információtechnológiai szaktanácsadás; Számítógép szoftver tanácsadás; Információtechnológiai projektvezetés; Termékfejlesztés; Termékfejlesztési tanácsadás; Számítógépes szoftver fejlesztése; Termékek formatervezése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Consulenza in materia di informatica; Consulenza in materia di software; Gestione di progetti informatici; Sviluppo di prodotti; Consulenza in materia di sviluppo di prodotti; Sviluppo di software; Progettazione di prodotti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Konsultacijos informacinių technologijų srityje; Kompiuterių programinės įrangos konsultacijos; IT projektų valdymas; Produktų plėtra; Konsultacijos produktų plėtros klausimais; Programinės įrangos tobulinimas; Gaminių dizainas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Konsultācijas informācijas tehnoloģiju jomā; Konsultēšana datoru programmatūras jomā; IT projektu vadīšana; Produktu attīstīšana; Konsultācijas par produktu attīstīšanu; Programmatūras izstrāde; Produktu dizains.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Konsulenza dwar it-teknoloġija tal-informatika; Konsulenza (fis-softwer tal-kompjuter); Ġestjoni ta' proġetti tal-IT; L-iżviluppar ta' prodotti; Konsultazzjoni dwar żvilupp tal-prodotti; Żvilupp ta' softwer; Disinn ta' prodott.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Advisering op het gebied van informatietechnologie; Advisering op het gebied van software; IT-projectmanagement; Productontwikkeling; Raadgeving op het gebied van productontwikkeling; Ontwikkeling van software; Productontwerp.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Konsultacje w dziedzinie technologii informacyjnej; Doradztwo w zakresie oprogramowania komputerowego; Zarządzanie projektami w zakresie technologii informacyjnych; Opracowywanie produktów; Doradztwo w zakresie opracowywania produktów; Opracowywanie oprogramowania komputerowego; Projektowanie produktu [wzornictwo].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Consultadoria em tecnologia da informação; Consultoria em software; Gestão de projetos de TI; Desenvolvimento de produtos; Consultadoria sobre o desenvolvimento de produtos; Desenvolvimento de software; Design de produtos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Consultanță în domeniul tehnologiei informației; Consultanță în domeniul programelor de calculator; Managementul proiectelor IT; Dezvoltare de produse; Consultanță pentru dezvoltarea de produse; Dezvoltare de software; Proiectare de produs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Konzultačné služby pre informatiku; Poradenstvo v oblasti počítačových programov; Riadenie IT projektov; Vývoj výrobkov; Poradenstvo v oblasti vývoja nových výrobkov; Vývoj počítačového softvéru; Navrhovanie výrobkov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Informacijsko tehnološko svetovanje; Svetovanje na področju računalniške programske opreme; Vodenje IT projektov; Razvoj izdelkov; Svetovanje pri razvoju izdelkov; Razvoj programske opreme; Oblikovanje izdelkov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Konsultation inom området för informationsteknik och datorer; Rådgivning avseende datormjukvara; IT-projektledning; Produktutveckling; Konsultation avseende produktutveckling; Utveckling av mjukvara; Produktformgivning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/085</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-07</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/155</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-17</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
