<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T09:40:06</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229288</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229288</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>fr</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>RALPH'S CLUB</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Козметични средства; Парфюмерия; Одеколон; Лични дезодоранти; Препарати за бръснене; Лосиони за след бръснене; Препарати за коса и за третиране на окосмяването; Етерични масла.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kosmetické přípravky; Parfémy; Toaletní voda; Osobní deodoranty; Holicí přípravky; Přípravky po holení; Přípravky pro péči o vlasy; Éterické oleje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kosmetik; Parfumer; Eau de toilette [lotioner til toiletbrug]; Kropsdeodoranter; Præparater til barbering; Aftershavepræparater; Præparater til hår og behandling af hår; Æteriske olier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kosmetika; Parfüms; Toilettewasser; Deodorants für den persönlichen Gebrauch; Rasiermittel; Rasierwasser; Haarpräparate und Haarkuren; Ätherische Öle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καλλυντικά· Αρωματισμού (Προϊόντα -)· Κολώνιες· Αποσμητικά σώματος· Ξυρίσματος (Προϊόντα -)· Προϊόν για μετά το ξύρισμα (after shave)· Παρασκευάσματα για την περιποίηση και τη θεραπεία των μαλλιών· Αιθέρια (Έλαια -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Cosmetics; Perfumes; Toilet water; Personal deodorants; Shaving preparations; After-shave preparations; Hair preparations and treatments; Ethereal oils.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cosméticos; Perfumes; Aguas de tocador; Desodorantes personales; Productos de afeitar; Preparaciones para después del afeitado; Preparaciones y tratamientos para el cabello; Aceites esenciales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kosmeetikavahendid; Parfüümid, lõhnaõlid; Tualettvesi; Deodorandid isiklikuks kasutamiseks; Raseerained; Habemeajamisjärgsed näoveed; Juuksehooldus- ja -töötlusvahendid; Eeterlikud õlid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kosmetiikka; Hajuvedet; Kölninvesi; Deodorantit henkilökohtaiseen käyttöön; Parranajovalmisteet; After shave -valmisteet; Hiusten hoito- ja käsittelyvalmisteet; Eteeriset öljyt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Cosmétiques; parfums; eaux de toilette; déodorants corporels; produits de rasage; préparations après rasage; préparations et traitements capillaires; huiles essentielles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kozmetički proizvodi; Mirisi; Kolonjska voda; Dezodoransi za osobnu uporabu; Proizvodi za brijanje; Losioni za upotrebu poslije brijanja; Pripravci i tretmani za kosu; Esencijalna ulja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kozmetikai szerek; Illatszer készítmények; Kölnivíz; Dezodorok személyes használatra; Készítmények borotválkozáshoz; Borotválkozás utáni arcszeszek; Hajápoló készítmények; Esszenciális olajok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cosmetici; Profumi; Acque da toilette; Deodoranti personali; Prodotti per la rasatura; Lozioni dopobarba; Preparati e trattamenti per i capelli; Oli essenziali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kosmetika; Kvepalai; Tualetinis vanduo; Dezodorantai asmeninėms reikmėms; Skutimosi preparatai; Preparatai po skutimosi; Plaukų priežiūros preparatai; Eteriniai aliejai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kosmētikas līdzekļi; Smaržas; Tualetes ūdens; Dezodoranti personīgai lietošanai; Skūšanās līdzekļi; Pēcskūšanās līdzekļi; Līdzekļi matu kopšanai un ārstēšanai; Ēteriskās eļļas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kożmetiċi; Prodotti ta' fwejjaħ; Ilma mfewwaħ għall-użu fuq il-ġilda; Deodoranti għall-użu personali; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tqaxxir tal-leħja; Lozjonijiet ta' wara t-tqaxxir tal-leħja; Preparazzjonijiet u trattamenti għax-xagħar; Żjut meħudin minn pjanti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Cosmetica; Parfums; Eau de toilette; Persoonlijke deodorants; Producten voor het scheren; After-shave lotions; Haarverzorgingsproducten en haarbehandelingsproducten; Etherische oliën.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kosmetyki; Produkty perfumeryjne; Woda kolońska; Dezodoranty do użytku osobistego; Preparaty do golenia; Środki stosowane po goleniu; Preparaty do włosów; Olejki eteryczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cosméticos; Perfumes; Águas de toilette; Desodorizantes para uso pessoal; Preparações para barbear; Loções pós-barba [after-shave]; Produtos e tratamentos para o cabelo; Óleos essenciais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cosmetice; Parfumerie (Produse de -); Apă de colonie; Deodorante de uz personal; Bărbierit (Produse pentru -); Loțiune după bărbierit; Preparate și tratamente pentru păr; Uleiuri eterice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kozmetické prípravky; Parfumy; Toaletné vody; Dezodoranty na osobné použitie; Prípravky na holenie; Prípravky po holení; Vlasová kozmetika a prípravky na ošetrenie vlasov; Esenciálne (éterické) oleje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kozmetični izdelki; Parfumerijski izdelki; Kolonjska voda; Osebni dezodoranti; Pripravki za britje; Vodica za po britju; Sredstva za nego in obdelavo las; Eterična olja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kosmetika; Parfymer; Eau-de-toilette; Deodoranter för personligt bruk; Rakpreparat; Aftershave; Preparat för behandling och vård av hår; Flyktiga oljor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/080</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/151</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-11</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>38512</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>79776</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
