<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-17T08:58:47</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229820</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229820</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-13</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-17</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Mcrokied</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Мишка (компютърна периферия); Бебефони; Кутии за високоговорители; Телескопи; Електронни везни за персонална употреба; Литиеви батерии; Слушалки; Очиларски изделия за употреба в спорта; Микрофони; Неонови надписи.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Myši [počítačová periferní zařízení]; Chůvičky; Reproduktorové skříně; Teleskopy; Elektronické váhy pro osobní použití; Lithiové baterie; Sluchátka; Optické zboží pro sportovní účely; Mikrofony; Neonové reklamy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Mus [perifere enheder til computere]; Babyalarmer; Højttalerkabinetter; Teleskoper; Elektroniske vægte til personlig brug; Litiumbatterier; Hovedtelefoner; Øjenbeskyttelse til brug ved sportsudøvelse; Mikrofoner; Neonskilte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Mäuse [Computerzubehör]; Babyüberwachungsgeräte; Lautsprecherboxen; Teleskope; Elektronische Personenwaagen; Lithiumbatterien; Kopfhörer; Schutzbrillen für den Sport; Mikrofone; Neonröhren für die Werbung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ποντίκια [εξοπλισμός πληροφορικής]· Μέσα παρακολούθησης βρεφών· Κουτιά ηχείων· Τηλεσκόπια· Ηλεκτρονικοί ζυγοί μπάνιου· Μπαταρίες λιθίου· Ακουστικά κεφαλής με μικρόφωνο· Αθλητικά οπτικά είδη· Μικρόφωνα· Φωσφορίζουσες (λυχνίες -) διαφημιστικές [νέον].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Mouse [computer peripheral]; baby monitors; cabinets for loudspeakers; telescopes; electronic weighing scales for personal use; lithium batteries; headsets; sports eyewear; microphones; neon signs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Ratones [periféricos informáticos]; Dispositivos de audio y vídeo para la vigilancia de bebés; Cajas de altavoces; Telescopios; Básculas electrónicas para uso personal; Pilas y baterías de litio; Cascos con micrófono; Artículos de óptica para deporte; Micrófonos; Tubos luminosos [publicidad].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hiired [arvuti välisseadmed]; Beebimonitorid; Kõlarikastid; Teleskoobid; Elektroonilised kaalud isiklikuks kasutamiseks; Liitiumakud; Mikrofoniga kõrvaklapid; Sportimisel kasutatavad kaitseprillid; Mikrofonid; Neoonmärgid, neoontähised.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hiiri [tietokoneen oheislaite]; Vauvamonitorit; Kaiutinkotelot; Kaukoputket; Elektroniset punnitusvaa'at henkilökäyttöön; Litiumparistot; Kuulokkeet; Suojalasit urheilemiseen; Mikrofonit; Neon-kyltit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Souris [périphérique d'ordinateur]; Dispositifs audio et vidéo pour la surveillance de bébés; Boîtiers de haut-parleurs; Télescopes; Balances électroniques à usage personnel; Piles au lithium; Casques d'écoute; Articles de lunetterie pour le sport; Microphones; Tubes lumineux pour la publicité.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Miš [računalna oprema]; Monitori za bebe; Kućišta razglasa; Teleskopi; Elektroničke vage za osobnu upotrebu; Litijske baterije; Slušalice; Sportski optički artikli; Mikrofoni; Svjetleće cijevi za reklame.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Egér [számítógép-periféria]; Bébiőrök; Hangszórószekrények, hangszóródobozok; Teleszkópok; Elektronikus mérlegek személyi használatra; Lítium akkumulátorok; Fejhallgatók; Szemvédő viselet sportoláshoz; Mikrofonok; Neon világítások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Mouse [informatica]; Dispositivi audio e video per la sorveglianza dei neonati; Casse acustiche; Telescopi; Bilance elettroniche per uso personale; Batterie al litio; Cuffie per la musica; Articoli ottici per lo sport; Microfoni; Tubi luminosi per la pubblicità.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Pelės [kompiuterio išoriniai įtaisai]; Prietaisai kūdikiams stebėti; Garsiakalbių korpusai; Teleskopai; Elektroninės svarstyklės asmeninio naudojimo reikmėms; Ličio baterijos; Ausinės; Akių apsaugos priemonės sporto reikmėms; Mikrofonai; Neoniniai ženklai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Peles (datoru perifērijas ierīces); Elektroniskas ierīces zīdaiņu uzraudzībai; Skandu korpusi; Teleskopi; Elektroniskie svari personīgiem nolūkiem; Litija baterijas; Radioaustiņas; Acu aizsargelementi sportistiem; Mikrofoni; Neona izkārtnes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Maws [periferal tal-kompjuter]; Moniters tat-trabi; Kabinetti għall-amplifikaturi tal-ħoss; Teleskopji; Imwieżen elettroniċi għall-użu personali; Batteriji tal-litju; Kuffji; Lbies għall-protezzjoni tal-għajnejn waqt l-isport; Mikrofoni; Sinjali tan-neon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Computermuizen; Babyfoons; Luidsprekerkasten; Telescopen; Elektronische weegschalen voor persoonlijk gebruik; Lithiumbatterijen; Hoofdtelefoons; Brillen voor de sport; Microfoons; Neonbuizen voor lichtreclame.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Myszy [sprzęt do przetwarzania danych]; Urządzenia do monitorowania niemowląt; Obudowy głośników; Teleskopy; Elektroniczne wagi do użytku osobistego; Baterie litowe; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Artykuły optyczne do uprawiania sportu; Mikrofony; Neony reklamowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Ratos [periféricos informáticos]; Dispositivos para vigilância de bebés; Caixas de altifalantes; Telescópios; Balanças eletrónicas para uso pessoal; Baterias de lítio; Auriculares; Artigos de ótica para desporto; Microfones; Tubos de néon para sinalização.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Mouse [periferice de calculator]; Dispozitive de monitorizare a bebelușilor; Cutii pentru difuzoare; Telescoape; Cântare electronice pentru uz personal; Baterii cu litiu; Căști; Ochelari de protecție pentru sport; Microfoane; Firme de neon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Myši (periférne zariadenia počítačov); Audiovizuálne prístroje na monitorovanie bábätiek; Reproduktorové skrinky; Teleskopy; Elektronické váhy na osobné účely; Lítiové batérie; Slúchadlá s mikrofónom; Športová očná optika; Mikrofóny; Neónové reklamy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Miška [računalniška periferna enota]; Otroške varuške; Ohišja zvočnikov; Teleskopi; Elektronske tehtnice za osebno uporabo; Litijeve baterije; Slušalke; Športna očala; Mikrofoni; Neonski znaki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Möss [datorutrustning]; Övervakningsapparater för spädbarn; Högtalarlådor; Teleskop; Elektroniska vågar för personligt bruk; Litiumbatterier; Headsets; Skyddsglasögon för sport; Mikrofoner; Neonskyltar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/083</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/155</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-17</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082634</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>85806</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
