<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-28T12:49:04</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229847</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229847</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-25</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-28</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Ontop Medical</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Фармацевтични препарати и натурални средства за лечение; Храна за бебета; Дезинфектанти и антисептици; Хранителни добавки и диетични препарати; Хигиенни препарати и изделия; Медицински препарати; Лечебни и хигиенизиращи сапуни и детергенти; Медицински превръзки, превързочни материали покрития и апликатори; Стоматологични препарати и изделия и лечебни средства за почистване на зъби.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Farmaceutické přípravky a přírodní léčiva; Potraviny pro kojence a batolata; Dezinfekční a antiseptické přípravky; Potravní doplňky a dietetické přípravky; Hygienické přípravky a výrobky; Lékařské přípravky; Léčebná a dezinfekční mýdla a čisticí přípravky; Obvazy, obvazový materiál a aplikátory léčebných přípravků; Zubní přípravky a výrobky a léčebné zubní pasty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Farmaceutiske præparater og naturlægemidler; Næringsmidler til spædbørn; Desinficerende og antiseptiske midler; Kosttilskud og diætetiske præparater; Hygiejniske præparater og artikler; Medicinske præparater; Medicinske og desinficerende sæber og rensemidler; Medicinske plaster, forbindsstoffer og applikatorer; Tandpræparater og -artikler samt medicinske tandpastaer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Arzneimittel und natürliche Heilmittel; Babynahrungsmittel; Desinfektionsmittel und Antiseptika; Diätetische Präparate und Nahrungsergänzungsmittel; Hygienepräparate und -artikel; Medizinische Präparate; Medizinische und desinfizierende Seifen sowie Detergenzien; Medizinische Verbandmaterialien, Abdeckmaterialien und Applikatoren; Zahnmedizinische Präparate und Erzeugnisse sowie medizinische Zahnputzmittel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Φαρμακευτικά προϊόντα και φυσικές θεραπείες· Βρεφικές/Παιδικές τροφές· Απολυμαντικά και αντισηπτικά· Συμπληρώματα διατροφής και διαιτητικά παρασκευάσματα· Παρασκευάσματα υγειονομικά και είδη αυτών· Ιατρικά ιδιοσκευάσματα· Φαρμακευτικά και απολυμαντικά σαπούνια και απορρυπαντικά· Ιατρικές γάζες, καλύμματα και εξαρτήματα εφαρμογής· Οδοντιατρικά παρασκευάσματα και είδη, και φαρμακευτικά οδοντοσκευάσματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Pharmaceuticals and natural remedies; Baby food; Disinfectants and antiseptics; Dietary supplements and dietetic preparations; Hygienic preparations and articles; Medical preparations; Medicated and sanitising soaps and detergents; Medical dressings, coverings and applicators; Dental preparations and articles, and medicated dentifrices.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Remedios naturales y farmacéuticos; Alimentos para bebés; Desinfectantes y antisépticos; Suplementos y preparaciones dietéticas; Preparaciones y artículos higiénicos; Productos médicos; Jabones y detergentes medicinales y desinfectantes; Apósitos, vendas y aplicadores médicos; Preparaciones y artículos dentales, así como dentífricos medicinales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Farmatseutilised ja looduslikud ravimid; Imikutoit; Desinfektsioonivahendid ja antiseptikumid; Toidulisandid ja farmatseutilised dieetained; Hügieenipreparaadid ja -tooted; Meditsiinilised preparaadid; Ravitoimega ja desinfitseerivad seebid ja pesuained; Meditsiinilised sidemed, katted ja aplikaatorid; Hambaravipreparaadid ja -tooted ning ravitoimega hambapuhastusained.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lääkkeet ja luonnonlääkkeet; Vauvanruoat; Desinfiointiaineet ja antiseptiset aineet; Lisäravinteet ja dieettivalmisteet; Hygieniavalmisteet ja -tuotteet; Lääketieteelliset valmisteet; Lääkeaineita sisältävät ja desinfioivat saippuat ja puhdistusaineet; Lääkinnälliset sidontatarvikkeet, suojat ja asettimet; Hammaslääkinnälliset valmisteet ja tuotteet sekä lääkeaineita sisältävät hampaidenpuhdistusaineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits pharmaceutiques et remèdes naturels; Aliments pour bébés; Désinfectants et antiseptiques; Compléments alimentaires et préparations diététiques; Préparations et articles d'hygiène; Préparations médicales; Savons et détergents désinfectants et médicinaux; Pansements, protections et applicateurs médicaux; Préparations et articles dentaires, et dentifrices médicinaux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Farmaceutski proizvodi i prirodna ljekovita sredstva; Hrana za bebe; Dezinfekcijska i antiseptička sredstva; Dodaci prehrani i dijetetski pripravci; Higijenski pripravci i proizvodi; Medicinski pripravci; Medicinski i dezinfekcijski sapuni i deterdženti; Medicinski povoji, pokrovi i aplikatori; Zubarski pripravci, proizvodi i medicinske paste za zube.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Gyógyszerek és természetes gyógykészítmények; Bébiételek; Fertőtlenítők és fertőzésgátlók; Táplálékkiegészítők és diétás készítmények; Higiéniai készítmények és cikkek; Orvosi készítmények; Gyógyszeres és fertőtlenítő szappanok és tisztítószerek; Gyógyászati kötszerek és applikátorok; Fogászati készítmények és árucikkek, gyógyhatású fogkrémek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Medicamenti farmaceutici e naturali; Alimenti per bambini (neonati); Disinfettanti ed antisettici; Integratori alimentari e preparati dietetici; Preparati ed articoli per l'igiene; Preparazioni mediche; Saponi e detergenti medicinali e igienizzanti; Bende mediche, fasciature ed applicatori; Preparati e articoli odontoiatrici, e dentifrici medicati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Farmaciniai ir natūralūs vaistiniai preparatai; Kūdikių maistas; Dezinfekavimo priemonės ir antiseptikai; Maisto papildai ir dietiniai produktai; Higienos preparatai ir priemonės; Gydomieji preparatai; Gydomieji ir dezinfekciniai muilai bei plovikliai; Medicininė tvarsliava, uždangalai ir kompresai; Dantų priežiūros preparatai ir priemonės, medicininės dantų valymo priemonės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Farmaceitiskie un dabiskie ārstniecības līdzekļi; Uzturs zīdaiņiem un maziem bērniem; Dezinfekcijas un antiseptiskie līdzekļi; Uztura bagātinātāji un diētiskie preparāti; Higiēnas līdzekļi un izstrādājumi; Ārstniecības līdzekļi; Ārstnieciskās un dezinficējošās ziepes un mazgāšanas līdzekļi; Medicīniskie pārsēji, pārklāji un aplikatori; Zobārstniecības preparāti un izstrādājumi, ārstnieciskas zobu pastas un pulveri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Farmaċewtiċi u rimedji naturali; Ikel għat-trabi; Diżinfettanti u antisettiċi; Supplimenti tad-dieta u preparazzjonijiet dijetetiċi; Preparazzjonijiet u oġġetti iġjenici; Preparazzjonijiet mediċi; Sapunijiet u deterġenti li jimmedikaw u jtejbu l-iġjene; Infaxxar, oġġetti li kgħattu w applikaturi mediċi; Preparazzjonijiet u oġġetti għas-snien, u dentifriċi medikati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Farmaceutische en natuurlijke geneesmiddelen; Babyvoeding; Ontsmettingsmiddelen en antiseptica; Diëtische supplementen en diëtische preparaten; Hygiënische preparaten en producten; Medische substanties; Medicinale en steriliserende zepen en detergenten; Verbandartikelen, pleisters en medische applicators; Tandheelkundige preparaten en producten, en medicinale tandpasta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Farmaceutyki i naturalne środki lecznicze; Żywność dla niemowląt; Środki dezynfekcyjne i antyseptyczne; Suplementy diety i preparaty dietetyczne; Preparaty i artykuły higieniczne; Preparaty medyczne; Mydła i detergenty lecznicze i odkażające; Opatrunki medyczne, materiały opatrunkowe i aplikatory; Preparaty i artykuły dentystyczne oraz lecznicze środki do czyszczenia zębów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Produtos farmacêuticos e remédios naturais; Alimentos para bebés; Desinfetantes e antissépticos; Suplementos e preparações dietéticos; Preparações e artigos higiénicos; Preparações médicas; Sabões e detergentes higiénicos e medicinais; Curativos, ligaduras e aplicadores médicos; Preparações e artigos dentários, e dentífricos medicinais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Remedii naturale şi farmaceutice; Alimente pentru bebeluşi; Dezinfectanţi şi antiseptice; Suplimente alimentare si preparate dietetice; Produse şi articole pentru igienă; Preparate medicale; Săpunuri şi detergenţi medicinali şi dezinfectanţi; Pansamente, bandaje şi plasturi medicali; Preparate şi articole dentare şi produse medicinale pentru îngrijirea dinţilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Farmaceutické a prírodné liečivá; Potraviny pre dojčatá; Dezinfekčné a antiseptické prípravky; Výživové doplnky a dietetické prípravky; Hygienické prípravky a potreby; Lekárske prípravky; Mydlá a detergenty s liečivými a dezinfekčnými účinkami; Zdravotnícke obväzové materiály, obklady a aplikátory; Dentálne prípravky a potreby, liečivé prípravky na čistenie zubov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Farmacevtski proizvodi in naravna zdravila; Hrana za dojenčke; Dezinfekcijska in antiseptična sredstva; Prehranska dopolnila in dietetske snovi; Izdelki in preparati za higieno; Medicinski preparati; Mila in detergenti z zdravilnimi in razkuževalnimi učinkovinami; Obvezilni material, obliži in aplikatorji za oskrbo ran; Zobni pripravki in izdelki ter zobne paste z zdravilnimi učinkovinami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Läkemedel och naturläkemedel; Spädbarnsmat; Desinfektions- och antiseptiska medel; Dietiska tillskott och preparat; Hygieniska preparat och artiklar; Läkemedelspreparat; Medicinska och desinficerande tvålar och rengöringsmedel; Medicinska förband, -höljen och -skydd; Dentala preparat och artiklar samt medicinska tandpulver, -krämer och -pastor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Материали и продукти за зашиване и затваряне на рани; Оборудване за хирургически цели и лечение на рани; Оборудване за диагностициране, прегледи и наблюдение; Противозачатъчни средства [приспособления]; Изкуствени органи и импланти; Апарати за медицинска образна диагностика; Апарати за физически упражнения за медицински цели; Медицински и ветеринарни апарати и инструменти; Оборудване за физиотерапия и рехабилитация; Облекло, шапки и принадлежности за глава, обувки за медицински персонал и пациенти; Стоматологично оборудване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Materiály a potřeby na šití ran; Zařízení pro chirurgii a pro ošetřování ran; Zařízení pro diagnostiku, vyšetřování a monitorování; Antikoncepční prostředky; Umělé orgány a implantáty; Lékařské zobrazovací přístroje; Přístroje na tělesná cvičení pro lékařské účely; Lékařské a veterinární přístroje a nástroje; Zařízení pro fyzioterapii a rehabilitaci; Oděvy, pokrývky hlavy a obuv pro zdravotnické pracovníky a pacienty; Zařízení pro zubní lékařství.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sutur og sårlukkende materieler og produkter; Kirurgisk og sårbehandlende udstyr; Udstyr til diagnostik, undersøgelse og monitorering; Svangerskabsforebyggende udstyr; Kunstige organer og implantater; Medicinske apparater til dannelse af billeder; Apparater til fysisk træning, medicinske formål; Medicinske og veterinære apparater og instrumenter; Udstyr til fysioterapi og rehabilitering; Beklædningsgenstande, hovedbeklædning og fodtøj til medicinsk personale og patienter; Dentalt udstyr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Chirurgische Naht- und Wundverschlussmaterialien und -produkte; Chirurgische und Wundversorgungsausrüstung; Diagnose-, Untersuchungs- und Überwachungsgeräte; Empfängnisverhütende Vorrichtungen; Künstliche Organe und Implantate; Medizinische bildgebende Apparate; Medizinische Geräte für Körperübungen und Krankengymnastik; Medizinische und veterinärmedizinische Apparate und Instrumente; Physiotherapie- und Rehabilitationsgeräte; Bekleidung, Kopfbedeckungen und Schuhwaren für medizinisches Personal und Patienten; Zahnärztliche Geräte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υλικά και προιόντα χειρουργικών ραμμάτων και επούλωσης πληγών· Χειρουργικός εξοπλισμός και εξοπλισμός για τη θεραπεία πληγών· Εξοπλισμός διάγνωσης,εξέτασης και παρακολούθησης/ελέγχου· Συσκευές αντισύλληψης· Τεχνητά όργανα και εμφυτεύματα· Συσκευές ιατρικής απεικόνισης· Ιατρικές συσκευές για σωματική άσκηση· Ιατρικές και κτηνιατρικές συσκευές και όργανα· Εξοπλισμός φυσιοθεραπείας και αποκατάστασης· Ενδύματα, είδη πιλοποιίας και υποδήματα για ιατρικό προσωπικό και ασθενείς.· Οδοντιατρικός εξοπλισμός.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Suture and wound closing materials and products; Surgical and wound treating equipment; Diagnostic, examination, and monitoring equipment; Contraceptive devices; Artificial organs and implants; Medical imaging apparatus; Physical exercise apparatus for medical purposes; Medical and veterinary apparatus and instruments; Physiotherapy and rehabilitation equipment; Clothing, headgear and footwear for medical personnel and patients.; Dental equipment.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Productos y materiales de sutura y para cerrar heridas; Instrumental quirúrgico y para el tratamiento de heridas; Equipos de diagnóstico, examen y monitorización; Dispositivos anticonceptivos; Implantes y órganos artificiales; Aparatos de imágenes médicas; Aparatos de ejercicio físico para uso médico; Aparatos e instrumentos médicos y veterinarios; Equipos de fisioterapia y rehabilitación; Prendas de vestir, artículos de sombrerería y calzado para el personal médico y los pacientes; Equipamientos para dentistas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Haavaõmblus- ja haavasulgemismaterjalid ja -tooted; Haavaravi- ja kirurgiavahendid; Diagnoosi-, testimis- ja jälgimisseadmed; Rasestusvastased seadmed; Tehisorganid ja -implantaadid; Meditsiinilised pilte kuvavad seadmed; Meditsiinilised võimlemisseadmed; Meditsiinilised ja veterinaarsed seadmed ja riistad; Füsioteraapia- ja rehabilitatsiooniseadmed; Meditsiinitöötajate ja patsientide rõivad, peakatted ja jalatsid; Hambaraviseadmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Haavan ompelemis- ja sulkemismateriaalit ja -tuotteet; Kirurgiset välineet ja haavanhoitovälineet; Diagnostiset välineet ja tutkimus- ja seurantavälineet; Ehkäisyvälineet; Keinotekoiset elimet ja implantit; Lääketieteelliset kuvantamislaitteistot; Kuntoiluvälineet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Lääketieteelliset ja eläinlääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Fysioterapia- ja kuntoutusvälineet; Vaatteet, päähineet ja jalkineet lääkintähenkilöstölle ja potilaille; Hammaslääketieteelliset välineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Matières et produits de suture et de fermeture des blessures; Équipement chirurgical et de traitement des blessures; Équipement de diagnostic, d'examen et de surveillance; Dispositifs contraceptifs; Organes artificiels et implants; Appareils d'imagerie médicale; Appareils médicaux pour exercices corporels; Appareils et instruments médicaux et vétérinaires; Appareils pour la physiothérapie et la réeducation à usage médical; Vêtements, articles de chapellerie et articles chaussants pour personnel médical et patients; Appareils et instruments dentaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Materijali i proizvodi za šivanje i zatvaranje rana; Kirurška oprema i oprema za liječenje rana; Oprema za dijagnostiku, preglede i nadzor; Kontracepcijske naprave; Umjetni organi i implantati; Uređaji za medicinsko snimanje; Uređaji za vježbe za medicinske potrebe; Medicinski i veterinarski uređaji i instrumenti; Oprema za fizioterapiju i rehabilitaciju; Odjeća, pokrivala za glavu i obuća za medicinsko osoblje i pacijente; Stomatološka oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Varró és sebzáró anyagok és termékek; Sebészeti és sebkezelési felszerelések; Diagnosztikai, vizsgálati és felügyeleti berendezések; Fogamzásgátló eszközök; Mesterséges szervek és implantátumok; Orvosi képalkotó berendezések; Testmozgásra szolgáló gyógyászati eszközök, készülékek; Gyógyászati és állatgyógyászati berendezések és készülékek; Fizioterápiás és rehabilitációs berendezések; Ruházat, fejfedők és lábbelik ápolószemélyzet és páciensek számára; Fogászati berendezések.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Materiali e prodotti di sutura e chiusura delle ferite; Attrezzatura chirurgica e per il trattamento delle ferite; Attrezzatura per diagnostica, esami e monitoraggio; Dispositivi contraccettivi; Organi ed impianti artificiali; Apparecchi medici per formazioni di immagine; Apparecchi per esercizi fisici per scopi medici; Apparecchi e strumenti medici e veterinari; Attrezzatura per la fisioterapia e la riabilitazione; Capi d'abbigliamento, articoli di cappelleria e calzature per personale medico e pazienti; Attrezzature dentarie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Žaizdų siuvimo ir uždarymo medžiagos ir priemonės; Chirurginiai ir žaizdų gydymo aparatai ir instrumentai; Diagnozavimo, tyrimo ir stebėjimo įranga; Kontraceptinės priemonės; Dirbtiniai organai ir implantai; Medicininiai vaizdo aparatai; Fizinių pratimų aparatai (medicinos reikmėms); Medicinos ir veterinarijos aparatai ir instrumentai; Fizioterapijos ir reabilitacijos įranga; Apranga, galvos apdangalai ir avalynė medicinos personalui ir pacientams; Odontologinė įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Šuvju materiāli un brūču ārstēšanas materiāli un izstrādājumi; Ķirurģiskās un brūču ārstēšanas iekārtas; Diagnostikas, medicīniskās ekspertīzes un uzraudzības iekārtas; Kontracepcijas ierīces; Mākslīgie orgāni un implanti; Medicīniskās attēlveidošanas iekārtas; Fizisko vingrinājumu aparāti medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Medicīnas un veterinārās ierīces un instrumenti; Fizioterapijas un rehabilitācijas iekārtas; Apģērbi, galvassegas un apavi medicīnas personālam un pacientiem; Zobārstniecības iekārtas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Materjali u prodotti tas-sutura u għeluq ta' feriti; Tagħmir kiruġiku għat-trattament tal-feriti; Tagħmir għad-djanjosi, eżaminazzjoni u monitoraġġ; Mezzi kontraċettivi; Organi u mpjanti artifiċjali; Apparat għall-immaġni mediċi; Apparat għall-eżerċizzju fiżiku, għal skopijiet mediċi; Apparat u strumenti mediċi u veterinarji; Tagħmir tal-fiżjoterapija u r-rijabilitazzjoni; Ħwejjeġ, xedd ir-ras u xedd is-saqajn għall-persunal fil-qasam mediku u għall-pazjenti; Tagħmir dentali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Materialen en instrumenten voor het hechten en dichten van wonden; Chirurgische apparaten en instrumenten voor wondbehandeling; Diagnostische, onderzoeks- en bewakingsapparaten en instrumenten; Anticonceptieve artikelen; Kunstmatige organen en implantaten; Beeldapparatuur voor medisch gebruik; Medische apparatuur voor lichaamsoefeningen; Geneeskundige en diergeneeskundige apparaten en instrumenten; Fysiotherapeutische toestellen en toestellen voor revalidatie; Kleding, hoofdbedekking en schoeisel voor medisch personeel en patiënten; Tandheelkundige apparaten en instrumenten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Produkty i materiały do zszywania i zamykania ran; Urządzenia, narzędzia i przybory chirurgiczne i do leczenia ran; Urządzenia do diagnostyki, badania i kontroli; Artykuły antykoncepcyjne; Sztuczne organy i implanty; Urzędzenia do obrazowania medycznego; Urządzenia do ćwiczeń fizycznych do celów medycznych; Aparaty i instrumenty medyczne i weterynaryjne; Urządzenia i przyrządy do fizjoterapii i rehabilitacji; Odzież, nakrycia głowy i obuwie dla personelu medycznego i pacjentów; Przyrządy i przybory dentystyczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Materiais e produtos de sutura e fecho de feridas; Equipamento para tratamento cirúrgico e de lesões; Equipamento para diagnóstico, exame e monitorização; Dispositivos contracetivos; Órgãos e implantes artificiais; Aparelhos de imagiologia médica; Aparelhos de exercício físico para fins médicos; Aparelhos e instrumentos médicos e veterinários; Equipamento para fisioterapia e reabilitação; Vestuário, chapelaria e calçado para pessoal médico e doentes; Equipamento dentário.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Materiale şi produse pentru sutură şi închiderea rănilor; Echipament chirurgical şi de tratare a rănilor; Echipament pentru diagnosticare, examinare şi monitorizare; Dispozitive contraceptive; Organe artificiale şi implanturi; Aparate de imagistică medicală; Aparate pentru exerciţii fizice de uz medical; Aparate şi instrumente medicale şi veterinare; Echipament de fizioterapie şi de recuperare; Îmbrăcăminte, articole pentru acoperirea capului și încălțăminte pentru personal medical și pacienți; Echipament stomatologic.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Materiály a potreby na chirurgické šitie; Chirurgické prístroje a nástroje a prístroje a nástroje na ošetrovanie rán; Diagnostické, skúmacie a monitorovacie zariadenia; Antikoncepčné pomôcky; Umelé orgány a implantáty; Lekárske snímacie a zobrazovacie zariadenia; Telocvičné prístroje na liečebné použitie; Lekárske a zverolekárske prístroje a nástroje; Fyzioterapeutické a rehabilitačné zariadenia; Odevy, pokrývky hlavy a obuv pre zdravotníckych pracovníkov a pacientov; Zubárske vybavenie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Proizvodi in materiali za šivanje in zapiranje ran; Kirurške naprave in pripomočki za oskrbo ran; Diagnostične, preiskovalne in kontrolne naprave; Kontracepcijski pripomočki; Umetni organi in vsadki; Medicinske prikazovalne naprave; Aparati za telesno vadbo za medicinske namene; Medicinske in veterinarske naprave in instrumenti; Fizioterapevtska in rehabilitacijska oprema; Oblačila, pokrivala in obutev za medicinsko osebje in bolnike; Zobozdravstveni aparati in instrumenti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Suturer samt produkter för förslutning av sår och skador; Utrustning för kirurgi och behandling av sår/skador; Utrustning för diagnostik, undersökning och övervakning; Preventivmedelsanordningar; Konstgjorda organ och implantat; Medicinska bildbehandlingsapparater; Kroppsträningsapparater för medicinska ändamål; Medicinska och veterinära apparater och instrument; Utrustning för fysioterapi och rehabilitering; Kläder, huvudbonader och fotbeklädnader för medicinsk personal och patienter; Dentala utrustningar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за търговия на едро и услуги за търговия на дребно във връзка с лекарствени продукти и естествени лечебни средства, храна за бебета, дезинфектанти и антисептици, диетични препарати и хранителни добавки, препарати и артикули за хигиена, медицински препарати, медицински и дезинфекциращи сапуни, както и почистващи препарати, медицински превързочни материали, покриващи материали и апликатори, стоматологични препарати и изделия, както и медицински средства за почистване на зъби; Услуги за търговия на едро и услуги за търговия на дребно във връзка с хирургични материали и продукти за зашиване и затваряне на рани, хирургическо оборудване и оборудване за лечение на рани, оборудване за диагностика, преглед и наблюдение, противозачатъчни принадлежности, изкуствени органи и импланти, апарати за медицински изображения, медицински уреди за физически упражнения и физиотерапия, медицински и ветеринарномедицински апарати и инструменти; Услуги за търговия на едро и услуги за търговия на дребно във връзка с уреди за физиотерапия и рехабилитационни уреди, oблекло, шапки и други принадлежности за глава и обувки за медицински персонал и пациенти, стоматологични уреди.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby s ohledem na léky a přírodní léčiva, potraviny pro batolata, dezinfekční přípravky a antiseptika, dietetické přípravky a potravní doplňky, hygienické výrobky a potřeby, lékařské přípravky, léčebná a dezinfekční mýdla, jakož i detergenty, lékařské obvazové materiály, zakrývací materiály a aplikátory, zubní lékařské přípravky a výrobky, jakož i léčivé přípravky na čištění zubů; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby s ohledem na chirurgické materiály a výrobky pro šití a uzavírání ran, chirurgické vybavení a vybavení pro ošetření ran, diagnostické, vyšetřovací a monitorovací přístroje, antikoncepční prostředky, umělé orgány a implantáty, lékařské zobrazovací přístroje, lékařské přístroje pro tělesné cvičení a gymnastiku nemocných, lékařské a veterinářské přístroje a nástroje; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby s ohledem na fyzioterapeutické a rehabilitační přístroje, oděvy, pokrývky hlavy a obuv pro lékařský personál a pacienty, zubní lékařské přístroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Engros- og detailhandel med lægemidler og naturlige helsepræparater, næringsmidler til spædbørn, desinfektionsmidler og antiseptiske midler, diætetiske præparater og kosttilskud, hygiejnepræparater og -artikler, medicinske præparater, medicinske og desinficerende sæber samt rensemidler, medicinske forbindsstoffer, afdækningsmaterialer og applikatorer, odontologiske præparater og produkter samt medicinske tandplejemidler; Engros- og detailhandel med kirurgiske suturer og materialer og produkter til sårafdækning, kirurgisk udstyr og udstyr til behandling af sår, apparater til diagnose, undersøgelse og overvågning, svangerskabsforebyggende midler, kunstige organer og implantater, apparater til medicinske billeder, medicinske apparater til legemsøvelser og fysioterapi, medicinske og veterinærmedicinske apparater og instrumenter; Engros- og detailhandel med apparater til fysioterapi og genoptræning, beklædningsgenstande, hovedbeklædning og fodtøj til medicinsk personale og patienter, odontologiske apparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Arzneimittel und natürliche Heilmittel, Babynahrungsmittel, Desinfektionsmittel und Antiseptika, diätetische Präparate und Nahrungsergänzungsmittel, Hygienepräparate und -artikel, medizinische Präparate, medizinische und desinfizierende Seifen sowie Detergenzien, medizinische Verbandmaterialien, Abdeckmaterialien und Applikatoren, zahnmedizinische Präparate und Erzeugnisse sowie medizinische Zahnputzmittel; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf chirurgische Naht- und Wundverschlussmaterialien und -produkte, chirurgische und Wundversorgungsausrüstung, Diagnose-, Untersuchungs- und Überwachungsgeräte, empfängnisverhütende Vorrichtungen, künstliche Organe und Implantate, medizinische bildgebende Apparate, medizinische Geräte für Körperübungen und Krankengymnastik, medizinische und veterinärmedizinische Apparate und Instrumente; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Physiotherapie- und Rehabilitationsgeräte, Bekleidung, Kopfbedeckungen und Schuhwaren für medizinisches Personal und Patienten, zahnärztliche Geräte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες χονδρικής και λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με φάρμακα και φυσικά φάρμακα, βρεφικές τροφές, απολυμαντικά και αντισηπτικά, διαιτητικά παρασκευάσματα και συμπληρώματα διατροφής, παρασκευάσματα και προϊόντα υγιεινής, ιατρικά παρασκευάσματα, φαρμακευτικά και απολυμαντικά σαπούνια καθώς και απορρυπαντικά, ιατρικά υλικά επιδέσμων, υλικά επικάλυψης και διατάξεις εφαρμογής, οδοντιατρικά παρασκευάσματα και προϊόντα καθώς και φαρμακευτικές οδοντόκρεμες· Υπηρεσίες χονδρικής και λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με υλικά και προϊόντα χειρουργικών ραμμάτων και κλεισίματος τραυμάτων, εξοπλισμό χειρουργικό και θεραπείας τραυμάτων, συσκευές διάγνωσης, εξέτασης και παρακολούθησης, αντισυλληπτικές διατάξεις, τεχνητά όργανα και εμφυτεύματα, ιατρικές απεικονιστικές συσκευές, ιατρικές συσκευές για σωματικές ασκήσεις και για φυσικοθεραπεία, ιατρικές και κτηνιατρικές συσκευές και εργαλεία· Υπηρεσίες χονδρικής και λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με συσκευές φυσιοθεραπείας και αποκατάστασης, ενδύματα, είδη πιλοποιίας και υποδήματα για ιατρικό προσωπικό και ασθενείς, οδοντιατρικές συσκευές.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Wholesaling and retailing relating to pharmaceuticals and natural remedies, food for babies, disinfectants and antiseptics, dietetic preparations and food supplements, sanitary preparations and articles, medical preparations, medicated and sanitising soaps and detergents, medical dressings, coverings and applicators, dental preparations and substances and medical dentrifices; Wholesaling and retailing relating to suture and wound closing materials and goods, surgical and wound treating equipment, diagnostic, examination and monitoring apparatus, contraceptive devices, artificial organs and implants, medical imaging apparatus, physical exercise apparatus for medical purposes and physiotherapy, medicinal and veterinary apparatus and instruments; Wholesaling and retailing relating to physiotherapy and rehabilitation equipment, clothing, headwear and footwear for medical personnel and patients, dental apparatus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de venta mayorista y minorista de medicamentos y remedios naturales, alimentos para bebés, desinfectantes y antisépticos, preparaciones dietéticas y complementos nutricionales, productos y artículos higiénicos, preparaciones medicinales, jabones y detergentes medicinales y desinfectantes, apósitos, vendas y aplicadores médicos, preparaciones y artículos dentales, así como dentífricos medicinales; Servicios de venta mayorista y minorista de productos y materiales de sutura y para cerrar heridas, instrumental quirúrgico y para el tratamiento de heridas, equipos de diagnóstico, examen y monitorización, dispositivos anticonceptivos, órganos artificiales e implantes, aparatos de imágenes médicas, aparatos médicos para ejercicios corporales y fisioterapia, médico y aparatos e instrumentos médicos y veterinarios; Servicios de venta mayorista y minorista de equipos de fisioterapia y rehabilitación, prendas de vestir, artículos de sombrerería y calzado para personal y pacientes médicos, equipamientos para dentistas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Järgmiste kaupadega seotud hulgi- ja jaemüügiteenused: ravimid ja looduslikud ravimid, imikutoidud, desinfektsioonivahendid ja antiseptikumid, dieetained ja toidulisandid, hügieenitarbed ja -kaubad, meditsiinilised preparaadid, raviseep ja desinfitseeriv seep, samuti pesuained, meditsiinilised sidemematerjalid, kattematerjalid ja aplikaatorid, hambaravi preparaadid ja -tooted, samuti ravitoimega hambapuhastusained; Järgmiste kaupadega seotud hulgi- ja jaemüügiteenused: kirurgilised õmblus- ja haavasulgemismaterjalid ja -tooted, kirurgilised ja haavaravivahendid, diagnostika-, uuringu- ja seireseadmed, rasestumisvastased vahendid, tehiselundid ja implantaadid, meditsiinilised pildindusseadmed, meditsiinilised võimlemis- ja füsioteraapiaseadmed, meditsiin- ja veterinaariaseadmed ning -riistad; Järgmiste kaupadega seotud hulgi- ja jaemüügiteenused: füsioteraapia- ja rehabilitatsiooniseadmed, rõivad, peakatted ja jalatsid meditsiinipersonali ja patsientide jaoks, hambaraviseadmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tukku- ja vähittäismyyntipalvelut seuraavilla aloilla: lääkkeet ja luonnonlääkkeet, vauvanruoat, desinfiointiaineet ja antiseptiset aineet, dieettivalmisteet ja lisäravintoaineet, hygieniavalmisteet ja -tarvikkeet, lääkinnälliset valmisteet, lääkinnälliset ja desinfioivat saippuat sekä pesuaineet, lääkinnälliset sidontatarvikkeet, päällystysmateriaalit ja levittimet, hammaslääketieteelliset valmisteet ja tuotteet sekä lääkeaineita sisältävät hampaidenpuhdistusaineet; Tukku- ja vähittäismyyntipalvelut seuraavilla aloilla: haavan ompelemis- ja sulkemismateriaalit ja -tuotteet, kirurgiset ja haavankäsittelyvälineet, diagnoosi-, tutkimus- ja valvontalaitteet, ehkäisyvälineet, tekoelimet ja implantit, lääketieteelliset kuvantamislaitteet, lääketieteelliset laitteet fyysiseen harjoitteluun ja fysioterapiaan, lääketieteelliset ja eläinlääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Tukku- ja vähittäismyyntipalvelut seuraavilla aloilla: fysioterapia- ja kuntoutuslaitteet, lääkintähenkilöstön ja potilaiden vaatteet, päähineet ja jalkineet, hammaslääketieteelliset välineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de vente en gros et au détail en relation avec des médicaments et remèdes naturels, aliments pour bébés, désinfectants et antiseptiques, préparations diététiques et compléments alimentaires, préparations et articles d'hygiène, préparations médicales, savons médicaux et désinfectants ainsi que détergents, matériaux médicaux de bandage, matériaux de recouvrement et applicateurs, préparations et produits dentaires ainsi que dentifrices ainsi que dentifrices médicaux; Services de vente en gros et au détail en relation avec des matériaux et produits de suture chirurgicale et de fermeture de plaies, dispositifs chirurgicaux et de soins de plaies, équipements de diagnostic, examen et surveillance, dispositifs de contraception, organes artificiels et implants, appareils d'imagerie médicale, équipements médicaux d'exercice physique et kinésithérapie, appareils et instruments médicaux et vétérinaires; Services de vente en gros et au détail en relation avec des équipements de physiothérapie et réhabilitation, vêtements, articles de chapellerie et chaussures pour personnel médical et patients, équipements dentaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge veleprodaje i maloprodaje u vezi s lijekovima i prirodnim lijekovima, hranom za bebe, dezinfekcijskim sredstvima i antisepticima, dijetetskim pripravcima i dodacima prehrani, higijenskim preparatima i proizvodima, medicinskim preparatima, medicinskim i dezinficirajućim sapunima i deterdžentima, medicinskim zavojnim materijalima, pokrovnim materijalima i aplikatorima, stomatološkim preparatima i proizvodima kao i medicinskim pastama za zube; Usluge veleprodaje i maloprodaje u vezi s kirurškim materijalima i proizvodima za šivanje i zatvaranje rana, kirurškom opremom i opremom za tretiranje rana, uređajima za dijagnozu, pretrage i nadzor, kontracepcijskim napravama, umjetnim organima i implantatima, medicinskim uređajima za davanje slike, medicinskim uređajima za tjelovježbu i medicinsku gimnastiku, medicinskim i veterinarskim aparatima i instrumentima; Usluge veleprodaje i maloprodaje u vezi s uređajima za fizioterapiju i rehabilitaciju, odjećom, pokrivalima za glavu i obućom za medicinsko osoblje i pacijente, stomatološkim uređajima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások a következőkre vonatkozóan: gyógyszerek és természetes orvosságok, baba tápszerek, fertőtlenítőszerek és antiszeptikus készítmények, dietetikus készítmények és étrend- és táplálékkiegészítők, egészségügyi készítmények és cikkek, orvosi készítmények, gyógyászati és fertőtlenítő szappanok, valamint tisztítószerek, orvosi kötszeranyagok, burkoló anyagok és applikátorok, fogászati készítmények és termékek és orvosi fogkrémek; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások a következőkre vonatkozóan: sebészeti varrat- és sebzáró anyagok és termékek, sebészeti és sebkezelő berendezések, diagnosztikai, vizsgálati és megfigyelő eszközök, fogamzásgátlók, mesterséges szervek és implantátumok, gyógyászati képeket nyújtó készülékek, gyógyászati eszközök fizikai gyakorlatokhoz és fizioterápiához, orvosi és állatorvosi készülékek és eszközök; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások a következőkre vonatkozóan: fizioterápiás és rehabilitációs felszerelések, ruházat, fejfedő és lábbeli az orvosi személyzet és a betegek számára, fogászati készülékek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di vendita all'ingrosso e al dettaglio di prodotti farmaceutici e rimedi naturali, prodotti alimentari per lattanti, disinfettanti e antisettici, prodotti dietetici e integratori alimentari, preparati e articoli per l'igiene, preparati medici, saponi medici e disinfettanti nonché detergenti, bende mediche, materiali di copertura e applicatori, preparati e articoli odontoiatrici, nonché dentifrici medicati; Servizi di vendita all'ingrosso e al dettaglio di materiali e prodotti chirurgici di sutura e chiusura delle ferite, attrezzatura chirurgica e per il trattamento delle ferite, apparecchi per diagnosi, esami e monitoraggio, dispositivi contraccettivi, organi e impianti artificiali, apparecchiature di scansione per uso medico, apparecchi medici per esercizi fisici e fisioterapia, apparecchiature e strumenti medici e veterinari; Servizi di vendita all'ingrosso e al dettaglio di apparecchi per la fisioterapia e la riabilitazione, abbigliamento, copricapo e calzature per personale medico e pazienti, apparecchi odontoiatrici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Didmeninės ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, susijusios su vaistais ir natūraliais gydomaisiais preparatais, kūdikių maisto produktais, dezinfekavimo preparatais ir antiseptikais, dietiniais preparatais ir maisto papildais, higienos preparatais ir gaminiais, medicinos preparatais, medicininiu ir dezinfekuojamuoju muilu bei plovikliais, medicinine tvarsliava, dengiamosiomis medžiagomis ir aplikatoriais, odontologijos preparatais ir gaminiais bei medicininiais dantų miteliais ir pastomis; Didmeninės ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, susijusios su chirurginėmis siūlių ir žaizdų siuvimo medžiagomis ir produktais, chirurgine ir žaizdų priežiūros įranga, diagnozavimo, tyrimų ir stebėjimo prietaisais, kontraceptiniais įtaisais, dirbtiniais organais ir implantais, medicininiais vaizduojamaisiais aparatais, medicininiais fizinio lavinimo ir ligonių gimnastikos prietaisais, medicinos ir veterinarijos aparatais ir instrumentais; Didmeninės ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, susijusios su fizioterapijos ir reabilitacijos prietaisais, medicinos personalo ir pacientų apranga, galvos apdangalais ir avalyne, odontologijos prietaisais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi šādās jomās: farmācijas produkti un dabīgie dziedniecības līdzekļi, uzturs zīdaiņiem, dezinfekcijas līdzekļi un antiseptiskie līdzekļi, diētiskie preparāti un uztura bagātinātāji, sanitārie līdzekļi un preces, ārstniecības līdzekļi, medicīniskas un dezinfekcijas ziepes, kā arī mazgāšanas līdzekļi, medicīniski pārsienamie materiāli, nosegšanas materiāli un aplikatori, zobārstniecības preparāti un izstrādājumi, kā arī medicīniskas zobu pastas; Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar šādām precēm: ķirurģiskie šuvju materiāli un brūču ārstēšanas materiāli un produkti, ķirurģiskās iekārtas un aprīkojums ievainojumu apstrādei, diagnostikas, izmeklēšanas un monitoringa aparāti, kontraceptīvie līdzekļi, mākslīgie orgāni un implantāti, medicīniskās attēlveidošanas iekārtas, fizisko vingrinājumu aparāti medicīniskām vajadzībām un psihoterapija, medicīniskas un veterinārijas iekārtas un instrumenti; Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar fizioterapijas un rehabilitācijas iekārtām, apģērbs, galvassegas un apavi medicīnas personālam un pacientiem, zobārstniecības iekārtas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut b'rabta ma' mediċini u rimedji naturali, ikel tat-trabi, diżinfettanti u antisettiċi, preparazzjonijiet djetetiċi u supplimenti tal-ikel, preparazzjonijiet u oġġetti sanitarji, preparazzjonijiet mediċinali, sapun immedikati u diżinfettanti kif ukoll deterġenti, materjali tal-faxxaturi tal-feriti mediċi, materjali tal-kisi u tagħmir tal-applikazzjoni, preparazzjonijiet u prodotti dentali kif ukoll dentifriċi mediċinali; Bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut b'rabta ma' materjali u prodotti tas-sutura u tal-faxxaturi tal-feriti kirurġiċi, tagħmir kirurġiku u ta' trattament ta' feriti, tagħmir dijanjostiku, tal-eżaminazzjoni u monitoraġġ, tagħmir kontraċettiv, organi u impjanti artifiċjali, apparat tat-teħid ta' immaġnijiet mediċi, apparat għall-eżerċizzju fiżiku, għal skopijiet mediċi u fiżjoterapija, apparat u strumenti mediċi u veterinarji; Bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut b'rabta ma' tagħmir tal-fiżjoterapija u tar-riabilitazzjoni, ħwejjeġ, xedd ir-ras u xedd is-saqajn għal persunal u pazjenti mediċi, tagħmir dentali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Groot- en detailhandelsdiensten met betrekking tot geneesmiddelen en natuurlijke geneesmiddelen, voedingsmiddelen voor baby's, ontsmettingsmiddelen en antiseptische middelen, diëtische preparaten en voedingssupplementen, hygiënische preparaten en artikelen, medische preparaten, medische en desinfecterende zepen alsmede detergentia, medische verbandmiddelen, afdekmaterialen en aanbrenghulpmiddelen, tandheelkundige preparaten en producten alsmede medische tandreinigingsmiddelen; Groot- en detailhandelsdiensten met betrekking tot chirurgische naad- en wondafsluitmaterialen en -producten, chirurgische uitrusting en uitrusting voor het behandelen van wonden, diagnose-, onderzoeks- en controleapparaten, anticonceptie-inrichtingen, kunstorganen en implantaten, medische beeldvormingsapparatuur, medische toestellen voor lichaamsoefeningen en fysiotherapie, medische en diergeneeskundige toestellen en instrumenten; Groot- en detailhandelsdiensten met betrekking tot fysiotherapie- en revalidatietoestellen, kleding, hoofddeksels en schoeisel voor medisch personeel en patiënten, tandheelkundige apparaten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi handlu hurtowego i handlu detalicznego w odniesieniu do towarów, takich jak lekarstwa i naturalne środki lecznicze, żywność dla niemowląt, środki odkażające i antyseptyki, preparaty dietetyczne i suplementy diety, środki i artykuły sanitarne, preparaty medyczne, mydła lecznicze i odkażające oraz detergenty, opatrunki medyczne, materiały opatrunkowe i aplikatory, preparaty i produkty stomatologiczne oraz lecznicze środki do czyszczenia zębów; Usługi handlu hurtowego i handlu detalicznego w odniesieniu do towarów, takich jak materiały i produkty do szycia i zamykania ran, sprzęt chirurgiczny do zaopatrywania ran, urządzenia diagnostyczne, do badań i monitorowania, urządzenia antykoncepcyjne, sztuczne narządy i implanty, urządzenia medyczne do obrazowania, urządzenia medyczne do ćwiczeń fizycznych i rehabilitacji, urządzenia i przyrządy medyczne i weterynaryjne; Usługi handlu hurtowego i handlu detalicznego w odniesieniu do towarów, takich jak urządzenia do fizjoterapii i rehabilitacji, odzież, nakrycia głowy i obuwie dla personelu medycznego i pacjentów, urządzenia stomatologiczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de comércio grossista e retalhista relacionados com produtos farmacêuticos e remédios naturais, alimentos para bebés, desinfetantes e antisséticos, produtos dietéticos e suplementos nutricionais, produtos e artigos higiénicos, preparações medicinais, sabões desinfetantes e medicinais, bem como detergentes, artigos para pensos médicos, materiais de cobertura e aplicadores, preparações e artigos dentários, bem como dentífricos medicinais; Serviços de comércio grossista e retalhista relacionados com materiais e produtos de sutura e fecho de feridas, equipamento para tratamento cirúrgico e de lesões, aparelhos de diagnóstico, equipamento para diagnóstico, exame e monitorização, dispositivos contracetivos, órgãos e implantes artificiais, aparelhos de imagens médicas, aparelhos medicinais para exercícios corporais e fisioterapia, aparelhos e instrumentos medicinais e veterinários; Serviços de comércio grossista e retalhista relacionados com equipamento para fisioterapia e reabilitação, vestuário, chapelaria e calçado para pessoal médico e doentes, aparelhos de medicina dentária.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de comerț cu ridicata și cu amănuntul în legătură cu produse farmaceutice și remedii naturale, alimente pentru bebeluși, dezinfectante și antiseptice, preparate dietetice și suplimente nutritive, produse și articole de igienă, preparate medicinale, săpunuri medicinale și dezinfectante, precum și detergenți, materiale pentru pansamente medicale, materiale de acoperit și aplicatoare, preparate și produse stomatologie, precum și produse medicinale pentru curățarea dinților; Servicii de comerț cu ridicata și cu amănuntul în legătură cu materiale și produse pentru suturi chirurgicale și închiderea rănilor, echipamente chirurgicale și pentru îngrijirea rănilor, aparate de diagnostic, examinare și monitorizare, instrumente contraceptive, organe și implanturi artificiale, aparate de imagistică medicală, aparate medicale pentru exerciții de întreținere a corpului și gimnastică terapeutică, aparate și instrumente medicale și veterinare; Servicii de comerț cu ridicata și cu amănuntul în legătură cu aparate pentru fizioterapie și de recuperare, îmbrăcăminte, articole care servesc la acoperirea capului și încălțăminte pentru personalul medical și pacienți, aparate dentare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Veľkoobchodný a maloobchodný predaj so zameraním na liečivá a prírodné liečivá, výživové doplnky pre bábätká, dezinfekčné prípravky a antiseptické prípravky, dietetické prípravky a výživové doplnky, hygienické prípravky a výrobky, lekárske prípravky, medicínske a dezinfekčné mydlá, ako aj detergencie, medicínske obväzové materiály, maskovacie materiály a aplikátory, stomatologické prípravky a výrobky, ako aj medicínske prípravky na čistenie zubov; Veľkoobchodný a maloobchodný predaj so zameraním na chirurgické materiály a materiály a výrobky na uzatváranie rán, chirurgické a prístroje a nástroje na ošetrovanie rán, diagnostické, vyšetrovacie a monitorovacie prístroje, antikoncepčné prípravky, umelé orgány a implantáty, lekárske snímacie a zobrazovacie zariadenia, zariadenia na fyzické cvičenie na lekárske účely a pre fyzioterapiu, medicínske a veterinárne lekárske zariadenia a nástroje; Veľkoobchodný a maloobchodný predaj so zameraním na fyzioterapiu a rehabilitačné prístroje, odevy, pokrývky hlavy a obuv pre medicínsky personál a pacientov, zubárske prístroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Veleprodajne in maloprodajne storitve v zvezi z zdravili in naravnimi zdravili, hrano za dojenčke, dezinfekcijskimi sredstvi in antiseptiki, dietetičnimi pripravki in prehranskimi dopolnili, sanitarnimi sredstvi in izdelki, medicinskimi pripravki, medicinskimi in dezinfekcijskimi mili ter detergenti, medicinskim obvezilnim materialom, prekrivni materiali in aplikatorji, zobnimi pripravki in proizvodi ter medicinskimi sredstvi za čiščenje zob; Veleprodajne in maloprodajne storitve in v zvezi s kirurškimi materiali in izdelki za zapiranje šivov in ran , kirurško opremo za zdravljenje ran, napravami za diagnosticiranje, pregledovanje in opazovanje, kontracepcijskimi sredstvi, umetnimi organi in implantati, medicinskimi aparati za slikanje, medicinskimi napravami za telesno vadbo in fizioterapijo, medicinskimi in veterinarskimi aparati in instrumenti; Veleprodajne in maloprodajne storitve v zvezi z napravami za fizioterapijo in rehabilitacijo, oblačili, pokrivali in obutvijo za medicinsko osebje in paciente, zobozdravstvenimi napravami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster avseende läkemedel och naturläkemedel, spädbarnsnäringsmedel, desinfektionsmedel och antiseptiska medel, dietetiska preparat och näringstillskott, hygienpreparat och artiklar, medicinska preparat, medicinska och desinficerande tvålar samt tvättmedel, medicinskt förbandsmaterial, täckmaterial och applikatorer, tandvårdspreparat och produkter samt medicinska tandputsmedel; Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster avseende kirurgiska söm- och sårförslutningsmaterial och produkter, kirurgisk och sårbehandlingsutrustning, diagnos-, undersöknings- och övervakningsanordningar, preventivmedelsanordningar, konstgjorda organ och implantat, medicinska bilderingsapparater, medicinska apparater för kroppsträning och sjukgymnastik, medicinska och veterinära apparater och instrument; Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster avseende fysioterapi- och rehabiliteringsanordningar, kläder, huvudbonader och fotbeklädnader för sjukvårdspersonal och patienter, odontologiska apparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/091</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-15</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/163</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-27</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>769651</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>18935</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018000409</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Proprietor - Change of name and address</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>18935</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-10</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
