<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-24T10:47:41</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229590</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229590</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-26</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-21</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-26</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-24</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>CallySonic</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Четки за зъби, електрически; Ръчни четки за зъби; Накрайници за електрически четки за зъби; Четки за зъби; Водни апарати за почистване на зъби и венци; Контейнери за четки за зъби; Копринени конци за зъболекарски цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Elektrické zubní kartáčky; Ruční zubní kartáčky; Hlavy k elektrickým zubním kartáčkům; Zubní kartáčky; Ústní sprchy na čištění zubů a masáž dásní; Pouzdra na zubní kartáčky; Zubní nit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tandbørster, elektriske; Manuelle tandbørster; Hoveder til elektriske tandbørster; Tandbørster; Vandapparater til rengøring af tænder og gummer; Beholdere til tandbørster; Tandtråd.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Elektrische Zahnbürsten; Manuelle Zahnbürsten; Bürstenköpfe für elektrische Zahnbürsten; Zahnbürsten; Mundduschen; Zahnbürstenbehälter; Zahnseide.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Οδοντόβουρτσες [ηλεκτρικές]· Χειροκίνητες οδοντόβουρτσες· Κεφαλές για ηλεκτρικές οδοντόβουρτσες· Βουρτσες (Οδοντό -)· Πλύσεων στοματικών (Συσκευές -)· Θήκες για οδοντόβουρτσες· Νήμα οδοντικό.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Toothbrushes, electric; non-electric toothbrushes; heads for electric toothbrushes; toothbrushes; water apparatus for cleaning teeth and gums; toothbrush cases; floss for dental purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cepillos de dientes eléctricos; Cepillos de dientes manuales; Cabezales para cepillos de dientes eléctricos; Cepillos de dientes; Duchas bucales; Recipientes para cepillos de dientes; Hilo dental.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Elektrihambaharjad; Mitteelektrilised hambaharjad; Elektriliste hambaharjade otsakud; Hambaharjad; Hammaste ja igemete vesipuhastuse seadmed; Hambaharjavutlarid; Hambaniit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sähköhammasharjat; Käsikäyttöiset hammasharjat; Sähköhammasharjojen vaihtopäät; Hammasharjat; Suihkuttimet hampaiden ja ikenien puhdistukseen; Hammasharjakotelot; Hammaslanka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Brosses à dents électriques; Brosses à dents manuelles; Têtes pour brosses à dents électriques; Brosses à dents; Douches buccales; Récipients pour brosses à dents; Fil dentaire.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Četkice za zube, električne; Ručne četkice za zube; Glave za električne četkice za zube; Četkice za zube; Tuševi za ispiranje usta; Kutijice za četkice za zube; Konac za njegu zubi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Fogkefék (Elektromos -); Fogkefe; Fejek elektromos fogkefékhez; Fogkefék; Szájzuhanyok; Fogkefe tokok; Fogselyem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Spazzolini da denti elettrici; Spazzolini da denti manuali; Testine per spazzolini da denti elettrici; Spazzolini da denti; Docce per bocca; Contenitori per spazzolini da denti; Filo dentario.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektriniai dantų šepetukai; Rankiniai dantų šepetėliai; Elektrinių dantų šepetėlių galvutės; Dantų šepetukai; Dantų ir dantenų valymo vandens aparatai; Dantų šepetėlių dėžutės; Tarpdančių valymo siūlai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elektriskās zobu sukas; Rokas zobu sukas; Elektrisko zobu suku galviņas; Zobu sukas; Ūdens ierīces zobu un smaganu tīrīšanai; Zobu suku trauki; Zobu diegi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Xkupilji tas-snien, tal-elettriku; Xkupilji manwali tas-snien; Irjus għall-ixkupilji tas-snien li jaħdmu bl-elettriku; Xkupilji tas-snien; Apparat għat-tindif tas-snien u tal-ħanek; Kontenituri għall-ixkupilji tas-snien; Ħajt għal skopijiet ta' tindif dentali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Elektrische tandenborstels; Tandenborstels (Handmatige -); Opzetstukken voor elektrische tandenborstels; Tandenborstels; Monddouches; Tandenborsteldozen; Tandzijde.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Szczoteczki do zębów elektryczne; Szczoteczki do zębów do szczotkowania ręcznego; Końcówki do szczoteczek elektrycznych; Szczoteczki do zębów; Wodne aparaty do czyszczenia jamy ustnej; Pojemniki na szczoteczki do zębów; Nici dentystyczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Escovas de dentes elétricas; Escovas de dentes manuais; Cabeças para escovas de dentes elétricas; Escovas de dentes; Dispositivos de água para limpeza de dentes e gengivas; Recipientes para escovas de dentes; Fio dental.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Perii de dinți electrice; Periuțe de dinți manuale; Capete pentru periuțe de dinți electrice; Periuțe de dinți; Dușuri de gură pentru curățarea dinților si gingiilor; Recipiente pentru periuțe de dinți; Ață dentară.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Elektrické zubné kefky; Ručné zubné kefky; Hlavice na elektrické zubné kefky; Zubné kefky; Ústne sprchy na čistenie zubov a masáž ďasien; Nádoby na zubné kefky; Dentálne nite.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zobne ščetke, električne; Ročne zobne ščetke; Glave za električne zobne ščetke; Zobne ščetke; Ustne prhe za čiščenje zob; Etuiji za zobno ščetko; Zobna nitka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Elektriska tandborstar; Manuella tandborstar; Borsthuvuden för elektriska tandborstar; Tandborstar; Vattenanordningar för rengöring av tänder och tandkött; Behållare för tandborstar; Tandtråd för dentala ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/106</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-08</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/182</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-23</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1074795</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15173</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
