<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-14T18:58:15</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229800</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229800</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-26</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-10</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>MEOTE</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162491307</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229800/000162491307.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>03.07.17</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.12</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.21</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.01</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Светлини за велосипеди; Електрическо фенерче; Осветителни уреди и инсталации; Електрически фенерчета; Подводни прожектори; Противобактерийни лампи за пречистване на въздух; Ултравиолетови лампи, не за медицински цели; Обезопасени лампи за рудници; Миньорски лампи; Рефлектори за превозни средства; Осветителни устройства за превозни средства; Абажури за лампи; Светодиодни [LED] лампи; Фенери за осветление; Фарове за автомобили; Улични лампи; Осветление за аквариуми; Електрически захранвани духалки с цел вентилиране; Стерилизатори; Джобни грейки; Прожектори за светлина.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Světla pro jízdní kola; Vyhledávací světlomety; Osvětlovací přístroje a zařízení; Baterky (elektrické svítilny); Potápěčská světla; Germicidní lampy na čištění vzduchu; UV lampy, ne pro léčebné účely; Bezpečnostní lampy; Důlní lampy; Reflektory pro vozidla; Osvětlovací zařízení pro dopravní prostředky; Stínidla pro svítidla; Lampy LED; Lucerny; Světlomety pro automobily; Pouliční lampy; Osvětlení pro akvária; Elektricky napájené větráky na ventilaci; Sterilizátory; Kapesní ohřívače; Světelné projektory.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Cykellygter; Lyskastere; Belysningsapparater og installationer; Lommelygter, elektriske; Dykkerlamper; Bakteriedræbende lamper til rensning af luft; Lamper til ultraviolet bestråling, ikke til medicinske formål; Sikkerhedslamper; Minelamper; Reflektorer til befordringsmidler; Belysningsapparater til befordringsmidler; Lampeskærme; LED-lamper; Lanterner til belysning; Forlygter til biler; Gadelamper; Akvarielamper; Elektriske ventilatorer; Steriliseringsapparater; Lommevarmere; Spotlamper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Fahrradleuchten; Suchscheinwerfer; Beleuchtungsapparate und -anlagen; Taschenlampen; Tauchlampen; Luftreinigungslampen mit keimtötender Wirkung; Ultraviolettlampen, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Sicherheitslampen; Grubenlampen; Fahrzeugrückstrahler; Beleuchtungsgeräte für Fahrzeuge; Lampenschirme; LED-Lampen; Laternen; Scheinwerfer für Kraftfahrzeuge; Stehlampen, Straßenlampen; Beleuchtung für Aquarien; Elektroventilatoren; Sterilisiergeräte; Taschenwärmer; Lichtprojektoren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δικύκλων φανάρια· Προβολείς εντοπισμού· Φωτισμός (μηχανισμοί και εγκαταστάσεις -ού)· Ηλεκτρικοί φορητοί φανοί· Προβολείς κατάδυσης· Μικροβιοκτόνες (- λυχνίες) για το καθαρισμό του αέρα· Λαμπτήρες υπεριωδών ακτίνων για μη ιατρική χρήση· Λυχνίες ασφαλείας· Μεταλλωρύχοι (λυχνίες -ων)· Ανακλαστήρες οχημάτων· Οχημάτων φανάρια· Αμπαζούρ· Λυχνίες φωτοδιόδων (LED)· Φανοί φωτισμού· Προβολείς για αυτοκίνητα· Λάμπες για οδικό φωτισμό· Λυχνίες φωτισμού ενυδρείων· Ηλεκτρικοί ανεμιστήρες για χρήσεις αερισμού· Αποστειρωτές· Θερμάστρες τσέπης· Προβολείς φωτισμού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Bicycle lights; Searchlights; Lighting apparatus and installations; Electric flashlights; Diving lights; Germicidal lamps for purifying air; Ultraviolet ray lamps, not for medical purposes; Safety lamps; Miners' lamps; Vehicle reflectors; Lighting apparatus for vehicles; Lamp shades; LED lamps; Lanterns for lighting; Headlights for automobile; Street lamps; Aquarium lights; Electric fans; Sterilizers; Pocket warmers; Light projectors.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Luces para bicicletas; Proyectores de luz; Aparatos e instalaciones de alumbrado; Linternas eléctricas; Lámparas de buceo; Lámparas germicidas para purificar el aire; Lámparas de rayos ultravioleta que no sean para uso médico; Lámparas de seguridad; Lámparas de minero; Reflectores para vehículos; Aparatos de iluminación para vehículos; Pantallas de lámparas; Lámparas LED; Faroles de alumbrado; Faros para automóviles; Farolas; Luces para iluminar acuarios; Ventiladores eléctricos para ventilar; Esterilizadores; Calentadores de bolsillo; Proyectores de luz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Jalgrattalaternad; Taskulambid [valgustusseadmed], helgiheitjad, prožektorid; Valgustusaparaadid ja -seadised; Elektrilised taskulambid; Tuukrite lambid; Bakterihävituslambid, bakteritsiidlambid õhupuhastuseks; Ultraviolettlambid, v.a meditsiinilised; Turvalambid; Kaevurilambid; Sõidukihelkurid; Sõidukite valgustusseadmed; Lambivarjud; Valgusdioodlambid, LED-lambid; Valgustuslaternad; Autode esilaternad; Tänavalaternad; Akvaariumide valgustid; Elektriventilaatorid; Sterilisaatorid, steriliseeraparaadid; Taskusoojendid; Valgusprožektorid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lamput polkupyöriin; Soihdut valaistukseen; Valaistuslaitteet; Sähkökäyttöiset käsivalaisimet; Sukelluslamput; Itiöitä ja mikro-organismeja tuhoavat lamput ilmanpuhdistukseen; Ultraviolettisäteilylamput, ei-lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Turvalamput; Kaivoslamput; Heijastimet ajoneuvoille; Ajoneuvojen valaisimet; Lampunvarjostimet; LED-lamput; Lyhdyt valaistukseen; Ajovalaisimet autoihin; Jalkalamput; Akvaariolamput; Sähkötuulettimet; Sterilointilaitteet; Taskulämmittimet; Valoprojektorit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Feux pour vélos; Projecteurs d'éclairage; Appareils et installations d'éclairage; Torches électriques; Éclairage de plongée; Lampes germicides pour la purification de l'air; Lampes à rayons ultraviolets autres qu'à usage médical; Lampes de sûreté; Lampes de mineurs; Réflecteurs pour véhicules; Appareils d'éclairage pour véhicules; Abat-jour; Ampoules DEL; Lanternes d'éclairage; Phares pour automobiles; Lampadaires; Lampes d'éclairage pour aquariums; Ventilateurs électriques; Stérilisateurs; Chaufferettes de poche; Projecteurs de lumière.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Svjetla za bicikle; Džepne svjetiljke za rasvjetu; Rasvjetni uređaji i instalacije; Električne baterijske svjetiljke; Projektori za ronjenje; Svjetiljke za uništavanje klica radi pročišćavanja zraka; Ultraljubičaste lampe, nisu za medicinske potrebe; Svjetiljke, sigurnosne; Rudarske svjetiljke; Reflektori za vozila; Svjetla za automobile; Sjenila za svjetiljke; Svjetiljke LED; Rasvjetni fenjeri; Farovi za vozila; Stajaće svjetiljke; Svjetiljke za akvarije; Električni ventilatori; Sterilizatori; Džepne grijalice; Svjetlosni projektori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kerékpár lámpák; Keresőlámpák, zseblámpák; Világító berendezések és készülékek; Zseblámpák, elektromos; Búvárlámpák; Csíraölő lámpák a levegő tisztításához; Ultraviola lámpák nem gyógyászati használatra; Biztonsági lámpák; Bányászlámpák; Reflektorok járművekhez; Lámpák járművekhez; Lámpaernyők; LED-lámpák; Lámpások világításra; Fényszórók, reflektorok gépkocsikhoz; Beltéri állólámpák; Akváriumi világítótestek; Elektromos meghajtású ventilátorok szellőztetési célokra; Sterilizátorok; Zsebmelegítők; Fényprojektorok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Fanali per cicli; Proiettori; Apparecchi ed impianti di illuminazione; Lampadine tascabili; Faretti da sub; Lampade germicide per la depurazione dell'aria; Lampade a raggi ultravioletti non per uso medico; Lampade di sicurezza; Lampade per minatori; Riflettori per veicoli; Apparecchi di illuminazione per veicoli; Paralumi; Lampade a LED; Lanterne per illuminazione; Fari per automobili; Lampade a stelo; Lampadine per acquari; Ventilatori elettrici; Sterilizzatori; Scaldini da tasca; Lampade lenticolari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Dviračių žibintai; Prožektoriai; Apšvietimo prietaisai ir įrenginiai; Kišeniniai žibintuvėliai; Nardymo šviestuvai; Oro valymo baktericidinės lempos; Ultravioletinės lempos (ne medicinos reikmėms); Saugiosios lempos; Šachtininkų lemputės; Transporto priemonių atšvaitai; Transporto priemonių apšvietimo prietaisai; Lempų gaubtai; Šviesolaidžio (LED) lempos; Apšvietimo žibintai; Priekiniai automobilių žibintai; Gatvių šviestuvai; Akvariumų lempos [žibintai]; Elektriniai ventiliatoriai vėdinimo reikmėms; Sterilizatoriai; Kišeniniai šildytuvai; Šviesos prožektoriai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Velosipēdu lukturi; Kabatas baterijas; Apgaismošanas ierīces un aparāti; Elektriskie lukturīši; Ūdenslīdēju lukturi; Baktericīdas lampas gaisa attīrīšanai; Ultravioleto staru lampas nemedicīniskiem nolūkiem; Drošības lampas; Kalnraču lampas; Transporta līdzekļu atstarotāji; Transportlīdzekļu apgaismojuma ierīces; Lampu abažūri; LED lampas; Apgaismošanas laternas; Automašīnu priekšējie lukturi; Stāvlampas; Lampas akvārijiem; Elektriskie ventilatori gaisa ventilācijas nolūkiem; Sterilizētāji; Kabatas formāta sildītāji; Prožektori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Dwal tar-roti; Torċ għad-dawl; Apparat u sistemi tad-dawl; Torċi elettriċi; Lampi tal-għaddasa; Lampi li jnaddfu l-arja u li joqtlu l-imnibbta; Lampi tar-raġġi ultravjola, mhux għal skopijiet mediċi; Lampi tas-sigurtà; Lampi tal-minaturi; Rifletturi tal-vetturi; Dwal għall-vetturi; Paralumi; Lampi LED; Fanali għad-dawl; Fanali ta' quddiem għall-użu fil-karozzi; Lampi stàndard; Dwal għall-akkwarji; Ventilaturi elettriċi; Sterilizzaturi; Saħħâna tal-but; Projetturi tad-dawl.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Rijwielverlichting; Toortsen voor verlichting; Verlichtingsapparaten en -installaties; Zaklampen; Duikerlampen; Kiemdodende lampen voor het zuiveren van lucht; Ultravioletlampen, niet voor medisch gebruik; Veiligheidslampen; Mijnwerkerslampen; Voertuigreflectoren; Verlichtingsapparatuur voor voertuigen; Lampenkappen; Led-lampen; Lantaarns voor verlichting; Koplampen voor automobielen; Lantaarnpalen; Lampen voor aquaria; Elektrische ventilatoren voor ventilatie-doeleinden; Sterilisators; Zakhandwarmertjes; Lichtprojectoren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Światła rowerowe; Latarki; Urządzenia i instalacje oświetleniowe; Latarki kieszonkowe, elektryczne; Lampy nurkowe; Lampy bakteriobójcze do oczyszczania powietrza; Lampy ultrafioletowe, nie do celów medycznych; Lampy bezpieczeństwa; Lampy górnicze; Reflektory do pojazdów; Światła do pojazdów; Abażury do lamp; Lampy LED; Latarnie oświetleniowe; Reflektory samochodowe; Lampy stojące; Lampy do oświetlania akwarium; Wentylatory elektryczne; Sterylizatory; Ogrzewacze kieszonkowe; Rzutniki światła.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Luzes para bicicletas; Tochas [archotes] para a iluminação; Aparelhos e instalações de iluminação; Lanternas elétricas; Projetores de mergulho; Lâmpadas germicidas para a purificação do ar; Lâmpadas para raios ultravioletas não para uso medicinal; Lâmpadas de segurança; Lâmpadas de mineiros; Refletores de veículos; Aparelhos de iluminação para veículos; Abajures; Lâmpadas LED; Lanternas de iluminação; Faróis para automóveis; Lampadários; Lâmpadas de iluminação para aquários; Ventoinhas elétricas para fins de ventilação; Esterilizadores; Escalfetas de bolso; Projetores de luz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Lanterne de biciclete; Lanterne pentru iluminat; Aparate şi instalaţii de iluminat; Lămpi electrice; Lanterne pentru scufundări; Lămpi germicide pentru purificarea aerului; Lămpi cu raze ultraviolete (care nu sunt de uz medical); Lămpi de siguranţă; Lămpi pentru mineri; Proiectoare pentru vehicule; Aparate de iluminat pentru vehicule; Abajururi; Lămpi cu LED; Lanterne de iluminat; Automobile (Faruri pentru -); Lampadare; Lămpi de iluminat pentru acvarii; Ventilatoare acţionate electric folosite la ventilaţie; Sterilizatoare; Încălzitoare de buzunar; Proiectoare de lumină.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Svietidlá na bicykle; Baterky (svietidlá); Osvetľovacie prístroje a zariadenia; Vreckové baterky; Potápačské svetlomety; Lampy na čistenie vzduchu od baktérií (germicídne); UV-lampy nie na lekárske použitie; Bezpečnostné lampy; Banské lampy; Reflektory vozidiel; Osvetľovacie zariadenia na dopravné prostriedky; Tienidlá na lampy; LED lampy; Lampáše; Automobilové reflektory; Pouličné lampy; Svietidlá do akvárií; Elektrické ventilátory na vetracie účely; Sterilizátory; Vreckové ohrievače; Svetlomet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kolesarske luči; Žepne svetilke za razsvetljavo; Naprave in napeljave za razsvetljavo; Električne baterijske svetilke; Potapljaške svetilke; Germicidne svetilke za prečiščevanje zraka; Svetilke u ultravijoličnimi žarki, ne za medicinske namene; Varnostne svetilke; Rudarske svetilke; Reflektorji za vozila; Naprave za osvetlitev za vozila; Senčniki za svetilke; LED svetilke; Lanterne za razsvetljavo; Žarometi za avtomobile; Stoječe svetilke; Akvarijske luči; Električni ventilatorji za prezračevanje; Sterilizatorji; Žepni grelniki; Projektorji svetlobe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Cykelbelysning; Handlyktor; Belysningsapparater och -installationer; Ficklampor; Dykarlampor; Bakteriedödande lampor för luftrening; Lampor för ultraviolettstrålning, inte för medicinska ändamål; Säkerhetslampor; Gruvlampor; Reflektorer för fordon och farkoster; Billyktor; Lampskärmar; LED-lampor; Lanternor för belysning; Strålkastare för bilar; Golvlampor; Akvariebelysning; Elektriska fläktar för ventilation; Steriliseringsapparater; Fickvärmare; Ljusprojektorer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/108</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082569</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15173</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003130639</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-09-10</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>PT</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>333000</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>1998-10-15</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>333000</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>1999-04-14</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>SIM</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>1088215</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15273</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
