<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-15T17:20:16</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229830</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229830</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-11</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-15</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>MOE`S</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162501054</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229830/000162501054.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>02.01.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>02.01.97</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>4</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Въглен за наргиле.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Uhlíky do vodní dýmky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Trækul til vandpiber.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Holzkohle für Wasserpfeifen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κάρβουνα για ναργιλέδες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hookah charcoal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Carbón de narguile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Vesipiibusüsi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vesipiipuissa (hookah) käytettävä hiili.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Charbon pour narguilés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Drveni ugljen za nargile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vízipipa-faszén.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Carbone per narghilè.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kaljanų anglys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ūdenspīpes ogles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Faħam tal-pipa tad-duħħan tat-Torok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Houtskool voor waterpijpen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Węgiel do fajek wodnych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Carvão para cachimbo de água.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cărbune pentru narghilea.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Drevené uhlie pre vodné fajky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oglje za vodno pipo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Träkol till vattenpipor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Oблекло, особено тениски, жарсени облекла; Обувки; Шапки с козирка, ленти за глава (oблекло); Шапки и накити за глава (шапки, каскети); Шапки за слънце; Трикотаж, пуловери, жилетки за костюми, якета, поло-тениски, шалове, шалчета.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Oděvy, zejména trička, svetříky; Obuv; Kšiltovky, čelenky (oděvy); Kloboučnické zboží (čepice, kapuce); Klobouky proti slunci; Pletené zboží, svetry, vesty, saka, polokošile, košile, šály, šátky na krk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beklædningsgenstande, særlig T-shirts, jerseybeklædning; Fodtøj; Kasketskygger, pandebånd (beklædningsgenstande); Hovedbeklædning (huer, kasketter); Solhatte; Strikvarer, sweatere, veste, jakker, poloskjorter, skjorter, flipskånere, halstørklæder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bekleidungsstücke, insbesondere T-Shirts, Jerseybekleidung; Schuhwaren; Mützenschirme, Stirnbänder (Bekleidung); Kopfbedeckung (Mützen, Kappen); Sonnenhüte; Strickwaren, Sweater, Westen, Jacken, Polo-Shirts, Hemden, Schals, Halstücher.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ενδύματα, ειδικότερα κοντομάνικα μπλουζάκια, αθλητικές φανέλες· Υποδήματα· Γείσα, κεφαλόδεσμοι (ενδύματα)· Είδη πιλοποιίας (σκούφοι, κασκέτα)· Καπέλα για τον ήλιο· Πλεκτά είδη, πουλόβερ φούτερ, γιλέκα, σακάκια, μπλούζες τύπου πόλο, πουκάμισα, επώμια (σάλια), μαντίλια για τον λαιμό.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Clothing, in particular T-shirts, jersey clothing; Footwear; Cap peaks, headbands (clothing); Headgear (hats, caps); Sun hats; Knitwear, sweaters, waistcoats, jackets, polo shirts, shirts, scarves, neckerchiefs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Vestidos, en particular camisetas, jerseys; Calzado; Viseras, bandas para la cabeza (ropa); Cubrecabezas (gorros, gorras); Sombreros para el sol; Prendas de punto, jerseys, chalecos, chaquetas, polos, camisetas, bufandas, pañuelos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rõivad, eelkõige T-särgid, lühikeste varrukatega särgid; Jalatsid; Mütsinokad, peapaelad; Peakatted (mütsid, nokkmütsid); Päikesemütsid; Kudumid, sviitrid, vestid, jakid, polosärgid, päevasärgid, sallid, kaelarätid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatteet, erityisesti T-paidat, jerseyvaatteet; Jalkineet; Lipat, otsanauhat (vaatteet); Päähineet (lakit, lippalakit); Aurinkohatut; Neuleet, neulepuserot, liivit, pusakat, poolopaidat, paidat, huivit, kaulaliinat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vêtements, en particulier tee-shirts, vêtements en jersey; Chaussures; Visières, bandeaux (vêtements); Articles de chapellerie (bonnets, casquettes); Capelines; Tricots, chandails, gilets, vestes, polos, chemises, écharpes, foulards.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Odjevni predmeti, posebno majice kratkih rukava, odjeća od džerseja; Obuća; Šiltovi, trake za glavu (odjeća); Pokrivala za glavu (šeširi, kape); Šeširi za zaštitu od sunca; Pletena odjeća, džemperi, prsluci, jakne, polo majice, košulje, šalovi, rupci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ruházati cikkek, különösen pólók, dzsörzé ruházat; Lábbelik; Szemellenzők (sapkán), homlokpántok (ruházat); Kalapáruk (sapkák, sildes sapkák); Napvédő kalapok; Kötöttáru, szabadidőfelsők, mellények, zakók, dzsekik, pólók, ingek, sálak, nyaksálak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Articoli d'abbigliamento, in particolare t-shirt e abbigliamento in jersey; Calzature; Visiere, fasce per la testa (abiti); Copricapo (berretti, cappucci); Cappelli da sole; Maglieria, maglioni, gilet, giacche, polo, camicie, sciarpe, foulard.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Drabužiai, ypač marškinėliai, džersio drabužiai; Apavas; Kepurių snapeliai, plaukų/kaktos raiščiai (apranga); Galvos apdangalai (kepurės, kepuraitės); Skrybėlės nuo saulės; Trikotažo gaminiai, megztiniai, liemenės, švarkai, marškinėliai su atverčiama apykakle, marškiniai, šalikai, kaklaskarės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apģērbi, jo īpaši T-krekli, adīti apģērbi; Kurpes; Cepuru nadziņi, pieres lentes (apģērbs); Galvassegas (cepures, cepures ar nadziņu); Saules cepures; Trikotāžas izstrādājumi, svīteri, vestes, žaketes, polo krekli, krekli, šalles, kaklauti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ilbies, speċjalment tixerts u qomos, lbies tal-ġersi; Xedd is-saqajn; Pizz tal-brieret, strixx drapp ta' mar-ras (ilbies); Xedd ir-ras (brieret, kpiepel); Kpiepel għax-xemx; Maljerija, ġersi, sdieri, ġkieket, powlowxerts, qomos, xalel, xalpi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kledingstukken, met name T-shirts, kledingstukken van jersey; Schoeisel; Petkleppen, hoofdbanden (kleding); Hoofddeksels (mutsen, petten); Zonnehoeden; Breigoederen, truien, vesten, jasjes, poloshirts, overhemden, sjaals, halsdoeken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odzież, w szczególności t-shirty, dżerseje; Obuwie; Daszki do czapek, opaski na czoło (odzież); Nakrycie głowy (czapki, kaptury); Kapelusze przeciwsłoneczne; Wyroby dziane, swetry, kamizelki, kurtki, koszulki polo, koszule, szale, szaliki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vestuário, em especial t-shirts, vestuário de malha; Calçado; Palas, fitas para a cabeça (vestuário); Chapelaria (gorros, bonés); Chapéus de sol; Roupa de malha, camisolas, coletes, casacos, pólos, camisas, cachecóis, lenços de pescoço.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Imbracaminte, in special tricouri, imbracaminte din jerseu; Articole de încălţăminte; Cozoroace, cordelute (imbracaminte); Articole care servesc la acoperirea capului (sepci, caciuli); Pălării de soare; Articole tricotate, pulovere, veste, jachete, tricouri polo, camasi, baticuri, fulare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Odevy, predovšetkým tričká, dresy; Obuv; Čiapkové šilty, čelenky (odevy); Pokrývky hlavy (klobúky, čiapky); Klobúky proti slnku; Pleteniny, svetre, vesty, bundy, saká, zmrzliny, košele, šatky, šatky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oblačila, zlasti majice s kratkimi rokavi,oblačila iz jerseya; Obutev; Senčniki za čepice, naglavni trakovi (oblačila); Pokrivala (čepice, kape); Klobuki za sonce; Pletenine, svitri, telovniki, suknjiči, polo majice, moške srajce, šali, ovratne rute.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kläder, speciellt t-tröjor, jerseykläder; Fotbeklädnader; Mösskärmar, pannband (kläder); Huvudbonader (mössor, kepsar); Solhattar; Trikå, sweaters, västar, jackor/kavajer, polotröjor, skjortor, sjalar, halsdukar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>32</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Бира и пивоварни продукти; Безалкохолни напитки; Безалкохолни препарати за приготвяне на напитки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pivo a pivovarnické výrobky; Nealkoholické nápoje; Nealkoholické přípravky ke zhotovování nápojů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Øl og bryggeriprodukter; Ikke-alkoholholdige drikke; Ikke-alkoholholdige præparater til fremstilling af drikke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bier und Brauereiprodukte; Nichtalkoholische Getränke; Alkoholfreie Präparate für die Zubereitung von Getränken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μπύρα και προϊόντα ζυθοποιίας· Μη αλκοολούχα ποτά· Μη οινοπνευματώδη παρασκευάσματα για ποτοποιία.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Beer and brewery products; Non-alcoholic beverages; Non-alcoholic preparations for making beverages.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cervezas y sus derivados; Bebidas no alcohólicas; Preparaciones sin alcohol para hacer bebidas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Õlu ja pruulikojatooted; Alkoholivabad joogid; Mittealkohoolsed valmistusained jookide valmistamiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Oluet ja panimotuotteet; Alkoholittomat juomat; Alkoholittomat juomien valmistusaineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bière et produits de brasserie; Boissons sans alcool; Préparations non alcoolisées pour faire des boissons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pivo i pivarski proizvodi; Bezalkoholna pića; Bezalkoholni preparati za pripremu pića.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Sörök és sörtermékek; Alkoholmentes italok; Nem alkoholos készítmények italok készítéséhez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Birre e prodotti derivati; Bevande non alcoliche; preparazioni non alcoliche per fare bevande.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Alus ir alaus produktai; Gaivieji gėrimai; Nealkoholiniai preparatai gėrimams gaminti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Alus un alus darītavu produkti; Bezalkoholiskie dzērieni; Dzērienu gatavošanai paredzētās bezalkoholiskās sagataves.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Birra u prodotti tal-birrerija; Xarbiet mhux alkoħoliċi; Preparazzjonijiet mhux alkoħoliċi għat-tħejjija tax-xorb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Bier en brouwerijproducten; Niet-alcoholische dranken; Niet-alcoholische preparaten voor de bereiding van dranken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Piwo i produkty piwowarskie; Napoje bezalkoholowe; Preparaty bezalkoholowe do sporządzania napojów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cerveja e produtos de cervejaria; Bebidas sem álcool; Preparações não alcoólicas para fazer bebidas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Bere şi produse de bere; Băuturi nealcoolice; Preparate nealcoolice pentru pregătirea de băuturi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Pivo a pivovarnícke produkty; Nealkoholické nápoje; Nealkoholické prípravky na výrobu nápojov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pivo in pivovarski proizvodi; Brezalkoholne pijače; Brezalkoholni pripravki za pripravo pijač.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Öl och bryggeriprodukter; Icke alkoholhaltiga drycker; Alkoholfria preparat för framställning av drycker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>34</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Наргилета; Наргилета; Есенции за тютюн; Есенции, различни от етерични масла, за тютюн; Пепелници; Пепелници от благородни метали; Пепелници за пушачи, изработени от неблагородни метали; Кутии за поддръжане влажността на тютюна; Кутии за тютюневи изделия и кутии за пури с овлажнител; Кесии за тютюн; Торбички за лули; Електронни наргилета; Електронни лули за пушене; Електронни цигари; Кутии за лули, изработени от благородни метали; Kутии, лули от благороден метал; Запалки от благородни метали; Запалки за пушачи; Резервоарчета за газ за запалки; Поставки за лули; Треви за пушене; Мундщуци за лули; Тръбопроводи; Тапи за лули; Поставки за лули; Тютюн за лула; Принадлежности за пушачи; Тютюн за пушене; Емфие; Поставки за кибрити, не от благороден метал; Кибрит; Тютюн; Метални кутии за тютюн; Кесии за тютюн; Бурканчета за тютюн; Заместители на тютюн; Тръбопроводи; Цигари (Джобни машинки за свиване на -); Джобни запалки не от ценни метали; Изпарители на тютюн (пиви) за лична употреба и електронни цигари, и есенции и разтвори за тях; Изпарители, за пушачи; Тютюн за наргиле; Цигари, пури, пурети и други готови за употреба артикули за пушене.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vodní dýmky; Vodní dýmky; Příchutě do tabáku; Tabákové příchutě, jiné než éterické oleje; Popelníky pro kuřáky; Popelníky z drahých kovů; Popelníky vyrobené z obecných kovů; Zvlhčovače tabáku; Pouzdra na tabákové výrobky a humidory; Pouzdra na tabák; Pouzdra na dýmky; Elektronické vodní dýmky; Elektronické kuřácké dýmky; Elektronické cigarety; Pouzdra na dýmky z drahých kovů; Pouzdra na dýmky, nikoli z drahých kovů; Zapalovače z drahých kovů; Zapalovače pro kuřáky; Zásobníky plynu do zapalovačů; Stojánky na dýmky; Byliny ke kouření; Náustky dýmek; Dýmky; Nacpávače dýmek; Stojánky na dýmky; Dýmkový tabák; Potřeby pro kuřáky; Tabák ke kouření; Šňupací tabák; Držáky na zápalky; Zápalky; Tabák; Plechové nádoby na tabák; Pouzdra na tabák; Dózy na tabák; Náhražky tabáku; Dýmky; Kapesní baličky cigaret; Kapesní zapalovače nikoliv z drahých kovů; Osobní vaporizéry a elektronické cigarety a příchutě a roztoky pro ně; Ústní vaporizéry pro kuřáky; Tabák do vodní dýmky; Cigarety, doutníky, cigarillos a jiné kuřácké potřeby připravené k použití.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Vandpiber; Vandpiber; Smagsstoffer til tobak; Smagsstoffer til tobak, undtagen æteriske olier; Askebægre; Askebægre af ædelmetal; Askebægere til rygere, ikke af ædelmetaller; Luftfugtere til tobak; Tobaksbeholdere og humidorer; Tobakspunge; Pibetasker; Elektroniske vandpiber; Elektroniske piber; Elektroniske cigaretter; Pibeæsker af ædle metaller; Pibeetuier, ikke af ædle metaller; Lightere af ædelmetal; Lightere til rygere; Gasbeholdere til cigartændere; Pibestativer; Urter til rygning; Pibemundstykker; Tobakspiber; Pibestoppere; Pibestativer; Pibetobak; Artikler for rygere; Rygetobak; Snustobak; Tændstikholdere; Tændstikker; Tobak; Tobaksdåser; Tobakspunge; Tobakskrukker; Tobakserstatninger; Tobakspiber; Lommeredskaber til rulning af cigaretter; Lommelightere, ikke af ædle metaller; Fordampere og elektroniske cigaretter samt smagsstoffer og opløsninger hertil til personlig brug; Fordampere til oral brug til rygere; Hookah-tobak; Cigaretter, cigarer, cigarillos og andre artikler for rygere klar til brug.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wasserpfeifen; orientalische Wasserpfeifen; Aromastoffe für Tabak; Aromen für Tabak, ausgenommen ätherische Öle; Aschenbecher; Aschenbecher aus Edelmetall; Aschenbecher für Raucher aus unedlen Metallen; Befeuchter für Tabak; Behälter für Raucherartikel, Humidoren; Tabakbeutel; Beutel für Pfeifen; Elektronische Shishas; Elektronische Tabakpfeifen; Elektronische Zigaretten; Etuis aus Edelmetall für Tabakpfeifen; Etuis für Tabakpfeifen, nicht aus Edelmetall; Feuerzeuge aus Edelmetall; Feuerzeuge für Raucher; Gaspatronen für Feuerzeuge; Gestelle für Tabakpfeifen; Kräuter zum Rauchen; Mundstücke für Pfeifen; Pfeifen; Pfeifenstopfer; Pfeifenständer; Pfeifentabak; Raucherartikel; Rauchtabak; Schnupftabak; Streichholzhalter; Streichhölzer; Tabak; Tabakaufbewahrungsdosen; Tabakbehälter; Tabakdosen; Tabakersatzstoffe; Tabakpfeifen; Taschenapparate zum Drehen von Zigaretten; Taschenfeuerzeuge, nicht aus Edelmetall; Verdampfer für den persönlichen Gebrauch und elektronische Zigaretten sowie Aromastoffe und Lösungen hierfür; Verdampfer zum Inhalieren für Raucher; Wasserpfeifentabak; Zigaretten, Zigarren, Zigarillos und andere gebrauchsfertige Rauchartikel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ναργιλέδες· Ναργιλέδες· Αρωματικές ουσίες για καπνό· Αρωματικές ύλες, εκτός από αιθέρια έλαια, για καπνό· Σταχτοδοχεία· Σταχτοδοχεία από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Σταχτοδοχεία για καπνιστές από μη πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Υγραντήρες καπνού· Δοχεία και υγρές θήκες για καπνό· Σακουλάκια καπνού· Σακουλάκια για πίπες· Ηλεκτρονικοί ναργιλέδες· Ηλεκτρονικές πίπες· Ηλεκτρονικά τσιγάρα· Θήκες από πολύτιμα μέταλλα για πίπες· Θήκες από μη πολύτιμα μέταλλα για πίπες· Αναπτήρες από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Αναπτήρες για καπνιστές· Περιέκτες αερίου για αναπτήρες· Διάτρητες θήκες για πίπες· Κάπνισμα (Βότανα για -)· Επιστόμια για πίπες· Πίπες καπνίσματος· Πατητήρια για πίπες· Διάτρητες θήκες για πίπες· Καπνός για πίπα· Είδη για καπνιστές· Καπνός για κάπνισμα· Ταμπάκος· Θήκες σπίρτων· Σπίρτα· Καπνός· Μεταλλικά δοχεία αποθήκευσης καπνού· Σακουλάκια καπνού· Βαζάκια για καπνό· Υποκατάστατα καπνού· Πίπες καπνίσματος· Τσιγάρων (Συσκευές τσέπης για περιτύλιξη -)· Αναπτήρες τσέπης, όχι από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Ατομικοί εξατμιστήρες και ηλεκτρονικά τσιγάρα, καθώς και αρώματα και διαλύματα για αυτά· Στοματικός ατμοποιητής για καπνιστές· Καπνός για ναργιλέ· Τσιγάρα, πούρα, πουράκια και άλλα είδη καπνιστού έτοιμα για χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hookahs; Hookahs; Flavourings for tobacco; Flavorings, other than essential oils, for tobacco; Ashtrays; Ashtrays of precious metal; Ashtrays for smokers made of non-precious metals; Humidifiers for tobacco; Tobacco containers and humidors; Tobacco pouches; Bags for pipes; Electronic hookahs; Electronic smoking pipes; Electronic cigarettes; Cases of precious metal for pipes; Cases, not of precious metal for pipes; Lighters of precious metal; Lighters for smokers; Gas containers for cigar lighters; Pipe racks for tobacco pipes; Herbs for smoking; Mouth pieces for pipes; Pipes; Pipe tampers; Pipe racks for tobacco pipes; Pipe tobacco; Smokers' articles; Smoking tobacco; Snuff; Match holders; Matches; Tobacco; Tobacco tins; Tobacco pouches; Tobacco jars; Tobacco substitutes; Pipes; Pocket machines for rolling cigarettes; Pocket lighters not of precious metal; Personal vaporisers and electronic cigarettes, and flavourings and solutions therefor; Oral vaporizers for smokers; Hookah tobacco; Cigarettes, cigars, cigarillos and other ready-for-use smoking articles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pipas de agua; Narguiles (pipa oriental); Aromatizantes de tabaco; Aromatizantes para tabaco, que no sean aceites esenciales; Ceniceros; Ceniceros de metales preciosos; Ceniceros para fumadores hechos de metales no preciosos; Humidificadores para tabaco; Recipientes y humectantes para tabaco; Petacas para tabaco; Petacas para pipas; Narguilés electrónicos; Pipas electrónicas; Cigarrillos electrónicos; Cajas de metales preciosos para pipas; Estuches para pipas de metales preciosos; Encendedores de cigarrillos de metales preciosos; Encendedores para fumadores; Depósito de gas para encendedores; Soportes para pipas; Hierbas para fumar; Boquillas con filtro para pipas; Pipas de fumar; Prensadores para pipas; Soportes para pipas; Tabaco de pipa; Artículos para fumadores; Tabaco para fumar; Rapé [tabaco en polvo]; Fosforeras; Cerillas; Tabaco; Latas para tabaco; Petacas para tabaco; Botes para tabaco; Sucedáneos de tabaco; Pipas de fumar; Aparatos de bolsillo para liar cigarrillos; Encendedores de bolsillo que no sean de metales preciosos; Vaporizadores personales y cigarros electrónicos, aromatizantes y otras soluciones para los mismos; Vaporizadores bucales para fumadores; Tabaco de hookah; Cigarrillos, puros, puritos, y otros artículos para fumadores listos para utilizar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Vesipiibud; Vesipiibud; Tubakamaitsestajad; Tubakamaitseained, v.a eeterlikud õlid; Tuhatoosid; Tuhatoosid (väärismetallist); Tuhatoosid (v.a väärismetallist); Tubakaniisutid; Tubakakarbid ja humidorid; Tubakakotid; Piibukotid; Elektroonilised vesipiibud; Elektroonilised piibud; E-sigaretid; Väärismetallist piibutoosid; Piibukarbid, v.a väärismetallist; Väärismetallist tulemasinad; Välgumihklid; Tulemasinate gaasiballoonid; Piibualused, piiburiiulid; Suitsetamistaimed; Piibuhuulikud; Piibud (suitsetamistarbed); Piibutambitsad; Piibualused, piiburiiulid; Piibutubakas; Suitsetamistarbed; Tubakas suitsetamiseks; Nuusktubakas, ninatubakas; Tikuhoidikud; Tikud; Tubakas; Tubakatoosid; Tubakakotid; Tubakatoosid; Tubaka aseained; Piibud (suitsetamistarbed); Taskus kantavad sigaretikeerajad; Taskuskantavad tulemasinad, v.a väärismetallist; Isiklikud aurustid ja elektroonilised sigaretid, nende maitsestajad ja lahused; Suukaudseks kasutuseks mõeldud aurustid suitsetajatele; Vesipiibutubakas; Sigaretid, sigarid, sigarillod ja muud kasutusvalmis suitsetamistooted.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vesipiiput; Vesipiiput; Aromiaineet tupakalle; Tupakan makuaineet, muut kuin eteeriset öljyt; Tuhkakupit; Jalometalliset tuhkakupit; Muut kuin jalometalliset tuhkakupit tupakoitsijoiden käyttöön; Tupakankostuttimet; Tupakkasäiliöt ja humidorit; Tupakkakukkarot; Piippumassit; Sähköllä toimivat vesipiiput; Sähköpiiput; Sähkösavukkeet; Jalometalliset kotelot piipuille; Ei jalometalliset kotelot piipuille; Jalometalliset savukkeensytyttimet; Tupakansytyttimet; Kaasusäiliöt savukkeensytyttimiin; Piipputelineet; Yrtit (Tupakka -); Suukappaleet piippuihin; Piiput; Piipun sulloimet; Piipputelineet; Piipputupakka; Tupakointivälineet; Poltettava tupakka; Nuuska; Tulitikkutelineet; Tulitikut; Tupakka; Tupakka-astiat; Tupakkakukkarot; Tupakka-astiat; Tupakan korvikkeet; Piiput; Savukkeenkäärimet [taskussa pidettävät]; Ei-jalometalliset savukkeensytyttimet; Henkilökohtaiset höyrystimet ja sähkösavukkeet sekä niiden aromiaineet ja liuokset; Suusumuttimet tupakoitsijoille; Vesipiippuihin tarkoitettu tupakka; Savukkeet, sikarit, pikkusikarit ja muut käyttövalmiit tupakointituotteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Narguilés; Narguilés; Arômes pour tabac; Arômes, autres qu'huiles essentielles, pour tabacs; Cendriers; Cendriers en métaux précieux; Cendriers en métaux non précieux pour fumeurs; Humidificateurs de tabac; Récipients et humidificateurs de tabac; Blagues à tabac; Blagues à tabac pour pipes; Narguilés [hookahs] électroniques; Pipes électroniques; Cigarettes électroniques; Étuis en métaux précieux pour pipes; Étuis à pipes en métaux non précieux; Briquets en métaux précieux; Briquets pour fumeurs; Réservoirs à gaz pour briquets; Râteliers à pipes; Herbes à fumer; Embouts de pipes; Pipes; Bourre-pipe; Râteliers à pipes; Tabac à pipe; Articles pour fumeurs; Tabac à fumer; Tabac à priser; Porte-allumettes; Allumettes; Tabac; Boîtes à tabac en fer; Blagues à tabac; Pots à tabac; Succédanés du tabac; Pipes; Rouleuses à cigarettes de poche; Briquets de poche en métaux non précieux; Vaporisateurs personnels et cigarettes électroniques, et arômes et solutions pour ceux-ci; Vaporisateurs oraux pour fumeurs; Tabac pour narguilé; Cigarettes, cigares, cigarillos, et autres articles pour fumeurs prêts à l'emploi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Nargile; Narghile; Arome za duhan; Arome za duhan, osim eteričnih ulja; Pepeljare; Pepeljare od plemenitog metala; Pepeljare za pušače izrađene od neplemenitih metala; Ovlaživači za duhan; Spremnici za duhan i humidori; Torbice za duhan; Torbice za lule; Elektroničke nargile; Elektroničke lule za pušenje; Elektronske cigarete; Kutije za lule od plemenitih metala; Kutije za lule, od neplemenitih metala; Upaljači od plemenitih metala; Upaljači za pušače; Spremnici z plin za upaljače za cigarete; Stalci za lule; Trave za pušenje; Usnici za lule; Lule; Tamperi za lule; Stalci za lule; Duhan za lule; Predmeti za pušače; Duhan za pušenje; Burmut; Držači šibica; Šibice; Duhan; Limenke za duhan; Torbice za duhan; Posude za duhan; Zamjene za duhan; Lule; Cigarete (džepne naprave za savijanje cigareta); Džepni upaljači, od neplemenitih metala; Isparivači i elektroničke cigarete te arome i otopine za osobnu uprabu; Raspršivači za usta za pušače; Duhan za nargile; Cigarete, cigare, cigariljosi [male cigare] i ostali predmeti za pušače.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vízipipák; Vízipipák; Dohányízesítők; Dohányaromák, az illóolajok kivételével; Hamutartók/-tálcák; Hamutartók nemesfémből; Hamutálak, hamutartók dohányosoknak, nem nemesfémekből; Párásítók dohányhoz; Dohánytartók és szivartartók; Dohányzacskók; Pipazacskók; Elektromos vízipipák; Elektromos pipák; Elektromos cigaretták; Nemesfém pipatokok; Nem nemesfém dobozok pipákhoz; Nemesfém öngyújtók; Öngyújtók dohányosoknak; Gáztartályok öngyújtókhoz; Pipaállványok; Szívható füvek; Szopókák pipákhoz; Pipák; Pipapiszkálók; Pipaállványok; Pipadohány; Dohányzási cikkek; Dohány, pipadohány; Tubák; Gyufatartók; Gyufák; Dohány; Dohánydobozok; Dohányzacskók; Dohánytartó edények; Dohánypótlók; Pipák; Zsebben hordható cigaretta sodró; Nem nemesfém öngyújtók; Elektromos cigaretták és ezekhez való ízesítőszerek/aromák és oldatok; Szájnyálkahártya-nedvesítő dohányosoknak; Vízipipa dohány; Cigaretták, szivarok, szivarkák és egyéb, használatra kész dohányzási cikkek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Narghilé; Narghilè; Aromi per tabacco; Aromi per il tabacco, diversi dagli olii essenziali; Posacenere; Posacenere in metalli preziosi; Posacenere per fumatori in metalli non preziosi; Umidificatori per tabacco; Contenitori ed umidificatori per il tabacco; Borse per tabacco; Astucci per pipe; Narghilè elettronici; Pipe elettroniche; Sigarette elettroniche; Astucci in metallo prezioso per pipe; Astucci per pipe in metalli non preziosi; Accendini in metalli preziosi; Accendini per fumatori; Serbatoi di gas per accendini; Raschiatoi per pipe; Erbe da fumare; Bocchini per pipe; Pipe; Pigini per pipe; Raschiatoi per pipe; Tabacco da pipa; Articoli per fumatori; Tabacco da fumo; Tabacco da naso; Portafiammiferi; Fiammiferi; Tabacco; Scatole di latta per tabacco; Borse per tabacco; Vasi per il tabacco; Succedanei del tabacco; Pipe; Apparecchi tascabili per arrotolare le sigarette; Accendini da tasca non in metalli preziosi; Vaporizzatori personali e sigarette elettroniche, nonché aromi e soluzioni relativi; Vaporizzatori orali per fumatori; Tabacco per narghilè; Sigarette, sigari, cigarillos e altri articoli per fumatori pronti per l'uso.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kaljanai; Kaljanai; Tabako kvapiosios medžiagos; Tabako aromatinės medžiagos (išskyrus eterinius aliejus); Peleninės; Peleninės (brangiųjų metalų); Peleninės (ne brangiųjų metalų); Tabako drėkintuvai; Tabako talpyklos ir dėžutės su drėkintuvais; Tabakinės; Maišeliai pypkėms laikyti; Elektroninės vandens pypkės; Elektroninės pypkės; Elektroninės cigaretės; Pypkių dėklai iš brangiųjų metalų; Pypkių dėžutės [ne brangiųjų metalų]; Žiebtuvėliai [brangiųjų metalų]; Žiebtuvėliai (rūkorių); Dujų balionėliai cigarų žiebtuvėliams; Pypkių stoveliai; Žolės (Rūkomosios -); Pypkių kandikliai; Pypkės; Pypkės grūstuvai; Pypkių stoveliai; Pypkių tabakas; Rūkymo reikmenys; Rūkomasis tabakas; Uostomasis tabakas; Degtukų laikikliai; Degtukai; Tabakas; Tabako dėžutės; Tabakinės; Tabako talpyklos; Tabako pakaitalai; Pypkės; Cigarečių sukimo kišeniniai įtaisai; Kišeniniai žiebtuvėliai [nebrangiųjų metalų]; Asmeniniai inhaliatoriai ir elektroninės cigaretės ir jų aromatinės medžiagos ir tirpalai; Rūkymo inhaliatoriai; Kaljano tabakas; Cigaretės, cigarai, cigarilės ir kiti paruošti naudoti rūkymo reikmenys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ūdenspīpes; Ūdenspīpes; Aromatizētāji tabakai; Tabakas aromatizētāji, kas nav ēteriskās eļļas; Pelnutrauki; Pelnu trauki no dārgmetāliem; Pelnu trauki smēķētājiem, kas nav izgatavoti no dārgmetāliem; Tabakas mitrinātāji; Tabakas izstrādājumu kārbas un humidori; Tabakmaki; Pīpju maki; Elektroniskās ūdens pīpes; Elektroniskās pīpes; Elektroniskās cigaretes; Pīpju futrāļi no cēlmetāliem; Pīpju futrāļi (izņemot no dārgmetāliem); Šķiltavas no dārgmetāliem; Šķiltavas smēķētājiem; Gāzes baloni cigāru šķiltavām; Tabakas pīpju statņi; Smēķējamie augi; Iemutņi pīpēm; Pīpes; Tabakas stampiņa pīpēm; Tabakas pīpju statņi; Pīpju tabaka; Smēķēšanas piederumi; Smēķējamā tabaka; Šņaucamā tabaka; Sērkociņu turētāji; Sērkociņi; Tabaka; Tabakdozes; Tabakmaki; Tabakdozes; Tabakas aizvietotāji; Pīpes; Kabatas ierīces cigarešu tīšanai; Kabatas šķiltavas (izņemot no dārgmetāliem); Personīgie iztvaicētāji un elektroniskās cigaretes, kā arī to aromatizētāji un šķīdumi; Elektroniskās smēķēšanas ierīces; Ūdenspīpju tabaka; Cigaretes, cigāri, cigarillas un citas smēķēšanai gatavas preces.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pajpijiet tal-ilma; Ħuka; Togħmiet għat-tabakk; Ħwawar, minbarra żjut essenzjali, għat-tabakk; Axtrejs; Axtrejs tal-metall prezzjuż; Axtrejs magħmulin minn metalli mhux prezzjużi għal min ipejjep; Umdaturi għat-tabakk; Kontenituri tat-tabakk u tip ta' kaxxi fejn iżżomm it-tabakk umdu; Kaxxetti tat-tabakk; Boroż għall-pipi; Sigaretti elettroniċi; Pipi elettroniċi tat-tipjip; Sigaretti elettroniċi; Kaxxetti tal-metall prezzjuż għall-pipi; Kaxex, mhux tal-metall prezzjuż għall-pipi; Lajters magħmula minn metall prezzjuż; Lajters għal min ipejjep; Kontenituri tal-gass għal lajters tas-sigarri; Trej tal-pipa; Ħwawar għat-tipjip; Biċċiet tal-pipa li tidħol fil-ħalq; Pipi; Plageg tal-pipa; Trej tal-pipa; Tabakk tal-pipi; Oġġetti relatati mat-tipjip; Tabakk għat-tipjip; Tabakk tal-imnieħer; Reċipjenti tas-sulfarini; Sulfarini; Tabakk; Landi tat-tabakk; Kaxxetti tat-tabakk; Ġarar tat-tabakk; Sostituti tat-tabakk; Pipi; Sigaretti (Magni tal-but għall-brim tas- -); Lajters tal-but mhux ta' metall prezzjuż; Vaporizzaturi personali u sigaretti elettroniċi, u togħmiet u soluzzjonijiet għalihom; Apparat ta' evaporazzjoni orali għal min ipejjep; Tabakk tal-hookah; Sigaretti, sigarri, sigarri żgħar u oġġetti oħra tat-tipjip lesti biex jintużaw.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">waterpijpen; Waterpijpen (turks); Tabaksaromaten; Aromaten voor tabak, anders dan etherische oliën; Asbakken; Asbakken van edele metalen; Asbakken voor rokers, gemaakt van onedele metalen; Bevochtigers voor tabak; Containers voor tabak en humidors; Tabakszakken; Pijpzakjes; Elektronische waterpijpen [hookahs]; Elektronische tabakspijpen; Elektronische sigaretten; Kistjes van edele metalen voor pijpen; Kokers, niet van edele metalen voor pijpen; Aanstekers van edele metalen; Aanstekers voor rokers; Gasreservoirs voor aanstekers; Pijpenrekken; Rookkruiden; Mondstukken voor pijpen; Pijpen; Pijpaanstampers; Pijpenrekken; Pijptabak; Artikelen voor rokers; Rooktabak; Snuiftabak; Lucifershouders; Lucifers; Tabak; Tabaksblikken; Tabakszakken; Tabakspotten; Tabakssurrogaten; Pijpen; Sigarettenrollers [zakformaat]; Aanstekers in zakformaat, niet van edele metalen; Persoonlijke verstuivers en elektronische sigaretten, en smaakstoffen en oplossingen daarvoor; Orale verstuivers voor rokers; Tabak voor waterpijpen; Sigaretten, sigaren, cigarillo's en andere kant-en-klare rookartikelen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pompy wodne; Fajki wodne; Aromaty do tytoniu; Środki aromatyzujące do tytoniu, inne niż olejki eteryczne; Popielniczki dla palaczy; Popielniczki z metali szlachetnych; Popielniczki dla palaczy wykonane z metali nieszlachetnych; Nawilżacze do tytoniu; Pojemniki na tytoń i humidory; Woreczki na tytoń; Torebki na fajki; Elektroniczne fajki wodne; Elektroniczne fajki do tytoniu; Papierosy elektroniczne; Etui na fajki wykonane z metali szlachetnych; Etui na fajki nie z metali szlachetnych; Zapalniczki z metali szlachetnych; Zapalniczki dla palaczy; Pojemniczki z gazem do zapalniczek; Fajki (Stojaczki na -); Zioła do palenia; Ustniki do fajek; Fajki; Ubijaki do fajek; Fajki (Stojaczki na -); Tytoń do fajek; Przybory dla palaczy; Tytoń do palenia; Tabaka; Pojemniki na zapałki; Zapałki; Tytoń; Puszki na tytoń; Woreczki na tytoń; Tytoń (Pojemniki na -); Substytuty tytoniu; Fajki; Papierosy (Kieszonkowe przyrządy do skręcania -); Kieszonkowe zapalniczki nie z metali szlachetnych; Waporyzatory osobiste i papierosy elektroniczne oraz aromaty i płyny do nich; Waporyzatory dla palaczy, do stosowania doustnego; Tytoń hookah; Papierosy, cygara, cygaretki i inne gotowe artykuły dla palaczy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cachimbos de água; Cachimbos turcos (narguilés); Aromas para tabaco; Aromas, não sendo óleos essenciais, para tabaco; Cinzeiros; Cinzeiros em metais preciosos; Cinzeiros para fumadores de metais não preciosos; Humidificadores para tabaco; Recipientes para tabaco e caixas humidifcantes para charutos; Bolsas para tabaco; Bolsas para cachimbos; Narguilés eletrónicos; Cachimbos eletrónicos para fumar; Cigarros eletrónicos; Estojos em metais preciosos para cachimbos; Estojos em metais não preciosos para cachimbos; Isqueiros de metais preciosos; Isqueiros para fumadores; Depósitos de gás para isqueiros; Suportes para cachimbos; Ervas para fumar; Boquilhas com filtros para cachimbos; Cachimbos; Calcadores de cachimbos; Suportes para cachimbos; Tabaco de cachimbo; Artigos para fumadores; Tabaco para fumar; Rapé; Fosforeiras; Fósforos; Tabaco; Latas para tabaco; Bolsas para tabaco; Potes para tabaco; Sucedâneos de tabaco; Cachimbos; Máquinas de bolso para enrolar cigarros; Isqueiros de bolso não de metais preciosos; Vaporizadores e cigarros eletrónicos pessoais, e aromas e soluções para os mesmos; Vaporizadores orais para fumadores; Tabaco para cachimbo de água; Cigarros,charutos, cigarrilhas, e outros artigos para fumadores prontos a usar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Narghilele; Narghilele; Arome pentru tutun; Arome, altele decât uleiurile esenţiale, pentru tutun; Scrumiere; Scrumiere din metale preţioase; Scrumiere pentru fumători confecţionate din metale nepreţioase; Umidificatoare pentru tutun; Recipiente şi umidificatori pentru tutun; Punguţe de tutun; Huse pentru pipe; Narghilele electronice; Pipe electronice; Ţigarete electronice; Cutii din metale preţioase pentru pipe; Cutii din metale nepreţioase pentru pipe; Brichete din metale preţioase; Brichete pentru fumători; Doze de gaz pentru brichete; Suporturi pentru pipe de tutun; Plante pentru fumat; Muştiucuri de pipă; Pipe; Butucel de pipe; Suporturi pentru pipe de tutun; Tutun de pipă; Articole pentru fumători; Tutun de fumat; Tutun de prizat; Suporturi pentru chibrituri; Chibrituri; Tutun; Recipiente de tutun; Punguţe de tutun; Recipiente de tutun; Înlocuitori de tutun; Pipe; Rularea ţigaretelor (Dispozitive de buzunar pentru -); Brichete (de buzunar) din metale nepreţioase; Vaporizatoare personale şi ţigarete electronice, şi arome şi soluţii pentru acestea; Vaporizatoare orale pentru fumători; Tutun pentru narghilea; Ţigări, ţigarete, trabucuri şi alte articole pentru fumători gata de utilizare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vodné fajky; Vodné fajky; Aromatické prísady do tabakov; Aromatické prísady do tabaku (okrem esenciálnych olejov); Popolníky; Popolníky zo vzácnych kovov; Popolníky pre fajčiarov nie z drahých kovov; Tabakové humidory (skrinky na zachovanie vlhkosti tabaku); Zásobníky a dózy na tabakové výrobky a humidory; Vrecúška na tabak; Puzdrá na fajky; Elektronické vodné fajky; Elektronické fajky; Elektronické cigarety; Puzdrá z drahých kovov na fajky; Puzdrá na fajky, nie z drahých kovov; Zapaľovače z drahých kovov; Zapaľovače pre fajčiarov; Zásobníky plynu do zapaľovačov; Stojany na fajky; Byliny na fajčenie; Náustky na fajky; Fajky; Fajkové náradie; Stojany na fajky; Fajkový tabak; Potreby pre fajčiarov; Tabak pre fajčiarov; Šnupavý tabak; Držiaky na zápalky; Zápalky; Tabak; Plechové škatuľky na tabak; Vrecúška na tabak; Dózy na tabak; Tabakové náhradky; Fajky; Vreckové strojčeky na šúľanie cigariet; Vreckové zapaľovače, nie z drahých kovov; Osobné vaporizéry a elektronické cigarety, aromatické príchute a roztoky do nich; Ústne vaporizéry pre fajčiarov; Tabak do vodnej fajky; Cigarety, cigary, krátke cigary a iné fajčiarske výrobky pripravené na použitie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Vodne pipe; Vodne pipe za kajenje; Arome za tobak; Arome, razen eteričnih olj, za tobak; Pepelniki; Pepelniki iz plemenitih kovin; Pepelniki za kadilce, narejeni iz nežlahtnih kovin; Vlažilniki za tobak; Posode in vlažilne škatle za tobačne izdelke; Mošnjički za tobak; Etuiji za pipe; Elektronske vodne pipe; Elektronske pipe za kajenje tobaka; Elektronske cigarete; Etuiji za pipe iz plemenitih kovin; Škatle za pipe, ne iz žlahtnih kovin; Vžigalniki iz žlahtnih kovin; Vžigalniki za kadilce; Plinske doze za vžigalnike; Stojala za pipe za kajenje tobaka; Zelišča za kajenje; Ustni nastavki za pipe; Pipe; Tlačilci tobaka za pipo; Stojala za pipe za kajenje tobaka; Tobak za pipo; Proizvodi za kadilce; Tobak za kajenje; Njuhanec (tobak za njuhanje); Podstavki za vžigalice; Vžigalice; Tobak; Doze za tobak; Mošnjički za tobak; Doze za tobak; Nadomestki tobaka; Pipe; Žepni strojček za zvijanje cigaret; Žepni vžigalniki, ne iz žlahtnih kovin; Osebni razprševalci in elektronske cigarete, arome in raztopine zanje; Ustniki z izhlapevanjem za kadilce; Tobak za nargilo; Cigarete, cigare, cigarilosi in drugi proizvodi za kadilce, pripravljeni na uporabo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Vattenpipor; Vattenpipor; Smaktillsatser för tobak; Smaktillsatser för tobak, inte eteriska oljor; Askkoppar; Askfat av ädelmetall; Askkoppar för rökare gjorda av oädla metaller; Befuktare för tobak; Tobaksbehållare och humidorer; Tobakspungar; Pippungar; Elektroniska vattenpipor; Elektroniska pipor; Elektroniska cigaretter; Etuier av ädelmetall för pipor; Askar för pipor, inte av ädelmetall; Cigarettändare, av ädla metaller; Tändare för rökare; Gaspatroner för cigarrtändare; Pipställ; Örter för rökning; Pipmunstycken; Pipor; Piphållare; Pipställ; Piptobak; Artiklar för rökare; Röktobak; Snus; Tändsticksställ; Tändstickor; Tobak; Tobaksaskar; Tobakspungar; Tobaksburkar; Tobaksersättningar; Pipor; Fickcigarrettrullare; Ficktändare, inte av ädelmetall; Personliga förångare och elektroniska cigaretter samt smakämnen och lösningar därtill; Orala förångare för rökare; Tobak för vattenpipor; Cigaretter, cigarrer, cigariller och andra rökartiklar färdiga för användning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Търговия на дребно и едро, включително по интернет и каталожна търговия, с принадлежности за пушачи и техните части и принадлежности, по-специално наргилета, тютюн, тютюн за наргиле, принадлежности за наргиле, маркучи, мундщуци или глави, дрехи, обувки, принадлежности за глава; Осигуряване на онлайн пазар за покупко-продажби на стоки и услуги; Услуги, свързани с продажба на стоки на търг чрез наддаване по интернет; Услуги за онлайн аукциони чрез Интернет; Услуги за търговия на дребно във връзка с принадлежности за употреба на тютюн; Услуги за търговия на дребно във връзка с тютюн; Онлайн реклами; Онлайн реклама на компютърни мрежи и уебсайтове; Предоставяне на пространство на уебсайтове за рекламиране на стоки и услуги; Рекламиране чрез пренос на онлайн публикация за трети лица чрез електронни комуникационни мрежи; Предоставяне на пространство на уебсайтове за рекламиране на стоки и услуги; Онлайн реклама в компютърна мрежа; Разпространение на реклами за други чрез онлайн комуникационна мрежа в интернет; Промотиране, реклама и маркетинг на онлайн уебсайтове; Предоставяне на пространство на уебсайтове за рекламиране на стоки и услуги; Рекламиране, включително онлайн рекламиране в компютърна мрежа.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Maloobchodní a velkoobchodní služby, rovněž prostřednictvím internetu a rovněž prostřednictvím zásilkového obchodu s ohledem na potřeby pro kuřáky a jejich části a součásti, zejména vodní dýmky, tabák, tabák do vodních dýmek, příslušenství pro vodní dýmky, hadice, náústky nebo hlavy, oděvy, obuv, pokrývky hlavy; Provozování online trhu pro kupující a prodejce výrobků a služeb; On-line obchodování, při němž prodejce vystaví výrobky ke dražbě a nabídky se provádí prostřednictvím internetu; Služby online aukcí prostřednictvím internetu; Maloobchodní prodej tabákových předmětů; Maloobchodní prodej tabáku; Reklama online; On-line propagace počítačových sítí a webových stránek; Poskytování prostoru na webových stránkách k reklamě na výrobky a služby; Reklama zasíláním on-line propagace třetím stranám prostřednictvím elektronických komunikačních sítí; Poskytování prostoru na webových stránkách k reklamě na výrobky a služby; Online inzerce v počítačové síti; Šíření reklamy pro třetí osoby prostřednictvím online komunikačních sítí po internetu; Propagace, reklama a marketing online webových stránek; Poskytování prostoru na webových stránkách k reklamě na výrobky a služby; Reklama, včetně online reklamy na počítačové síti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Detail- og engroshandel, også formidlet via internettet og via postordre, med artikler for rygere samt dele og tilbehør hertil, især vandpiber, tobak, vandpibetobak, vandpibetilbehør, slanger, mundstykker eller hoveder, beklædningsgenstande, fodtøj, hovedbeklædning; Tilvejebringelse af en onlinemarkedsplads til købere og sælgere af varer og tjenesteydelser; Onlinehandel hvor sælgere udbyder produkter til bortauktionering, og hvor der bydes via internettet; Online auktionsvirksomhed via internettet; Detailhandel med artikler til brug med tobak; Detailhandel med tobak; Online annoncer og reklamer; Online promovering af computernetværk og websites; Formidling af plads på websites til annoncering af varer og tjenesteydelser; Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed i form af onlinetransmission af reklamer for tredjemand via elektroniske kommunikationsnetværk; Formidling af plads på websites til annoncering af varer og tjenesteydelser; Online-annoncering på et computernetværk; Spredning af reklamer for andre via et onlinekommunikationsnetværk på internettet; Promovering, annonce- og reklamevirksomhed samt markedsføring af websites; Formidling af plads på websites til annoncering af varer og tjenesteydelser; Reklame- og annoncevirksomhed, herunder online reklamevirksomhed på et computernetværk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Einzel- und Großhandelsdienstleistungen auch über das Internet und auch über den Versandhandel in Bezug auf Raucherartikel und deren Teile und Zubehör, insbesondere Wasserpfeifen, Tabak, Wasserpfeifentabak, Wasserpfeifenzubehör, Schläuche, Mundstücke oder Köpfe, Bekleidungsstücke, Schuhwaren, Kopfbedeckungen; Bereitstellen eines Online-Marktplatzes für Käufer und Verkäufer von Waren und Dienstleistungen; Durchführung von online Auktionen, wobei die öffentliche Bekanntgabe der zu versteigernden Artikel durch den Verkäufer und die Abgabe von Angeboten elektronisch über das Internet erfolgt; Durchführung von Online-Auktionen über das Internet; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Artikel zur Verwendung mit Tabak; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Tabak; Online-Werbung; Online-Werbung für Computernetze und Websites; Online-Werbung für Dienstleistungen und Waren auf Websites; Online-Werbung für Dritte über elektronische Kommunikationsnetze; Online-Werbung für Waren und Dienstleistungen auf Websites; Online-Werbung in einem Computernetzwerk; Verbreitung von Werbung für Dritte über ein Online-Kommunikationsnetz im Internet; Verkaufsförderung, Werbung und Marketing durch Online-Websites; Werbung für Waren und Dienstleistungen auf Websites [online]; Werbung, einschließlich Online-Werbung über ein Computernet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, παρεχόμενες επίσης μέσω του Διαδικτύου και διά της πώλησης μέσω ταχυδρομικών παραγγελιών σε σχέση με είδη για καπνιστές και μέρη και εξαρτήματα αυτών, ειδικότερα ναργιλέδες, καπνό, καπνό για ναργιλέδες, εξαρτήματα ναργιλέδων, εύκαμπτους σωλήνες, επιστόμια ή κεφαλές, ενδύματα, υποδήματα, είδη πιλοποιίας· Παροχή χώρων αγορών επί γραμμής για αγοραστές και πωλητές προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών· Εμπορικές υπηρεσίες επί γραμμής στις οποίες ο πωλητής ανακοινώνει τα αντικείμενα προς πώληση και η πλειοδοσία γίνεται μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Επι γραμμής (on line) υπηρεσίες δημοπρασιών μέσω του Διαδικτύου INTERNET· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με είδη για χρήση με καπνό· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με καπνό· Διαφημίσεις επί γραμμής (on line)· On line πρόωθηση ηλεκτρονικών δικτύων και ιστοθέσεων· Παροχή χώρου σε ιστοθέσεις για διαφήμιση προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών· Υπηρεσίες διαφήμισης επί γραμμής για λογαριασμό τρίτων μέσω ηλεκτρονικών δικτύων επικοινωνίας· Παροχή χώρου σε ιστοθέσεις για διαφήμιση προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών· Διαφήμιση on line σε δίκτυο πληροφορικής· Διάδοση διαφημίσεων για λογαριασμό τρίτων μέσω δικτύου επικοινωνίας επί γραμμής στο Διαδίκτυο (INTERNET)· Υπηρεσίες προώθησης, διαφήμισης και μάρκετινγκ ιστοθέσεων επί γραμμής· Παροχή χώρου σε ιστοθέσεις για διαφήμιση προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών· Διαφήμιση, όπου περιλαμβάνεται επί γραμμής (on-line) διαφήμιση μέσω δικτύου πληροφορικής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Retailing and wholesaling, including via the internet and including via mail order relating to smokers requisites and parts and fittings therefor, in particular hookahs, tobacco, tobacco for hookahs, hookah accessories, hoses, mouthpieces or heads, clothing, footwear, headgear; Provision of an on-line marketplace for buyers and sellers of goods and services; On-line trading services in which seller posts products to be auctioned and bidding is done via the Internet; On-line auctioneering services via the Internet; Retail services in relation to articles for use with tobacco; Retail services in relation to tobacco; Online advertisements; On-line promotion of computer networks and websites; Provision of space on web-sites for advertising goods and services; Advertising by transmission of on-line publicity for third parties through electronic communications networks; Provision of space on web-sites for advertising goods and services; On-line advertising on a computer network; Dissemination of advertising for others via an on-line communications network on the internet; Promotion, advertising and marketing of on-line websites; Provision of space on web-sites for advertising goods and services; Advertising, including on-line advertising on a computer network.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de venta minorista y mayorista, incluso a través de Internet y por correspondencia, de artículos de uso conjunto con el tabaco y sus piezas y accesorios, en particular narguiles (pipa oriental), tabaco, tabaco de hookah, accesorios para narguiles, tubos flexibles, piezas bucales o boquillas, prendas de vestir, calzado, artículos de sombrerería; Suministro de espacios de venta en línea para vendedores y compradores de productos y servicios; Servicios de comercio en línea en los cuales el vendedor publica productos para su subasta y donde las pujas se realizan de manera electrónica a través de Internet; Servicios de subastas en línea (online) a través de Internet; Servicios de venta al por menor relacionados con artículos de uso con tabaco; Servicios de venta al por menor de tabaco; Publicidad en línea (online); Promoción en línea de redes informáticas y sitios web; Facilitación de espacios en sitios web para publicidad de productos y/o servicios; Publicidad mediante la transmisión de publicidad en línea para terceros a través de redes electrónicas de comunicaciones; Facilitación de espacios en sitios web para publicidad de productos y/o servicios; Publicidad en línea por una red informática; Divulgación de publicidad para terceros a través de una red de comunicaciones en línea en Internet; Promoción, publicidad y marketing de sitios web en línea; Facilitación de espacios en sitios web para publicidad de productos y/o servicios; Publicidad, incluida la publicidad en línea (online) en redes informáticas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Järgmiste kaupade jae- ja hulgimüügiteenused, ka interneti kaudu ja ka postimüügi kaudu: suitsetamistarbed ja nende osad ja tarvikud, eelkõige vesipiibud, tubakas, vesipiibutubakas, vesipiipude lisatarvikud, voolikud, huulikud või pead, rõivad, jalatsid, peakatted; Veebipõhise müügikeskkonna pakkumine kaupade ja teenuste ostjatele ning müüjatele; Elektroonilised kauplemisteenused, mis seisnevad selles, et müüja paneb kaubad oksjonile välja ja pakkumisi tehakse interneti teel; Interneti vahendusel pakutavad veebioksjoniteenused; Tubakaga kasutatavate toodete jaemüügiteenused; Tubaka jaemüügiteenused; Onlain-reklaam; Arvutivõrkude ja veebilehekülgede võrgureklaam; Kaupade ja teenuste reklaamipinna pakkumine veebisaitidel; Reklaami saatmine kolmandatele isikutele elektrooniliste sidevõrkude kaudu; Kaupade ja teenuste reklaamipinna pakkumine veebisaitidel; Arvutivõrgureklaam; Reklaami levitamise teenus interneti sidevõrkude kaudu; Veebilehekülgede reklaam ja turundus; Kaupade ja teenuste reklaamipinna pakkumine veebisaitidel; Reklaam, sh veebireklaam.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Seuraaviin tuotteisiin liittyvät vähittäis- ja tukkumyyntipalvelut, myös internetin välityksellä ja postimyynnin kautta: tupakointituotteet ja niiden osat ja tarvikkeet, erityisesti vesipiiput, tupakka, vesipiipputupakka, vesipiippujen tarvikkeet, letkut, suukappaleet tai päät, vaatteet, jalkineet, päähineet; Online-markkinapaikan tarjoaminen tavaroiden ja palvelujen ostajille ja myyjille; Online-kauppapalvelut, joiden välityksellä myyjät ilmoittavat huutokaupattavista tavaroista ja joissa tarjoaminen tapahtuu internetin välityksellä; Online-huutokauppapalvelut Internetin välityksellä; Tupakointitarvikkeisiin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut; Tupakkaan liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut; Online-mainokset; Tietokoneverkkojen ja verkkosivujen online-periaatteella tapahtuva myynninedistäminen; Tavaroiden ja palvelujen mainostamiseen tarkoitetun tilan tarjoaminen verkkosivustoilla; Mainonta välittämällä online-mainontaa kolmansille osapuolille elektronisten viestintäverkkojen kautta; Tavaroiden ja palvelujen mainostamiseen tarkoitetun tilan tarjoaminen verkkosivustoilla; Online-mainonta tietoverkoissa; Mainosten levittäminen muiden lukuun online-viestintäverkon välityksellä Internetissä; On-line-verkkosivustojen myynninedistäminen, mainonta ja markkinointi; Tavaroiden ja palvelujen mainostamiseen tarkoitetun tilan tarjoaminen verkkosivustoilla; Mainonta, mukaan lukien online-mainonta tietoverkossa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de vente au détail et en gros, également sur l'internet et également par correspondance d'articles pour fumeurs et leurs pièces et accessoires, en particulier pipes à eau, tabac, tabac pour pipes à eau, accessoires pour pipes à eau, tuyaux, embouchures ou têtes, vêtements, chaussures, articles de chapellerie; Mise à disposition d'espaces de vente en ligne pour acheteurs et vendeurs de produits et services; Services de commerce en ligne où le vendeur présente les articles à vendre aux enchères et où les offres sont faites sur Internet; Services de vente aux enchères en ligne par le biais d'Internet; Services de vente au détail concernant les articles utilisés avec le tabac; Services de vente au détail concernant le tabac; Publicité en ligne; Promotion en ligne de réseaux informatiques et de sites Web; Mise à disposition d'espace sur des sites Web pour la publicité de produits et de services; Services publicitaires par transmission de publicité en ligne pour le compte de tiers via des réseaux de communications électroniques; Mise à disposition d'espace sur des sites Web pour la publicité de produits et de services; Publicité en ligne sur un réseau informatique; Diffusion de publicité pour le compte de tiers via des réseaux de communications en ligne sur Internet; Promotion, publicité et marketing de sites web en ligne; Mise à disposition d'espace sur des sites Web pour la publicité de produits et de services; Publicité, y compris publicité en ligne sur un réseau informatique.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge maloprodaje i veleprodaje, također i putem interneta i prodajom putem pošte, u vezi s proizvodima za pušače te njihovim dijelovima i priborom, posebno nargilama, duhanom, duhanom za nargile, priborom za nargile, crijevima, nastavcima za usta ili glavama, odjevnim predmetima, obućom, pokrivalima za glavu; Pružanje internetskog tržišnog prostora za kupce i prodavatelje proizvoda i usluga; Online trgovačke usluge u kojima prodavatelj objavljuje proizvod za licitaciju koja se odvija putem Interneta; Usluge online dražbovanja putem Interneta; Maloprodajne usluge vezane uz artikle za uporabu s duhanom; Maloprodajne usluge u vezi s duhanom; Online reklame; Online promocija računalnih mreža i web stranica; Pružanje prostora na internetskim stranicama za oglašavanje robe i usluga; Oglašavanje prenošenjem internetskih promidžbenih materijala za treće strane, putem elektroničkih komunikacijskih mreža; Pružanje prostora na internetskim stranicama za oglašavanje robe i usluga; Online oglašavanje na računalnim mrežama; Distribucija reklamnog materijala za druge putem online komunikacijske mreže na Internetu; Promocija, oglašavanje i marketing internetskih stranica; Pružanje prostora na internetskim stranicama za oglašavanje robe i usluga; Oglašavanje, uključujući online oglašavanje na računalnoj mreži.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kis- és nagykereskedelmi szolgáltatások, interneten keresztül is és csomagküldő kereskedelem a következőkre vonatkozóan: dohányáruk és azok alkatrészei és tartozékai, különösen vízipipák, dohány, vízipipa dohány, vízipipa tartozékok, flexibilis csövek, szájrészek vagy fejek, ruházati cikkek, lábbelik, kalapáruk; Online piactér biztosítása áruk és szolgáltatások eladói és vásárlói részére; Online kereskedelmi szolgáltatások, amelyek során az árverezendő termék közzététele és a licitálás is az interneten keresztül történik; Online internetes árverési szolgáltatások; Dohánnyal használt cikkekkel kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Dohánnyal kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Online reklámozás; Számítógépes hálózatok és weboldalak online reklámozása; Termékek és szolgáltatások reklámozására szolgáló felület biztosítása weboldalakon; Elektronikus kommunikációs hálózatokon keresztüli, online reklámozási szolgáltatások; Termékek és szolgáltatások reklámozására szolgáló felület biztosítása weboldalakon; On-line hirdetői tevékenység számítógépes hálózaton; Reklámterjesztési szolgáltatások internetes online kommunikációs hálózaton keresztül; Online weblapok népszerűsítése, reklámozása és marketingje; Termékek és szolgáltatások reklámozására szolgáló felület biztosítása weboldalakon; Reklámozás, hirdetés, beleértve a számítógépes hálózatokon történő online reklámozást.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di vendita al dettaglio e all'ingrosso, anche via Internet e anche tramite vendita per corrispondenza in relazione ad articoli per fumatori e relative parti e accessori, in particolare narghilè, tabacco, tabacco per narghilè, accessori per narghilè, tubi flessibili, boccagli o teste, capi d'abbigliamento, calzature, copricapo; Fornitura su mercato on-line di beni e servizi per acquirenti e venditori; Servizi di compravendita on-line in cui il venditore immette prodotti da vendere e le offerte sono fatte via Internet; Servizi di vendite all'asta on-line tramite Internet; Servizi al dettaglio in relazione ad articoli associati al tabacco; Servizi al dettaglio in relazione al tabacco; Annunci pubblicitari on line; Promozione on-line di reti informatiche e siti web; Fornitura di spazio su siti Internet per la pubblicità di prodotti e servizi; Pubblicità mediante trasmissione di pubblicità on-line per conto terzi tramite reti di comunicazione elettroniche; Fornitura di spazio su siti Internet per la pubblicità di prodotti e servizi; Pubblicità on-line su rete informatica; Diffusione pubblicitaria per conto terzi tramite una rete di comunicazione on-line su Internet; Promozione, pubblicità e marketing di siti web on-line; Fornitura di spazio su siti Internet per la pubblicità di prodotti e servizi; Pubblicità, compresa pubblicità on-line su una rete informatica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Mažmeninės ir didmeninės prekybos paslaugos, taip pat teikiamos internetu ir kaip prekybos paštu paslaugos, susijusios su rūkymo reikmenimis ir jų dalimis bei priedais, ypač kaljanais, tabaku, kaljanų tabaku, kaljanų priedais, vamzdeliais, kandikliais ar galvutėmis, drabužiais, avalyne, galvos apdangalais; Interneto prekyviečių teikimas prekių ir paslaugų pardavėjams bei pirkėjams; Internetinės prekybos paslaugos, kai pardavėjas paskelbia aukcione parduodamų prekių sąrašą ir kainų pasiūlymai už prekes atliekami internetu; Tiesioginių aukcionų paslaugos internetu; Mažmeninė prekyba rūkymo reikmenimis; Mažmeninė prekyba tabaku; Skelbimai internetu; Internetinis kompiuterių tinklo ir svetainių reklamavimas; Prekių ir paslaugų reklamos erdvės parūpinimas interneto svetainėse; Viešas reklamos perdavimas trečiosioms šalims tiesioginiu ryšiu per elektroninių ryšių tinklus; Prekių ir paslaugų reklamos erdvės parūpinimas interneto svetainėse; Viešasis elektroninis reklamavimas kompiuterių tinkle; Reklamos platinimas tiesioginiu ryšių tinklu internete (kitiems); Internetinių svetainių palaikymas, reklamavimas ir rinkodara; Prekių ir paslaugų reklamos erdvės parūpinimas interneto svetainėse; Reklama, įskaitant tiesioginę reklamą kompiuterių tinkle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mazumtirdzniecības un vairumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, arī izmantojot internetu un izmantojot sūtījumtirdzniecību saistībā ar smēķēšanas precēm un to daļām un piederumiem, jo īpaši ūdenspīpes, tabaka, ūdens pīpes tabaka, ūdenspīpju piederumi, lokanas caurules, iemuši vai galviņas, apģērbi, apavi, galvassegas; Tiešsaistes tirgus nodrošināšana preču un pakalpojumu pārdevējiem un pircējiem; Tiešsaistes tirdzniecības pakalpojumi, kad pārdevējs piedāvā produktus izsolei un vairāksolīšana notiek internetā; Tiešsaistes izsoļu pakalpojumi, izmantojot internetu; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar smēķēšanas piederumiem; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar tabaku; Reklāma tiešsaistē; Datortīklu un mājaslapu veicināšanas pakalpojumi tiešsaistē; Preču un pakalpojumu reklāmas platības nodrošināšana tīmekļa vietnēs; Reklamēšana, pārraidot tiešsaistē trešo personu reklāmu ar elektronisko komunikāciju tīklu palīdzību; Preču un pakalpojumu reklāmas platības nodrošināšana tīmekļa vietnēs; Reklāma tiešsaistes režīmā, izmantojot datortīklus; Trešo personu reklāmas izplatīšana ar tiešsaistes sakaru tīklu starpniecību internetā; Tiešsaistes tīmekļa vietņu sekmēšana, reklāma un mārketings; Preču un pakalpojumu reklāmas platības nodrošināšana tīmekļa vietnēs; Reklāma, ieskaitot reklāmu tiešsaistē datoru tīklā.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Bejgħ bl-imnut u bl-ingrossa, anki minn fuq l-internet u inkluż bejgħ bl-imnut permezz ta' ordni bil-posta b'rabta ma' oġġetti tat-tipjip u l-partijiet u aċċessorji tagħhom, speċjalment ħukas, tabakk, tabakk tal-ħukas, aċċessorji tal-ħukas, pajpijiet flessibbli, bċejjeċ tal-ħalq jew irjus, oġġetti tal-ilbies, xedd is-saqajn, xedd ir-ras; Forniment ta' suq onlajn għal xerrejja u bejjiegħa ta' prodotti u servizzi; Servizzi ta' kummerċ online li fihom il-bejjiegħ iqiegħed prodotti għall-irkant u t-tfigħ tal-offerti jsir permezz tal-Internet; Servizzi ta' rkantijiet onlajn permezz tal-Internet; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut fir-rigward ta' oġġetti maħsuba biex jintużaw mat-tabakk; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut fir-rigward tat-tabakk; Reklamar onlajn; Promozzjoni onlajn fuq netwerk u websajts tal-kompjuters; Il-provvista ta' spazju fuq websajts għar-reklamar ta' oġġetti u servizzi; Reklamar permezz tat-trasmissjoni ta' pubbliċità online għal terzi persuni permezz ta' netwerks tal-komunikazzjonijiet elettroniċi; Il-provvista ta' spazju fuq websajts għar-reklamar ta' oġġetti u servizzi; Reklamar onlajn fuq netwerk tal-kompjuters; It-tixrid ta' reklami għal oħrajn permezz ta' netwerk tal-komunikazzjonijiet onlajn fuq l-Internet; Il-promozzjoni, ir-reklamar u l-kummerċjalizzazzjoni ta' websajts online; Il-provvista ta' spazju fuq websajts għar-reklamar ta' oġġetti u servizzi; Reklamar, inklużi reklamar online fuq netwerk tal-kompjuters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Detail- en groothandelsdiensten, ook via internet en ook via verzendhandel, met betrekking tot artikelen voor rokers en onderdelen en accessoires daarvoor, met name waterpijpen, tabak, tabak voor waterpijpen, accessoires voor waterpijpen, slangen, mondstukken of koppen, kledingstukken, schoeisel, hoofddeksels; Ter beschikking stellen van online verkoopplaats voor kopers en verkopers van goederen en diensten; Handelsdiensten (online) waarbij verkopers producten ter veiling aanbieden en waarbij het bieden elektronisch via het internet geschiedt; Onlineveilingdiensten via het internet; Detailhandelsdiensten op het gebied van artikelen te gebruiken voor het consumeren van tabak; Detailhandelsdiensten op het gebied van tabak; Onlinereclame; Promotie, online ten behoeve van computernetwerken en websites; Verschaffen van ruimte op websites voor het maken van reclame voor goederen en diensten; Reclame via verzending van online reclame voor derden via elektronische communicatienetwerken; Verschaffen van ruimte op websites voor het maken van reclame voor goederen en diensten; Reclame [on-line] op een computernetwerk; Verspreiding van reclame voor derden via een online communicatienetwerk op internet; Promotie, reclame en marketing van online websites; Verschaffen van ruimte op websites voor het maken van reclame voor goederen en diensten; Reclame, waaronder onlinereclame op een computernetwerk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi detaliczne i hurtowe, w tym przez internet, a także sprzedaż wysyłkową, artykułów do palenia oraz ich części i akcesoriów, w szczególności fajki wodnej, tytoniu, tabaki do fajki wodnej, akcesoriów do fajki wodnej, rurek, ustników lub główek, odzieży, obuwia, nakryć głowy; Zapewnianie platformy internetowej dla nabywców i sprzedawców towarów i usług; Usługi handlowe online, w ramach których sprzedający wystawiają produkty na aukcję, a licytacja odbywa są za pośrednictwem Internetu; Usługi aukcyjne online za pośrednictwem Internetu; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej w związku z artykułami do stosowania z tytoniem; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej w związku z tytoniem; Reklamy online; Promocja online sieci komputerowych i stron internetowych; Udostępnianie miejsca na stronach internetowych na reklamę towarów i usług; Reklama poprzez przesyłanie materiałów reklamowych online dla osób trzecich poprzez elektroniczne sieci komunikacyjne; Udostępnianie miejsca na stronach internetowych na reklamę towarów i usług; Reklama online za pośrednictwem sieci komputerowej; Rozpowszechnianie reklam dla osób trzecich za pomocą sieci komunikacyjnej online w Internecie; Promocja, reklama i marketing stron internetowych on-line; Udostępnianie miejsca na stronach internetowych na reklamę towarów i usług; Usługi reklamowe, w tym reklama on-line w sieci komputerowej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de comércio retalhista e grossista, prestados inclusive via Internet e por encomendas, relacionados com artigos para fumadores e respetivas peças e acessórios, em especial cachimbos de água, tabaco, tabaco para narguilés, acessórios para cachimbos de água, mangueiras flexíveis, proteções para a boca ou cabeças, vestuário, calçado, chapelaria; Disponibilização de um espaço de mercado on-line para compradores e vendedores de produtos e serviços; Serviços de transações comerciais on-line em que o vendedor coloca os produtos a serem leiloados e a licitação é feita através da Internet; Serviços de leilões online através da internet; Serviços retalhistas relacionados com artigos para consumo de tabaco; Serviços retalhistas relacionados com tabaco; Anúncios publicitários online; Promoção on-line de redes informáticas e websites; Fornecimento de espaço em websites para publicidade de produtos e serviços; Publicidade por transmissão de anúncios online para terceiros através de redes de comunicações eletrónicas; Fornecimento de espaço em websites para publicidade de produtos e serviços; Publicidade on-line numa rede informática; Difusão de publicidade para terceiros através de uma rede de comunicações on-line na internet; Promoção, publicidade e marketing de páginas online; Fornecimento de espaço em websites para publicidade de produtos e serviços; Publicidade, incluindo publicidade online em redes informáticas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul și cu ridicata, inclusiv prin internet și prin corespondență, în legătură cu articole pentru fumători și piese și accesorii pentru acestea, în special narghilele, tutun, tutun pentru narghilea, accesorii pentru narghilele, furtunuri, muștiucuri sau capete, îmbrăcăminte, încălțăminte, articole care servesc la acoperirea capului; Furnizarea unei pieţe online pentru cumpărătorii şi vânzătorii de bunuri şi servicii; Servicii comerciale online în cadrul cărora vânzătorul publică produsele care urmează a fi licitate, iar licitaţia are loc pe Internet; Servicii de vânzare prin licitaţii online prin internet; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul în legătură cu articole utilizate împreună cu tutunul; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul în legătură cu tutun; Publicitate online; Promovare online de reţele informatizate şi pagini web; Furnizare de spaţiu pe pagini web pentru promovarea de produse şi servicii; Publicitate prin transmisia de publicitate online pentru terţi prin reţele de comunicaţii electronice; Furnizare de spaţiu pe pagini web pentru promovarea de produse şi servicii; Publicitate on-line într-o reţea informatizată; Difuzare de materiale publicitare pentru terţi, printr-o reţea de comunicaţii on-line pe Internet; Promovare, publicitate şi marketing pentru pagini web online; Furnizare de spaţiu pe pagini web pentru promovarea de produse şi servicii; Publicitate, inclusiv publicitatea online în reţele informatice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Maloobchodné a veľkoobchodné služby, aj cez internet a aj cez zásielkové obchodné služby so zameraním na potreby pre fajčiarov a ich časti a doplnky, predovšetkým vodné fajky, tabak, tabak pre vodné fajky, doplnky k vodným fajkám, hadice, špičky na cigarety alebo hlavy, odevy, obuv, pokrývky hlavy; Online poskytovanie obchodného priestoru pre nákupcov a predajcov tovarov a služieb; Organizovanie a vedenie dražobného predaja prostredníctvom internetu; Aukčné služby (online) prostredníctvom internetu; Maloobchodné služby so zameraním na výrobky používané s tabakom; Maloobchodné služby s tabakom; On line reklama; On-line propagácia na počítačových sieťach a webových stránkach; Poskytovanie priestoru na internetových stránkach na reklamu tovarov a služieb; Reklamné služby pre tretie osoby prenosom on-line propagácie prostredníctvom elektronických komunikačných sietí; Poskytovanie priestoru na internetových stránkach na reklamu tovarov a služieb; Online reklama na počítačovej komunikačnej sieti; Rozširovanie reklamy pre tretie osoby prostredníctvom on line komunikačných sietí na internete; Propagovanie, reklama a marketing on-line webových stránok; Poskytovanie priestoru na internetových stránkach na reklamu tovarov a služieb; Reklama vrátane on-line reklamy na počítačovej sieti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Maloprodajne in veleprodajne storitve, tudi prek interneta in tudi prek prodaje po pošti, v zvezi s proizvodi za kadilce in njihovimi deli in dodatki, zlasti vodnimi pipami, tobakom, tobakom za vodne pipe, dodatki za vodne pipe, gibkimi cevmi, ustniki ali glavami, oblačili, obutvijo, pokrivali; Zagotavljanje spletnega trga za kupce in prodajalce blaga in storitev; Storitve spletnega trgovanja, pri katerih prodajalec objavi izdelke za dražbo, izklicevanje pa se opravlja preko interneta; Storitve spletne prodaje na dražbi preko interneta; Storitve prodaje na drobno v zvezi z izdelki za uporabo s tobakom; Storitve prodaje na drobno v zvezi s tobakom; Spletni oglasi; Spletna promocija računalniških mrež in internetnih strani; Zagotavljanje prostora na spletnih straneh za oglaševanje blaga in storitev; Oglaševanje s prenašanjem spletnih reklam za tretje osebe preko elektronskih komunikacijskih omrežij; Zagotavljanje prostora na spletnih straneh za oglaševanje blaga in storitev; Spletno oglaševanje preko računalniškega omrežja; Razširjanje oglasov za druge po spletnem komunikacijskem omrežju na internetu; Promocija, oglaševanje in trženje internetnih spletnih strani; Zagotavljanje prostora na spletnih straneh za oglaševanje blaga in storitev; Oglaševanje, vključno s spletnim oglaševanjem prek računalniškega omrežja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Detalj- och grossisthandelstjänster, även via Internet och även via postorder med avseende på artiklar för rökare och delar därav och tillbehör, speciellt vattenpipor, tobak, tobak för vattenpipor, tillbehör för vattenpipor, slangar, munstycken eller huvuden, kläder, fotbeklädnader, huvudbonader; Tillhandahållande av en marknadsplats on-line för köpare och säljare av varor och tjänster; Direktanslutna handelstjänster, där säljare lägger ut föremål som skall auktioneras ut och där budgivningen sker via Internet; Onlineauktioner via internet; Återförsäljartjänster avseende artiklar för användning med tobak; Återförsäljartjänster avseende tobak; Onlineannonsering; Marknadsföring via direktanslutning till datornätverk och webbplatser; Upplåtande av utrymme på webbplatser för reklam av varor och tjänster; Annonsering genom överföring av reklam online för tredje part på elektroniskt kommunikationsnät; Upplåtande av utrymme på webbplatser för reklam av varor och tjänster; Annonsering on-line via datanätverk; Spridning av reklam för andra via ett direktanslutet kommunikationsnät på Internet; Säljfrämjande tjänster, annonsering och marknadsföring via webbplatser online; Upplåtande av utrymme på webbplatser för reklam av varor och tjänster; Reklam, inklusive reklam online via datornätverk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>43</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за продоволствие и настаняване на гости; Обслужване на барчета; Барове; Барове с наргилета; Обслужване на бар; Услуги за коктейлни салони; Self-service cafeterias; Барчета; Услуги за коктейлни салони; Малки ресторанти, в които се сервира кафе, чай и закуски; Вино барове; Услуги на ресторанти на самообслужване; Ресторанти на самообслужване; Кетъринг (приготвяне и доставка на храни и напитки); Услуги за коктейлни салони; Услуги за коктейлни салони; Малки ресторанти, в които се сервира кафе, чай и закуски; Услуги за изхранване и настаняване на гости в локали, предлагащи мобилен кетъринг; Ресторанти; Ресторанти за бързо хранене [снек барове] (обслужване на гости в -); Клубни услуги (за предоставяне на храна и напитки); Услуги, предоставяни от нощни клубове [предоставяне на храна]; Малки ресторанти, в които се сервира кафе, чай и закуски.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby pro stravování a ubytování hostů; Bary (služby-); Bary; Služby barů s vodními dýmkami; Bary (Služby -); Služby denních barů; Samoobslužné restaurace; Kavárny; Služby denních barů; Čajovny; Služby vináren; Samoobslužné restaurace; Služby zajišťující stravování a nápoje hostů v jídelnách; Zajišťování hromadného stravování (catering); Služby denních barů; Služby denních barů; Čajovny; Služby zajišťující stravování a nápoje a dočasné ubytování hostů v provozovnách s nabídkou mobilního cateringu; Restaurace (stravování hostů v restauracích); Péče o hosty v restauracích s rychlým občerstvením [snackbary]; Klubové služby (poskytování jídla a nápojů); Služby nočního klubu (poskytování jídel); Čajovny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Restaurationsvirksomhed og udbringning af mad og drikke, værelsesudlejning; Barer; Barer; Vandpibebarer; Tjenester ydet af barer; Cocktailbarvirksomhed; Cafeterier med selvbetjening; Cafévirksomhed; Cocktailbarvirksomhed; Tesaloner; Vinbarer; Cafeteriavirksomhed; Cafeterier; Catering; Cocktailbarvirksomhed; Cocktailbarvirksomhed; Tesaloner; Forplejning og indkvartering af gæster i etablissementer med tilbud om mobil catering; Restaurationsvirksomhed; Forplejning af gæster på snackbarer; Klubtjenester til tilvejebringelse af mad og drikke; Natklubber [tilvejebringelse af mad]; Tesaloner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Dienstleistungen zur Verpflegung und Beherbergung von Gästen; Bar (Betrieb einer -); Bars; Betrieb von Shisha-Bars; Betrieb einer Bar; Betrieb einer Cocktailbar; Betrieb von Cafeterien mit Selbstbedienung; Betrieb von Cafés mit kleiner Restauration; Betrieb von Cocktailbars; Betrieb von Teestuben; Betrieb von Weinbars; Cafeteriabetrieb; Cafeterias (Verpflegung von Gästen in -); Catering; Dienstleistungen einer Cocktailbar; Dienstleistungen von Cocktailbars; Dienstleistungen von Teestuben; Dienstleistungen zur Verpflegung und Beherbergung von Gästen in Lokalen mit Angebot von Mobiles Catering; Restaurants (Verpflegung von Gästen in -); Schnellimbissrestaurants [Snackbars] (Verpflegung von Gästen in -); Verpflegung von Gästen in Clubs; Verpflegung von Gästen in Nachtklubs; Verpflegung von Gästen in Teestube.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες εστίαση (παροχή διατροφής) και προσωρινής κατάλυσης· Υπηρεσίες μπαρ· Μπαρ· Μπαρ καπνίσματος ναργιλέ· Μπαρ (Υπηρεσίες -)· Υπηρεσίες κοκτέιλ μπαρ· Καφετέριες αυτοεξυπηρέτησης· Καφετέριες· Υπηρεσίες κοκτέιλ μπαρ· Τσαγερίες· Μπαρ που σερβίρουν κυρίως κρασί· Υπηρεσίες καφετέριας· (υπηρεσίες παροχής διατροφής και ποτών σε) καφετέριες· Τροφοδοσία· Υπηρεσίες κοκτέιλ μπαρ· Υπηρεσίες κοκτέιλ μπαρ· Τσαγερίες· Υπηρεσίες παροχής διατροφής και ποτών και υπηρεσίες προσωρινής κατάλυσης σε καταστήματα που παρέχουν υπηρεσίες τροφοδοσίας από κινητές μονάδες· Εστίαση (παροχή διατροφής)· Εστίαση (παροχή διατροφής και ποτών) σε εστιατόρια γρήγορης εξυπηρέτησης (Snackbars)· Υπηρεσίες λεσχών εστίασης (παροχή φαγητού και ποτού)· Υπηρεσίες νυχτερινών κέντρων [παροχή τροφίμων]· Τσαγερίες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Providing of food and drink and temporary accommodation; bar services; Bars; Hookah bar services; Bar services; Cocktail lounge services; Self-service cafeterias; Café services; Cocktail lounge services; Tea rooms; Wine bar services; Cafeteria services; Cafeterias; Catering for the provision of food and beverages; Cocktail lounge services; Cocktail lounge services; Tea rooms; Services for providing food and drink and accommodation in pubs with the offer of mobile catering; Restaurants; Snack-bars; Club services for the provision of food and drink; Night club services [provision of food]; Tea rooms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de restauración (alimentación) y hospedaje temporal; Servicios de bar; Bares; Servicios de bar con pipas de agua; Servicios de bar; Cocktail bar; Cafetería de autoservicio; Servicios de cafés; Cocktail bar; Salones de té; Servicios de bares de vinos; Servicios de cafetería; Restauración de clientes, en cafeterías; Catering para el suministro de comidas y bebidas; Cocktail bar; Cocktail bar; Salones de té; Servicios de restauración y alojamiento de huéspedes en locales con oferta de catering móvil; Restaurantes; Restauración (alimentación) en restaurantes de servicio rápido y permanente; Servicios de clubes (para el suministro de alimentos y bebidas); Suministro de comida en clubes nocturnos; Salones de té.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Söökide ja jookide ning majutuse pakkumine; Baariteenused; Baarid; Vesipiibubaari teenused; Baariteenused; Kokteilibaaride teenused; Iseteeninduskohvikud; Kohvikuteenused; Kokteilibaaride teenused; Teemajad; Veinibaariteenused; Kohvikuteenused; Selvekohvikud (külaliste toitlustamine); Toitlustusteenindus; Kokteilibaaride teenused; Kokteilibaaride teenused; Teemajad; Külaliste toitlustamine ja tähtajaline majutamine lokaalides mobiilse toitlustuse pakkumisega; Restoranid (külaliste toitlustamine nendes); Kiirtoidurestoranid (einelauad) (külaliste eest hoolitsemiseks); Klubide toitlustamisteenused; Ööklubiteenused [toitlustamine]; Teemajad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ravitsemis- ja tilapäismajoituspalvelut; Baaripalvelut; Baarit; Vesipiippubaaripalvelut; Baaripalvelut; Cocktailbaaripalvelut; Itsepalvelukahviot; Kahviot; Cocktailbaaripalvelut; Teehuoneet; Viinibaaripalvelut; Kahvilapalvelut; Ravitseminen kahvioissa; Pitopalvelu; Cocktailbaaripalvelut; Cocktailbaaripalvelut; Teehuoneet; Sellainen ravitseminen ja tilapäismajoitus huoneistoissa, joihin sisältyy mobiili ateriapalvelu; Ruokailupalvelut; Ravitseminen pikaruokaloissa; Ruoan ja juomien tarjoamiseen liittyvät klubipalvelut; Yökerhopalvelut (ruokapalvelut); Teehuoneet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de restauration et hébergement temporaire; Services de bars; Bars; Services de bars à narguilé; Services de bars; Bar à cocktails; Cafétérias libre-service; Services de cafés; Bar à cocktails; Salons de thé; Bars à vins; Services de cafétérias; Restauration d'hôtes dans des cafétérias; Services de traiteurs pour l'approvisionnement en nourriture et boissons; Bar à cocktails; Bar à cocktails; Salons de thé; Services de restauration et d'hébergement d'hôtes dans des locaux offrant des services de restauration mobile; Services de restauration; Restaurants à service rapide et permanent (snack-bars); Services de restauration [alimentation] et de bars proposés dans des clubs; Services de boîtes de nuit [fourniture de nourriture]; Salons de thé.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge serviranja hrane i pića, privremenog smještaja; Bar (rad jednog -); Usluge barova; Nargila barovi; Usluge barova; Usluge koktel bara; Samoposlužne zalogajnice; Kafići; Usluge koktel bara; Čajane [poslužionice čaja]; Usluge vinoteke [posluživanje vina]; Usluge kafeterija; Kafeterije (posluživanje gostiju u -); Catering; Usluge koktel bara; Usluge koktel bara; Čajane [poslužionice čaja]; Usluge posluživanja hrane i pića gostima te smještaja gostiju u lokalima s ponudom mobilnog cateringa; Restorani; Restorani brze hrane [barovi brze hrane] (posluživanje gostiju u -); Usluge kluba za ponudu hrane i pića; Usluge noćnog kluba [posluživanje hrane]; Čajane [poslužionice čaja].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vendégek ellátása és elszállásolása; Bárban nyújtott szolgáltatások; Bárok; Vízipipás bárok szolgáltatásai; Bár szolgáltatások; Koktélbárok szolgáltatásai; Önkiszolgáló étkezdék szolgáltatásai; Kávéházak; Koktélbárok szolgáltatásai; Teaházak; Borozói szolgáltatások; Önkiszolgáló éttermi szolgáltatások; Étkezdei (vendéglátás); Vendéglátás; Koktélbárok szolgáltatásai; Koktélbárok szolgáltatásai; Teaházak; Vendégek ellátására és elszállásolására irányuló szolgáltatások mobil vendéglátást kínáló éttermekben; Éttermek (vendégek ellátása éttermekben); Gyorséttermek [snackbárok] (vendéglátás azokban); Klub szolgáltatások étel és ital biztosítására; Night club szolgáltatások [ételszolgáltatás]; Teaházak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi per la ristorazione e alloggiamento di ospiti; Servizi di bar; Bar; Fumerie di narghilè; Servizi di bar; Servizi di bar specializzati in cocktail; Caffetterie self-service; Servizi di bar-ristoranti; Servizi di bar specializzati in cocktail; Sale da tè; Servizi di enoteche; Servizi di tavole calde; Ristorazione in caffetterie; Catering; Servizi di bar specializzati in cocktail; Servizi di bar specializzati in cocktail; Sale da tè; Servizi di ristorazione e alloggio in locali che offrono servizi di ristorazione mobile; Ristoranti; Snack-bar; Servizi di ristorazione forniti da club; Servizi per night club [ristorazione]; Sale da tè.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Maisto ir gėrimų tiekimas bei laikinas apgyvendinimas; Barų paslaugos; Barai; Kaljanų barų paslaugos; Barų paslaugos; Kokteilių baro paslaugos; Savitarnos kavos barai; Kavinės; Kokteilių baro paslaugos; Arbatinės; Vyno barai; Kavinių paslaugos; Lankytojų aptarnavimo kavos baruose paslaugos; Viešojo maitinimo paslaugos; Kokteilių baro paslaugos; Kokteilių baro paslaugos; Arbatinės; Svečių maitinimas ir apgyvendinimas įstaigose, kuriose teikiamos išvažiuojamojo maitinimo paslaugos; Restoranų paslaugos (svečių maitinimas restoranuose); Svečių maitinimas užkandinėse (užkandinės); Klubų aprūpinimas maistu ir gėrimais; Naktinių klubų aprūpinimas maistu; Arbatinės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Viesu ēdināšana un izmitināšana; Bāru pakalpojumi; Bāru pakalpojumi; Ūdenspīpju bāru pakalpojumi; Bāru pakalpojumi; Kokteiļu bāru pakalpojumi; Pašapkalpošanās kafejnīcas; Kafejnīcu pakalpojumi; Kokteiļu bāru pakalpojumi; Tējnīcas; Vīna bāru pakalpojumi; Kafetēriju pakalpojumi; Kafetērijas (viesu apkalpošana tajās); Ēdienu sagatavošana un piegāde pēc pasūtījuma; Kokteiļu bāru pakalpojumi; Kokteiļu bāru pakalpojumi; Tējnīcas; Pakalpojumi saistībā ar viesu aprūpi un izmitināšanu ēdnīcās ar izbraukuma ēdināšanas piedāvājumu; Restorāni (Viesu ēdināšana); Ātrās ēšanas restorāni [uzkodu bāri] (viesu apkalpošana tajos); Klubu pakalpojumi pārtikas un dzērienu nodrošināšanai; Naktsklubu pakalpojumi (pārtikas nodrošināšana); Tējnīcas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Il-provvista ta' ikel u xorb u akkomodazzjoni temporanja; Servizzi ta' bar; Barijiet; Servizzi ta' bar bil-Hookah (normalment jissejħu bars tax-shisha); Servizzi ta' barijiet; Servizzi ta' salotti bil-barijiet [cocktail lounges]; Kafetteriji selfservis; Kafetteriji; Servizzi ta' salotti bil-barijiet [cocktail lounges]; Ħwienet tat-tè; Servizzi ta' barijiet tal-inbid; Servizzi ta' kafetterija; (kejtering ta' klijenti f') kafetteriji; Catering; Servizzi ta' salotti bil-barijiet [cocktail lounges]; Servizzi ta' salotti bil-barijiet [cocktail lounges]; Ħwienet tat-tè; Servizzi għall-kejtering u akkomodazzjoni temporanja għall-klijenti f'pabbs b'offerta ta' kejtering mobbli; (Catering tal-mistednin f') restoranti; Barijiet li jagħmlu ikel ta' malajr [barijiet ta' l-ikel ta' malajr ) (il-forniment tal-klijenti f'); Servizzi ta' każin għall-provvista tal-ikel u x-xorb; Servizzi ta' klabbs ta' bil-lejl [Il-provvista ta' ikel]; Ħwienet tat-tè.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diensten op het gebied van restauratie (het verstrekken van voedsel en dranken) en tijdelijke huisvesting; Bars; Bars; Shishalounge-diensten; Bardiensten; Cocktailbardiensten; Zelfbedieningscafetaria's; Diensten van café-restaurants; Cocktailbardiensten; Theesalons (Diensten van -); Wijnbars; Cafetariadiensten; Cafetaria's; Catering; Cocktailbardiensten; Cocktailbardiensten; Theesalons (Diensten van -); Restauratie (het verstrekken van voedsel en dranken) en tijdelijke huisvesting in lokalen met mobiel cateringaanbod; Restauratie (maaltijden); Snackbars; Clubs voor de verstrekking van voedsel en dranken (Diensten van -); Nachtclubs [het verstrekken van voedsel]; Theesalons (Diensten van -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Aprowizacja w żywność i napoje oraz zapewnianie zakwaterowania na pobyt czasowy; Barowe (usługi ); Bary; Usługi barów z fajkami wodnymi; Usługi barowe; Usługi koktajlbarów; Kafeterie samoobsługowe; Kafeterie [bufety]; Usługi koktajlbarów; Herbaciarnie; Winiarnie; Usługi w zakresie kafeterii; Żywienie gości w kafeteriach; Obsługa gastronomiczna z własnym zapleczem, produktami i transportem; Usługi koktajlbarów; Usługi koktajlbarów; Herbaciarnie; Usługi gastronomiczne i noclegowe dla gości w lokalach oferujących catering mobilny; Restauracje (wyżywienie gości w); Bary szybkiej obsługi [bary przekąskowe] (wyżywienie gości w); Usługi klubów w zakresie dostarczania żywności i napojów; Usługi klubów nocnych [zaopatrzenie w żywność]; Herbaciarnie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de restauração (alimentação) e alojamento temporário; Serviços de bar; Bares; Serviços de bar de cachimbo turco (narguilé); Serviços de bar; Serviços de bar de cocktails; Cafetarias de self-service; Cafés; Serviços de bar de cocktails; Salões de chá; Serviços de bar de vinhos; Serviços de cafetaria; Cafetarias (serviços de restauração em -); Catering; Serviços de bar de cocktails; Serviços de bar de cocktails; Salões de chá; Serviços de restauração (alimentação) e alojamento temporário, em locais com oferta de catering móvel; Restaurantes (alimentação); Snack-bars (serviços de restauração em -); Serviços de clubes para o fornecimento de alimentação e de bebidas; Serviços de clube noturno, incluindo o fornecimento de refeições; Salões de chá.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de pensiune si servicii de cazare; Servicii bar; Baruri; Servicii de baruri cu narghilea; Servicii ale barurilor; Servicii specifice barurilor de cocteiluri; Cofetarii cu autoservire; Bufete cu autoservire; Servicii specifice barurilor de cocteiluri; Ceainării; Bodegi de vinuri; Servicii de restaurant cu autoservire; Cofetarii; Catering; Servicii specifice barurilor de cocteiluri; Servicii specifice barurilor de cocteiluri; Ceainării; Servicii de alimentație publică și servicii de cazare temporară în localuri cu ofertă de catering mobil; Restaurante; Restaurante destinate prepararii mancarurilor rapide [Snack - baruri] (asigurarea mesei turistilor in astfel de spatii); Servicii de club pentru furnizare de mâncare şi băuturi; Servicii prestate de cluburi de noapte [furnizare de produse alimentare]; Ceainării.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Hoteliérske a gastronomické služby; Barové služby; Bary; Služby barov s vodnými fajkami; Bary (služby); Služby kokteilových barov; Samoobslužné kaviarne; Kaviarne; Služby kokteilových barov; Čajovne; Služby vinární; Služby samoobslužných jedální; Stravovacie služby pre hostí v kafetériách; Dodávanie hotových jedál a nápojov na objednávku (ketering); Služby kokteilových barov; Služby kokteilových barov; Čajovne; Reštauračné služby (strava) a prechodné ubytovanie v podnikoch s ponukou mobilných cateringových služieb; Reštaurácie (zaopatrenie hostí v -); Bufety (rýchle obcerstvenie); Klubové služby súvisiace s poskytovaním jedla a nápojov; Nočné kluby (poskytovanie jedál); Čajovne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve nudenja hrane in pijače ter začasne nastanitve; Priprava in strežba mešanih pijač; Bari; Storitve barov z vodnimi pipami za kajenje; Storitve barov; Storitve koktajl barov; Samopostrežne restavracije; Kavarne; Storitve koktajl barov; Čajnice; Storitve vinotek; Storitve samopostrežne restavracije; Kavarne (preskrba gostov v kavarnah); Catering; Storitve koktajl barov; Storitve koktajl barov; Čajnice; Storitve nudenja hrane in pijače in začasne nastanitve v lokalih s ponudbo mobilnega cateringa; Restavracije (oskrba gostov v restavracijah); Postrežba gostov v restavracijah s hitro prehrano [snack bari]; Storitve klubov za nudenje hrane in pijače; Storitve nočnih klubov [nudenje hrane]; Čajnice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Utskänkning av mat och dryck, upplåtande av kortvarigt boende; Barverksamhet; Barer; Barverksamhet i barer för rökning av vattenpipor; Cocktailbartjänster; Cocktailbarverksamhet; Självserveringskafeterior; Kafeterior; Cocktailbarverksamhet; Teservering; Vinbarstjänster; Kafeteriatjänster; Kaffeterior (förplägnad av gäster i -); Catering; Cocktailbarverksamhet; Cocktailbarverksamhet; Teservering; Tjänster för förplägnad och härbärgering av gäser i lokalier som erbjuder mobil catering; Restauranger; Tjänster tillhandahållna i snabbrestauranger (snackbarer); Klubbtjänster avseende utskänkning av mat och dryck; Utskänkning av mat och dryck [nattklubbar]; Teservering.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/104</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/175</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-14</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>873367</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>38027</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
