<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-20T08:59:06</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229239</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229239</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-19</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>ro</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-20</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>EXPERTTO</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162456107</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229239/000162456107.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>01.01.04</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>01.01.10</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>01.01.12</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>01.01.13</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>07.01.09</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.01.12</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.12</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Почистващи и ароматизиращи препарати; Препарати за грижа за тоалета на животни; Козметични тоалетни принадлежности; Восък за шивашки конци и oбущарски восък; Етерични масла и ароматни екстракти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Čistící prostředky a vonné přípravky; Kosmetické přípravky pro péči o zvířata; Toaletní přípravky; Krejčovský vosk a ševcovská smůla; Vonné oleje a aromatické výtažky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Rengørings- og duftpræparater; Plejemidler til dyr; Toiletartikler; Skrædder- og skomagervoks; Æteriske olier og aromatiske udtræk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Reinigungs- und Duftpräparate; Tierpflegemittel; Körperpflegemittel; Schneider- und Schusterwachs; Ätherische Öle und aromatische Extrakte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καθαριστικά και αρωματικά παρασκευάσματα· Παρασκευάσματα για την περιποίηση ζώων· Καλλυντικά· Κερί ραπτικής και υποδηματοποιίας· Αιθέρια έλαια και αρωματικά εκχυλίσματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Cleaning and fragrancing preparations; Animal grooming preparations; Toiletries; Tailors' and cobblers' wax; Essential oils and aromatic extracts.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Preparaciones para limpiar y aromatizar; Productos para el cuidado y limpieza de animales; Artículos de tocador; Cera para zapateros y sastres; Aceites esenciales y extractos aromáticos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Puhastus- ja lõhnastusained; Tooted loomade karvastiku hoolduseks; Tualett-tarbed; Rätsepa- ja kingsepavaha; Eeterlikud õlid ja aroomiekstraktid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Puhdistus- ja raikastusvalmisteet; Siistimisvalmisteet eläimille; Kosmeettiset ja peseytymisvalmisteet; Räätälin- ja suutarinvaha; Eteeriset öljyt ja aromaattiset uutteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Préparations nettoyantes et parfumantes; Préparations pour le toilettage d'animaux; Produits de toilettes; Cire pour tailleurs et pour cordonniers; Huiles essentielles et extraits aromatiques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pripravci za čišćenje i osvježivanje prostora; Pripravci za njegu životinja; Toaletni proizvodi; Vosak za krojače i postolare; Esencijalna ulja i aromatični ekstrakti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tisztító és illatosító készítmények; Állatápolási készítmények; Testápolási cikkek; Szabó- és cipészviaszok; Olajesszenciák és aromakivonatok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Preparati per pulire e profumare; Prodotti per la toilette degli animali; Toiletteria; Pece per sarti e calzolai; Olii essenziali ed estratti aromatici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Valymo ir kvėpinimo preparatai; Gyvūnų higieninės ir grožio priežiūros preparatai; Tualeto reikmenys; Siuvėjų ir siūlų vaškas; Eteriniai aliejai ir aromatiniai ekstraktai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tīrīšanas un aromatizēšanas līdzekļi; Kopšanas līdzekļi dzīvniekiem; Personiskās tualetes līdzekļi; Vaska krītiņi drēbniekiem un kurpnieku piķis; Ēteriskās eļļas un aromātiskie ekstrakti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif u għal riħa tfuħ; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif ta' l-annimali; Preparazzjonijiet tat-twaletta; Xama' għall-ħajjata u ġħall-iskrapan; Żjut essenzjali u estratti aromatiċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reinigingsproducten en geurproducten; Producten voor cosmetische dierenverzorging; Preparaten voor de toiletverzorging; Kleermakerswas en schoenmakerswas; Essentiële oliën en aromatische extracten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Preparaty do czyszczenia i odświeżania; Preparaty do pielęgnacji zwierząt; Środki toaletowe; Wosk krawiecki i szewski; Olejki esencjonalne i ekstrakty aromatyczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Produtos para limpar e perfumar; Produtos para tratamento (limpeza, etc.) de animais; Produtos de toilette; Cera para alfaiates e sapateiros; Óleos essenciais e extratos aromáticos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Preparate pentru curățare și odorizante; Preparate pentru îngrijirea animalelor; Produse pentru toaletă; Ceară de croitorie, ceară pentru cizmărie; Uleiuri esențiale și extracte aromatice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Čistiace a vonné prípravky; Toaletné prípravky pre zvieratá; Kozmetické výrobky; Krajčírsky a obuvnícky vosk; Éterické oleje a aromatické výťažky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Preparati za čiščenje in odišavljanje; Pripravki za nego živali; Toaletna sredstva; Krojaški in čevljarski vosek; Eterična olja in aromatični ekstrakti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Rengöringsmedel och välluktande preparat; Preparat för pälsvård; Toalettartiklar; Skrädderi- och skomakerivax; Eteriska oljor och aromatiska extrakt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Санитарни препарати и изделия; Препарати за дезодориране и пречистване на въздуха; Препарати и изделия за контрол на вредителите; Хигиенни препарати и изделия за медицински цели; Стоматологични препарати и изделия и лечебни средства за почистване на зъби; Стоматологични препарати и изделия; Хранителни добавки и диетични препарати; Медицински спирт; Медицински превръзки, превързочни материали покрития и апликатори; Живи органи и тъкани за хирургически цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Hygienické přípravky a výrobky; Přípravky na dezodoraci a čištění vzduchu; Přípravky proti rostlinným a živočišným škůdcům; Hygienické přípravky a výrobky; Zubní přípravky a výrobky a léčebné zubní pasty; Zubní přípravky a výrobky; Potravní doplňky a dietetické přípravky; Alkohol pro farmaceutické účely; Obvazy, obvazový materiál a aplikátory léčebných přípravků; Živé orgány a tkáně pro chirurgické účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Hygiejniske præparater og artikler; Luftdeodoriserings- og luftrensningspræparater; Præparater og artikler til skadedyrsbekæmpelse; Hygiejniske præparater og artikler; Tandpræparater og -artikler samt medicinske tandpastaer; Dentale præparater og artikler; Kosttilskud og diætetiske præparater; Alkohol til farmaceutiske formål; Medicinske plaster, forbindsstoffer og applikatorer; Levende organer og væv til kirurgiske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Hygienepräparate und -artikel; Luftdesodorierungs- und Luftreinigungspräparate; Schädlingsbekämpfungspräparate und -artikel; Hygienepräparate und -artikel; Zahnmedizinische Präparate und Erzeugnisse sowie medizinische Zahnputzmittel; Zahnmedizinische Präparate und Erzeugnisse; Diätetische Präparate und Nahrungsergänzungsmittel; Alkohol für pharmazeutische Zwecke; Medizinische Verbandmaterialien, Abdeckmaterialien und Applikatoren; Lebende Organe und Gewebe für den chirurgischen Gebrauch.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παρασκευάσματα υγειονομικά και είδη αυτών· Παρασκευάσματα απόσμησης και καθαρισμού του αέρα· Παρασκευάσματα καταπολέμισης παρασίτων και ειδη αυτών· Παρασκευάσματα υγειονομικά και είδη αυτών· Οδοντιατρικά παρασκευάσματα και είδη, και φαρμακευτικά οδοντοσκευάσματα· Παρασκευάσματα οδοντιατρικά και είδη αυτών· Συμπληρώματα διατροφής και διαιτητικά παρασκευάσματα· Φαρμακευτικό οινόπνευμα· Ιατρικές γάζες, καλύμματα και εξαρτήματα εφαρμογής· Ζωντανοί οργανισμοί και ιστοί για χειρουργικούς σκοπούς.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Sanitary preparations and articles; Air deodorising and air purifying preparations; Pest control preparations and articles; Hygienic preparations and articles; Dental preparations and articles, and medicated dentifrices; Dental preparations and articles; Dietary supplements and dietetic preparations; Alcohol for pharmaceutical purposes; Medical dressings, coverings and applicators; Live organs and tissues for surgical purpose.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Preparaciones sanitarias y productos de las mismas; Productos para desodorizar y purificar el aire; Productos y preparaciones para el control de plagas; Preparaciones y artículos higiénicos; Preparaciones y artículos dentales, así como dentífricos medicinales; Productos y preparaciones dentales; Suplementos y preparaciones dietéticas; Alcohol para uso farmacéutico; Apósitos, vendas y aplicadores médicos; Órganos y tejidos vivos para fines quirúrgicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hügieenipreparaadid ja -tooted; Õhudesodoreerimis- ja -puhastuspreparaadid; Kahjuritõrjepreparaadid ja -tooted; Hügieenipreparaadid ja -tooted; Hambaravipreparaadid ja -tooted ning ravitoimega hambapuhastusained; Hambaravipreparaadid ja -tooted; Toidulisandid ja farmatseutilised dieetained; Alkohol farmaatsias kasutamiseks; Meditsiinilised sidemed, katted ja aplikaatorid; Elusorganid ja -koed kirurgias kasutamiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Saniteettivalmisteet ja -tarvikkeet; Ilmanraikastus- ja -puhdistusvalmisteet; Tuholaistorjuntavalmisteet ja -tuotteet; Hygieniavalmisteet ja -tuotteet; Hammaslääkinnälliset valmisteet ja tuotteet sekä lääkeaineita sisältävät hampaidenpuhdistusaineet; Hammasvalmisteet ja -tuotteet; Lisäravinteet ja dieettivalmisteet; Lääkealkoholi; Lääkinnälliset sidontatarvikkeet, suojat ja asettimet; Elävät elimet ja kudokset kirurgisiin tarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Préparation et articles d’hygiène; Préparations pour désodoriser et purifier l’air; Préparations et articles pour la lutte contre les animaux nuisibles; Préparations et articles d'hygiène; Préparations et articles dentaires, et dentifrices médicinaux; Préparations et articles dentaires; Compléments alimentaires et préparations diététiques; Alcools à usage pharmaceutique; Pansements, protections et applicateurs médicaux; Organes et tissus vivants à usage chirurgical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sanitarni pripravci i proizvodi; Preparati za osvježavanje i pročišćavanje zraka; Pripravci i proizvodi za uklanjanje štetočina; Higijenski pripravci i proizvodi; Zubarski pripravci, proizvodi i medicinske paste za zube; Zubarski pripravci i proizvodi; Dodaci prehrani i dijetetski pripravci; Medicinski alkohol; Medicinski povoji, pokrovi i aplikatori; Živi organi i tkiva za kirurške svrhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Egészségügyi készítmények és cikkek; Légillatosító és légfrissítő készítmények; Kártevőirtó készítmények és cikkek; Higiéniai készítmények és cikkek; Fogászati készítmények és árucikkek, gyógyhatású fogkrémek; Fogászati készítmények és cikkek; Táplálékkiegészítők és diétás készítmények; Orvosi alkohol; Gyógyászati kötszerek és applikátorok; Élő szervezetek és szövetek sebészeti célra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Preparati e prodotti per l'igiene; Preparati per la deodorizzazione dell'aria e la purificazione dell'aria; Preparati ed articoli antiparassitari; Preparati ed articoli per l'igiene; Preparati e articoli odontoiatrici, e dentifrici medicati; Preparati ed articoli dentali; Integratori alimentari e preparati dietetici; Alcool per uso farmaceutico; Bende mediche, fasciature ed applicatori; Organi e tessuti vivi per scopi chirurgici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Higienos preparatai ir gaminiai; Oro dezodoravimo ir oro valymo preparatai; Kenkėjų naikinimo preparatai ir priemonės; Higienos preparatai ir priemonės; Dantų priežiūros preparatai ir priemonės, medicininės dantų valymo priemonės; Odontologijos preparatai ir medžiagos; Maisto papildai ir dietiniai produktai; Spiritas (farmacijos reikmėms); Medicininė tvarsliava, uždangalai ir kompresai; Gyvybingi organai ir audiniai chirurgijos reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Sanitārie līdzekļi un izstrādājumi; Gaisa dezodorēšanas un gaisa attīrīšanas preparāti; Preparāti un izstrādājumi kaitēkļu iznīcināšanai un aizsardzībai pret kaitēkļiem; Higiēnas līdzekļi un izstrādājumi; Zobārstniecības preparāti un izstrādājumi, ārstnieciskas zobu pastas un pulveri; Zobārstniecības preparāti un izstrādājumi; Uztura bagātinātāji un diētiskie preparāti; Alkohols medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Medicīniskie pārsēji, pārklāji un aplikatori; Ķermeņa orgāni un audi ķirurģiskiem nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Prodotti u preparazzjonijiet sanitarji; Preparazzjonijiet għad-deodorizzazzjoni tal-arja u l-purifikazzjoni tal-arja; Preparazzjonijiet u oġġetti għall-kontrol tal-pesti; Preparazzjonijiet u oġġetti iġjenici; Preparazzjonijiet u oġġetti għas-snien, u dentifriċi medikati; Preparazzjonijiet u oġġetti dentali; Supplimenti tad-dieta u preparazzjonijiet dijetetiċi; Alkoħol mediċinali; Infaxxar, oġġetti li kgħattu w applikaturi mediċi; Organi ħajja u tessuti għal skop kirurġiku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Hygiënische preparaten en artikelen; Luchtverfrissings- en luchtzuiveringspreparaten; Preparaten en producten voor het bestrijden van ongedierte; Hygiënische preparaten en producten; Tandheelkundige preparaten en producten, en medicinale tandpasta; Tandheelkundige preparaten en producten; Diëtische supplementen en diëtische preparaten; Alcohol voor farmaceutisch gebruik; Verbandartikelen, pleisters en medische applicators; Levende organen en weefsels voor heelkundige doeleinden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Preparaty i artykuły higieniczne; Preparaty do dezodoryzacji i oczyszczania powietrza; Preparaty i artykuły do tępienia szkodników; Preparaty i artykuły higieniczne; Preparaty i artykuły dentystyczne oraz lecznicze środki do czyszczenia zębów; Preparaty i artykuły dentystyczne; Suplementy diety i preparaty dietetyczne; Alkohol leczniczy; Opatrunki medyczne, materiały opatrunkowe i aplikatory; Żywe narządy i tkanki do celów chirurgicznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Preparações e artigos de higiene; Produtos para desodorizar e purificar o ar; Preparações e artigos pesticidas; Preparações e artigos higiénicos; Preparações e artigos dentários, e dentífricos medicinais; Preparações e artigos dentários; Suplementos e preparações dietéticos; Álcool para fins farmacêuticos; Curativos, ligaduras e aplicadores médicos; Órgãos e tecidos vivos para fins cirúrgicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Preparate și articole sanitare; Produse pentru dezodorizarea și purificarea aerului; Produse și articole pentru distrugerea dăunătorilor; Produse și articole pentru igienă; Preparate și articole dentare și produse medicinale pentru îngrijirea dinților; Preparate și articole dentare; Suplimente alimentare si preparate dietetice; Alcool medicinal; Pansamente, bandaje și plasturi medicali; Organe vii și șervețele pentru uz chirurgical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Hygienické prípravky a výrobky; Prípravky na dezodoráciu a čistenie vzduchu; Prípravky a pomôcky na reguláciu škodcov; Hygienické prípravky a potreby; Dentálne prípravky a potreby, liečivé prípravky na čistenie zubov; Dentálne prípravky a potreby; Výživové doplnky a dietetické prípravky; Alkoholy na farmaceutické použitie; Zdravotnícke obväzové materiály, obklady a aplikátory; Živé orgány a tkanivá na chirurgické účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Sanitarni pripravki in izdelki; Pripravki za osveževanje in čiščenje zraka; Izdelki in preparati za uničevanje škodljivcev; Izdelki in preparati za higieno; Zobni pripravki in izdelki ter zobne paste z zdravilnimi učinkovinami; Izdelki in preparati za dentalne namene; Prehranska dopolnila in dietetske snovi; Medicinski alkohol; Obvezilni material, obliži in aplikatorji za oskrbo ran; Živi organi in tkiva za kirurške namene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Sanitära preparat och -artiklar; Preparat för deodorisering och rening av luft; Preparat och artiklar för skadedjursbekämpning; Hygieniska preparat och artiklar; Dentala preparat och artiklar samt medicinska tandpulver, -krämer och -pastor; Dentala preparat och -artiklar; Dietiska tillskott och preparat; Alkohol för farmaceutiska ändamål; Medicinska förband, -höljen och -skydd; Levande organ och vävnader för kirurgiska ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Хартия и картон; Чанти и изделия за пакетиране, опаковане и съхранение от хартия, картон или пластмаса; Хартиени кърпички; Хартиени лигавници с ръкави; Лигавници от хартия; Бебешки лигавници от хартия; Абсорбиращи подложки за еднократна употреба за тренировки за домашни любимци; Хартиени кърпи за миене; Хартиени покрития за тоалетни чинии; Декорация за маса от хартия; Украшения от картон за хранителни продукти; Подложки за грим от хартия за премахване на грим; Необработени тъкани [за тоалетна употреба]; Абсорбираща хартия; Хартиени гирлянди; Влагоконтролиращи листове от хартия или пластмаса за опаковане на хранителни продукти; Абсорбиращи листове от хартия или пластмаса за опаковане на хранителни продукти; Хартиени филтри за чай; Водни филтри от хартия; Хартиени знаменца; Хартиени ширити; Картички за обозначение мястото на госта; Хартиени подложки за клетки за домашни любимци; Изтривалки с формата на монети; Хартиени знамена; Декоративни хартиени украси за маса; Хартиени покривки за таблички за зъболекарски инструменти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Papír a lepenka; Pytle a balicí a obalové materiály a materiály pro skladování z papíru, lepenky nebo z plastů; Papírové utěrky; Papírové bryndáčky s rukávy; Papírové bryndáčky; Papírové bryndáčky pro miminka; Jednorázové absorpční koberečky pro výchovu domácích zvířat k hygienickému chování; Papírové žínky; Papírové kryty na záchodové mísy; Dekorace na stůl z papíru; Ozdoby z lepenky na potraviny; Papírové odličovací polštářky; Drsné papírové ubrousky pro toaletní účely; Absorpční papír; Papírové girlandy; Listy papíru nebo plastu sloužící k regulaci vlhkosti pro balení potravin; Listy absorpčního papíru nebo plastu pro balení potravin; Papírové filtry na čaj; Vodní filtry z papíru; Papírové vlajky a vlaječky; Papírové krajky; Jmenovky na stůl; Papírové podložky do klecí pro domácí zvířata; Gumové podložky s výstupky na pokladny usnadňující sebrání mincí; Papírové bannery; Papírové ozdoby na stůl; Papírové podložky na dentální tácky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Papir og karton; Poser og artikler til emballering, indpakning og opbevaring af papir, pap eller plastic; Aftørringspapir; Hagesmække med ærmer, af papir; Hagesmække af papir; Papirhagesmække til spædbørn; Absorberende engangstisseunderlag til kæledyr til træning; Vaskeklude af papir; Papirbeklædning til toiletkummer; Papirartikler til borddekoration; Papdekorationer til næringsmidler; Rondeller af papir til fjernelse af makeup; Groft papir [toiletartikler]; Absorberende papir; Papirguirlander; Fugtighedskontrolerende ark af papir eller plastik til pakning af fødevarer; Absorberende ark af papir eller plastik til emballering af fødevarer; Tefiltre af papir; Vandfiltre af papir; Vimpler af papir; Papirblonder; Bordkort; Papirmåtter til transportkasser til kæledyr; Møntmåtter; Papirbannere; Borddekorationer af papir; Papirovertræk til bakker til odontologiske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Papier und Pappe; Taschen, Beutel und Waren für Verpackungs-, Einpack- und Ablagezwecke aus Papier, Pappe oder Kunststoff; Papierabtrockentücher; Lätzchen aus Papier mit Ärmeln; Lätzchen aus Papier; Babylätzchen aus Papier; Wegwerf-Saugunterlagen für das Sauberkeitstraining von Haustieren; Papierwaschtücher; WC-Sitzabdeckungen aus Papier; Tischdekorationen aus Papier; Pappdekorationen für Lebensmittel; Make-up-Pads aus Papier zum Abschminken; Grobe Papiertücher für Toilettezwecke; Saugfähiges Papier; Papiergirlanden; Feuchtigkeitsregulierende Blätter aus Papier oder Kunststoff für Lebensmittelverpackungen; Saugfähige Blätter aus Papier oder Kunststoff für Lebensmittelverpackungen; Teefilter aus Papier; Wasserfilter aus Papier; Papierwimpel; Papierspitzen; Platzkarten; Papiermatten für Haustierboxen; Münzenmatten; Banner aus Papier; Papiermittelstücke für Dekorationszwecke; Papierauflagen für zahnärztliche Tabletts.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Χαρτί, χαρτόνι· Τσάντες και είδη συσκευασίας, αποθήκευσης και περιτυλίγματος από χαρτί, χαρτόνι ή πλαστικό· Χάρτινα μαντηλάκια· Σαλιάρες, με μανίκια, από χαρτί· Σαλιάρες χάρτινες· Βρεφικές σαλιάρες από χαρτί· Απορροφητικά χαλάκια μιας χρήσης για την εκπαίδευση τουαλέτας κατοικίδιων ζώων· Χάρτινες πετσέτες προσώπου· Χάρτινο προκάθισμα για λεκάνες τουαλέτας· Χάρτινα διακοσμητικά για το τραπέζι· Διακοσμήσεις από χαρτόνι για τρόφιμα· Δίσκοι μακιγιάζ από χαρτί για την αφαίρεση του μακιγιάζ· Τραχύ χαρτί υγείας για ατομική περιποίηση· Απορροφητικό χαρτί· Χάρτινες γιρλάντες· Φύλλα ελέγχου της υγρασίας από χαρτί ή πλαστικό για συσκευασίες τροφίμων· Απορροφητικά φύλλα από χαρτί ή πλαστικό για συσκευασίες τροφίμων· Φίλτρα για τσάι από χαρτί· Φίλτρα νερού από χαρτί· Σημαιάκια από χαρτί· Δαντέλα από χαρτί· Κάρτες καλεσμένων· Χάρτινα υποθέματα για εσχαροκιβώτια κατοικίδιων ζώων· Ελαστικές κερματοθήκες· Πανό από χαρτί· Χάρτινα διακοσμητικά για το κέντρο του τραπεζιού· Καλύμματα οδοντιατρικών δισκαρίων από χαρτί.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Paper and cardboard; Bags and articles for packaging, wrapping and storage of paper, cardboard or plastics; Paper wipes; Bibs, sleeved, of paper; Bibs of paper; Paper baby bibs; Disposable absorbent training pads for pets; Paper washcloths; Paper toilet bowl liners; Table decorations of paper; Decorations of cardboard for foodstuffs; Make-up pads of paper for removing make-up; Coarse tissue [for toiletry use]; Absorbent paper; Paper garlands; Humidity control sheets of paper or plastic for foodstuff packaging; Absorbent sheets of paper or plastic for foodstuff packaging; Paper tea filters; Water filters of paper; Paper pennants; Paper lace; Place cards; Paper pet crate mats; Coin mats; Banners of paper; Decorative paper centerpieces; Dental tray covers of paper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Papel y cartón; Bolsas y artículos para empaquetar, envasar y almacenar, de papel, cartón y materias plásticas; Papel para limpiar; Baberos de papel con mangas; Baberos de papel; Baberos de papel para bebés; Almohadillas desechables absorbentes para el adiestramientos de animales de compañía; Paños de papel para lavado; Protectores de papel para tazas de inodoro; Decoraciones para la mesa de papel; Decoraciones de cartón para productos alimenticios; Almohadillas desmaquillantes de papel; Papel higiénico de textura áspera; Papel absorbente; Guirnaldas de papel; Hojas de control de humedad, de papel o de materias plásticas, para embalar productos alimenticios; Hojas absorbentes de papel o de materias plásticas para embalar productos alimenticios; Filtros de papel para té; Filtros de agua de papel; Banderín de papel; Papel de encaje; Tarjetas de mesa; Alfombrillas de papel para jaulas de animales de compañía; Tapetes para monedas; Banderolas de papel; Centros de mesa decorativos de papel; Papel para cubrir bandejas dentales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Paber ja papp; Paberist, papist või plastist kotid ja muud tooted pakkimiseks ja ladustamiseks; Paberist pühkimislapid; Käistega paberpudipõlled; Paberist pudipõlled; Imikute paberist pudipõlled; Ühekordsed imavad alusmatid lemmikloomade õpetamiseks; Paberist pesulapid; Paberist prill-lauavoodrid; Paberist lauakaunistused; Papist kaunistused toiduainetele; Paberist meigipadjad jumestuse eemaldamiseks; Jämedakoeline salvrätt [tualett-tarbena kasutamiseks]; Absorbeerpaber; Pabergirlandid; Niiskuse taset hoidvad paber- või plastlehed toiduainete pakendamiseks; Imavad paber- või plastlehed toiduainete pakendamiseks; Paberist teefiltrid; Paberist veefiltrid; Paberlipud; Paberpael; Kohakaardid; Pabermatid loomakastidele; Mündikogumisalused; Paberist ribareklaamid; Dekoratiivsed paberkaunistused; Paberkatted hambaarstiriistade kandikule.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Paperi ja pahvi; Paperista, pahvista tai muovista tehdyt pussit ja tavarat pakkaamista, käärimistä ja säilytystä varten; Paperipyyhkeet; Ruokalaput, hihalliset, paperista; Leukalaput, paperia; Paperiset leukalaput vauvoille; Imukykyiset kertakäyttöalustat lemmikkieläinten sisäsiisteyteen oppimiseen; Paperiset pesulaput; WC-istuinten suojat paperista; Paperiset pöydänkoristeet; Pahviset koristeet elintarvikkeita varten; Paperista tehdyt meikkityynyt meikin poistoon; Karkea paperiliina [toalettikäyttöön]; Imukykyinen paperi; Paperiköynnökset; Kosteutta säätävät paperi- tai muoviarkit elintarvikkeiden pakkaamiseen; Imukykyiset paperi- tai muoviarkit elintarvikkeiden pakkaamiseen; Teesuodatinpaperit; Paperiset vedensuodattimet; Paperiset liput; Paperipitsi; Paikkakortit; Paperialustat lemmikkieläinten kuljetushäkkeihin; Kolikkomatot; Paperiviirit; Paperiset koristeet pöydän keskelle; Hammaslääketieteellisten tarjotinten paperisuojukset.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Papier et carton; Sacs et articles d'emballage, d'empaquetage et de stockage en papier, carton ou plastique; Lingettes en papier; Bavoirs à manches en papier; Bavoirs en papier; Bavoirs en papier pour bébés; Alèses absorbantes d'entraînement jetables pour animaux de compagnie; Petites serviettes en papier pour la toilette; Couvre-sièges de toilettes en papier; Décorations de table en papier; Décorations en carton pour produits alimentaires; Tampons démaquillants en papier; Papier de soie brut pour la toilette; Papier absorbant; Guirlandes en papier; Feuilles régulatrices d'humidité en papier ou matières plastiques pour l'emballage de produits alimentaires; Feuilles absorbantes en papier ou matières plastiques pour l'emballage de produits alimentaires; Filtres à thé en papier; Filtres à eau en papier; Fanions en papier; Dentelle de papier; Marque place; Tapis en papier pour caisses d'animaux domestiques; Supports pour monnaies; Bannières en papier; Centres de table décoratifs en papier; Papier pour recouvrir des plateaux dentaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Papir i karton; Papirnate, kartonske i plastične vreče i artikli za pakiranje, zamatanje i skladištenje; Papirnati brisači; Podbradnici od papira s rukavima; Papirnati podbradnjaci; Papirnati podbradnjaci za bebe; Jednokratne upijajuće podloge za vježbanje higijenskih navika kod kućnih ljubimaca; Papirnate krpe za pranje; Papirnate podloge za toaletne daske; Papirnate stolne dekoracije; Dekoracije od kartona za prehrambene proizvode; Papirni jastučići za uklanjanje šminke; Gruba papirnata maramica [za kozmetičku uporabu]; Upijajući papir; Girlande od papira; Folije od papira ili plastike za održavanje vlage [za pakiranje hrane]; Upijajuće folije od papira ili plastike za pakiranje hrane; Papirnati filtri za čaj; Papirnati filtri za vodu; Papirnati plamenci; Papirnata čipka; Kartice s imenima za stolove; Papirnate podloge za kaveze za kućne ljubimce; Podloge s izbočinama za lakše prikupljanje kovanica; Papirnate zastavice; Ukrasi od papira za sredinu stola; Papirnati pokrov za dentalne pladnjeve.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Papír és karton; Papírból, kartonból vagy műanyagból készült tasakok és cikkek árucikkek csomagolásához és tárolásához; Papírtörlők; Ujjas előkék, papírból; Előkék papírból; Előkék csecsemőknek papírból; Eldobható nedvszívó pelenkák kisállatoknak szobatisztaságra neveléshez; Papír törlőkendők; Papírból készült vécécsésze-bélések; Papírból készült asztaldíszek; Díszek kartonpapírból élelmiszerekhez; Sminkeltávolító papírpárnák, korongok; Durva papírkendők [pipere célokra]; Nedvszívó papír; Papírgirlandok; Papír- vagy műanyaglapok nedvesség ellenőrzésére élelmiszerek csomagolásánál; Abszorbens papír vagy műanyag, élelmiszerek csomagolásához; Papír teaszűrők; Papír vízszűrők; Papírzászlók; Papírcsipke; Ültetőkártyák; Papír bélések házi kedvencek kosarába; Aprópénztartó lapok; Papír feliratok, zászlók; Papír asztaldíszek; Papírból készült fedők fogászati tálcákhoz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Carta e cartone; Sacche ed articoli per imballaggio, impacchettatura e immagazzinaggio di carta, cartone o plastica; Salviettine di carta; Pettorine con maniche di carta; Bavaglini di carta; Bavaglini in carta per neonati; Tappetini assorbenti monouso per l'addestramento d'animali domestici; Strofinacci di carta; Rivestimenti protettivi di carta per W.C.; Decorazioni da tavola di carta; Decorazioni di cartone per alimenti; Batuffoli struccanti in carta; Tessuti grezzi per la toilette; Carta assorbente; Ghirlande di carta; Fogli regolatori di umidità in carta o plastica per l'imballaggio di prodotti alimentari; Fogli assorbenti in carta o plastica per l'imballaggio di prodotti alimentari; Filtri da tè in carta; Filtri dell'acqua in carta; Bandiere di carta; Lacci di carta; Segnaposto; Stuoie in carta per le gabbie di animali domestici; Stuoie per monete; Striscioni di carta; Centrotavola decorativi di carta; Tovagliette di carta per vassoi dentistici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Popierius ir kartonas; Popieriniai, kartoniniai ar plastikiniai pakavimo, vyniojimo ir laikymo maišeliai ir reikmenys; Popieriniai šluostukai; Popieriniai seilinukai su rankovėmis; Popieriniai seilinukai; Popieriniai kūdikių seilinukai; Vienkartiniai sugeriantys naminių gyvūnų dresūros kilimėliai; Popierinės prausimosi šluostės; Klozeto kraštų popieriniai užklotai; Popierinės stalo dekoracijos; Kartoniniai maisto produktų papuošalai; Popieriniai makiažo valymo diskeliai; Šiurkštus popierius tualeto reikmėms; Sugeriamasis popierius; Popierinės girliandos; Drėgmę reguliuojantieji popieriaus ar plastiko lapai [maisto produktų pakavimui]; Sugeriamojo popieriaus ar plastiko lapai [maisto produktų pakavimui]; Popieriniai arbatos filtrai; Popieriniai vandens filtrai; Popierinės vėliavėlės; Popieriniai nėriniai; Stalo kortelės; Popieriniai gyvūnų dėžių patiesalai; Monetų padėklai; Popierinės reklamjuostės; Dekoratyviniai popieriniai papuošimai; Popieriniai odontologinių padėklų patiesalai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Papīrs un kartons; Papīra, kartona vai plastmasas maisi un maisiņi (somas) iepakošanai, ietīšanai vai uzglabāšanai; Papīra salvetes slaucīšanai; Papīra krūšautiņi ar piedurknēm; Papīra krūšautiņi; Papīra krūšautiņi bērniem; Vienreizlietojami absorbējoši paliktņi mājas (istabas) dzīvnieku dresēšanai; Papīra dvieļi higiēnai; Tualetes podu uzliktņi no papīra; Galda dekorācijas no papīra; Pārtikas produktu kartona rotājumi; Papīra spilventiņi dekoratīvās kosmētikas noņemšanai; Raupjās salvetes [ķermeņa kopšanai]; Sūcējpapīrs; Papīra virtenes; Mitrumu aizturošas papīra vai plastmasas loksnes pārtikas produktu iesaiņošanai; Absorbējošas papīra vai plastmasas loksnes pārtikas produktu iesaiņošanai; Papīra filtri tējai; Papīra ūdens filtri; Papīra vimpeļi; Papīra mežģīnes; Galda kartes; Mājdzīvnieku būrīšu paklājiņi no papīra; Kabatiņas monētām; Papīra reklāmplakāti; Novietošanai galda centrā paredzēti rotājumi no papīra; Zobārstniecības paplāšu pārvalki no papīra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Karti u kartunċin; Basktijiet u oġġetti tal-karti, kartunċin jew plastiks għall-ippakkjar, tgeżwir u ħażna; Msielaħ tal-karti; Vavalori, bil-kmiem, tal-karta; Bavalori tal-karti; Vavalori tal-karti tat-trabi; Kuxxinetti assorbenti li jintremew għat-taħriġ tal-annimali domestiċi; Ċraret tal-ħasil, magħmula mill-karti; Inforor tal-karti għall-bwieqi tat-tojlit; Dekorazzjonijiet tal-karti, għall-mejda; Dekorazzjonijiet tal-kartunċin għall-oġġetti tal-ikel; Peds tal-karta għat-tneħħija tal-irtokk; Karta iġenika ħoxna [għall-użu fit-tojlit]; Karti assorbenti; Girlandi tal-karti; Folji tal-karti jew tal-plastik għall-kontroll tal-umdità għall-ippakkjar ta' oġġetti tal-ikel; Folji assorbenti tal-karti jew tal-plastik għall-ippakkjar ta' oġġetti tal-ikel; Filtri tat-te tal-karti; Filtri tal-ilma tal-karti; Pinnuri tal-karti; Bizzilla magħmula mill-karti; Kards għall-identifikazzjoni ta' postijiet; Mattijiet tal-karti għall-kontenituri tal-annimali domestiċi; Matt tal-muniti; Banners tal-karti; Dekorazzjonijiet għal fuq il-mejda magħmula mill-karti; Kavers tat-trejs dentali magħmulin mill-karti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Papier en karton; Zakken en artikelen voor verpakking, omwikkeling en bewaring van papier, karton of plastic; Papieren doekjes; Slabbetjes met mouwtjes van papier; Slabbetjes van papier; Babyslabbetjes van papier; Absorberende wegwerppads voor training van huisdieren; Papieren washandjes; Bedekkingen van papier voor toiletpotten; Tafelversieringen van papier; Versieringen van karton voor voedingsmiddelen; Make-upschijfjes van papier voor het verwijderen van make-up; Papier (grof -) [voor toiletgebruik]; Absorberend papier; Papieren guirlandes; Vochtregulerende vellen van papier of plastic, voor de verpakking van voedingsmiddelen; Absorberende vellen van papier of plastic voor het verpakken van voedingsmiddelen; Theefilters van papier; Waterfilters van papier; Wimpels van papier; Kant van papier; Tafelkaartjes; Matjes van papier voor dierenverblijven; Matjes voor wisselgeld [munten]; Vaandels van papier; Decoratieve middenstukjes van papier; Papieren bedekkingen voor tandartsschalen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Papier i karton; Torebki oraz artykuły do pakowania i przechowywania z papieru, kartonu lub tworzyw sztucznych; Papierowe chusteczki do wycierania; Śliniaki z rękawami, papierowe; Śliniaki papierowe; Niemowlęce śliniaki papierowe; Jednorazowe pochłaniające podkładki szkoleniowe dla zwierząt domowych; Papierowe chusteczki do mycia; Papierowe nakładki na muszle klozetowe; Dekoracje na stół z papieru; Ozdoby kartonowe na artykuły spożywcze; Płatki papierowe do demakijażu; Szorstkie chusteczki [do użytku toaletowego]; Papier chłonny; Girlandy papierowe; Utrzymujące wilgoć arkusze papieru lub plastiku do pakowania żywności; Chłonne arkusze papieru lub plastiku do pakowania żywności; Papierowe filtry do herbaty; Filtry do wody z papieru; Proporczyki z papieru; Papierowe koronki; Bileciki stołowe; Papierowe podkładki do klatek dla zwierząt domowych; Maty [podstawki] na monety; Transparenty z papieru; Dekoracje na środek stołu z papieru; Papierowe podkładki na tacki dentystyczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Papel e cartão; Sacos e artigos para o acondicionamento, embrulho e armazenamento de papel, cartão ou matérias plásticas; Toalhitas de papel; Babetes em papel, com mangas; Babetes em papel; Babetes em papel para bebés; Tapetes absorventes descartáveis para treinar animais de estimação; Toalhetes de papel; Forros de papel para vaso sanitários; Decorações de mesa em papel; Enfeites em cartão para produtos alimentares; Discos/compressas desmaquilhantes em papel; Papel higiénico de textura áspera; Papel absorvente; Grinaldas de papel; Folhas para controlo de humidade em papel ou em plástico para embalagem de alimentos; Folhas absorventes em papel ou em plástico para embalagem de alimentos; Filtros para chá em papel; Filtros de água em papel; Bandeirolas em papel; Papel rendado; Cartões para marcar lugares; Tapetes de papel para caixas de transporte de animais domésticos; Tapetes para moedas; Estandartes em papel; Centros de mesa decorativos de papel; Proteções em papel para tabuleiros de dentista.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Hârtie și carton; Sacoșe și articole pentru ambalare, împachetare și depozitare din hârtie, carton sau plastic; Batistuțe de hârtie; Bavete cu mâneci, din hârtie; Bavete din hârtie; Bavete din hârtie pentru bebeluși; Covorașe absorbante de unică folosință pentru dresajul animalelor de companie; Cârpe de șters din hârtie; Căptușeli din hârtie pentru vasul de toaletă; Decorațiuni de hârtie pentru masă; Decorațiuni din carton pentru alimente; Dischete demachiante din hârtie; Hârtie aspră [pentru toaletă]; Hârtie absorbantă; Ghirlande de hârtie; Foi din hârtie sau plastic cu control al umidității, pentru ambalarea produselor alimentare; Foi absorbante din hârtie sau plastic pentru ambalarea produselor alimentare; Filtre de cafea din hârtie; Filtre de apă din hârtie; Fanioane de hârtie; Dantelă de hârtie; Cartonașe cu nume pentru mese; Carpete de hârtie pentru cuștile animalelor de companie; Bucăți de material cu textura în relief, utilizate pentru mărunțiș și pentru a facilita apucarea acestuia cu mâna; Bannere din hârtie; Articole decorative din hârtie pentru centrul mesei; Acoperitoare pentru tăvi de instrumente dentare, fabricate din hârtie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Papier a lepenka; Papierové, lepenkové alebo plastové vrecia a výrobky na balenie, obaľovanie a skladovanie; Papierové servítky; Podbradníky s rukávmi, papierové; Papierové podbradníky; Papierové podbradníky pre bábätká; Jednorazové absorpčné podložky na výchovu domácich zvieratiek k hygienickému správaniu; Papierové utierky; Papierové prikrývky na sedadlo záchodovej misy; Papierové ozdoby na stôl; Kartónové ozdoby pre potraviny; Papierové obrúsky na odstraňovanie líčidiel; Drsné papierové vreckovky na toaletné účely; Absorpčný papier; Papierové girlandy; Papierové alebo plastové hárky alebo fólie regulujúce vlhkosť na balenie potravín; Papierové alebo plastové absorpčné hárky alebo fólie na balenie potravín; Papierové čajové filtre; Vodné filtre z papiera; Zástavky, vlajky z papiera; Čipka z papiera; Menovky [na určenie rozmiestnenia]; Papierové podložky pre klietky pre domáce zvieratá; Gumené priehradky na zoraďovanie mincí; Papierové stolové vlajky; Dekoratívne papierové ozdoby na stred stola; Papierové podložky na stomatologické podnosy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Papir in lepenka; Vrečke in proizvodi za pakiranje, zavijanje in shranjevanje iz papirja, lepenke ali plastike; Papirnate brisačke; Slinčki z rokavi iz papirja; Slinčki iz papirja; Slinčki iz papirja, za dojenčke; Vpojne podloge za enkratno uporabo za učenje čistoče hišnih ljubljenčkov; Papirnate krpe za umivanje; Sedne obloge za straniščne školjke, iz papirja; Namizne dekoracije iz papirja; Okraski iz kartona za živila; Blazinice iz papirja za odstranjevanje ličil; Grob toaletni papir; Vpojni papir; Girlande iz papirja; Listi za kontrolo vlažnosti iz papirja ali plastike za embaliranje hrane; Vpojni listi iz papirja ali plastike za embaliranje hrane; Papirnati filtri za čaj; Papirnati filtri za vodo; Zastavice iz papirja; Papirnata čipka; Kartice za sedežni red; Podloge iz papirja, za zaboje za hišne ljubljenčke; Točkaste podlage; Papirnati transparenti; Papirnate dekoracije za na mizo; Papirnate podloge za zobozdravniške pladnje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Papper och kartong; Påsar och artiklar för emballering, förpackning och förvaring, av papper, kartong eller plast; Torkdukar av papper; Haklappar, med ärmar, av papper; Haklappar av papper; Pappershaklappar; Absorberande engångsträningsdynor för husdjur; Tvättservetter av papper; Toalettsitsskydd av papper; Bordsdekorationer av papper; Pappdekoration för livsmedel; Sminkdynor av papper för avsminkning; Grovt papper [för toalettändamål]; Absorberande papper; Pappersgirlanger; Fuktkontrollerande ark av papper eller plast för livsmedelsemballering; Absorberande ark av papper eller plast för livsmedelsemballering; Tefilter av papper; Vattenfilter av papper; Vimplar av papper; Spetspapper; Placeringskort; Pappersmattor för bärväskor/burar för sällskapsdjur; Myntmattor; Pappersfanor; Pappersdekorationer för bord; Överdrag av papper för dentala brickor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Изделия за грижа за облекла и обувки; Козметични и тоалетни принадлежности; Домакински изделия за почистване, четки и материали за изработване на четки; Сервизи и прибори за маса, кухненска посуда и съдини.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Výrobky pro péči o oděvy a obuv; Kosmetické a toaletní potřeby; Domácí náčiní k úklidu, kartáče a materiály na výrobu kartáčů; Nádobí, kuchyňské náčiní a nádoby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Artikler til pleje af beklædningsgenstande og fodtøj; Redskaber til kosmetisk brug og toiletredskaber; Redskaber til rengøring i hjemmet, børster og børstenbindermateriale; Bordservice, køkkengrej og beholdere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Haushaltsgegenstände für die Pflege von Bekleidung und Schuhwaren; Kosmetik- und Toiletteutensilien; Haushaltsreinigungsgegenstände, Bürsten und Bürstenmachermaterialien; Geschirr, Kochgeschirr und Behälter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Είδη περιποίησης ενδυμάτων και υποδημάτων· Σύνεργα καλλωπισμού και ατομικής περιποίησης· Οικιακά σύνεργα καθαρισμού, βούρτσες και υλικά ψηκτροποιίας· Επιτραπέζια σκεύη, μαγειρικά σκεύη και δοχεία.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Articles for the care of clothing and footwear; Cosmetic and toilet utensils; Household utensils for cleaning, brushes and brush-making materials; Tableware, cookware and containers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Artículos para el cuidado de prendas de vestir y calzado; Utensilios de cosméticos y de tocador; Utensilios domésticos de limpieza, cepillos y materiales para fabricar cepillos; Vajillas, baterías de cocina y recipientes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rõivaste ja jalatsite hooldustooted; Kosmeetika- ja tualett-tarvikud; Puhastusvahendid majatarvetena, harjad ja harjamaterjalid; Lauanõud, toiduvalmistusnõud ja mahutid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tarvikkeet vaatteiden ja jalkineiden hoitoon; Kosmetiikka- ja toilettitarvikkeet; Kodinpuhdistusvälineet, harjat ja harjanvalmistusaineet; Pöytäastiat, keittoastiat ja säiliöt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Articles pour l’entretien de vêtements et de chaussures; Ustensiles cosmétiques et de toilette; Ustensiles de nettoyage, brosses et matériaux pour la brosserie; Vaisselle, ustensiles de cuisine et récipients pour la cuisine ou le ménage.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Artikli za održavanje odjeće i obuće; Kozmetički i toaletni pribor; Kućanski pribor za čišćenje, četke i materijali za izradu četki; Pribor za jelo, kuhinjski pribor i spremnici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Árucikkek ruhák és lábbelik ápolásához; Kozmetikai és piperecikkek; Háztartási tisztítóeszközök, kefék és kefekészítő anyagok; Asztalneműk, főzőedények és tárolók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Articoli per la cura di capi di abbigliamento e calzature; Utensili per uso cosmetico e per la toilette; Utensili per le pulizie domestiche, spazzole e materiali per la fabbricazione di spazzole; Vasellame, pentole e recipienti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Drabužių ir avalynės prižiūros reikmenys; Kosmetiniai ir tualetiniai reikmenys; Namų apyvokos valymo reikmenys, šepečiai ir šepečių darymo medžiagos; Valgomieji reikmenys, virtuvės reikmenys ir buitinės talpyklos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Preces apģērbu un apavu kopšanai; Kosmētikas un tualetes piederumi; Mājsaimniecības piederumi tīrīšanai, birstes un birstu izgatavošanas materiāli; Galda un virtuves piederumi, tilpnes un trauki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Artikli għall-kura ta' ħwejjeġ u ta' xedd is-saqajn; Għodod kosmetiċi u tat-twaletta; Utensili domestiċi għat-tindif, xkupilji u materjali biex tagħmel l-ixkupilji u l-pniezel; Oġġetti għal fuq il-mejda, oġġetti li ssajjar bihom u kontenituri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Artikelen voor het verzorgen van kleding en schoeisel; Cosmetisch gerei en toiletgerei; Huishoudelijk schoonmaakgerei, borstels en materialen voor de borstelfabricage; Vaatwerk, kookgerei en houders voor de keuken of de huishouding.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Artykuły do pielęgnacji odzieży i obuwia; Przybory kosmetyczne i toaletowe; Przybory do użytku domowego do czyszczenia, szczotki i materiały do wytwarzania szczotek; Zastawa stołowa, przybory kuchenne i pojemniki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Artigos para a conservação de vestuário e calçado; Utensílios cosméticos e de toilette; Utensílios domésticos para a limpeza, escovas e materiais para o fabrico de escovas; Utensílios de mesa, cozinha e recipientes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Material pentru îngrijirea articolelor de îmbrăcăminte și încălțăminte; Ustensile cosmetice și de toaletă; Ustensile de uz menajer pentru curățat, perii și materiale pentru perii; Veselă, articole de bucătărie și recipiente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Výrobky pre starostlivosť o odevy a obuv; Kozmetické a toaletné potreby; Domáce alebo kuchynské potreby na čistenie, kefy a materiály na výrobu kief; Stolovacie potreby, kuchynský riad a nádoby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Izdelki za nego oblačil in obutve; Kozmetični in toaletni pripomočki; Gospodinjski pripomočki za čiščenje, krtače in materiali za ščetkarstvo; Namizna posoda, posoda za kuhanje in shranjevalna posoda.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Artiklar för vård av kläder och fotbeklädnader; Kosmetiska redskap och toalettredskap; Hushållsredskap för rengöringsändamål, borstar och borstmakerimaterial; Bordsserviser, köksredskap och behållare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Шапки и принадлежности за глава; Облекло; Обувки; Части от облекло, обувки, шапки и принадлежности за глава.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pokrývky hlavy; Oděvy; Boty; Části oděvů, obuvi a pokrývek hlavy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Hattemagervarer; Beklædningsgenstande; Sko; Dele af beklædningsgenstande, fodtøj og hovedbeklædning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Hüte; Bekleidungsstücke; Schuhe [Halbschuhe]; Teile von Bekleidungsstücken, Schuhwaren und Kopfbedeckungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Είδη πιλοποιίας· Ενδύματα· Υποδήματα· Μέρη ενδυμάτων, υποδημάτων και ειδών πιλοποιίας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hats; Clothing; Shoes; Parts of clothing, footwear and headgear.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Sombreros; Prendas de vestir; Zapatos; Partes de indumentaria, calzado y sombrerería.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kübarad, vormimütsid; Rõivad; Kingad; Rõivaste, jalatsite ja peakatete osad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Päähineet; Vaatteet; Jalkineet; Vaatteiden, jalkineiden ja päähineiden osat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Chapeaux; Vêtements; Souliers; Parties de vêtements, articles chaussants et articles de chapellerie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pokrivala za glavu; Odjeća; Obuća; Dijelovi odjeće, obuće i pokrivala za glavu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kalapáruk; Ruházati cikkek; Lábbelik; Ruházat, lábbelik és fejfedők részei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cappelli; Abbigliamento; Scarpe; Parti di abbigliamento, calzature e articoli di cappelleria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Galvos apdangalai; Drabužiai, apranga; Avalynė; Drabužių, avalynės ir galvos apdangalų dalys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Cepures; Apģērbi; Kurpes; Apģērbu, apavu un galvassegu daļas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Xedd ir-ras; Ilbies; Xedd is-saqajn; Partijiet minn ħwejjeġ, xedd is-saqajn u xedd ir-ras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Hoofddeksels; Kleding; Schoenen; Delen van kleding, schoeisel en hoofdbedekking.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Nakrycia głowy; Odzież; Obuwie; Części odzieży, obuwia i nakryć głowy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Chapéus; Vestuário; Sapatos; Partes de vestuário, calçado e chapelaria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole pentru acoperirea capului; Articole de îmbrăcăminte; Articole de încălțăminte; Părți de îmbrăcăminte, încălțăminte și articole pentru acoperirea capului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Pokrývky hlavy; Odevy; Topánky; Časti oblečenia, obuvi a pokrývok hlavy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pokrivala; Oblačila; Obutev; Deli oblačil, obutve in pokrival.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hattar; Kläder; Skor; Delar av kläder, fotbeklädnader och huvudbonader.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/088</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-12</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/158</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-20</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1070316</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
