<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-17T08:58:57</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229029</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229029</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="1">Application published</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-17</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Animal Tree</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162457712</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229029/000162457712.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.11</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.13</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.15</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.12</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>20</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ковчези и погребални урни, по-специално за хора или животни, по-специално домашни животни; Погребални урни, изработени от благородни метали; Погребални урни, от които растат растения или дървета; Рамки за картини, по-специално от метал, дървесина, благороден метал, пластмаса или кожа.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Rakve a pohřební urny, zejména pro lidi a zvířata, zejména domácí zvířata; Pohřební urny vyrobené z drahých kovů; Pohřební urny z nichž rostou rostliny nebo stromy; Obrazové rámy, zejména z kovu, dřeva, vzácných kovů, plastické hmoty nebo kůže.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Ligkister og begravelsesurner, især til mennesker eller dyr, især kæledyr; Begravelsesurner fremstillet af ædle metaller; Begravelsesurner, der vokser planter eller træer ud af; Billedrammer, især af metal, træ, ædle metaller, plastic eller læder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Särge und Bestattungsurnen, insbesondere für Menschen oder Tiere, insbesondere Haustiere; Bestattungsurnen aus Edelmetall; Bestattungsurnen aus denen Pflanzen oder Bäume wachsen; Bilderrahmen, insbesondere aus Metall, Holz, Edelmetall, Kunststoff oder Leder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Φέρετρα και τεφροδόχοι, ειδικότερα για ανθρώπους ή ζώα, ειδικότερα κατοικίδια ζώα· Τεφροδόχοι από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Τεφροδόχοι, στις οποίες καλλιεργούνται φυτά ή δέντρα· Πλαίσια (κορνίζες), ειδικότερα από μέταλλο, ξύλο, πολύτιμα μέταλλα, πλαστικό ή δέρμα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Coffins and funerary urns, in particular for humans or animals, in particular pets; Funerary urns made of precious metals; Plant or tree-growing funerary urns; Picture frames, in particular of metal, wood, precious metals, plastic or leather.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Ataúdes y urnas funerarias, especialmente para personas o animales, especialmente animales de compañía; Urnas funerarias de metales preciosos; Urnas funerarias para que crezcan plantas o árboles; Marcos, en particular de metal, maderas, metales preciosos, plástico o cuero.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kirstud ja matuseurnid, eelkõige inimestele või loomadele, eelkõige lemmikloomadele; Väärismetallist matuseurnid; Matuseurnid, millest kasvavad taimed või puud; Pildiraamid, eelkõige metallist, puidust, väärismetallist, plastist või nahast.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Arkut ja hautausuurnat, erityisesti ihmisille tai eläimille, erityisesti kotieläimille; Jalometalliset tuhkauurnat; Hautausuurnat, joista kasvaa kasveja tai puita; Taulunkehykset, erityisesti metallista, puusta, jalometallista, muovista tai nahasta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Cercueils et urnes funéraires, en particulier pour humains ou animaux, en particulier animaux domestiques; Urnes funéraires en métaux précieux; Urnes funéraires desquelles poussent des plantes ou arbres; Cadres, en particulier en métal, bois, métaux précieux, plastique ou cuir.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Mrtvački ljesovi i pogrebne urne, posebno za ljude ili životinje, posebno kućne ljubimce; Pogrebne urne od plemenitih metala; Pogrebne urne iz kojih rastu biljke ili drveće; Okviri za slike, posebice od metala, drva, plemenitog metala, plastike ili kože.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Koporsók és temetkezési urnák, elsősorban emberek vagy állatok, elsősorban háziállatok számára; Nemesfémből készült temetési urnák; Temetkezési urnák, amelyekből növények vagy fák nőnek; Képkeretek, elsősorban fémből, fából, nemesfémből, műanyagból vagy bőrből.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Bare e urne funerarie, in particolare per umani o animali, in particolare animali domestici; Urne funerarie in metalli preziosi; Urne funerarie dalle quali crescono piante o alberi; Cornici, in particolare in metallo, legno, metalli preziosi, plastica o cuoio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Karstai ir laidojimo urnos, ypač žmonių ar gyvūnų, ypač augintinių; Brangiųjų metalų laidojimo urnos; Laidojimo urnos, iš kurių išauga augalai ar medžiai; Paveikslų rėmai, ypač iš metalo, medienos, brangiųjų metalų, plastikų ar odos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Zārki un kremācijas pelnu urnas, īpaši cilvēkiem vai dzīvniekem, jo īpaši lolojumdzīvniekiem; Apbedīšanas urnas, kas izgatavotas no dārgmetāliem; Kremācijas pelnu urnas no kurām izaug augi vai koki; Attēlu rāmji, jo īpaši no metāla, koka, dārgmetāla, plastmasas vai ādas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Twiebet u urni funerarji, speċjalment għal bnedmin jew annimali, speċjalment abitazzjonijiet għall-annimali; Urni tal-funerali magħmula minn metalli prezzjużi; Urni funerarji li minn ġo fihom jikbru l-pjanti jew is-siġar; Frejms tar-ritratti, speċjalment tal-metall, injam, metall prezzjuż, plastik jew ġilda.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Doodkisten en urnen voor crematie-as, met name voor mensen of dieren, met name huisdieren; Grafurnen gemaakt van edele metalen; Urnen voor crematie-as, waaruit planten of bomen groeien; Fotolijsten, met name van metaal, hout, edele metalen, plastic of leder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Trumny i urny pogrzebowe, w szczególności dla ludzi lub zwierząt, w szczególności zwierząt domowych; Urny na prochy wykonane z metali szlachetnych; Urny pogrzebowe, z których wyrastają rośliny lub drzewa; Ramki obrazów, w szczególności z metalu, drewna, metalu szlachetnego, tworzywa sztucznego lub skóry.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Caixões e urnas funerárias, em especial para humanos ou animais, em especial animais de estimação; Urnas funerárias em metais preciosos; Urnas funerárias a partir das quais crescem plantas ou árvores; Molduras, em especial metálicas, em madeira, metais preciosos, matérias plásticas ou couro.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Sicrie și urne funerare, în special pentru oameni sau animale, în special animale de companie; Urne funerare din metale prețioase; Urne funerare din care cresc plante sau flori; Rame, în special din metal, lemn, metale prețioase, plastic sau piele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Pohrebné kazety a pohrebné urny, predovšetkým pre ľudí alebo zvieratá, predovšetkým domáce zvieratá; Pohrebné urny vyrobené z drahých kovov; Pohrebné urny, z ktorých rastú rastliny alebo stromy; Rámy na obrazy, predovšetkým z kovu, dreva, drahého kovu, plastu alebo kože.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Krste in pogrebne žare, zlasti za ljudi ali živali, zlasti hišne živali; Pogrebne žare iz žlahtnih kovin; Pogrebne žare, iz katerih rastejo rastline ali drevesa; Okvirji za slike, zlasti iz kovine, lesa, žlahtnih kovin, plastike ali usnja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Likkistor och begravningsurnor, speciellt för människor eller djur, speciellt sällskapsdjur; Begravningsurnor av ädla metaller; Begravningsurnor ur vilka växter eller träd växer; Tavelramar, speciellt av metall, trä, ädelmetaller, plast eller läder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Онлайн търговия на дребно с ковчези и погребални урни, по-специално за хора или животни, по-специално домашни животни, погребални урни от благороден метал, урни, от които растат растения или дървета; Онлайн търговия на дребно с живи растения, семена, грудки и разсад за развъждане на растения и дървета, рамки за картини, по-специално от метал, дърво, благороден метал, пластмаса или кожа, украшения (бижутерийни продукти), скъпоценни камъни, перли и благородни метали, както и техни имитации, бижута, украшения (бижутерийни продукти), кутии за бижута [ковчежета], по-специално за пълнене с животинска пепел, мемориални емблеми; Обединяване на разнообразни услуги в полза на други, а именно погребални услуги, провеждане на погребения, погребални услуги, включително кремация, провеждане на погребални церемонии, погребални услуги за домашни любимци, включително тяхното кремиране, за да могат потребителите удобно да сравняват и купуват тези услуги.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">On-line maloobchodní služby s ohledem na rakve a pohřební urny, zejména pro lidi nebo zvířata, zejména domácí zvířata, pohřební urny ze vzácných kovů, urny z nichž rostou rostliny nebo stromy; On-line maloobchodní služby s ohledem na živé rostliny, semena, hlízy a sazenice pro pěstování rostlin a stromů, obrazové rámy, zejména z kovu, dřeva, vzácných kovů, plastické hmoty nebo kůže, klenoty, drahokamy, perly a vzácné kovy a jejich imitace, klenoty, šperky, kazety na šperky, zejména pro naplnění popelem zvířat, vzpomínkové cedulky; Shromažďování většího počtu služeb v zájmu druhých, jmenovitě pohřebních služeb, pohřebních služeb, provádění pohřbů, pohřební služby včetně kremací, vedení pohřebních obřadů, pohřební služby pro domácí zvířata včetně jejich zpopelnění, aby si spotřebitelé mohli tyto služby pohodlně porovnat a nakoupit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Online-detailhandel med ligkister og begravelsesurner, især til mennesker eller dyr, især kæledyr, begravelsesurner af ædle metaller, urner, der vokser planter eller træer ud af; Online-detailhandel med levende planter, såsæd, rodknolde og stiklinger til planteavl samt træer, billedrammer, især af metal, træ, ædle metaller, plastic eller læder, smykker, ædelstene, perler og ædle metaller samt imitationer heraf, juvelerarbejder, smykker, smykkeskrin, især til fyldning med aske fra dyr, erindringsemblemer; Sammensætning af flere forskellige tjenesteydelser til fordel for tredjepart, nemlig begravelsesvirksomhed, bedemandsvirksomhed, gennemførelse af begravelser, begravelsesvirksomhed, herunder kremering, afholdelse af begravelsesceremonier, begravelse af kæledyr, inklusive kremering heraf, således at forbrugere kan sammenligne og gøre brug af disse tjenesteydelser på en bekvem måde.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Online- Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Särge und Bestattungsurnen, insbesondere für Menschen oder Tiere, insbesondere Haustiere, Bestattungsurnen aus Edelmetall, Urnen aus denen Pflanzen oder Bäume wachsen; Online- Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf lebende Pflanzen, Samen, Knollen und Setzlinge für die Pflanzenzucht und Bäume, Bilderrahmen, insbesondere aus Metall, Holz, Edelmetall, Kunststoff oder Leder, Schmuck, Edelsteine, Perlen und Edelmetalle sowie Imitationen hiervon, Juwelierwaren, Schmuckwaren, Schmuckkästen, insbesondere zum Befüllen mit Tierasche, Erinnerungsembleme; Zusammenführung einer Vielfalt von Dienstleistungen zugunsten anderer, nämlich Bestattungsdienste, Bestattungsdienstleistungen, Durchführen von Bestattungen, Bestattungsdienste einschließlich Einäscherung, Durchführung von Bestattungszeremonien, Bestattungsdienste für Haustiere inklusive deren Einäscherung, damit die Verbraucher diese Dienstleistungen bequem vergleichen und erwerben können.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης επί γραμμής σε σχέση με φέρετρα και τεφροδόχους, ειδικότερα για ανθρώπους και ζώα, ειδικότερα κατοικίδια ζώα, τεφροδόχους από πολύτιμα μέταλλα, τεφροδόχους, στις οποίες καλλιεργούνται φυτά ή δέντρα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης επί γραμμής σε σχέση με ζώντα φυτά, σπόρους, κονδύλους και νεαρά φυτά για καλλιέργεια και δέντρα, πλαίσια (κορνίζες), ειδικότερα από μέταλλο, ξύλο, πολύτιμα μέταλλα, πλαστικό ή δέρμα, κοσμήματα, πολύτιμους λίθους, μαργαριτάρια και πολύτιμα μέταλλα, καθώς και απομιμήσεις αυτών, είδη κοσμηματοποιίας, είδη χρυσοχοΐας, κοσμηματοθήκες, ειδικότερα για γέμισμα με τέφρα ζώων, αναμνηστικά εμβλήματα· Υπηρεσίες συγκέντρωσης ποικιλίας υπηρεσιών για λογαριασμό τρίτων, συγκεκριμένα υπηρεσίες γραφείου τελετών, υπηρεσίες διεξαγωγής κηδειών, υπηρεσίες γραφείου τελετών, υπηρεσίες γραφείου τελετών, όπου περιλαμβάνεται η αποτέφρωση, διεξαγωγή νεκρώσιμων τελετών, υπηρεσίες γραφείου τελετών σε σχέση με κατοικίδια ζώα, όπου περιλαμβάνεται η αποτέφρωση αυτών, με σκοπό τη διευκόλυνση της σύγκρισης και της αγοράς των υπηρεσιών αυτών από τους καταναλωτές.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Online retailing relating to coffins and funerary urns, in particular for humans or animals, in particular pets, funerary urns of precious metal, plant or tree-growing funerary urns; Online retailing relating to natural plants, seeds, corms and tubers and plants for cultivation and trees, picture frames, in particular of metal, wood, precious metal, plastic or leather, jewellery, precious stones, pearls and precious metals, and imitations thereof, jewellery, jewellery items, jewellery caskets, in particular for filling with animal ashes, commemorative emblems; The bringing together of a variety of services for the benefit of others, namely funeral services, funerary undertaking, burial services, funeral services accompanying cremation, conducting funeral ceremonies, funeral services for pets, including the cremation thereof, enabling customers to conveniently compare and purchase these services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de venta minorista en línea en relación con ataúdes y urnas funerarias, especialmente para personas o animales, especialmente animales de compañía, urnas funerarias de metales preciosos, urnas para que crezcan plantas o árboles; Servicios de venta minorista en línea en relación con plantas vivas, semillas, tubérculos y plantones de cultivo y árboles vegetales, marcos, en particular de metal, madera, metales preciosos, materias plásticas o cuero, bisutería, pedrería, perlas y metales preciosos así como imitaciones de los mismos, artículos de joyería, joyería, estuches para joyas, especialmente para llenar con cenizas de animales, emblemas de recuerdo; Realización de una variedad de servicios para otras personas, en concreto servicios funerarios, servicios funerarios, servicios de inhumación, servicios funerarios en el marco de la incineración, celebración de ceremonias funerarias, servicios funerarios para mascotas, incluyendo la incineración, para que los clientes de estos servicios puedan comparar y adquirir estos servicios cómodamente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Järgmiste kaupade sidus-jaemüügi teenused: kirstud ja matuseurnid, eelkõige inimestele või loomadele, eelkõige lemmikloomadele, väärismetallist matuseurnid, urnid, millest kasvavad taimed või puud; Järgmiste kaupade sidus-jaemüügi teenused: elustaimed, seemned, mugulad, sibulad ja seemikud taimekasvatuseks ja puud, pildiraamid, eelkõige metallist, puidust, väärismetallist, plastist või nahast, ehted, vääriskivid, pärlid ja väärismetallid ning nende imitatsioonid, juveeltooted, ehted, ehiskarbid, eelkõige loomatuhaga täitmiseks, mälestusembleemid; Mitmesuguste teenuste koondamine kolmandatele isikutele, nimelt matuseteenused, matusetalitusteenused, matuste korraldamine, matuseteenused, sh tuhastamine, matusetalituste läbiviimine, lemmikloomamatuse teenused, sh tuhastamine, et kliendid saaksid neid teenuseid mugavalt võrrelda ja osta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Arkkuihin ja hautausuurniin, erityisesti ihmisille tai eläimille, erityisesti kotieläimille, liittyvät online-vähittäiskauppapalvelut, hautausuurnat jalometallista, uurnat, joista kasvaa kasveja tai puita; Seuraaviin liittyvät online-vähittäiskauppapalvelut: elävät kasvit, siemenet, mukulat ja pistokkaat kasvien viljelyyn ja puihin, taulunkehykset, erityisesti metallista, puusta, jalometallista, muovista tai nahasta, korut, jalokivet, helmet ja jalometallit sekä niiden jäljitelmät, jalokivituotteet, korutuotteet, korulippaat, erityisesti eläimen tuhkalla täytettävät, muistotunnuskuvat; Monenlaisten palveluiden kokoaminen yhteen muiden hyväksi, jotta kuluttajat voivat vaivattomasti vertailla ja ostaa näitä palveluita, nimittäin: hautaustoimet, hautauspalvelut, hautausten toteuttaminen, hautaustoimet mukaan lukien tuhkaus, hautajaisseremonioiden toteuttaminen, hautaustoimet kotieläimille mukaan lukien niiden tuhkaus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de vente au détail en ligne en relation avec des cercueils et urnes funéraires, en particulier pour humains ou animaux, en particulier animaux domestiques, urnes funéraires en métaux précieux, urnes desquelles poussent des plantes ou arbres; Services de vente au détail en ligne en relation avec des plantes vivantes, semences, tubercules et plants pour la culture et les arbres, cadres, en particulier en métal, bois, métaux précieux, plastique ou cuir, bijoux, pierres précieuses, perles et métaux précieux ainsi que leurs imitations, articles de joaillerie, articles de bijouterie, coffrets à bijoux, en particulier à remplir avec des cendres d'animaux, emblèmes de souvenirs; Compilation d'une diversité de services pour le compte de tiers, à savoir services funéraires, prestations de services funéraires, réalisation de funérailles, services funéraires, y compris la crémation, réalisation de cérémonies funéraires, services funéraires pour animaux domestiques, y compris leur crémation, afin que des consommateurs puissent comparer et acquérir aisément ces services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Internetske usluge maloprodaje u vezi sa sljedećim: mrtvački ljesovi i pogrebne urne, posebno za ljude ili životinje, posebno kućne ljubimce, pogrebne urne od plemenitog metala, urne iz kojih rastu biljke ili drveće; Internetske usluge maloprodaje u vezi sa sljedećim: žive biljke, sjemenje, gomolji i sadnice za uzgoj biljaka i drveća, okviri za slike, posebno od metala, drva, plemenitog metala, plastike ili kože, nakit, drago kamenje, biseri i plemeniti metali te njihove imitacije, bižuterija, nakit, kutije za nakit, posebno za punjenje životinjskim pepelom, spomenice; Grupiranje brojnih usluga u korist drugih, i to usluge pogreba, usluge pogrebnog poduzeća, provođenje pogreba, usluge pogreba, uključujući kremiranje, provođenje pogrebnih ceremonija, usluge pogreba kućnih ljubimaca, uključujući njihovo kremiranje, kako bi potrošači navedene usluge mogli lako usporediti i kupiti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Online kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások a következőkkel kapcsolatban: koporsók és temetkezési urnák, elsősorban emberek vagy állatok, elsősorban háziállatok számára, temetkezési urnák, amelyekből növények vagy fák nőnek; Online kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások a következőkre vonatkozóan: élő növények, magok, gumók és facsemeték növénytermesztés és fák számára, képkeretek, elsősorban fémből, fából, nemesfémből, műanyagból vagy bőrből, ékszerek, ékkövek, gyöngyök és nemesfémek, valamint ezek utánzatai, ékszerek, dísztárgyak, ékszerdobozok, elsősorban állati hamvakkal való megtöltésre, emlékjelvények; Szolgáltatások sokszínűségének összesítése mások számára, nevezetesen temetkezési szolgáltatások, hamvasztással kapcsolatos temetések, temetkezési szolgáltatások, temetési ceremóniák lebonyolítása, temetkezési szolgáltatások háziállatok számára, beleértve azok hamvasztását, azért, hogy a felhasználók ezeket a szolgáltatásokat kényelmesen összehasonlíthassák és megpályázhassák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di vendita online in relazione a bare e urne funerarie, in particolare per umani o animali, in particolare animali domestici, urne funerarie in metalli preziosi, urne funerarie dalle quali crescono piante o alberi; Servizi di vendita online in relazione a piante vive, semi, tuberi e piantine per la coltivazione di piante e alberi, cornici, in particolare di metallo, legno, metalli preziosi, plastica o cuoio, gioielli, pietre preziose, perle e metalli preziosi nonché loro imitazioni, gioielli, articoli di bigiotteria, scatole per gioielli, in particolare per il riempimento con cenere animale, emblemi commemorativi; Composizione di una pluralità di servizi a favore di terzi, vale a dire servizi funerari, realizzazione di funerali, servizi funerari inclusa la cremazione, realizzazione di cerimonie funebri, servizi funerari per animali domestici inclusa la loro cremazione, affinché i consumatori possano facilmente confrontare e acquistare questi servizi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Internetinė mažmeninė prekyba karstais ir laidojimo urnomis, ypač žmonių ar gyvūnų, ypač augintinių, laidojimo urnos iš brangiųjų metalų, urnos, iš kurių išauga augalai ar medžiai; Internetinė mažmeninė prekyba natūraliais augalais, sėklomis, svogūnėliais ir sodinukais augalams ir medžiams auginti, paveikslų rėmais, ypač iš metalo, medienos, brangiųjų metalų, plastiko ar odos, papuošalais, brangakmeniais, perlais ir brangiaisiais metalais bei jų pakaitalais, juvelyriniais dirbiniais, papuošalais, papuošalų dėžutėmis, ypač gyvūnų pelenams pilti, prisiminimų emblemomis; Įvairių paslaugų atrinkimas tretiesiems asmenims, būtent laidojimo paslaugų, laidojimo ceremonijų, įskaitant kremavimą, laidojimo ceremonijų vedimo paslaugų, augintinių laidojimo paslaugų, įskaitant jų kremavimą, kad klientai galėtų patogiai palyginti šias paslaugas ir jomis pasinaudoti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tiešsaistes mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar zārkiem un kremācijas pelnu urnām, jo īpaši cilvēkiem vai dzīvniekiem, jo īpaši lolojumdzīvniekiem, kremācijas pelnu urnas no dārgmetāla, urnas no kurām izaug augi vai koki; Tiešsaistes mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar dzīviem augiem, sēkla, bumbuļsīpoli un gumi un kultūraugi un koki, gleznu un attēlu rāmji, jo īpaši no metāla, koks, dārgmetāli, plastmasas materiāli vai āda, juvelierizstrādājumi, juvelierizstrādājumu akmeņi, pērles un dārgmetāli, kā arī to imitācijas, juvelierizstrādājumi, juvelierizstrādājumi, dārglietu lādītes, jo īpaši dzīvnieku pelnu iepildīšanai, atgādinājuma emblēmas; Dažādu pakalpojumu apkopošana par labu citiem, proti, apbedīšanas pakalpojumi, apbedīšanas pakalpojumi, apbedīšanas biroju pakalpojumi, apbedīšanas pakalpojumi ar kremēšanu, bēru ceremoniju vadīšana, apbedīšanas pakalpojumi lolojumdzīvniekiem tostarp to kremēšana, lai patērētāji šos pakalpojumus varētu ērti salīdzināt un iegādāties.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Bejgħ bl-imnut online b'rabta ma' twiebet u urni funerarji, speċjalment għal bnedmin jew annimali, speċjalment abitazzjonijiet għall-annimali, urni funerarji magħmula minn metall prezzjuż, urni li minn ġo fihom jikbru l-pjanti jew is-siġar; Bejgħ bl-imnut online b'rabta ma' pjanti naturali ħajjin, żrieragħ, basal u nebbieta għat-tnissil tal-pjanti, frejms tar-ritratti, speċjalment tal-metall, injam, metall prezzjuż, plastik jew ġilda, ġojjellerija, ħaġar prezzjuż, perli u metalli prezzjużi kif ukoll imitazzjonijiet tagħhom, ġojjellerija, ġojjelli, kontenituri tal-ġojjelli [kaxxetti], speċjalment biex jimtlew bi rmied tal-annimali, emblemi kommemorattivi; Il-ġabra flimkien ta' varjetà ta' servizzi għal oħrajn, jiġifieri impriża funebri, servizzi funerarji, servizzi ta' funerali, servizzi ta' funerali li jakkumpanjaw il-kremazzjoni, it-twettiq ta' ċerimonji ta' funerali, servizzi ta' funerali għal annimali domestiċi li jakkumpanjaw il-kremazzjoni, sabiex il-konsumatur ikun jista' jqabbel u jikseb dawn is-servizzi bil-kumdità.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Onlinedetailhandelsdiensten met betrekking tot doodkisten en urnen voor crematie-as, met name voor mensen of dieren, met name huisdieren, urnen voor crematie-as, van edele metalen, urnen waaruit planten of bomen groeien; Onlinedetailhandelsdiensten met betrekking tot levende planten, zaden, bollen en stekken voor de teelt en bomen, fotolijsten, met name van metaal, hout, edele metalen, plastic of leder, juwelen, edelstenen, parels en edele metalen alsmede imitaties hiervan, juwelierswaren, bijouterieën, juwelenkistjes, met name voor het vullen met as van dieren, herdenkingsschilden; Bijeenbrenging van een veelvoud van diensten ten gunste van derden, te weten uitvaartdiensten, begrafenisdiensten, teraardebestelling, uitvaartdiensten, waaronder crematies, organisatie van begrafenisceremoniën, uitvaartdiensten voor huisdieren, waaronder crematie ervan, zodat consumenten deze diensten gemakkelijk kunnen vergelijken en afnemen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi handlu detalicznego online w odniesieniu do towarów, takich jak trumny i urny pogrzebowe, w szczególności dla ludzi lub zwierząt, w szczególności zwierząt domowych, urny pogrzebowe z metalu szlachetnego, urny, z których wyrastają rośliny lub drzewa; Usługi handlu detalicznego online w odniesieniu do towarów, takich jak żywe rośliny, nasiona, bulwy i sadzonki do uprawy roślin i drzewa, ramki obrazów, w szczególności z metalu, drewna, metalu szlachetnego, tworzywa sztucznego lub skóry, wyroby jubilerskie, kamienie szlachetne, perły i metale szlachetne i ich imitacje, wyroby jubilerskie, ozdoby [biżuteria], kasetki na biżuterię, w szczególności do wypełniania prochami zwierząt, odznaki pamiątkowe; Zestawianie rożnych usług na rzecz innych osób, mianowicie usług pogrzebowych, usług pogrzebowych, usług pogrzebowych, usług pogrzebowych towarzyszących kremacji, prowadzenia ceremonii pogrzebowych, usług pogrzebowych dla zwierząt domowych towarzyszących kremacji, w celu umożliwienia konsumentom wygodnego porównywania i kupowania tych usług.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de comércio retalhista de venda online, relacionados com caixões e urnas funerárias, em especial para humanos ou animais, em especial animais de estimação, urnas funerárias de metal precioso, urnas a partir das quais crescem plantas ou árvores; Serviços de comércio retalhista de venda online, relacionados com plantas vivas, sementes, tubérculos e sementeiras para criação de plantas e árvores, molduras, em especial de metal, madeira, metais preciosos, matérias plásticas ou couro, artigos de bijutaria, pedras preciosas, pérolas e metais preciosos, assim como imitações dos mesmos, joalharia, bijutaria, caixas para artigos de joalharia e de fantasia, em especial para encher com cinzas de animais, emblemas comemorativos; Compilação de uma variedade de serviços em benefício de terceiros, nomeadamente serviços funerários, prestação de serviços funerários, realização de funerais, serviços funerários incluindo cremação, realização de cerimónias fúnebres, serviços funerários para animais de estimação incluindo a sua cremação, para que os consumidores possam comparar e adquirir comodamente estes serviços.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul online în legătură cu sicrie și urne funerare, în special pentru oameni sau animale, în special animale de companie, urne funerare din metal prețios, urne funerare din care cresc plante sau flori; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul online în legătură cu plante vii, semințe, tuberculi și plante de cultură și arbori, cadre, în special din metal, lemn, metale prețioase, plastic sau piele, bijuterii, pietre prețioase, perle și metale prețioase, precum și imitații ale acestora, articole de bijuterie, produse sub formă de articole de bijuterii, casete de bijuterii, în special pentru păstrarea cenușii animalelor, embleme comemorative; Regruparea de diverse servicii, pentru alte persoane, și anume servicii funerare, servicii funerare, servicii funerare, servicii funerare conexe incinerării, organizarea de ceremonii funerare, servicii funerare pentru animale de companie, inclusiv incinerare, astfel încât clienții să poată compara și cumpăra comod acest servicii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">On-line maloobchodné služby so zameraním na pohrebné kazety a pohrebné urny, predovšetkým pre ľudí alebo zvieratá, predovšetkým domáce zvieratá, pohrebné urny z drahých kovov, urny, z ktorých rastú rastliny alebo stromy; On-line maloobchodné služby so zameraním na živé rastliny, semená, hľuzy a sadenice na sadenie rastlín a stromov, rámy na obrazy, predovšetkým z kovu, dreva, drahého kovu, plastu alebo kože, šperky, drahokamy, perly a drahé kovy, ako aj ich imitácie, šperky, šperkovnice, predovšetkým na plnenie popola zo zvierat, pamätné plakety; Zlúčenie rozmanitosti služieb v prospech zákazníkov, menovite pohrebné služby, pohrebné obrady, pohrebné služby, pohrebné služby pri kremáciách, vedenie pohrebných obradov, pohrebné služby pri kremáciách zvierat chovaných v domácnosti na pohodlné porovnanie a nákup týchto služieb pre zákazníkov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Spletne maloprodajne storitve v zvezi s krstami in pogrebnimi žarami, zlasti za ljudi ali živali, zlasti hišne živali, pogrebne žare iz žlahtnih kovin, žare, iz katerih rastejo rastline ali drevesa; Spletne maloprodajne storitve v zvezi z živimi rastlinami, semeni, gomolji in sadikami za gojenje rastlin in dreves, okvirji za slike, zlasti iz kovine, lesa, žlahtnih kovin, plastike ali usnja, nakitom, dragimi kamni, biseri in žlahtnimi kovinami ter njihovimi imitacijami, zlatarskimi izdelki, nakitom, škatlami za nakit, zlasti za polnjenje z živalskim pepelom, spominskimi emblemi; Združevanje različnih storitev v korist drugih, in sicer pogrebne storitve, pogrebne storitve, opravljanje pogrebov, pogrebne storitve, vključno s kremacijo, pogrebne slovesnosti, pogrebne storitve za hišne živali, vključno s kremacijo, tako da lahko potrošniki te storitve ugodno primerjajo in kupijo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Direktanslutna detaljhandelstjänster med avseende på likkistor och begravningsurnor, speciellt för människor eller djur, speciellt sällskapsdjur, begravningsurnor av ädelmetall, urnor ur vilka växter eller träd växer; Direktanslutna detaljhandelstjänster med avseende på levande växter, frön, rotknölar och plantor för odling och träd, tavelramar, speciellt av metall, trä, ädelmetall, plast eller läder, smycken, smyckesstenar, pärlor och ädelmetaller samt imitationer av dessa, juvelerarvaror, smycken, smyckeskrin, speciellt för påfyllning med djuraska, påminnelsemarkeringar; Sammanförande av många olika tjänster åt andra, nämligen begravningstjänster, begravningstjänster, genomförande av begravningar, begravningstjänster inklusive kremering, genomförande av begravningsceremonier, begravningstjänster för husdjur inklusive deras kremering, så att konsumenter bekvämt kan jämföra och förvärva dessa tjänster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>45</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Погребални услуги; Погребални услуги, по-специално за крематориуми; Погребални услуги; Погребални услуги във връзка с кремация; Провеждане на погребални церемонии; Услуги за погребения на домашни любимци във връзка с кремация.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pohřební služby; Pohřební služby, zejména pro krematoria; Pohřbívání; Pohřební služby při kremacích; Provádění pohřebních obřadů; Pohřební služby při kremacích domácích zvířat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Bedemandsvirksomhed; Bedemandsvirksomhed, især i forbindelse med krematorier; Begravelsesvirksomhed; Begravelsestjenester i forbindelse med kremering; Afholdelse af begravelsesceremonier; Begravelsestjenester i forbindelse med kremering af kæledyr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bestattungsdienste; Bestattungsdienstleistungen, insbesondere für Krematorien; Durchführen von Bestattungen; Bestattungsdienste einschließlich Einäscherung; Durchführung von Bestattungszeremonien; Bestattungsdienste für Haustiere inklusive deren Einäscherung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες γραφείου τελετών, εργολαβιών κηδειών· Υπηρεσίες γραφείου τελετών, ειδικότερα σε σχέση με αποτεφρωτήρια· Υπηρεσίες γραφείου τελετών· Υπηρεσίες γραφείου τελετών καθώς και αποτέφρωσης· Διεξαγωγή νεκρώσιμων τελετών· Υπηρεσίες γραφείου τελετών καθώς και καύσης οικιακών ζώων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Funerary services; Funerary undertaking, in particular for crematoria; Burial services; Funeral services accompanying cremation; Conducting funeral ceremonies; Pet funeral services accompanying cremation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios funerarios; Servicios funerarios, especialmente para crematorios; Servicios de inhumación; Servicios funerarios en el marco de la incineración; Celebración de ceremonias funerarias; Servicios funerarios para animales de compañía en el marco de la incineración.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Matusetalitusteenused; Matusetalitusteenused, eelkõige krematooriumidele; Muldasängitusteenused; Krematsiooniga kaasnevad matuseteenused; Matusetalituste läbiviimine; Krematsiooniga kaasnevad lemmiklooma matuseteenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hautausurakointi; Hautauspalvelut, erityisesti krematorioille; Hautauspalvelut; Kremaatioon liittyvät hautauspalvelut; Hautajaisseremonioiden johtaminen; Lemmikkieläinten kremaatioon liittyvät hautauspalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services funéraires; Prestations de services funéraires, en particulier pour crématoriums; Services d'inhumation; Services funéraires de crémation; Conduite de cérémonies funéraires; Services funéraires de crémation pour animaux de compagnie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pogrebno poduzeće; Usluge pogrebnog poduzeća, posebno za krematorije; Pogrebne usluge; Pogrebne usluge povezane s kremiranjem; Obavljanje pogrebnih obreda; Usluge povezane s kremiranjem kućnih ljubimaca.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Temetkezési vállalkozás; Temetkezési szolgáltatások, elsősorban krematóriumok számára; Temetkezési szolgáltatások; Hamvasztással kapcsolatos temetkezési szolgáltatások; Temetési ceremóniák levezetése; Kisállatok hamvasztásával kapcsolatos temetkezési szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi funerari; Servizi funerari, in particolare per crematori; Servizi di inumazione; Servizi funebri di accompagnamento alla cremazione; Conduzione di cerimonie funebri; Servizi funebri di accompagnamento alla cremazione di animali domestici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Laidojimo biurų paslaugos; Laidojimo paslaugos, ypač krematoriumų; Laidojimo paslaugos; Su kremavimu susijusios laidojimo paslaugos; Laidotuvių ceremonijų vedimas; Su kremavimu susijusios gyvūnų laidojimo paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apbedīšanas biroju pakalpojumi; Apbedīšanas pakalpojumi, jo īpaši krematorijām; Bēru rīkošana; Apbedīšanas pakalpojumi ar kremēšanu; Bēru ceremoniju vadīšana; Mājdzīvnieku apbedīšanas pakalpojumi ar kremēšanu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Impriża funebri; Impriża funebri, speċjalment għal kremazzjonijiet; Servizzi funerarji; Servizzi ta' funerali li jakkumpanjaw il-kremazzjoni; It-twettiq ta' ċerimonji ta' funerali; Servizzi ta' funerali għal annimali domestiċi li jakkumpanjaw il-kremazzjoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Begrafenisondernemingen; Begrafenisdiensten, met name voor crematoria; Begrafenisdiensten; Rouwdiensten bij crematies; Organiseren van begrafenisceremoniën; Rouwdiensten bij crematie van huisdieren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi pogrzebowe; Usługi pogrzebowe, w szczególności dla krematoriów; Usługi pogrzebowe; Usługi pogrzebowe towarzyszące kremacji; Prowadzenie ceremonii pogrzebowych; Usługi pogrzebowe dla zwierząt domowych towarzyszące kremacji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de agências funerárias; Serviços fúnebres, em especial para crematórios; Serviços funerários; Serviços funerários de acompanhamento à incineração; Organização de cerimónias fúnebres; Serviços funerários de acompanhamento à incineração para animais de estimação.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii funerare; Servicii funerare, în special pentru crematorii; Servicii funerare; Servicii funerare conexe incinerării; Organizarea de ceremonii funerare; Servicii funerare conexe incinerării pentru animale de companie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Pohrebné obrady; Pohrebné obrady, predovšetkým pre kremácie; Pohrebné služby; Pohrebné služby pri kremáciách; Vedenie pohrebných obradov; Pohrebné služby pri kremáciách zvierat chovaných v domácnosti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pogrebne storitve'; Pogrebne storitve, zlasti za krematorije; Pogrebne storitve; Pogrebne storitve ob upepelitvi; Izvajanje pogrebnih obredov; Pogrebne storitve za domače ljubljenčke ob upepelitvi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Begravningsverksamhet; Begravningstjänster, speciellt för krematorier; Begravningstjänster; Begravningstjänster i samband med kremering; Genomförande av begravningsceremonier; Begravningstjänster för husdjur i samband med kremering.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/155</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-17</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081971</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>38999</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
