<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-18T14:29:20</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229842</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229842</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-13</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-18</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Railee</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Светлини за монтиране на стени; Светодиодни осветителни тела; Крушки за осветление тип LED; Лампи за бюро; Светлини за велосипеди; Лампиони; Машини за печене на хляб; Електрически уреди за производство на кисело мляко; Нагреватели, електрически, за биберони за хранене; Електрически дехидрататори за храни за домакински цели; Овлажнители [за домакински цели]; Газопречистватели; Въздухопречистватели; Преносими електрически сушилни с топъл въздух; LED апарати за сушене на нокти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nástěnná světla; LED svítidla; LED žárovky; Lampy na pracovní stoly; Světla pro jízdní kola; Světelné řetězy pro slavnostní dekorace; Stroje na pečení chleba; Elektrické jogurtovače; Elektrické ohřívače kojeneckých lahví; Elektrické sušičky potravin pro domácí použití; Zvlhčovače (k použití v domácnosti); Zařízení na čištění plynu; Čističe vzduchu; Přenosné elektrické horkovzdušné vysoušeče; LED sušičky na nehty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Væglamper; LED-belysningslegemer; LED-pærer til belysning; Skrivebordslamper; Cykellygter; Kulørte lamper til festdekoration; Brødbagemaskiner; Elektriske apparater til fremstilling af yoghurt; Varmere til sutteflasker, elektriske; Elektriske apparater til tørring af fødevarer til husholdningsbrug; Befugtere [til husholdningsbrug]; Gasrensere; Luftrensere; Bærbare, elektriske varmluftstørrere; LED-apparater til negletørring.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wandleuchten für Beleuchtungszwecke; LED-Leuchten; LED-Glühlampen; Schreibtischleuchten; Fahrradleuchten; Lichterketten für die Festtagsdekoration; Brotbackmaschinen; Elektrische Joghurtbereiter; Elektrische Babyflaschenwärmer; Elektrische Lebensmitteldörrgeräte für Haushaltszwecke; Luftbefeuchter [für Haushaltszwecke]; Gasfilter und -reiniger; Luftreiniger; Tragbarer elektrischer Warmlufttrockner; LED-Nagellampen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Λαμπτήρες τοίχου· Φωτιστικά σώματα με φωτοδιόδους (LED)· Λυχνίες λαμπτήρων LED· Λάμπες γραφείου· Δικύκλων φανάρια· Λαμπιόνια χρωματιστά διακοσμητικά για γιορτινές διακοσμήσεις· Αρτοπαρασκευαστές· Ηλεκτρικές συσκευές παρασκευής γιαουρτιού· Θερμαντήρες για μπιμπερό ηλεκτρικοί· Ηλεκτρικοί αφυγραντήρες τροφίμων οικιακής χρήσης· Υγραντήρες για οικιακή χρήση· Καθαριστήρες αερίου και συσκευές αφαίρεσης ρύπων αερίου· Απολυμαντές του αέρα [συσκευές απολύμανσης του αέρα]· Φορητός ηλεκτρικός στεγνωτήρας θερμού αέρα· Συσκευές στεγνώματος νυχιών με φωτοδιόδους.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Wall lights; LED luminaires; LED light bulbs; Desk lamps; Bicycle lights; Fairy lights for festive decoration; Bread baking machines; Electric appliances for making yogurt; Electric heaters for babies' bottles; Electric food dehydrators for household purposes; Humidifiers for household use; Gas purification machines; Air purifiers; Portable electric warm air dryer; LED nail drying apparatus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Lámparas de pared; Luminarias LED; Bombillas de iluminación LED; Lámparas de escritorio; Luces para bicicletas; Guirnaldas de luces decorativas para fiestas; Hornos de pan; Yogurteras eléctricas; Calientabiberones eléctricos; Deshidratadores eléctricos de alimentos para uso doméstico; Humidificadores [para uso doméstico]; Depuradores y purificadores de gas; Purificadores de aire; Secador de aire caliente eléctrico portátil; Aparatos de secado de uñas mediante led.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Seinavalgustid; LED-valgustid; LED-lambipirnid; Kirjutuslaualambid; Jalgrattalaternad; Dekoreertuled, ehistuled, ilutuled pidulikuks kaunistamiseks; Leivaküpsetusmasinad; Elektriseadmed jogurti valmistamiseks; Elektrilised lutipudelisoojendid; Elektrilised toidu dehüdraatorid majapidamises kasutamiseks; Niisutid [majapidamises kasutamiseks]; Gaasipuhastid; Õhupuhastid; Kaasaskantavad elektrilised kuuma õhuga töötavad kuivatid; Küünelaki LED-kuivatusseadmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Seinälamput; LED-valaisimet; LED-valolamput; Työpöytälamput; Lamput polkupyöriin; Värilliset lamput koristeluun; Leipäkoneet; Sähkölaitteet jogurtin valmistukseen; Tuttipullojen lämmittimet, sähkökäyttöiset; Sähkökäyttöiset elintarvikkeiden kuivurit kotitaloustarkoituksiin; Kostuttimet [kotitaloustarkoituksiin]; Kaasunpuhdistimet; Ilmanpuhdistimet; Sähkökäyttöiset kannettavat lämminilmakuivaajat; LED-toimiset kynsienkuivauslaitteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils d'éclairage fixés au mur; Luminaires à LED; Ampoules LED; Lampes de bureau; Feux pour bicyclettes; Guirlandes lumineuses pour décoration de fête; Machines pour cuire du pain; Yaourtières électriques; Chauffe-biberons électriques; Déshydrateurs électriques d’aliments à usage ménager; Humidificateurs à usage domestique; Épurateurs et purificateurs de gaz; Purificateurs d'air; Séchoirs à air chaud électriques portables; Appareils à diodes électroluminescentes pour le séchage des ongles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Zidna rasvjeta; LED rasvjeta; LED žarulje za svjetiljke; Lampe za pisaći stol; Svjetla za bicikle; Lampioni za svečane dekoracije; Aparati za pečenje kruha; Električni aparati za pripremu jogurta; Grijalice za bočice s dudom, električne; Električni dehidratori hrane za kućansku uporabu; Humidifikatori [za kućanske namjene]; Čistači i pročiščivaći plina; Pročišćivači zraka; Prijenosna električna sušilica na topli zrak; Uređaji za sušenje noktiju diodama LED.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Fali világítás; LED-es lámpatestek, fényforrások; LED-izzók; Íróasztali lámpák; Kerékpár lámpák; Lámpák, égők ünnepi díszkivilágításhoz; Kenyérsütő gépek; Elektromos joghurtkészítők; Elektromos cumisüveg melegítők; Elektromos élelmiszer szárítók/aszalók háztartási célokra; Párásítók [háztartási célokra]; Gáztisztítók; Légtisztítók; Hordozható elektromos hőlégszárítók; LED-es körömszárító készülékek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Lampade da parete; Illuminazioni a LED; Lampadine LED; Lampade da scrivania; Fanali per biciclette; Ghirlande luminose decorative per le feste; Macchine per cuocere il pane; Yogurtiere elettriche; Scalda-poppatoi [elettrici]; Disidratatori elettrici di alimenti per uso domestico; Umidificatori [per uso domestico]; Pulitori e purificatori di gas; Depuratori d'aria; Asciugacapelli elettrico portatile; Apparecchi LED per asciugare le unghie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Sieniniai šviestuvai; Šviesos diodų apšvietimo įtaisai; Šviesos diodų lemputės; Stalinės lempos; Dviračių žibintai; Šventinių lempučių girliandos; Duonos kepimo mašinos; Elektriniai jogurto gaminimo prietaisai; Žindymo buteliukų elektriniai šildytuvai; Elektriniai maisto dehidratoriai namų apyvokos reikmėms; Drėkinimo prietaisai [namų apyvokos reikmėms]; Dujų valymo įrenginiai; Oro gryninimo mašinos; Nešiojamieji elektriniai šilto oro džiovintuvai; Šviesadiodžio (LED) nagų lako džiovinimo aparatai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Sienas gaismekļi; Gaismas diožu gaismekļi; Gaismas diožu spuldzes (LED); Rakstāmgalda lampas; Velosipēdu lukturi; Lampiņu virtenes svētku dekorācijām; Maizes cepamās mašīnas; Elektriskas ierīces jogurta gatavošanai; Elektriskie barošanas pudelīšu sildītāji; Elektriski pārtikas dehidratori mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Mitrinātāji (mājsaimniecības nolūkiem); Gāzu attīrīšanas iekārtas; Gaisa attīrīšanas ierīces; Pārvietojami elektriski silta gaisa žāvētāji; Gaismas diožu (LED) aparāti un ierīces nagu žāvēšanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Dwal tal-ħajt; Dawl LED; Bozoz tad-dawl tal-LED; Lampi tal-iskrivaniji; Dwal tar-roti; Lampi żgħar tat-tiżjin għad-dekorazzjoni festivi; Magni li jaħmu l-ħobż; Tagħmir elettriku li jagħmel il-jogurt; Tagħmir elettriku tat-tisħin, għall-fliexken tat-tisqija; Deidraturi tal-ikel elettriċi għal skopijiet domestiċi; Umdaturi [għal skopijiet domestiċi]; Tagħmir għat-tindif tal-gass u purifikaturi; Purifikaturi tal-arja; Tagħmir elettriku li jnixxef bl-arja sħuna, li jista' jinġarr; Apparat LED għat-tnixxif tad-dwiefer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Wandverlichting; Led-verlichting; LED-lichtpeertjes; Bureaulampen; Fietslampen; Lampions; Broodbakmachines; Elektrische yoghurtmachines; Zuigflesverwarmers, elektrisch; Elektrische voedseldehydrators voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Bevochtigers [voor huishoudelijke doeleinden]; Gasreinigings- en -zuiveringsinstallaties; Luchtzuiveraars; Draagbare elektrische warmeluchtdrogers; Ledapparaten voor het drogen van de nagels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Oświetlenie ścienne; Urządzenia oświetleniowe LED; Żarówki oświetleniowe LED; Lampki biurkowe; Światła rowerowe; Kolorowe światełka do dekoracji świątecznych; Urządzenia do pieczenia chleba; Urządzenia elektryczne do robienia jogurtu; Elektryczne podgrzewacze do butelek do karmienia; Elektryczne suszarki do żywności do użytku domowego; Nawilżacze powietrza [do celów domowych]; Urządzenia do oczyszczania gazu; Oczyszczacze powietrza; Przenośne elektryczne suszarki wykorzystujące ciepłe powietrze; Urządzenia LED do suszenia paznokci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Lâmpadas de murais; Luminárias LED; Lâmpadas de iluminação LED; Candeeiros de secretária; Luzes para bicicletas; Correntes de luzes para decorações festivas; Máquinas para cozinhar pão; Iogurteiras elétricas; Aquece-biberões elétricos; Desidratadores elétricos de alimentos para uso doméstico; Humidificadores [para fins domésticos]; Produtos de limpeza e purificação do gás; Purificadores do ar; Secadores de ar quente elétricos portáteis; Aparelhos de secagem de unhas por meio de LED.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aplice de perete; Luminatoare LED; Becuri cu LED; Lămpi de birou; Lanterne de biciclete; Ghirlande luminoase pentru decorațiuni festive; Mașini de făcut pâine; Aparate electrice de făcut iaurt; Încălzitoare electrice de biberoane; Dispozitive electrice pentru deshidratarea alimentelor, de uz casnic; Umidificatoare [pentru uz domestic]; Epurare și purificare a gazelor; Purificatoare de aer; Uscător electric portabil, cu aer cald; Aparate cu leduri pentru uscarea unghiilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Svetlá na priedeloch; LED svietidlá; LED žiarovky; Lampy na písacie stoly; Svietidlá na bicykle; Dekoračné svetelné reťaze; Zariadenia na pečenie chleba; Elektrické prístroje na výrobu jogurtov; Elektrické ohrievače na detské fľaše; Elektrické sušičky potravín pre domácnosti; Zvlhčovače vzduchu pre domácnosť; Prístroje na čistenie plynu; Čističe vzduchu; Prenosné elektrické teplovzdušné sušiče; LED prístroje na sušenie nechtov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Stenske svetilke; LED svetila; LED žarnice; Svetilke za pisalno mizo; Kolesarske luči; Lučke za praznično okrasitev; Naprave za peko kruha; Električni aparati za izdelavo jogurta; Električni grelniki za stekleničke za hranjenje otrok; Električni sušilniki hrane za gospodinjske namene; Vlažilniki [za gospodinjske namene]; Plinske naprave za čiščenje in prečiščevanje; Prečiščevalci zraka; Prenosni električni sušilniki s toplim zrakom; LED aparati za sušenje nohtov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Lampor för väggprydnad; LED-ljuskällor; LED-glödlampor; Skrivbordslampor; Cykelbelysning; Ljusslingor för dekoration; Brödbakningsmaskiner; Elektriska anordningar för tillverkning av yoghurt; Elektriska uppvärmningsanordningar för nappflaskor; Elektriska livsmedelsavfuktare för hushållsändamål; Luftfuktare [för hushållsändamål]; Gasrenings- och gasrengöringsanordningar; Luftrenare; Bärbara elektriska varmluftstorkar; LED-apparater för torkning av naglar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/083</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/155</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-17</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082683</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15066</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
