<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T09:40:08</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229231</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229231</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>YH-MAY</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Спортни топки; Игли за помпи за надуване на топки за игри; Помпи, специално пригодени за употреба с топки за игри; Гимнастически уреди; Делтаплани; Рингове за стискане с цел заздравяване на ръцете; Топки за упражнения; Уреди за трениране на тялото; Боксови круши; Гимнастически лостове и успоредки; Успоредка; Ръчно задвижвано оборудване за упражнения; Въжета за скачане; Тежести за крака за упражнения; Топка с перце [за бадминтон]; Боксови ръкавици; Кожени калъфи [спортни артикули]; Налакътници [спортни артикули]; Наколенки [спортни артикули]; Ремъци за йога; Йога блокчета; Люлки за йога; Топки за йога; Колани за щангисти; Ленти за дръжки за ракети за бадминтон.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Sportovní míče; Jehly do pumpiček na nafukování míčů na míčové hry; Pumpy speciálně upravené k použití se herními míči; Posilovače prsních svalů (expandéry); Závěsné kluzáky; Kroužky na posilování stisku ruky; Míče na cvičení; Posilovací stroje; Boxovací pytle; Gymnastické hrazdy; Bradla na gymnastiku; Ručně ovládaná zařízení ke cvičení; Švihadla; Závaží na cvičení nohou; Bedmintonové míčky; Boxerské rukavice; Chrániče holení [sportovní potřeby]; Loketní chrániče [sportovní potřeby]; Kolení chrániče [sportovní potřeby]; Pásy na cvičení jógy; Bloky (pomůcky) na cvičení jógy; Popruhy na jógu; Míče ke cvičení jógy; Vzpěračské pásy [sportovní výstroj]; Ovinovací pásky na rukojeti badmintonových raket.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sportsbolde; Nåle til pumper til oppustning af bolde til spil; Pumper, der er særligt beregnet til spillebolde; Ekspandere [muskelstrækkere]; Dragefly; Ringe til træning af håndgrebsstyrke; Træningsbolde; Apparater til bodybuilding; Boksebolde; Vandrette barrer til gymnastik; Gymnastikbarrer; Manuelt træningsudstyr; Sjippetov; Ankelvægte til træningsbrug; Badmintonbolde; Handsker (bokse -); Skinnebensbeskyttere [sportsartikler]; Albuebeskyttere [sportsartikler]; Knæbeskyttere [sportsartikler]; Yogastropper; Yogablokke; Yogagynger; Gymnastikbolde til yoga; Nyrebælter [sportsartikler]; Grebsbånd til badmintonketsjere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Sportball; Nadeln für Pumpen zum Aufblasen von Spielbällen; Speziell angepasste Pumpen für Spielbälle; Expander; Hängegleiter; Handübungsringe; Trainingsbälle; Bodybuilding-Geräte; Punchingbälle; Recks; Barren als Turngerät; Manuell betätigte Fitnessgeräte; Springseile; Beingewichte für Trainingszwecke; Federballspiele; Boxhandschuhe; Schienbeinschutz [Sportartikel]; Ellbogenschützer [Sportartikel]; Knieschützer [Sportartikel]; Yoga-Gurte; Yogablöcke; Yogaschaukeln; Yoga-Bälle; Gewichthebergürtel [Sportartikel]; Griffbänder für Federballschläger.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αθλητικές μπάλες· Βελόνες για αεραντλίες για το φούσκωμα μπαλών παιχνιδιού· Αντλίες ειδικά προσαρμοσμένες για χρήση με μπάλες για παιχνίδια· Ανάπτυξης-όργανα· Ανεμόπτερα· Κρίκοι ενδυνάμωσης λαβής· Μπάλες σωματικής άσκησης· Αποκατάστασης σώματος συσκευές· Πυγμαχίας σάκκοι· Μονόζυγα [για γυμναστική]· Δίζυγα γυμναστικής· Χειροκίνητος εξοπλισμός άσκησης· Σχοινάκια για υπερπηδήσεις· Βάρη ποδιών για άσκηση· Μπαλάκια του μπάντμιντον [παιχνίδια]· Γάντια πυγμαχίας· Περικνήμια [είδη αθλητισμού]· Προστατευτικά αγκώνων [αθλητικά είδη]· Επιγονατίδες [αθλητικά είδη]· Ιμάντες για γιόγκα· Κύβοι για γιόγκα· Κούνιες για γιόγκα· Μπάλες γυμναστικής για γιόγκα· Άρση βαρών (ζώνες για -) [αθλητικά είδη]· Ταινίες λαβής για ρακέτες μπάντμιντον.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Balls for sports; Needles for pumps for inflating balls for games; Pumps for inflating sports balls; Chest expanders; Hang gliders; Hand grip strengthener rings; Exercise balls; Chest exercisers; Body-building apparatus; Punching bags for boxing; Horizontal bars [for gymnastic]; Gymnastic parallel bars; Manually operated exercise equipment; Jump ropes; Leg weights for exercising; Shuttlecocks; Boxing gloves; Shin guards for athletic use; Elbow guards [sports articles]; Knee guards for athletic use; Yoga straps; Yoga blocks; Yoga swings; Gym balls for yoga; Weight lifting belts; Grip bands for badminton rackets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pelotas de deporte; Agujas de infladores para pelotas de juego; Bombas especialmente adaptadas para su uso con pelotas para juegos; Extensores para pectorales; Alas delta; Anillos fortalecedores de manos; Pelotas para hacer ejercicio; Aparatos de culturismo; Sacos de boxeo; Barras horizontales para gimnasia; Barras paralelas para gimnasia; Equipos manuales de ejercicios físicos; Cuerdas para saltar a la comba; Pesas para ejercitar las piernas; Volantes para juegos de raqueta; Guantes de boxeo; Espinilleras [artículos de deporte]; Coderas [artículos de deporte]; Rodilleras [artículos de deporte]; Cintas para yoga; Bloques para yoga; Columpios de yoga; Pelotas de gimnasia para yoga; Cinturones de halterofilia; Cintas para empuñaduras de raquetas de bádminton.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Spordipallid; Pallipumpade nõelad; Spetsiaalselt mängupallidega kasutamiseks kohandatud pumbad; Ekspandrid, tõmmitsad; Lohelennukid, deltaplaanid; Käehaarde tugevdusrõngad; Võimlemispallid; Füüsilise vormi parandamise/taastamise seadmed; Poksikotid; Rööbaspuud [võimlemiseks]; Rööbaspuud; Käsitsi käitatav treeningvarustus; Hüppenöörid; Jalaraskused treenimiseks; Sulgpallid; Poksikindad; Säärekaitsmed [sporditarbed]; Küünarnukikaitsmed [sporditarbed]; Põlvekaitsmed [sporditarbed]; Joogarihmad; Joogas kasutatavad klotsid; Joogakiiged; Võimlemispallid joogaharjutusteks; Tõstevööd [sporditarbed]; Sulgpallireketite käepidemeteip.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Pallot (urheiluvälineet); Peleissä käytettävien pallojen täyttämiseen käytettävät neulat; Erityisesti pelipallojen kanssa käytettävät pumput; Voimaharjoitusvälineet [venytyslaitteet]; Riippuliitimet; Käsiotteen vahvistusrenkaat; Harjoittelupallot; Kehonrakennusvälineet; Nyrkkeilysäkit; Voimistelurekit; Nojapuut (voimistelu); Käsikäyttöiset kuntoiluvälineet; Hyppynarut; Jalkapainot harjoitteluun; Sulkapallot; Nyrkkeilyhansikkaat; Säärisuojukset [urheiluun]; Kyynärsuojat [urheiluun]; Polvisuojukset [urheiluun]; Joogahihnat; Joogapalikat; Joogakeinut; Voimistelupallot joogaa varten; Vyöt (painonnosto -) [urheiluun]; Otenauhat sulkapallomailoihin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Ballons de sport; Aiguilles de pompe de gonflage pour balles de jeu; Pompes spécialement conçues pour ballons de jeu; Exerciseurs [extenseurs]; Ailes delta; Anneaux pour muscler les mains; Balles d'exercice; Appareils pour le culturisme; Punching-balls; Barres horizontales pour la gymnastique; Barres parallèles de gymnastique; Équipements d'exercice physique à commande manuelle; Cordes à sauter; Poids pour exercer les jambes; Volants [jeux]; Gants de boxe; Protège-tibias [articles de sport]; Protège-coudes [articles de sport]; Protège-genoux [articles de sport]; Sangles de yoga; Blocs de yoga; Balançoires de yoga; Ballons de gym pour le yoga; Ceintures d'haltérophilie [articles de sport]; Bandes antidérapantes [grips] pour raquettes de badminton.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Lopte za sport; Igle za pumpe za napuhivanje lopti za igru; Pumpe posebno prilagođenu za lopte za igre; Ekspanderi za prsa; Zmajevi [letjelice]; Koluti za jačanje stiska šake; Lopte za vježbanje; Sprave za body building; Boksačke vreće; Vodoravne prečke [za gimnastiku]; Gimnastičke paralelne prečke; Oprema za vježbanje s ručnim pogonom; Užad za preskakanje; Utezi za noge za tjelovježbu; Loptice za badminton; Boksačke rukavice; Zaštita za cjevanice [sportski pribor]; Štitnici za laktove [sportski artikli]; Zaštita za koljena [sportski artikli]; Remenje za jogu; Kocke za jogu; Ljuljačke za jogu; Lopte za vježbanje joge; Remenje za dizanje utega [sportski artikli]; Trake za drške badmintonskih reketa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Sportlabdák; Szeleptűk játéklabdák felfújására szolgáló pumpákhoz; Speciális pumpák labdajátékokhoz használt labdákhoz; Mellkas expanderek [edzőeszközök]; Sárkányrepülők; Marokerősítő gyűrűk; Fitness labdák; Testedző berendezések; Bokszzsákok [boxzsákok]; Nyújtók [szertornához]; Párhuzamos tornakorlátok; Kézi működtetésű edzőfelszerelések; Ugrálókötelek; Lábsúlyok testedzéshez; Tollaslabdák; Ökölvívó kesztyűk, bokszkesztyűk [boxkesztyűk]; Sípcsontvédők [sportcikkek]; Könyökvédők [sportcikkek]; Térdvédők [sportcikkek]; Jógaszalagok; Jógablokkok; Jógahinták; Jógalabdák; Súlyemelő övek [sportcikkek]; Szalagok tollaslabda ütők markolatára.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Palle per lo sport; Anelli di pompaggio per gonfiare palle da gioco; Pompe specifiche per palle per giochi; Estensori [attrezzi ginnici]; Deltaplani; Anelli per rafforzare la presa; Palloni per esercizi; Apparecchi per il culturismo; Punchingball; Barre orizzontali per la ginnastica; Sbarre parallele da ginnastica; Attrezzi per esercizi fisici azionati manualmente; Corde per fare saltelli; Pesi per le gambe per l'esercizio fisico; Volani [giochi]; Guantoni da pugilato; Parastinchi [articoli per lo sport]; Paragomiti [articoli sportivi]; Paraginocchi [articoli sportivi]; Cinghie per yoga; Blocchetti per lo yoga; Altalene per lo yoga; Palle da ginnastica per yoga; Cinture per sollevatore di pesi [articoli sportivi]; Fasce per impugnature per racchette da volano.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Sportiniai kamuoliai; Pompų adatos (žaidimų kamuoliams pripūsti); Specialiosios žaidimų kamuolių pompos; Krūtinės treniravimo espanderiai; Skraidyklės; Plaštakos stiprinimo žiedai; Fizinių pratimų kamuoliai; Fizinių pratimų prietaisai [kūnui treniruoti]; Bokso kriaušės; Skersiniai [gimnastikos]; Gimnastikos lygiagretės; Rankiniu būdu valdoma treniruočių įranga; Šokdynės; Kojų svarmenys mankštos reikmėms; Plunksninukai (badmintono kamuoliukai); Bokso pirštinės; Blauzdų apsaugos [sporto reikmenys]; Antalkūniai [sporto reikmenys]; Antkeliai [sporto reikmenys]; Jogos diržai; Jogos kaladėlės; Jogos sūpynės; Jogos gimnastikos kamuoliai; Sunkumų kilnojimo diržai [sporto reikmenys]; Badmintono rakečių rankenų [kotų] juostos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Sporta bumbas; Spēļu bumbu sūkņu adatas; Spēļu bumbu sūkņi; Espanderi; Deltaplāni; Roku tvēriena stiprināšanas riņķi; Treniņu bumbas; Atlētiskās vingrošanas ierīces; Boksa maisi; Horizontālie vingrošanas stieņi; Vingrošanas līdztekas; Ar roku darbināmi trenažieri; Lecamauklas; Kāju atsvari vingrinājumiem; Badmintona volāni; Boksa cimdi; Apakšstilbu aizsargi sportam; Elkoņu aizsargi sportistiem; Ceļgalu aizsargi sportistiem; Siksnas jogas nodarbībām; Klucīši jogas nodarbībām; Jogas šūpoles; Sporta zāles bumbas jogai; Svarcēlāju jostas (sporta piederumi); Rokturu pretslīdes saites badmintona raketēm.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Blalen tal-isports; Labar għal pompi biex jintefħu l-blalen għal logħob; Pompi adattati b'mod partikolari għall-użu ma' blalen tal-logħob; Wessiegħa tas-sider [apparat għall-eżerċizzji fiżiċi]; Strutturi li jixbħu lil tajra kbira għal prattikar tat-tajran; Ċrieket li jsaħħu l-qabda tal-idejn; Blalen ta' l-eżerċizzju; Apparat għat-taħriġ tal-muskoli; Xkejjer għat-taħriġ tad-daqqiet ta' ponn (għall-prattika sportiva); Żbarri orizzontali tal-ġinnastika; Żbarri paralleli għall-ġinnastika; Tagħmir għall-eżerċizzju mħaddem bl-idejn; Ħbula tal-qbiż; Piżijiet għal mas-saqajn għall-eżerċizzju; Sufra tonda b'dawra rix mixħuta fil-badmintin; Ingwanti kkuttunati tal-boksing; Kuxxinetti għall-protezzjoni tal-qasba tas-sieq (oġġetti tal-isports); Protezzjoni għall-minkbejn [oġġetti sportivi]; Kuxxinetti għall-protezzjoni tal-irkoppa (oġġetti tal-isports); Ċineg tal-Joga; Blokki tal-joga; Bandli tal-joga; Blalen tal-ġimm għall-Yoga; Ċinturini għall-irfigħ tal-piżijiet [oġġetti sportivi]; Faxex għall-qabda tal-manku tar-rakketti tal-bedmintin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Sportballen; Naalden voor pompen voor opblaasbare ballen voor spellen; Pompen voor speelballen; Trekveren voor spieroefeningen; Deltavliegers; Ringen voor het versterken van de handgreep; Trainingsballen; Fitnesstoestellen; Boksballen; Gelijke brug [voor gymnastiek]; Bruggen voor gymnastiekoefeningen; Handbediende fitnessapparatuur; Springtouwen; Beengewichten voor oefendoeleinden; Shuttles; Bokshandschoenen; Scheenbeschermers [sportartikelen]; Elleboogbeschermers [sportartikelen]; Kniebeschermers [sportartikelen]; Yogariemen; Yogablokken; Yogaschommels; Yogaballen; Gewichtheffersgordels; Gripbanden voor badmintonrackets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Piłki sportowe; Igły do pompek do pompowania piłek do gier; Pompki specjalnie przystosowane do użytku z piłkami do gier; Ekspandery [ćwiczenia]; Lotnie; Krążki do wzmacniania uchwytu; Piłki do ćwiczeń; Przyrządy stosowane do ćwiczeń fizycznych; Worki treningowe; Gimnastyczne drążki poziome; Poręcze równoległe do gimnastyki; Sprzęt do ćwiczeń fizycznych obsługiwany ręcznie; Skakanki; Treningowe obciążniki na nogi; Lotki [gry]; Rękawice bokserskie; Nagolenniki [artykuły sportowe]; Ochraniacze na łokcie [artykuły sportowe]; Nakolanniki [artykuły sportowe]; Paski do jogi; Bloczki do jogi; Chusty do jogi; Piłki gimnastyczne do jogi; Pasy do podnoszenia ciężarów [artykuły sportowe]; Opaski na uchwyt do rakiet do badmintona.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Bolas de desporto; Agulhas para bombas para insuflar bolas de jogar; Bombas especificamente concebidas para uso com bolas para jogos; Exercitadores [extensores]; Asas delta; Anéis para fortalecer a força de preensão das mãos; Bolas de exercício; Aparelhos para o culturismo; Sacos de boxe; Barras horizontais de ginástica; Barras paralelas para ginástica; Equipamentos de exercício operados manualmente; Cordas de saltar; Pesos para as pernas para fazer exercício; Volantes [artigos de desporto]; Luvas de boxe; Caneleiras [artigos desportivos]; Cotoveleiras [artigos de desporto]; Joelheiras [artigos de desporto]; Cordas para ioga; Plataformas para ioga; Baloiços para ioga; Bolas de ginástica para ioga; Cintos para levantamento de pesos [artigos desportivos]; Faixas para punhos de raquetes de badminton.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Mingi de sport; Ace pentru pompe de umflat mingi de joc; Pompe adaptate special pentru utilizarea cu mingi de jocuri; Extensoare; Deltaplane; Inele de exercițiu pentru întărirea mâinii; Mingi de antrenament; Aparate pentru culturism; Saci de box; Bare orizontale [pentru gimnastică]; Bare paralele [pentru gimnastică]; Echipament de exerciții acționat manual; Coarde de sărit; Greutăți pentru picioare pentru exerciții; Fluturași [badminton]; Mănuși de box; Apărători de tibie [articole de sport]; Apărători de cot [articole de sport]; Apărători de genunchi [articole de sport]; Benzi elastice pentru yoga; Blocuri yoga; Leagăne pentru yoga; Mingi de gimnastică pentru yoga; Centuri pentru halterofili [articole de sport]; Benzi pentru mânerele rachetelor de badminton.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Lopty na použitie pri športe; Ihly do púmp na nafukovanie hracích lôpt; Pumpy na použitie s hracími loptami; Cvičebné náradie na posilňovanie hrudníka; Klzáky (rogalá); Kruhy na posilňovanie stisku rúk; Cvičebné lopty; Posilňovacie stroje; Boxovacie vrecia; Gymnastické hrazdy; Gymnastické bradlá; Manuálne ovládané športové zariadenia na cvičenie; Švihadlá; Závažia na nohy na cvičenie; Bedmintonové košíky; Boxerské rukavice; Chrániče na píšťaly (športový tovar); Chrániče na lakte (športové potreby); Chrániče na kolená (športový tovar); Pásy na cvičenie jogy; Bloky na cvičenie jogy; Popruhy na jogu; Lopty na cvičenie jogy; Opasky pre vzpieračov (športové potreby); Ovinovacie pásky na rukoväti bedmintonových rakiet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Žoge za šport; Igle za tlačilke za napihovanje žog za igro; Zračne tlačilke za žoge; Ekspanderji [za raztegovanje prsnih mišic]; Jadralni zmaji; Obroči za krepitev prstov in zapestja; Žoge za vadbo; Naprave za telovadbo; Boksarske vreče; Horizontalni drogovi za gimnastiko; Gimnastične bradlje; Ročno upravljana oprema za vadbo; Kolebnice; Uteži za noge za vadbo; Žogice za badminton; Boksarske rokavice; Golenski ščitniki [izdelki za šport]; Ščitniki za komolce [športni artikli]; Ščitniki za kolena [športni artikli]; Trakovi za jogo; Bloki za jogo; Gugalnice za jogo; Gimnastične žoge za jogo; Pasovi za dvigovanje uteži (izdelki za šport); Oprijemalni trakovi za loparje za badminton.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Sportbollar; Munstycken till pumpar för pumpning av bollar för spel; Pumpar särskilt anpassade för användning med bollar för spel; Muskelstärkare; Hängglidare; Ringar för stärkande av handgrepp; Bollar för träning; Träningsapparater; Sandsäckar för boxning; Horisontella stänger för gymnastik; Barrer (gymnastikredskap); Manuellt driven träningsutrustning; Hopprep; Benvikter för motion; Badmintonbollar; Boxhandskar; Benskydd [sportartiklar]; Armbågsskydd [sportartiklar]; Knäskydd [sportartiklar]; Remmar för användning med yoga; Yogablock; Yogagungor; Gymnastikbollar för yoga; Tyngdlyftningsbälten [sportartiklar]; Grepptejp för badmintonracketar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/080</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/151</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-11</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081940</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017950257</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-05-29</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
