<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T09:10:20</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229025</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229025</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Boat Hero</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Бази данни; Бази данни (електронни); Компютърен софтуер за управление на база данни; Електронни публикации, които могат да бъдат прехвърляни върху друг носител; Мобилни приложения; Набор за разработване на софтуер (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Databáze; Databáze (elektronické); Počítačový software pro správu databází; Stahovatelné elektronické publikace; Mobilní aplikace; Softwarové vývojové sady (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Databaser; Elektroniske databaser; Computersoftwareprogrammer til databasestyring; Elektroniske publikationer, downloadable; Mobilapplikationer; Udviklingsværktøjer til softwareudvikling [SDK].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Datenbanken; Elektronische Datenbanken; Computersoftware für Datenbankverwaltung; Elektronische Publikationen [herunterladbar]; Mobile Apps; Softwareentwicklungskits [SDK].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Βάσεις δεδομένων· Βάσεις δεδομένων (ηλεκτρονικές)· Προγράμματα λογισμικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για τη διαχείριση βάσεων δεδομένων· Ηλεκτρονικές εκδόσεις, με δυνατότητα μεταφόρτωσης· Εφαρμογές κινητών· Σετ ανάπτυξης λογισμικού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Databases; Databases (electronic); Computer software for database management; Electronic publications, downloadable; Mobile apps; Software development kit [SDK].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bancos de datos; Bases de datos electrónicas; Software de gestión de bases de datos; Publicaciones electrónicas descargables; Aplicaciones de móviles; Kits de desarrollo de software (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arvutite andmebaasid; Elektroonilised andmebaasid; Arvutitarkvaraprogrammid andmebaasi haldamiseks; Elektroonilised allalaaditavad publikatsioonid; Mobiilirakendused; Arendustarkvara (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tietokonetietokannat; Tietokannat (sähköiset); Tietokoneohjelmat tietokantojen hallintaa varten; Elektroniset julkaisut [järjestelmästä toiseen poimittavat]; Mobiilisovellukset; Ohjelmistonkehittämissarjat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bases de données; Bases de données (électroniques); Logiciels de gestion de bases de données; Publications électroniques téléchargeables; Applications logicielles pour téléphones mobiles; Kits de développement logiciel (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Baze podataka; Baze podataka (elektroničke); Računalni softver za upravljanje bazama podataka; Elektronske publikacije koje se mogu preuzeti s Interneta; Mobilne aplikacije; Komplet za razvoj softvera (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Adatbázisok; Elektronikus adatbázisok; Számítógépes szoftver programok adatbáziskezeléshez; Letölthető elektronikus kiadványok, publikációk; Mobil alkalmazások; Szoftverfejlesztési készlet [SDK].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Banche dati; Banche dati (elettroniche); Programmi software per la gestione di banche dati; Pubblicazioni elettroniche [scaricabili]; Applicazioni per cellulari; Kit per sviluppo di software (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Duomenų bazės (programinė įranga); Elektroninės duomenų bazės; Kompiuterių programinė įranga programos duomenų bazėms tvarkyti; Elektroniniai leidiniai [parsisiunčiamieji]; Mobiliųjų įrenginių taikomoji programinė įranga; Programinės įrangos tobulinimo priemonių rinkiniai (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Datubāzes; Elektroniskās datubāzes; Datoru programmatūra datubāzu pārvaldībai; Lejupielādējamas elektroniskās publikācijas; Mobilas lietotnes; Programmatūru izstrādes komplekti (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Banek tad-data; Bażi tad-dejta (elettroniċi); Softwer tal-kompjuter għall-ġestjoni tad-database; Pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi, li jistgħu jitniżżlu; Applikazzjoni tat-tagħmir ċellulari; Kit għall-iżvilupp ta' softwer (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Computerdatabases; Databases (elektronische-); Computer software voor databasebeheer; Elektronische publicaties [te downloaden]; Mobiele applicaties; Sets voor software-ontwikkeling (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Komputerowe bazy danych; Elektroniczne bazy danych; Oprogramowanie komputerowe [programy] do zarządzania bazami danych; Publikacje elektroniczne, do pobrania; Mobilne aplikacje; Zestawy narzędzi do rozwoju oprogramowania (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Bases de dados; Bases de dados eletrónicas; Software para gestão de bases de dados; Publicações eletrónicas descarregáveis; Aplicações móveis; Kit de desenvolvimento de software (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Baze de date computerizate; Baze de date (electronice); Programe informatice pentru administrarea bazelor de date; Publicații electronice descărcabile; Aplicatii mobile; Seturi pentru dezvoltare de software (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Počítačové databázy; Elektronické databázy; Počítačový sofvér na manažment databáz; Elektronické publikácie (sťahovateľné); Mobilné aplikácie; Súbor nástrojov na vývoj softvéru (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Podatkovne baze; Elektronske zbirke podatkov; Računalniška programska oprema za upravljanje baz podatkov; Naložljive elektronske publikacije; Mobilna aplikacija; Kompleti za razvijanje programske opreme [SDK].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Databaser; Databaser (elektroniska); Datorprogram för hantering av databaser; Tidskrifter (elektroniska), nedladdningsbara; Mobilappar; Satser för programvaruutveckling (SDK).</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>12</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Кораби; Превозни средства; Плавателни съдове [лодки и кораби]; Превозни и транспортни средства; Водни превозни средства; Апарати за придвижване по вода; Лодки за продажба като комплект; Моторни яхти; Моторни платноходи; Плавателни съдове за отдих; Платноходи.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Čluny; Vozidla; Plavidla (čluny a lodě); Vozidla a dopravní prostředky; Vodní dopravní prostředky; Prostředky na pohyb po vodě; Čluny na prodej jako soupravy; Motorové čluny; Motorové plachetnice; Čluny pro volný čas; Plachetnice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Både; Transportmidler; Fartøjer [både og skibe]; Køretøjer og befordringsmidler; Vandfartøjer; Apparater til befordring på vand; Både til salg som samlesæt; Motorbåde; Motorsejlbåde; Lystbåde; Sejlbåde.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Boote; Fahrzeuge; Wasserfahrzeuge [Boote und Schiffe]; Fahrzeuge und Beförderungsmittel; Wasserfahrzeuge; Apparate zur Beförderung auf dem Wasser; Boote zum Verkauf in Bauteilen; Motorboote; Motorsegelschiffe; Freizeitboote; Segelboote.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Πλοία· Οχήματα· Σκάφη (σκάφη και πλοία)· Οχήματα και μέσα μεταφοράς· Πλοία /Βάρκες· Μηχανήματα κίνησης στο νερό· Λέμβοι για πώληση σε μορφή σετ· Μηχανοκίνητες λέμβοι· Μηχανοκίνητα ιστιοφόρα· Σκάφη αναψυχής· Ιστιοφόρα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Boats; Vehicles; Vessels [boats and ships]; Vehicles and conveyances; Water vehicles; Apparatus for locomotion by water; Boats for sale in kit form; Powerboats; Motorsailers; Leisure boats; Sailboats.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Barcos; Vehículos; Embarcaciones [barcas y barcos]; Vehículos y medios de transporte; Vehículos acuáticos; Aparatos de locomoción marítima; Barcos para su venta en forma de kit; Embarcaciones a motor; Motoveleros; Barcos de ocio; Barcos de vela.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Paadid, laevad; Transpordivahendid; Veesõidukid [paadid ja laevad]; Sõidukid ja transpordivahendid; Veesõidukid; Veetranspordivahendid; Komplektina müüdavad paadid; Mootorpaadid; Mootorpurjekad; Vabaajapaadid; Purjepaadid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Laivat; Ajoneuvot; Alukset [veneet ja laivat]; Ajoneuvot ja kulkuneuvot; Vesikulkuneuvot; Laitteet vedessä kulkemista varten; Rakennussarjana myytävät veneet; Moottoriveneet; Moottoripurjehtijat; Vapaa-ajan veneet; Huvipurret.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bateaux; Véhicules; Vaisseaux [bateaux et navires]; Véhicules et moyens de transport; Véhicules nautiques; Appareils de locomotion maritimes; Bateaux vendus en kit; Bateaux à moteur; Voiliers à moteur; Bateaux de plaisance; Bateaux à voiles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Brodovi; Vozila; Plovila [čamci i brodovi]; Vozila i prijevozna sredstva; Vodena vozila; Uređaj za kretanje po vodi; Čamci za prodaju u obliku kompleta; Motorni čamci; Motorni jedrenjaci; Plovila za slobodno vrijeme; Jedrilice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hajók; Járművek; Vízi járművek [csónakok és hajók]; Járművek és szállítóeszközök; Vízijárművek; Eszközök vízen történő helyváltoztatáshoz; Összeszerelhető formában árusított csónakok, hajók; Versenymotorcsónakok; Motoros vitorlás hajók, motoros vitorlások; Szabadidős hajók, csónakok; Vitorlások, vitorláshajók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Battelli; Veicoli; Imbarcazioni [navi e barche]; Veicoli e mezzi di trasporto; Veicoli acquatici; Apparecchi di locomozione nautici; Imbarcazioni in vendita in kit; Barche a motore; Barche a vela a motore; Barche da diporto; Catboat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Valtys; Transporto priemonės; Laivai [valtys ir laivai]; Transporto priemonės ir vežimėliai; Vandens transporto priemonės; Aparatai, skirti judėti vandeniu; Laiveliai, parduodami sukomplektuoti; Motorinės valtys; Varikliniai burlaiviai; Laisvalaikio laiveliai; Burlaiviai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Laivas; Transporta līdzekļi; Kuģi (laivas un kuģi); Transportlīdzekļi un pārvietošanas līdzekļi; Ūdens transportlīdzekļi; Aparāti, kas paredzēti, lai pārvietotos pa ūdeni; Laivas pārdošanai komplektu veidā; Ātrlaivas; Motorjahtas; Atpūtas laivas; Buru laivas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Dgħajjes; Vetturi; Bastimenti [dgħajjes u vapuri]; Vetturi u vetturi għall-ġarr; Vetturi tal-ilma; Apparat għal-lokomozzjoni fuq l-ilma; Dgħajjes għall-bejgħ fil-forma ta' kittijiet; Dgħajjes b'magni qawwija; Dgħajjes tal-qlugħ motorizzati; Dgħajjes tal-ħin ħieles; Dgħajjes tal-qlugħ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Boten; Vervoermiddelen; Vaartuigen [boten en schepen]; Voertuigen en vervoermiddelen; Vaartuigen; Apparaten voor vervoer over het water; Boten als pakket te koop; Motorjachten; Motorzeilboten; Plezierboten; Zeilboten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Łodzie; Pojazdy; Jednostki pływające [łodzie i statki]; Pojazdy i środki transportu; Pojazdy do poruszania się po wodzie; Urządzenia do poruszania się po wodzie; Łodzie do sprzedaży w zestawach; Łodzie motorowe; Żaglówki motorowe; Rekreacyjne łodzie; Łodzie żaglowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Barcos; Veículos; Embarcações [barcos e navios]; Veículos e meios de transporte; Veículos aquáticos; Aparelhos para locomoção aquática; Barcos para serem vendidos em kits; Barcos a motor; Veleiros motorizados; Barcos de lazer; Veleiros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Nave; Vehicule; Nave [bărci și vapoare]; Vehicule și mijloace de transport; Vehicule acvatice; Mijloace de locomoție pe apă; Bărci comercializate sub formă de set; Bărci cu motor; Veliere motorizate; Ambarcațiuni de agrement; Veliere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Lode, člny; Vozidlá; Plavidlá [lode a člny]; Vozidlá a dopravné prostriedky; Vodné dopravné prostriedky; Zariadenia na pohyb po vode; Člny predávané v podobe súprav; Rýchle motorové člny; Motorové plachetnice; Lode na trávenie voľného času; Plachetnice (lode poháňané náporom vetra do napnutých plachiet).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Čolni; Vozila; Plovila [čolni in ladje]; Vozila in prevozna sredstva; Vodna vozila; Aparati za gibanje po vodi; Čolni, ki se prodajajo v kompletu; Motorni čolni; Motorne jadrnice; Čolni za prosti čas; Jadrnice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Båtar; Fordon och farkoster; Fartyg [båtar och skepp]; Fordon och -fortskaffningsmedel; Vattenfarkoster; Fortskaffningsmedel för transport på vatten; Båtar till försäljning i form av satser; Motoriserade lustjakter; Motorsegelbåtar; Fritidsbåtar; Segelbåtar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Организиране и провеждане на търгове по интернет; Рекламни, маркетингови и промоционални услуги; Осигуряване на онлайн пазар за покупко-продажби на стоки и услуги; Организиране на търгове; Осигуряване на онлайн аукционни услуги; Провеждане на интерактивни виртуални аукциони; Аукциони за превозни средства; Провеждане на търгове през интернет; Рекламиране чрез афиши; Осигуряване на рекламно пространство, време и средства; Компютъризирано насърчаване на покупко-продажбите; Рекламни услуги, свързани с бази данни; Осигуряване на услуги за онлайн сравнение на цени.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Sjednávání a vedení internetových aukcí; Reklamní, marketingové a propagační služby; Provozování online trhu pro kupující a prodejce výrobků a služeb; Vedení dražeb; Poskytování služeb v oblasti online aukcí; Pořádání interaktivních virtuálních aukcí; Dražba vozidel; Pořádání dražeb na internetu; Venkovní reklama; Poskytování prostor, času a médií pro reklamu; Počítačová propagace obchodní činnosti; Reklamní služby v oblasti databází; Poskytování online služeb týkajících se porovnávání cen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Arrangering og afholdelse af internetauktioner; Virksomhed vedrørende reklame, marketing og salgsfremstød; Tilvejebringelse af en onlinemarkedsplads til købere og sælgere af varer og tjenesteydelser; Auktionsvirksomhed; Udbydelse af online auktionsvirksomhed; Afholdelse af interaktive virtuelle auktioner; Bortauktionering af køretøjer; Auktionsvirksomhed via internettet; Udendørs avertering; Tilvejebringelse af reklameplads, -tid og -medier; Computerstyret virksomhedspromovering; Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed vedrørende databaser; Tilvejebringelse af en onlineprissammenligningstjeneste.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Veranstaltung und Durchführung von Internetauktionen; Werbung, Marketing und Verkaufsförderung; Bereitstellen eines Online-Marktplatzes für Käufer und Verkäufer von Waren und Dienstleistungen; Auktions- und Versteigerungsdienste; Durchführung von online Auktionen; Durchführung von interaktiven virtuellen Auktionen; Durchführung von Fahrzeugauktionen; Durchführung von Auktionen und Versteigerungen im Internet; Außenwerbung; Zur Verfügung stellen von Werbeflächen, Werbezeiten und Werbeträgern; Computergestützte Werbung; Werbung für Datenbanken; Online bereitgestellte Preisvergleichsdienste.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διοργάνωση και διεξαγωγή διαδικτυακών δημοπρασιών· Διαφήμιση, ενέργειες πώλησης (μάρκετινγκ) και υπηρεσίες προώθησης· Παροχή χώρων αγορών επί γραμμής για αγοραστές και πωλητές προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών· Υπηρεσίες δημοπρασιών· Υπηρεσίες δημοπρασιών επί γραμμής (on line)· Διεξαγωγή διαδραστικών εικονικών δημοπρασιών· Δημοπρασίες οχημάτων· Δημοπρασίες παρεχόμενες μέσω του Διαδικτύου (INTERNET)· Αφισοκόλληση· Παροχή διαφημιστικού χώρου, χρόνου και διαφημιστικών μέσων ενημέρωσης· Προώθηση επιχειρήσεων μέσω ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Υπηρεσίες διαφήμισης σχετικά με βάσεις δεδομένων· Παροχή υπηρεσιών σύγκρισης τιμών επί γραμμής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Arranging and conducting of Internet auctions; Advertising, marketing and promotional services; Provision of an online marketplace for buyers and sellers of goods and services; Auctioneering services; Providing on-line auction services; Conducting interactive virtual auctions; Auctioning of vehicles; Auctioneering provided on the internet; Outdoor advertising; Provision of advertising space, time and media; Computerised business promotion; Advertising services relating to data bases; Provision of online price comparison services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Organización y celebración de subastas por Internet; Servicios promocionales, de marketing y publicidad; Suministro de espacios de venta en línea para vendedores y compradores de productos y servicios; Prestación de servicios de subasta; Prestación de servicios de subastas en línea; Celebración de subastas virtuales interactivas; Subastas de vehículos; Servicios de subastas prestados en Internet; Publicidad exterior; Servicios de provisión de espacios multimedia y publicitarios; Promoción de negocios por ordenador; Servicios publicitarios relacionados con bases de datos; Prestación de servicios de comparación de precios en línea.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Internetioksjonite korraldamine ja läbiviimine; Reklaam ja turundus; Veebipõhise müügikeskkonna pakkumine kaupade ja teenuste ostjatele ning müüjatele; Oksjonid, enampakkumised; Võrguoksjonite korraldamine; Interaktiivsete virtuaaloksjonite läbiviimine; Sõidukioksjonid; Interneti kaudu oksjonite korraldamine; Välireklaam; Reklaamipindade, -aja ja -vahendite pakkumine; Ettevõtte reklaam arvuti kaudu; Andmebaaside reklaam; Hinnavõrdlusteenuste pakkumine veebis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Verkkohuutokauppojen järjestäminen ja toteutus; Mainonta-, markkinointi- ja myynninedistämispalvelut; Online-markkinapaikan tarjoaminen tavaroiden ja palvelujen ostajille ja myyjille; Huutokauppapalvelut; Online-muodossa tarjottavat huutokauppapalvelut; Vuorovaikutteisten virtuaalihuutokauppojen toteutus; Ajoneuvojen huutokauppa; Huutokauppatoiminta Internetissä; Ulkomainonta; Mainostilan, -ajan ja -välineiden tarjoaminen; Tietokoneistettu yritysten myynninedistäminen; Tietokantoihin liittyvät mainontapalvelut; Online-hintavertailupalveluiden tarjoaminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Organisation et conduite d’enchères sur Internet; Services de publicité, de marketing et de promotion; Mise à disposition d'espaces de vente en ligne pour acheteurs et vendeurs de produits et services; Services de vente aux enchères; Prestation de services de vente aux enchères en ligne; Conduite d’enchères virtuelles interactives; Vente aux enchères de véhicules; Services de ventes aux enchères disponibles sur Internet; Publicité extérieure; Mise à disposition d'espace, de temps et de supports publicitaire; Promotion commerciale informatisée; Services publicitaires liés à des bases de données; Fourniture de services de comparaison des prix en ligne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Organizacija i provedba internetskih dražbi; Usluge oglašavanja, marketinga i promidžbe; Pružanje internetskog tržišnog prostora za kupce i prodavatelje proizvoda i usluga; Usluge prodaja na dražbi; Pružanje usluge dražbi putem Interneta; Provedba interaktivnih virtualnih dražbi; Dražba vozila; Dražbovanje na Internetu; Plakatiranje [oglašavanje]; Pružanje oglasnog prostora, vremena i usluge oglasnih medija; Računalna promocija poslovanja; Usluge oglašavanja u svezi s bazama podataka; Pružanje usluga usporedbe cijena na mreži.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Internetes aukciók megrendezése és lebonyolítása; Reklámozási, marketing és promóciós szolgáltatások; Online piactér biztosítása áruk és szolgáltatások eladói és vásárlói részére; Árverési szolgáltatások; Online árverési szolgáltatás biztosítása; Interaktív virtuális aukciók lebonyolítása; Járművek árverezése; Internetes árverezés; Szabadtéri reklámozás, hirdetés; Hirdetési hely, idő és média rendelkezésre bocsátása; Számítógépesített üzleti promóció; Adatbázisokkal kapcsolatos reklámozási szolgáltatások; Online árösszehasonlítási szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Organizzazione e conduzione di aste su Internet; Servizi pubblicitari, di marketing e promozionali; Fornitura di un mercato online per acquirenti e venditori di beni e servizi; Servizi di vendita all'asta; Fornitura di servizi di aste on-line; Attuazione di aste virtuali interattive; Vendita all'asta di veicoli; Vendite all'asta su Internet; Pubblicità esterna; Fornitura di spazi pubblicitari, orario e mezzi di comunicazione; Promozione aziendale computerizzata; Servizi pubblicitari relativi a bance dati; Servizi di confronto di prezzi online.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Internetinių aukcionų rengimas ir vykdymas; Reklamos, rinkodaros ir pardavimų skatinimo paslaugos; Interneto prekyviečių teikimas prekių ir paslaugų pardavėjams bei pirkėjams; Pardavimas aukcione; Internetinių aukcionų paslaugų teikimas; Interaktyvių virtualiųjų aukcionų vedimas; Transporto priemonių aukcionai; Aukcionų rengimas internete; Viešasis reklamavimas; Reklamos vietos, laiko ir žiniasklaidos priemonių parūpinimas; Kompiuterizuotas verslo skatinimas; Reklamos paslaugos, susijusios su duomenų bazėmis; Tiesioginės kreipties kainų palyginimo paslaugų teikimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Interneta izsoļu rīkošana un vadīšana; Reklāmas, tirgvedības un preču noieta veicināšanas pakalpojumi; Tiešsaistes tirgus nodrošināšana preču un pakalpojumu pārdevējiem un pircējiem; Izsoļu organizēšana; Tiešsaistes izsoļu nodrošināšana; Interaktīvo virtuālo izsoļu vadīšana; Transportlīdzekļu izsole; Izsoles ar interneta starpniecību; Afišu izvietošana; Reklāmas laukumu, reklāmas laika un reklāmas nesēju nodrošināšana; Datorizēta biznesa veicināšana; Reklāmas pakalpojumi, kas ir saistīti ar datubāzēm; Tiešsaistes cenu salīdzināšanas pakalpojumu nodrošināšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Organizzazzjoni u tmexxija ta’ rkanti fuq l-Internet; Servizzi ta' reklamar, kummerċjaliżżazzjoni u promozzjonali; Forniment ta' suq onlajn għal xerrejja u bejjiegħa ta' prodotti u servizzi; Servizzi ta' irkantijiet; Il-provvista ta' servizzi ta' rkant onlajn; Twettiq ta’ rkanti virtwali interattivi; Irkant ta' vetturi; Irkant provdut permezz tal-internet; Reklamar fuq barra; Proviżjoni ta' spazju għar-reklamar, ħin u midja; Promozzjoni kompjuterizzata tan-negozju; Servizzi ta' reklamar dwar dejtabejżis; Provvista ta' servizzi ta' paragun ta' prezzijiet onlajn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Het organiseren en houden van veilingen via het internet; Reclame, marketing en promotionele diensten; Ter beschikking stellen van online verkoopplaats voor kopers en verkopers van goederen en diensten; Veilingdiensten; Online veilingen; Het houden van interactieve virtuele veilingen; Veiling van voertuigen; Veilingen op internet; Reclame door aanplakbiljetten; Verschaffen van advertentieruimte, -tijd en -media; Promotie (Geautomatiseerde zakelijke -); Reclame met betrekking tot databases; Verstrekking van onlineprijsvergelijkingen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Organizowanie i przeprowadzanie aukcji za pośrednictwem internetu; Usługi reklamowe, marketingowe i promocyjne; Zapewnianie platformy internetowej dla nabywców i sprzedawców towarów i usług; Usługi aukcyjne; Usługi aukcyjne online; Przeprowadzanie interaktywnych aukcji wirtualnych; Aukcje samochodowe; Usługi w zakresie licytacji świadczone w Internecie; Reklama zewnętrzna; Udostępnianie powierzchni reklamowej, czasu reklamowego i mediów; Skomputeryzowana promocja działalności gospodarczej; Usługi reklamowe dotyczące baz danych; Świadczenie usług porównania cen online.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Organização e realização de leilões na Internet; Serviços de publicidade, de marketing e de promoção; Disponibilização de um espaço de mercado online para compradores e vendedores de produtos e serviços; Serviços de leilões; Serviços de venda em leilão prestados on-line; Realização de leilões virtuais interativos; Leilão de veículos; Leilões prestados na Internet; Serviços de publicidade de exterior; Fornecimento de espaço, tempo e meios publicitários; Promoção informatizada de empresas; Serviços publicitários relacionados com bases de dados; Fornecimento de serviços de comparação de preços em linha.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Organizare și coordonare de licitații pe Internet; Servicii de publicitate, marketing și promovare; Furnizarea unei piețe online pentru cumpărătorii și vânzătorii de bunuri și servicii; Vânzare prin licitație publică; Furnizare de servicii online de licitație; Organizare de licitații virtuale interactive; Vânzare prin licitație a vehiculelor; Vânzări prin licitații disponibile pe internet; Afișaj; Închiriere spațiu publicitar, închirierea minutelor publicitare și a presei; Promovare computerizată de afaceri; Servicii publicitare privind baze de date; Furnizarea de servicii online de comparare de prețuri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Organizovanie a vedenie internetových aukcií; Reklamné, marketingové a propagačné služby; Online poskytovanie obchodného priestoru pre nákupcov a predajcov tovarov a služieb; Dražby; Poskytovanie dražobných služieb online; Realizácia interaktívnych virtuálnych aukcií; Dražba vozidiel; Dražby na internete; Vonkajšia reklama; Poskytovanie priestorov, času a médií na reklamu; Počítačová obchodná propagácia; Reklamné služby v oblasti databáz; Poskytovanie služieb v oblasti on-line porovnávania cien.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Organizacija in vodenje internetnih dražb; Oglaševalske, tržne in promocijske storitve; Zagotavljanje spletnega trga za kupce in prodajalce blaga in storitev; Storitve v zvezi s prodajami na dražbi; Nudenje storitev spletnih dražb; Vodenje interaktivnih virtualnih dražb; Dražba vozil; Prodajanje na dražbi, na internetu; Plakatiranje; Nudenje oglaševalskega prostora, časa in medijev; Računalniško podprta poslovna promocija; Oglaševalske storitve v zvezi z bazami podatkov; Nudenje storitev spletne primerjave cen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Arrangerande och genomförande av internetauktioner; Reklam, marknadsföring och säljfrämjande tjänster; Tillhandahållande av en marknadsplats online för köpare och säljare av varor och tjänster; Auktionering; Upplåtande av auktionstjänster online; Genomförande av interaktiva virtuella auktioner; Auktionering av fordon; Auktionering via Internet; Utomhusreklam; Upplåtande av annonsutrymme, tid och media; Datoriserad företagsfrämjande verksamhet; Reklamtjänster avseende databaser; Tillhandahållande av tjänster avseende prisjämförelser online.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>38</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Предоставяне на достъп до онлайн бази данни; Предоставяне на потребителски достъп до платформи в интернет; Предоставяне на достъп до платформи за електронна търговия в Интернет.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Poskytování přístupu k on-line databázím; Poskytování uživatelského přístupu k platformám na internetu; Poskytování přístupu k platformám elektronického obchodování na internetu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tilvejebringelse af adgang til online-computerdatabaser; Tilvejebringelse af brugeradgang til platforme på internettet; Tilvejebringelse af adgang til e-handel-platforme.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bereitstellung des Zugriffs auf Online-Computerdatenbanken; Bereitstellung eines Benutzerzugangs zu Internet-Plattformen; Bereitstellung eines Zugangs zu einer E-Commerce-Plattform im Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παροχή πρόσβασης σε ηλεκτρονικές βάσεις δεδομένων· Παροχή πρόσβασης χρήστη σε διαδικτυακές πλατφόρμες· Παροχή πρόσβασης σε διαδικτυακή πλατφόρμα ηλεκτρονικού εμπορίου.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Providing access to online computer databases; Providing user access to platforms on the Internet; Providing access to e-commerce platforms on the Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de acceso a bases de datos en línea; Servicios de acceso de usuario a plataformas en Internet; Servicios de acceso a plataformas de comercio electrónico en Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Andmebaasidele juurdepääsu pakkumine veebis; Kasutajajuurdepääsu pakkumine internetiplatvormidele; Juurdepääsu pakkumine e-kaubanduse platvormidele Internetis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Yhteyden tarjoaminen online-tietokantoihin; Yhteyden tarjoaminen Internet-alustoille; Yhteyden tarjoaminen Internetissä oleviin verkkokauppa-alustoihin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Fourniture d'accès à des bases de données informatiques en ligne; Fourniture d'accès à des plates-formes sur Internet pour des utilisateurs; Fourniture d'accès à des plates-formes de commerce électronique sur Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Davanje pristupa online bazama podataka; Pružanje korisničkog pristupa platformama na Internetu; Davanje pristupa platformama za e-trgovinu na Internetu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Online adatbázisokhoz való hozzáférés biztosítása; Internetes felületekhez való felhasználói hozzáférés biztosítása; E-kereskedelmi platformokhoz való hozzáférés biztosítása az interneten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Fornitura di accesso a banche date online; Fornitura all'utenza di servizi d'accesso a piattaforme su internet; Fornitura di servizi d'accesso a piattaforme e-commerce su internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Prieigos prie internetinių kompiuterių duomenų bazių teikimas; Naudotojo prieigos prie interneto platformų teikimas; Prieigos prie internetinių elektroninės prekybos platformų teikimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Piekļuves nodrošināšana datoru datubāzēm tiešsaistē; Lietotāju piekļuves nodrošināšana internetā esošām platformām; Pieejas nodrošināšana elektroniskās komercijas platformām internetā.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Provvista ta' aċċess għal dejtabejżis tal-kompjuter onlajn; Il-provvista ta' aċċess tal-utenti għall-pjattaformi fuq l-Internet; Provvista ta' aċċess għall-pjattaforma tal-kummerċ elettroniku fuq l-Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verschaffen van toegang tot online databanken; Verschaffen van gebruikerstoegang tot platforms op het Internet; Verschaffen van toegang tot e-commerce platforms op het Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Zapewnianie dostępu do baz danych online; Zapewnianie użytkownikom dostępu do platform w Internecie; Zapewnianie dostępu do platform handlu elektronicznego w Internecie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Fornecimento de acesso a bases de dados online; Fornecimento de acesso de utilizador às plataformas na Internet; Fornecimento de acesso a plataformas de comércio eletrónico na Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Furnizarea accesului la baze de date electronice online; Furnizarea accesului utilizatorilor la platforme pe internet; Furnizarea accesului la platforme pentru comerț electronic pe internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Poskytovanie prístupu k počítačovým databázam online; Poskytovanie používateľského prístupu k platformám na internete; Poskytovanie prístupu k platformám elektronického obchodu na internete.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Nudenje dostopa do spletnih podatkovnih zbirk; Nudenje uporabniškega dostopa do platform na internetu; Nudenje dostopa do platform za elektronsko poslovanje na internetu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tillhandahållande av direktanslutna databaser; Tillhandahållande av användaråtkomst till plattformar på internet; Tillhandahållande av åtkomst till en plattform för e-handel på internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>39</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Отдаване под наем на плавателни съдове; Наемане на плавателни съдове; Провеждане на туристически обиколки; Воден транспорт; Превозване на пътници с кораб; Услуги за организиране на обиколки, екскурзии.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pronájem plavidel; Pronájem lodí; Vedení zájezdů; Doprava (Lodní -); Doprava cestujících lodí; Služby pořádání zájezdů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Bådudlejning; Chartring af skibe; Ledelse af ture; Transport via båd; Passagertransport med skib; Serviceydelser inden for arrangering af ture.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Vermietung von Booten; Chartern von Schiffen; Vermietung von Schiffen; Durchführung von Touren; Beförderung per Schiff; Beförderung von Passagieren mit Booten; Dienste in Bezug auf die Veranstaltung von Ausflügen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εκμίσθωση σκαφών· Ναύλωση πλοίων· Διεξαγωγή περιηγήσεων· Μεταφορά με πλοίο· Μεταφορά επιβατών με πλοία· Υπηρεσίες για την οργάνωση ταξιδίων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Boat rental; Ship chartering; Tour conducting; Ship transport; Transportation of passengers by boat; Services for the arranging of tours.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Alquiler de barcos; Fletamento de buques; Servicios de guía de viajes organizados; Transporte en buque; Transporte de personas por barco; Servicios de organización de visitas turísticas (tours).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Paadilaenutus; Laevade tellimine tšarterreisideks; Turismireiside korraldamine; Laevatransport, -veod; Reisijate laevatransport; Ringreiside korraldamise teenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Veneiden vuokraus; Laivojen tilauskäyttö; Kiertomatkojen ohjaaminen; Laivakuljetus; Matkustajalaivakuljetus; Kiertomatkojen järjestämispalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Location de bateaux; Affrètement de navires; Encadrement d'excursions, de visites touristiques et de voyages; Transport en navire; Transport de passagers en bateau; Services d'organisation d'excursions, de visites touristiques et de voyages.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Iznajmljivanje čamaca; Iznajmljivanje [čarter] brodova; Usluge turističkog vođenja; Prijevoz brodom; Prijevoz putnika brodom; Usluge organiziranja izleta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hajók, csónakok kölcsönzése; Hajók bérlése; Idegenvezetés; Vízi járművel történő szállítás; Utasszállítás hajóval; Körutazások, társasutazások szervezésével kapcsolatos szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Noleggio di battelli; Noleggio di navi; Conduzione di viaggi turistici; Trasporto via nave; Trasporto di passeggeri su imbarcazioni; Servizi d'organizzazione di viaggi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Valčių nuoma; Laivų užsakymas; Turų vedimas; Jūrų laivų transportas; Keleivių vežimas laivais; Turistinių kelionių organizavimo paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kuģu iznomāšana; Kuģu fraktēšana; Ceļojumu vadīšana; Kuģu pārvadājumi; Pasažieru pārvadājumi ar laivu; Ceļojumu rīkošanas pakalpojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kiri ta' dgħajjes; Kiri ta' vapuri; Tmexxija ta' ġiti; Trasport bil-vapur; It-trasport ta' passiġġieri bid-dgħajsa; Servizzi ta' arranġament ta' turs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verhuur van boten; Charteren van schepen; Het begeleiden van rondreizen; Transport per schip; Vervoer van passagiers per schip; Organisatie van excursies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Wynajem łodzi; Czarterowanie statków; Oprowadzanie wycieczek; Statkami (Transport -); Transport pasażerski łodzią; Usługi organizowania wycieczek ze zwiedzaniem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aluguer de barcos; Fretamento de navios; Realização de excursões; Transporte por navio; Transporte de passageiros por barco; Serviços para organização de excursões.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Închirieri de bărci; Navlosire (de nave); Coordonare de tururi turistice; Transport cu vaporul; Transport de pasageri cu barca; Servicii pentru organizare de tururi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Prenajímanie plavidiel (člnov, lodí); Prenajímanie lodí; Vedenie zájazdov; Lodná doprava; Preprava cestujúcich loďou; Služby v oblasti zabezpečovania zájazdov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Najem čolnov; Čarterski najem ladij; Izvajanje potovanj; Ladijski transport; Prevoz potnikov s čolnom; Storitve za organizacijo izletov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Båtuthyrning; Fartygschartring; Ledning av rundturer; Fartygstransporter; Transport av passagerare med båt; Tjänster avseende arrangerande av rundresor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Програмиране на софтуер за интернет платформи; Изграждане на интернет платформа за електронна търговия; Хостинг услуги и софтуер като услуга и отдаване под наем на софтуер; Разработване, програмиране и внедряване на компютърен софтуер; Програмиране на софтуер за управление на база данни; Отдаване под наем на софтуер за управление на база данни; Софтуер като услуги; Консултантски услуги в областта на софтуер като услуга [SaaS]; Софтуер като услуга [SaaS] със софтуер за дълбоко изучаване; Програмиране на софтуер за платформи за електронна търговия; Хостинг на платформи за електронна търговия в интернет; Разработване на софтуер; Проектиране на компютърен софтуер и компютърно програмиране; Програмиране на уебстраници; Създаване на уебсайтове; Създаване и поддържане на уеб страници за трети лица.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Programování softwaru pro internetové platformy; Tvorba internetové platformy k elektronickému obchodování; Webhostingové služby a software jako služba a pronájem softwaru; Vývoj softwaru, programování a implementace softwaru; Programování softwaru pro správu databází; Pronájem softwaru pro správu databází; Software jako služba [SaaS]; Konzultační služby v oboru software jako služba (SAAS); Software jako služba [SaaS] zaměřený na software pro hluboké učení; Programování softwaru pro platformy elektronického obchodování; Hosting platformy pro elektronický obchod na internetu; Vývoj softwaru; Počítačové programování a návrhy počítačového softwaru; Programování webových stránek; Vývoj webových stránek (služby); Vytváření a údržba webových stránek pro jiné osoby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Programmering af software til internetplatforme; Opbygning af en internetplatform til elektronisk handel; Hostingtjenesteydelser og software as a service og udlejning af software; Udvikling af software, programmering og implementering; Programmering af software til databasestyring; Udlejning af software til databasestyring; Software as a service [saas]; Rådgivning inden for software som en tjeneste (SaaS); Software as a service [SaaS] med software til dybdelæring; Programmering af software til e-handelsplatforme; Hosting af e-handelsplatforme på internettet; Softwareudvikling; Computerprogrammering og softwaredesign; Programmering af websider; Udvikling af websteder; Udvikling og vedligeholdelse af hjemmesider for andre.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Programmierung von Software für Internetplattformen; Entwicklung von Internetplattformen für den elektronischen Handel; Hosting-Dienste, Software as a Service [SaaS] und Vermietung von Software; Entwicklung, Programmierung und Implementierung von Software; Programmieren von Datenbankverwaltungssoftware; Vermietung von Datenbankverwaltungssoftware; Software as a Service [SaaS]; Beratung im Bereich Software as a Service [SaaS]; Software as a Service [SaaS] mit Deep-Learning-Software; Programmierung von Software für E-Commerce-Plattformen; Hosting von E-Commerce-Plattformen im Internet; Softwareentwicklung; Softwareentwicklungsleistungen; Computerprogrammierung und Softwareentwicklung; Programmierung von Webseiten; Webseitenentwicklung; Erstellung und Wartung von Webseiten für Dritte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Προγραμματισμός λογισμικού για διαδικτυακές πλατφόρμες· Δημιουργία πλατφόρμας στο Διαδίκτυο (Internet) για ηλεκτρονικό εμπόριο· Υπηρεσίες φιλοξενίας και λογισμικό ως μία υπηρεσία και ενοικίαση λογισμικού· Ανάπτυξη, προγραμματισμός και εφαρμογή λογισμικού· Προγραμματισμός λογισμικού για διαχείριση βάσης δεδομένων· Εκμίσθωση λογισμικού για διαχείριση βάσης δεδομένων· Λογισμικό σαν υπηρεσία· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών στον τομέα του λογισμικού ως υπηρεσίας· Λογισμικό ως υπηρεσία που περιλαμβάνει λογισμικό για βαθεία μάθηση· Προγραμματισμός λογισμικού για πλατφόρμες ηλεκτρονικού εμπορίου· Φιλοξενία πλατφορμών ηλεκτρονικού εμπορίου στο Διαδίκτυο· Ανάπτυξη λογισμικού για ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Προγραμματισμός ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών και σχεδίαση λογισμικού· Προγραμματισμός ιστοσελίδων· Υπηρεσίες ανάπτυξης ιστοθέσεων (web site)· Δημιουργία και συντήρηση ιστοθέσεων για τρίτους.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Programming of software for Internet platforms; Constructing an internet platform for electronic commerce; Hosting services, software as a service, and rental of software; Software development, programming and implementation; Programming of software for database management; Rental of database management software; Software as a service [SaaS]; Consulting services in the field of software as a service [SaaS]; Software as a service [SaaS] featuring software for deep learning; Programming of software for e-commerce platforms; Hosting of e-commerce platforms on the Internet; Software development; Computer programming and software design; Programming of web pages; Website development services; Creating and maintaining web sites for others.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Programación de software para plataformas de Internet; Creación de una plataforma en Internet para el comercio electrónico; Servicios de alojamientos de sitios web y alquiler de software; Desarrollo, programación e implementación de software; Programación de software de gestión de bases de datos; Alquiler de software de gestión de bases de datos; Software como servicio [SaaS]; Servicios de consultoría en materia de software como un servicio [SaaS]; Software como servicio (saas) con software de aprendizaje profundo; Programación de software para plataformas de comercio electrónico; Alojamiento de plataformas de comercio electrónico en Internet; Desarrollo de software; Programación de ordenadores y diseño de programas informáticos; Programación de páginas web; Servicios de desarrollo de sitios web; Creación y mantenimiento de sitios web para terceros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Interneti-platvormide tarkvara programmeerimine; E-kaubanduse internetiplatvormi loomine; Hostimine ja pilveteenused (SaaS) ning tarkvara rent; Arvutitarkvaraarendus ja -teostus, programmeerimine; Andmebaasihaldustarkvara programmeerimine; Andmebaaside haldustarkvara üürimine; Pilveteenused [SaaS]; Teenustarkvara [SaaS] valdkonna konsulteerimisteenused; Süvaõppe tarkvaraga teenustarkvara [SaaS]; E-kaubandusplatvormide tarkvara programmeerimine; E-kaubanduse platvormide hostimine Internetis; Tarkvara arendamine; Arvutiprogrammide ja tarkvara projekteerimine; Veebilehtede programmeerimine; Veebisaidi arendusteenused; Veebisaitide loomise ja haldamise teenus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ohjelmistojen ohjelmointi internet-ympäristöjä varten; Internet-ympäristön rakentaminen elektronista kaupankäyntiä varten; Verkkoisännöintipalvelut ja verkkosovelluspalvelut (SaaS) sekä ohjelmistojen vuokraus; Tietokoneohjelmistojen kehittäminen, ohjelmointi ja toteutus; Tietokantojen hallintaohjelmistojen ohjelmointi; Tietokantojen hallintaohjelmistojen vuokraus; Verkkosovelluspalvelut [SaaS]; Konsultointipalvelut verkkosovelluspalvelujen [SaaS] alalla; Verkkosovelluspalvelut [SaaS] ohjelmistoilla syväoppimista varten; Ohjelmistojen ohjelmointi sähköisiä kaupankäyntiympäristöjä varten; Sähköisen kaupankäynnin ympäristöjen ylläpito Internetissä; Ohjelmistokehitys; Tietokoneohjelmointi ja ohjelmistosuunnittelu; Web-sivustojen ohjelmointi; Verkkosivujen kehityspalvelut; Verkkosivustojen luominen ja ylläpito muille.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Programmation de logiciels pour des plates-formes Internet; Conception d'une plate-forme Internet pour le commerce électronique; Services d'hébergement et logiciel en tant que service, et location de logiciel; Développement, programmation et implémentation de logiciels; Programmation de logiciels pour la gestion de bases de données; Location de logiciels de gestion de bases de données; Logiciel-service [SaaS]; Services d’assistance dans le domaine des services de logiciels-services (SaaS); Logiciel à la demande (SaaS) en tant que logiciels pour l’apprentissage profond; Programmation de logiciels pour des plates-formes de commerce électronique; Hébergement de plates-formes de commerce électronique sur Internet; Développement de logiciels; Programmation informatique et conception de logiciels; Programmation de pages Web; Services de développement de sites Web; Création et entretien de sites web pour des tiers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Programiranje softvera za internetske platforme; Izrada internetske platforme za elektroničko poslovanje; Usluge hostinga i softver kao usluga te iznajmljivanje softvera; Razvoj, programiranje i implementacija softvera; Programiranje softvera za upravljanje bazama podataka; Iznajmljivanje softvera za upravljanje bazama podataka; Softver kao usluga [SaaS]; Usluge savjetovanja u području softvera kao usluge (SAAS); Softver kao usluga [SaaS] sa softverom za dubinsko učenje; Programiranje softvera za platforme za e-trgovinu; Hosting platformi za e-trgovinu na Internetu; Razvoj softvera; Računalno programiranje i dizajn softvera; Programiranje internetskih stranica; Kreiranje internetskih stranica; Izrada i održavanje Web stranica za druge.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Internetes platformokhoz való szoftverek programozása; Internetes platform készítése elektronikus kereskedelemhez; Webtárhely és szoftver szolgáltatások, szoftver bérlés; Szoftverfejlesztés, programozás és kivitelezés; Adatbázis kezelésére szolgáló szoftverek programozása; Adatbázis kezelésére szolgáló szoftverek bérbeadása; Szoftver mint szolgáltatás [SaaS]; Szoftverszolgáltatásokkal (SAAS) kapcsolatos konzultáció; Mély tanulásra szolgáló szoftvert tartalmazó szoftver mint szolgáltatás [SaaS]; Elektronikus kereskedelmi platformokhoz való szoftverek programozása; E-kereskedelmi felületek fenntartása az interneten; Számítógépes szoftver fejlesztése; Számítógép-programozás és szoftvertervezés; Weboldalak programozása; Weboldal fejlesztő szolgáltatások; Weboldal készítési és karbantartási szolgáltatás.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Programmazione di software per piattaforme internet; Allestimento di piattaforme Internet per il commercio elettronico; Servizi di hosting e software come servizio e noleggio di software; Sviluppo, programmazione ed implementazione di software; Programmazione di software per la gestione di banche dati; Noleggio di software per la gestione di banche dati; Servizi di software [SaaS]; Servizi di consulenza in materia di software come servizio [SaaS]; Software come servizio [SaaS] comprendente software per l'apprendimento profondo; Programmazione di software per piattaforme di e-commerce; Hosting di piattaforme per il commercio elettronico su internet; Sviluppo di software; Programmazione di computer ed elaborazione di software; Programmazione di pagine web; Creazione di siti Web; Creazione e manutenzione di siti web per i terzi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Interneto platformų programinės įrangos programavimas; Elektroninės prekybos interneto platformos kūrimas; Prieglobos (talpinimo) paslaugos ir programinė įranga kaip paslauga bei programinės įrangos nuoma; Programinės įrangos tobulinimas, programavimas ir įdiegimas; Duomenų bazės valdymo programinės įrangos programavimas; Duomenų bazių valdymo programinės įrangos nuoma; Programinė įranga kaip paslauga [SaaS]; Programinės įrangos kaip paslaugos [SaaS] konsultacijos; Programinė įranga kaip paslauga [SaaS] su giliojo mokymosi programine įranga; Elektroninės prekybos platformų programinės įrangos programavimas; Elektroninės prekybos platformų priegloba internete; Programinės įrangos tobulinimas; Kompiuterio programavimas ir programinės įrangos projektavimas; Tinklapių programavimas; Interneto svetainių plėtojimo paslaugos; Visuotinio kompiuterių tinklo svetainių kūrimas ir palaikymas kitiems.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Interneta platformu programmatūras programmēšana; Interneta platformu izstrāde elektroniskās komercijas vajadzībām; Datņu izvietošanas un uzturēšanas pakalpojumi, arī programmatūras izvietošana un uzturēšana mākonī un programmatūras iznomāšana; Programmatūras izstrāde, programmēšana un ieviešana; Programmatūras programmēšana datu bāzes pārvaldībai; Programmatūras noma datu bāzes pārvaldībai; Programmatūra kā pakalpojums (SaaS); Konsultāciju pakalpojumi programmatūras kā pakalpojums (SAAS) jomā; Programmatūra kā pakalpojums (SaaS), kas satur dziļās mācīšanās programmatūru; E-komercijas platformu programmatūras programmēšana; Elektroniskās komercijas platformu mitināšana internetā; Programmatūras izstrāde; Datorprogrammēšana un programmatūras izstrāde; Tīmekļa lapu programmēšana; Tīmekļa vietņu izstrādes pakalpojumi; Tīmekļa vietņu izveidošana un uzturēšana trešajām personām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">L-ipprogrammar ta' softwer għall-pjattaformi tal-Internet; Il-kostruzzjoni ta' pjattaforma fuq l-Internet għall-kummerċ elettroniku; Servizzi ta' hosting u softwer bħala servizz u kiri ta' softwer; Żvilupp tas-softwer, programmar u implimentazzjoni; L-ipprogrammar ta' softwer għall-ġestjoni ta' dejtabejżis; Kiri ta' softwer għall-ġestjoni ta' dejtabejżis; Softwer bħala servizz [SaaS]; Servizzi ta' konsulenza fil-qasam tas-softwer bħala servizz [SAAS]; Softwer bħala servizz [SaaS] li jinkludi softwer għal tagħlim profond; L-ipprogrammar ta' softwer għall-pjattaformi tal-kummerċ elettroniku; Ħosting ta' pjattaformi tal-kummerċ elettroniku fuq l-Internet; Żvilupp ta' softwer; Ipprogrammar tal-kompjuter u disinn ta' softwer; L-ipprogrammar ta' paġni web; Servizzi ta' żvilupp ta' websajts; Il-ħolqien u l-manutenzjoni ta' websajts għal terzi persuni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Programmering van software voor internet platforms; Het opzetten van een Internetplatform voor de elektronische handel; Hostingdiensten en ter beschikking stellen van software (Saas) en verhuur van software; Ontwikkeling, programmering en implementatie van software; Programmering van software voor databankbeheer; Verhuur van software voor databankbeheer; Ter beschikking stellen van software [SaaS]; Advisering op het gebied van het ter beschikking stellen van software [SaaS]; Software-als-een-dienst [SaaS] met software voor diep leren; Programmering van software voor e-commerce platforms; Hosting van e-commerceplatforms op internet; Ontwikkeling van software; Computerprogrammering en ontwikkeling van software; Het programmeren van websites; Ontwikkeling van websites; Ontwerpen en onderhouden van websites [voor derden].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Programowanie oprogramowania do platform internetowych; Tworzenie platform internetowych do handlu elektronicznego; Hosting, oprogramowanie jako usługa oraz wypożyczanie oprogramowania komputerowego; Rozwój, programowanie i wdrażanie oprogramowania komputerowego; Programowanie oprogramowania do zarządzania bazami danych; Wypożyczanie oprogramowania do zarządzania bazami danych; Oprogramowanie jako usługa [SaaS]; Usługi doradztwa w zakresie oprogramowania jako usługi [SaaS]; Oprogramowanie jako usługa [SaaS] obejmujące oprogramowanie do głębokiego uczenia; Programowanie oprogramowania do platform handlu elektronicznego; Hosting platform przeznaczonych do handlu elektronicznego przez Internet; Opracowywanie oprogramowania komputerowego; Programowanie komputerów i projektowanie oprogramowania; Programowanie stron internetowych; Usługi w zakresie tworzenia witryn internetowych; Tworzenie i utrzymywanie stron internetowych dla osób trzecich.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Programação de software para plataformas de Internet; Construção de uma plataforma na internet para comércio eletrónico; Serviços de alojamento de sites de Internet e software como serviço e aluguer de software; Desenvolvimento, programação e implementação de software; Programação de software para gestão de bases de dados; Aluguer de software para gestão de bases de dados; Software como serviço [SaaS]; Serviços de consultadoria no domínio do software como serviço [SaaS]; Serviços de software como serviço [SaaS] que incluem software para aprendizagem profunda; Programação de software para plataformas de comércio eletrónico; Alojamento de plataformas de comércio eletrónico na Internet; Desenvolvimento de software; Programação de computadores e design de software; Programação de páginas Web; Serviços de desenvolvimento de websites; Criação e manutenção de web sites para terceiros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Programare de software pentru platforme de internet; Construirea unei platforme de Internet pentru comerțul electronic; Servicii de găzduire, software ca și serviciu și închiriere de software; Dezvoltare software, programare și implementare; Programare de software pentru gestionarea bazelor de date; Închiriere de software pentru gestionarea bazelor de date; Software ca serviciu [SaaS]; Consultanță în domeniul software-ului ca serviciu [SAAS]; Software ca serviciu (SAAS) care oferă software pentru învățare profundă; Programare de software pentru platforme de comerț electronic; Găzduire de platforme de comerț electronic pe Internet; Dezvoltare de software; Elaborare de programe pentru calculator și proiectare de software; Programare de pagini web; Servicii de dezvoltare de pagini web; Crearea și întreținerea siturilor web pentru terți.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Programovanie softvéru pre internetové platformy; Zriaďovanie internetovej platformy pre elektronický obchod; Hosťovanie na internetových stránkach, softvérové služby, prenájom softvéru; Vývoj softvéru, programovanie a zavádzanie programov; Programovanie softvéru na správu databáz; Prenájom softvéru na riadenie databáz; Poskytovanie softvéru prostredníctvom internetu (SaaS); Konzultačné služby v oblasti softvéru ako služby [SaaS]; Softvér ako služba [SaaS] obsahujúci softvér na hĺbkové učenie; Programovanie softvéru pre platformy elektronického obchodu; Hosting platforiem elektronického obchodu na internete; Vývoj počítačového softvéru; Počítačové programovanie a dizajn softvéru; Programovanie webových stránok; Tvorba webstránok; Tvorba a udržiavanie webových stránok (pre tretie osoby).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Programiranje programske opreme za internetne platforme; Izdelava internetne platforme za elektronsko trgovanje; Storitve gostovanja in nudenje programske opreme preko spleta ter dajanje programske opreme v najem; Razvoj programske opreme, programiranje in uvajanje programske opreme; Programiranje programske opreme za upravljanje podatkovnih baz; Najem programske opreme za upravljanje podatkovnih baz; Programska oprema kot storitev [SaaS]; Svetovalne storitve na področju programske opreme kot storitve [SaaS]; Programska oprema kot storitev [SaaS] s programsko opremo za globoko učenje; Programiranje programske opreme za platforme za elektronsko poslovanje; Gostovanje platform za elektronsko poslovanje na internetu; Razvoj programske opreme; Računalniško programiranje in oblikovanje programske opreme; Programiranje spletnih strani; Storitve razvoja spletnih strani; Izdelava in vzdrževanje spletnih strani za druge.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Programmering av programvara för internetplattformar; Uppbyggnad av en Internetplattform för elektronisk handel; Hostingtjänster, molntjänster (SaaS) och uthyrning av mjukvara; Mjukvaruutveckling, -programmering och –implementering; Programmering av programvara för databashantering; Uthyrning av programvara för databashantering; Molntjänster [SaaS]; Rådgivning avseende molntjänster [SaaS]; Molntjänster med programvaror för djupinlärning [SaaS]; Programmering av programvara för plattformar för elektronisk handel; Hosting avseende e-handelsplattformar på internet; Utveckling av mjukvara; Datorprogrammering och konstruktion av programvara; Programmering av webbsidor; Utveckling av webbplatser; Skapande och underhåll av webbplatser för andra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/080</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/151</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-11</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>30919</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017791867</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>30919</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-04-30</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
