<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T09:40:08</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229226</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229226</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>VOIETOLT</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Периферни устройства, пригодени за използване с компютри; Калъфи за смартфони; Смарт часовници; Електрически съединители; Кабели за USB устройства; Слушалки; Безжични зареждащи устройства; Калъфи за пренасяне на компютри; Оптични влакна; Превключвателни кутии [електричество]; Смарт очила; Компютърни мишки; Слушалки; Високодетайлни мултимедийни кабели за интерфейс; Електрически кабели и жици; Етернет кабели; Адаптери за кабели; Слушалки за слагане в уши; Слушалки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Periferní zařízení počítačů; Pouzdra na chytré telefony (smartphony); Chytré hodinky; Spoje [elektrotechnika]; USB kabely; Sluchátka; Bezdrátové nabíječky; Tašky na přenosné počítače (laptopy); Optická vlákna [světlovodná vlákna]; Spínací skříně; Chytré brýle; Počítačové myši; Sluchátka; Kabely pro multimediální rozhraní s vysokým rozlišením; Kabely a dráty; Ethernetové kabely; Adaptéry na kabely; Pecky do uší; Sluchátka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Perifere enheder til computere; Etuier til smartphones; Smartwatches; Forbindelsesled, elektriske; USB-kabler; Høretelefoner; Trådløse opladere; Tasker tilpasset til laptops; Lysledere [glødetråde]; Afbryderdåser; Intelligente briller; Computermus; Hovedtelefoner; Kabler til brug med High-Definition Multimedia Interface; Kabler og ledninger; Ethernet-kabler; Kabeladaptere; Øresnegle; Hovedtelefoner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">An Computer angepasste Peripheriegeräte; Schalen für Smartphones; Smartwatches; Elektrische Kupplungen; USB-Kabel; Kopfhörer; Kabellose Ladegeräte; Laptoptaschen; Optische Fasern [Lichtleitfäden]; Klappenschränke [Elektrizität]; Datenbrillen; Computermaus; Kopfhörer; Hochauflösende Multimedia-Schnittstellenkabel; Kabel und Drähte; Ethernetkabel; Kabeladapter; Ohrhörer; Kopfhörer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Περιφερειακός εξοπλισμός προσαρμοσμένος για χρήση σε ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Θήκες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Έξυπνα ρολόγια χειρός· Ρευματοδότες· Καλώδια καθολικού σειριακού αγωγού (USB)· Ακουστικά· Ασύρματοι φορτιστές· Θήκες μεταφοράς φορητών ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Οπτικές ίνες· Κουτιά [πίνακες] ηλεκτρικών διακοπτών· Έξυπνα γυαλιά· Ποντίκια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Κάσκες ακουστικών· Καλώδια διεπαφών πολυμέσων υψηλής ευκρίνειας· Καλώδια και σύρματα· Καλώδια ethernet· Προσαρμογείς καλωδίων· Ακουστικά· Ακουστικά κεφαλής με μικρόφωνο.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Computer peripheral devices; Cases for smartphones; Smartwatches; Electric connections; USB cables; Earphones; Wireless chargers; Computer carrying cases; Optical fibers; Electrical switch boxes; Smartglasses; Computer mouse; Headphones; High definition multimedia interface cables; Cables and wires; Ethernet cables; Cable adapters; Earbuds; Headsets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Dispositivos periféricos utilizados con ordenadores; Estuches para teléfonos inteligentes; Relojes inteligentes; Empalmes eléctricos; Cables USB; Auriculares intraurales; Cargadores inalámbricos; Bolsas especiales para ordenadores portátiles; Fibras ópticas [filamentos conductores de ondas luminosas]; Cajas de distribución [electricidad]; Gafas inteligentes; Ratones de ordenador; Auriculares; Cables de interfaz multimedia de alta definición; Cables y conductores eléctricos; Cables Ethernet; Adaptadores de cable; Auriculares de botón; Cascos con micrófono.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arvutite välisseadmed; Nutitelefonide ümbrised; Nutikellad; Elektrilised klemmid; USB-kaablid; Kõrvaklapid; Juhtmeta laadurid; Sülearvutikotid; Optilised kiud [valgust juhtivad hõõgniidid]; Jaotuskarbid [elektrotehnika]; Nutiprillid; Arvutihiired; Kõrvaklapid; Kõrglahutusega multimeediumliideste kaablid; Elektrikaablid ja -juhtmed; Ethernetijuhtmed; Kaabliadapterid; Kõrvatropid; Mikrofoniga kõrvaklapid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tietokoneiden oheislaitteet; Älypuhelinten kuoret; Älykellot; Sähköliittimet; USB-kaapelit; Kuulokkeet; Langattomat laturit; Tietokoneen kantokotelot; Optinen kuitu; Kytkinkotelot [sähkötarvikkeina]; Älylasit; Tietokonehiiret; Kuulokkeet; Teräväpiirtomultimedialiittymien kaapelit; Sähkökaapelit ja –johdot; Ethernet-kaapelit; Kaapelinsovittimet; Korvanappikuulokkeet; Kuulokkeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Périphériques adaptés pour utilisation avec des ordinateurs; Étuis pour smartphones; Montres intelligentes; Raccordements électriques; Câbles USB; Casques d'écoute; Chargeurs sans fil; Sacoches conçues pour ordinateurs portables; Fibres optiques [fils conducteurs de rayons lumineux]; Boîtes à clapets [électricité]; Lunettes intelligentes; Souris d'ordinateur; Casques à écouteurs; Câbles d'interfaces multimédias haute définition; Câbles et fils électriques; Câbles Ethernet; Adaptateurs de câbles; Écouteurs-boutons; Casques d'écoute.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Periferni uređaji prilagođeni za uporabu s računalima; Etuiji za pametne telefone; Pametni ručni satovi; Električne spojke; USB kablovi; Slušalice; Bežični punjači; Torbe za prijenosna računala; Optička vlakna; Električne sklopne kutije; Pametne naočale; Računalni miševi; Slušalice; Kabeli za multimedijska sučelja visoke rezolucije; Kablovi i žice; Ethernet kablovi; Adapteri za kabele; Slušalice; Slušalice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Számítógéphez kialakított perifériák; Tokok okostelefonhoz; Okoskarórák; Elektromos csatolások; USB kábelek; Fejhallgatók; Vezeték nélküli töltők; Számítógép hordozó tokok, táskák; Optikai szálak [üvegszálak]; Kapcsolódobozok [elektromosság]; Okosszemüvegek; Számítógépes egerek; Fejhallgatók; Nagyfelbontású multimédiás interfész kábelek; Kábelek és vezetékek; UTP hálózati kábelek; Kábeladapterek; Fülhallgatók; Fejhallgatók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Periferiche concepite per essere utilizzate con i computer; Custodie per smartphones; Orologi intelligenti [smartwatch]; Collegamenti elettrici; Cavi USB; Auricolari; Caricatori senza filo; Borse porta computer portatile; Fibre ottiche [fili conduttori dei raggi luminosi]; Cassette per valvole [elettricità]; Occhiali intelligenti [smartglass]; Mouse per computer; Cuffie per la musica; Cavi di interfaccia multimediali ad alta definizione; Cavi e fili elettrici; Cavi Ethernet; Adattatori per cavi; Auricolari; Cuffie per la musica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kompiuterių išoriniai įrenginiai; Išmaniųjų telefonų dėklai; Išmanieji laikrodžiai; Elektrinės jungės; USB kabeliai; Ausinės; Belaidžiai įkrovikliai; Skreitinių kompiuterių krepšiai; Optiniai pluoštai [šviesolaidžiai]; Jungiamosios dėžutės [elektra]; Išmanieji akiniai; Kompiuterių pelės; Radijo ausinės; Raiškiosios daugialypės terpės sietuvų kabeliai; Elektriniai kabeliai ir laidai; Eterneto kabeliai; Kabelių adapteriai; Ausinės; Ausinės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Datoru perifērijas ierīces; Viedtālruņu maciņi; Viedie rokaspulksteņi; Elektropadeves savienojumi; Universālo seriālo kopņu (USB) kabeļi; Ieaušu austiņas; Bezvadu uzlādes ierīces; Klēpjdatoru somas; Optiskās šķiedras (gaismu vadošie kvēldiegi); Elektrosadales kārbas; Viedās brilles; Datorpele; Austiņas; Augstas izšķirtspējas multivides saskarnes kabeļi; Elektriskie kabeļi un vadi; Ethernet kabeļi; Kabeļu adapteri; Ieauši (austiņas); Radioaustiņas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Periferali addattati għall-użu mal-kompjuters; Kaxxi għall-ismartphones; Arloġġi tal-idejn tat-tip smart; Ganċijiet elettriċi; Kejbil tal-USB; Kuffji; Ċarġers mingħajr fili; Bagalji għall-ġarr ta' kompjuter portabbli; Fibri ottiċi; Kaxex tas-swiċċijiet (elettriċità); Nuċċalijiet intelliġenti (smartglasses); Maws tal-kompjuter; Kuffji; Kejbils tal-konnessjoni multimedjali ta' definizzjoni għolja; Kejbils u wajers; Kejbils tal-eternet; Adapters tal-kejbils; Earbuds; Kuffji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Computerrandapparatuur; Etuis voor smartphones; Smartwatches; Elektrische aansluitingen; USB kabels; Oortelefoons; Draadloze opladers; Aangepaste tassen voor laptops; Optische vezels [lichtgeleidend draad]; Schakeldozen [elektriciteit]; Intelligente brillen; Computermuis; Hoofdtelefoons; High-definition multimedia-interfacekabels; Kabels en leidingen; Ethernetkabels; Kabeladapters; Oortjes; Hoofdtelefoons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Sprzęt peryferyjny do komputerów; Etui na smartfony; Zegarki inteligentne; Sprzężenia elektryczne; Kable USB; Słuchawki [douszne]; Ładowarki bezprzewodowe; Torby do noszenia komputerów; Światłowody; Szafy rozdzielcze [elektryczność]; Okulary inteligentne; Myszki komputerowe; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Kable interfejsowe do multimediów o wysokiej rozdzielczości; Kable i przewody elektryczne; Kable wykorzystywane w sieci Ethernet; Przejściówki do kabli; Słuchawki douszne; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Periféricos adaptados para uso com computadores; Capas para smartphones; Relógios inteligentes; Acoplamentos elétricos; Cabos USB; Auriculares; Carregadores sem fios; Sacolas adaptadas para computadores portáteis; Fibras óticas [fios condutores de raios luminosos]; Caixas de comutadores [eletricidade]; Óculos inteligentes; Ratos para computador; Auriculares; Cabos de interfaces multimédia de alta-definição; Cabos e fios elétricos; Cabos Ethernet; Adaptadores para cabos; Auriculares; Auriculares.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Periferice adaptate pentru a fi folosite la calculatoare; Carcase pentru telefoane inteligente; Ceasuri inteligente; Conexiuni; Cabluri USB; Căști auriculare; Încărcătoare fără fir; Genți adaptate pentru laptopuri; Fibre optice; Cutii de distribuție [electricitate]; Ochelari inteligenți; Mouse-uri pentru computer; Căști audio; Cabluri pentru interfețe multimedia de înaltă definiție; Cabluri și fire; Cabluri Ethernet; Adaptoare pentru cabluri; Minicăști de urechi; Căști.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Periférne zariadenia počítačov; Puzdrá na smartfóny; Inteligentné hodinky; Elektrické spojky; USB káble; Slúchadlá; Bezdrôtové nabíjačky; Tašky na notebooky; Optické vlákna; Rozvodné skrine, spínacie skrine (elektrotechnika); Inteligentné okuliare; Počítačové myši; Slúchadlá; Hi-fi multimediálne prepojovacie káble; Káble a drôty; Ethernet káble; Adaptéry na káble; Slúchadlá do uší; Slúchadlá s mikrofónom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zunanje enote, prilagojene za uporabo z računalniki; Etuiji za pametne telefone; Pametne zapestne ure; Električne spojke; USB kabli; Slušalke; Brezžični polnilniki; Torbe, prilagojene prenašanje računalnikov; Optična vlakna; Stikalne omare [elektrika]; Pametna očala; Računalniške miške; Slušalke; Kabli za multimedijske vmesnike z visoko ločljivostjo; Kabli in žice; Ethernet kabli; Adapterji za kable; Slušalke za v uho; Slušalke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kringutrustning anpassade för användning med datorer; Skal för smartphones; Smarta klockor; Elektriska kopplingar; USB-kablar; Hörlurar; Trådlösa laddare; Väskor för bärbara datorer; Optiska fibrer [ljusledande filament]; Kopplingsdosor [el]; Smarta glasögon; Datormusar; On-ear hörlurar; Kablar för multimediegränssnitt med hög upplösning; Elektriska kablar och ledningar; Ethernetkablar; Kabeladaptrar; Öronsnäckor; Headsets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/080</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/151</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-11</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081929</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15066</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
