<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-10T08:16:24</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229609</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229609</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-08</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-10</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ALISAP</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162502677</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229609/000162502677.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.01</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Облекла за защита от злополуки, радиация и огън; Азбестови облекла за предпазване от огън; Защитни костюми за летци; Костюми за гмуркане; Предпазни платнища; Ръкавици за защита от злополуки; Ръкавици за водолази; Ръкавици за защита от рентгенови лъчи за промишлени цели; Облекла за защита от огън; Спасителни шамандури; Облекло, специално за лаборатории; Бронирано облекло; Светлоотражателни предпазни жилетки; Протектори за глава за спорт; Непромокаеми костюми за оцеляване за предотвратяване на удавяне.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Ochranné obleky k ochraně před úrazem, radiací a ohněm; Protipožární ochranné azbestové obleky; Letecké ochranné kombinézy; Potápěčské obleky; Ochranné plachty; Ochranné rukavice (k ochraně před úrazy a nehodami); Potápěčské rukavice; Ochranné rukavice proti rentgenovému záření pro použití v průmyslu; Ohnivzdorné oděvy; Záchranné vesty; Oděvy pro laboratoře; Neprůstřelné oděvy; Reflexní bezpečnostní vesty; Chrániče hlavy pro sport; Voděodolné záchranné kombinézy k zabránění utopení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tøj til beskyttelse mod ulykker, bestråling og ild; Asbestbeklædning til beskyttelse mod ild; Beskyttende dragter til piloter; Dykkerdragter; Sikkerhedspresenninger; Handsker til beskyttelse mod ulykker; Handsker til dykkere; Handsker til industriel brug til beskyttelse mod røntgenstråler; Beklædningsgenstande til beskyttelse mod ild; Redningsveste; Beklædningsgenstande specielt fremstillet til brug i laboratorier; Skudsikker beklædning; Reflekterende sikkerhedsveste; Hovedbeskyttere til sportsbrug; Vandtætte overlevelsesdragter til forhindring af drukneulykker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Unfall-, Strahlen- und Feuerschutzbekleidung; Asbestbekleidungsstücke zum Schutz gegen Feuer; Schutzanzüge für Flieger; Taucheranzüge; Rettungsplanen; Unfallschutzhandschuhe; Taucherhandschuhe; Schutzhandschuhe gegen Röntgenstrahlen für gewerbliche Zwecke; Feuerschutzbekleidung; Rettungswesten; Spezialbekleidung für Labore; Kugelsichere Bekleidung; Reflektierende Sicherheitswesten; Kopfschutz zur Verwendung beim Sport; Wasserdichte Überlebensanzüge zum Schutz vor dem Ertrinken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ενδύματα για προστασία από ατυχήματα, ακτινοβολία και πυρκαγιά· Αμιάντου (Ενδύματα -) πυροπροστασίας· Αεροπόρων (Ειδικά προστατευτικά ενδύματα -)· Φόρμες κατάδυσης· Αδιαβροχοποιημένα υφάσματα [μουσαμάδες] διάσωσης· Γάντια για προστασία από ατυχήματα· Γάντια κατάδυσης· Γάντια κατά των ακτίνων Χ βιομηχανικής χρήσης· Πυρίμαχα ενδύματα· Ζώνες σωστικές· Ενδύματα ειδικά κατασκευασμένα για εργαστήρια· Αλεξίσφαιρα ενδύματα· Ανακλαστικά γιλέκα ασφαλείας· Προστατευτικά κεφαλής για τον αθλητισμό· Αδιάβροχα ενδύματα επιβίωσης για πρόληψη πνιγμού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Clothing for protection against accidents, irradiation and fire; Asbestos clothing for protection against fire; Protective suits for aviators; Diving suits; Safety tarpaulins; Gloves for protection against accidents; Gloves for divers; Gloves for protection against X-rays for industrial purposes; Clothing for protection against fire; Life jackets; Clothing especially made for laboratories; Bullet-proof clothing; Reflective safety vests; Head guards for sports; Waterproof survival suits for the prevention of drowning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Trajes de protección contra los accidentes, las radiaciones y el fuego; Trajes de amianto ignífugos; Trajes especiales de protección para aviadores; Trajes de buceo; Lonas de salvamento; Guantes de protección contra accidentes; Guantes de buceo; Guantes de protección contra los rayos X para uso industrial; Ropa de protección contra el fuego; Chalecos salvavidas; Ropa especial de laboratorio; Trajes antibalas; Chalecos de seguridad reflectantes; Protectores de cabeza para deportes; Trajes de supervivencia impermeables para evitar el riesgo de ahogo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kaitserõivad, sh kiirgus- ja tulekindlad; Tulekindlad asbestrõivad; Lenduriülikonnad, lenduritürbid [kaitseriietus]; Skafandrid, tuukriülikonnad; Kaitsepresendid, ohutuspresendid; Kaitsekindad; Kindad sukeldujatele; Tööstuslikud röntgenikiirgusvastased kindad; Tulekindlad kaitserõivad; Päästevestid; Laborantide erirõivastus; Kuulikindlad rõivad; Helkur-turvavestid; Peakaitsmed spordivahenditena; Veekindlad päästeülikonnad uppumise vältimiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatteet suojaksi tapaturmilta, säteilyltä ja tulelta; Asbestivaatteet suojaksi tulelta; Lentäjille tarkoitetut suojapuvut; Sukelluspuvut; Suojapeitteet; Käsineet suojaksi onnettomuuksilta; Käsineet (Sukellus -); Käsineet suojaksi röntgensäteiltä teollisuuskäyttöön; Suojavaatteet tulta vastaan; Pelastusliivit; Vaatteet laboratoriokäyttöön, erikoisvalmisteiset; Luodinkestävät vaatteet; Heijastavat turvaliivit; Päänsuojaimet urheiluun; Vedenpitävät pelastuspuvut hukkumisen estämiseen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vêtements de protection contre les accidents, les radiations et le feu; Vêtements en asbeste pour la protection contre le feu; Combinaisons de protection pour aviateurs; Combinaisons de plongée; Bâches de sauvetage; Gants de protection contre les accidents; Gants de plongée; Gants de protection contre les rayons X à usage industriel; Habillement pour la protection contre le feu; Gilets de sauvetage; Vêtements conçus pour être portés en laboratoire; Vêtements pare-balles; Gilets de sécurité réfléchissants; Casques pour le sport; Combinaisons de survie étanches contre le risque de noyade.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Odjeća za zaštitu od nesreća, zračenja i vatre; Azbestna odjeća za zaštitu od vatre; Kombinezoni (specijalni zaštitni kombinezoni za zrakoplovce); Skafanderi za ronnjenje; Cerade za spašavanje; Zaštitne rukavice; Rukavice za ronioce; Rukavice za zaštitu od X-zraka u industriji; Vatrootporna odjeća; Prsluci za spašavanje; Specijalna odjeća za laboratorije; Neprobojna odjeća; Reflektirajući sigurnosni prsluci; Štitnici za glavu za sport; Vodonepropusna zaštitna odijela za spašavanje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Védőruhák balesetek, sugárzás és tűz ellen; Azbesztruhák tűzvédelmi célokra; Védőöltözetek pilóták részére; Búvárruhák; Biztonsági ponyvák; Balesetek elleni védőkesztyűk; Búvárkesztyűk; Röntgensugárzás elleni védőkesztyűk ipari célokra; Tűzálló ruházat; Mentőmellények; Speciális ruházat laboratóriumi használatra; Golyóálló ruházat; Fényvisszaverő biztonsági mellények; Fejvédők sportoláshoz; Vízálló túlélő ruhák vízbe fulladás ellen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Indumenti di protezione contro gli infortuni, le irradiazioni e il fuoco; Indumenti di amianto per la protezione contro il fuoco; Tute speciali di protezione per aviatori; Scafandri; Teloni di salvataggio; Guanti per la protezione contro gli infortuni; Guanti per subacquei; Guanti i protezione contro i raggi X per uso industriale; Indumenti per la protezione contro il fuoco; Giubotti salvagente; Indumenti speciali per laboratori; Abbigliamento anti-proiettile; Gilet di sicurezza riflettenti; Protezioni per la testa per lo sport; Tute di sopravvivenza impermeabili per prevenire il rischio di annegamento.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Apsauginiai drabužiai nuo nelaimingų atsitikimų, jonizuojančios spinduliuotės ir ugnies; Apsauginiai asbesto drabužiai nuo ugnies; Apsauginiai lakūnų kostiumai; Narų kostiumai; Apsauginiai brezentai; Apsauginės pirštinės; Nardytojų pirštinės; Pirštinės nuo rentgeno spinduliuotės (gamyboje); Ugniai atsparūs drabužiai; Gelbėjimo liemenės; Apranga darbui laboratorijose; Neperšaunamieji drabužiai; Šviesą atspindinčios apsauginės liemenės; Sportinės galvos apsaugos; Vandeniui atsparūs gelbėjimo kostiumai, apsaugantys nuo skendimo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apģērbi aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem, apstarošanu un uguni; Azbesta apģērbs aizsardzībai pret uguni; Aizsargtērpi lidotājiem; Niršanas kostīmi; Aizsargbrezents; Cimdi aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem; Ūdenslīdēju cimdi; Cimdi aizsardzībai pret rentgena starojumu rūpnieciskiem nolūkiem; Ugunsdrošs apģērbs; Glābšanas vestes; Apģērbs lietošanai laboratorijā; Ložu necaurlaidīgs apģērbs; Atstarojošas drošības vestes; Galvas aizsargi izmantošanai sportā; Ūdensnecaurlaidīgi glābšanas tērpi noslīkšanas novēršanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ilbies għall-protezzjoni kontra l-inċidenti, irradjazzjoni u n-nar; Ħwejjeġ tal-asbestos għall-protezzjoni kontra n-nar; Ilbies protettiv għall-avjaturi; Ħwejjeġ tal-għaddasa; Tarpolini tas-sigurtà; Ingwanti għall-protezzjoni kontra l-inċidenti; Ingwanti għall-għaddasa; Ingwanti ta' protezzjoni kontra r-raġġi-X għal skopijiet industrijali; Lbies reżistenti għan-nar; Salvawomi; Ħwejjeġ magħmula apposta għal-laboratorji; Ħwejjeġ kontra l-balal; Sdieri ta' protezzjoni li jirriflettu; Protetturi tar-ras għall-isport; Ilbies tas-sigurtà li ma jgħaddix ilma minnu għall-prevenzjoni mill-għarqa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Beschermende kleding tegen ongevallen, straling en vuur; Asbestkleding, ter bescherming tegen ongevallen; Speciale beschermende vliegeniers-overalls; Duikpakken; Springzeilen; Handschoenen ter bescherming tegen ongevallen; Duikerhandschoenen; Beschermende handschoenen tegen röntgenstralen, voor industrieel gebruik; Kleding ter bescherming tegen vuur; Reddingsvesten; Speciale kledingstukken voor laboratoria; Kogelvrije kleding; Reflecterende veiligheidsvesten; Hoofdbeschermers voor de sport; Waterdichte survivalpakken tegen verdrinking.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odzież chroniąca przed wypadkami, napromieniowaniem i ogniem; Odzież azbestowa do ochrony przed ogniem; Kombinezony ochronne dla lotników; Skafandry dla nurków; Plandeki ochronne; Rękawice do ochrony przed wypadkami; Rękawice dla nurków; Rękawice do ochrony przed promieniami rentgenowskimi do celów przemysłowych; Ognioodporna odzież; Kamizelki ratunkowe; Odzież przeznaczona do użycia w laboratoriach; Odzież kuloodporna; Odblaskowe kamizelki ochronne; Ochraniacze głowy do uprawiania sportu; Wodoszczelne kombinezony ratownicze zapobiegające przed utonięciem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vestuário de proteção contra acidentes, radiações e fogo; Vestuário em amianto para a proteção contra o fogo; Fatos especiais de proteção para aviadores; Fatos de mergulhador; Lonas de salvação; Luvas para proteção contra acidentes; Luvas para mergulho; Luvas de proteção contra raios-x para uso industrial; Roupas para proteção contra fogo; Coletes de salvação; Vestuário especial para laboratórios; Vestuário à prova de bala; Coletes refletores de segurança; Proteções para a cabeça para desporto; Fatos impermeáveis de sobrevivência para a prevenção de afogamento.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Îmbrăcăminte de protecţie contra accidentelor, iradierii şi incendiilor; Azbest (Îmbrăcăminte din -) pentru protecţia împotriva focului; Costume de protecţie pentru aviatori; Costume de scafandru; Prelate de protecţie; Mănuşi de protecţie împotriva accidentelor; Mănuşi de scafandru; Mănuşi de uz industrial pentru protecţie contra razelor X; Îmbrăcăminte de protecţie împotriva focului; Veste de salvare; Îmbrăcăminte specială pentru laborator; Îmbrăcăminte anti-glonţ; Veste de salvare reflectorizante; Căşti pentru sport; Costume de salvare impermeabile pentru prevenirea înecului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ochranné odevy proti úrazom, proti rádioaktívnej kontaminácii a protipožiarne ochranné odevy; Ochranné azbestové odevy (proti ohňu); Špeciálne ochranné letecké kombinézy; Potápačské kombinézy; Záchranné plachty; Rukavice pre ochranu pred zranením; Potápačské rukavice; Ochranné rukavice proti rtg. lúčom na priemyselné použitie; Protipožiarne ochranné odevy; Záchranné bóje; Špeciálne laboratórne odevy; Nepriestrelné odevy; Reflexné vesty; Chrániče hlavy na športovanie; Vodovzdorné záchranné odevy zabraňujúce utopeniu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zaščitna oblačila proti nesrečam, sevanju in ognju; Azbestna oblačila za zaščito pred ognjem; Zaščitna oblačila za letalce; Potapljaške obleke; Rešilne ponjave; Rokavice za zaščito pred nesrečam; Rokavice za potapljače; Rokavice za zaščito pred rentgenskimi žarki za industrijske namene; Ognjeodporna oblačila; Rešilni jopiči; Oblačila, posebej izdelana za laboratorije; Neprebojna oblačila; Odsevni varnostni jopiči; Ščitniki za glavo za šport; Vodoodporne potapljaške obleke za preprečitev utopitve.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Skyddskläder mot skador, strålning och eld; Asbestkläder för skydd mot eld; Skyddsdräkter för flygare; Dykardräkter; Säkerhetspresenningar; Handskar för skydd mot olyckor; Handskar för dykare; Handskar för skydd mot röntgenstrålning för industriella ändamål; Klädesplagg för skydd mot eld; Flytvästar; Kläder specialgjorda för laboratorier; Skottsäkra kläder; Reflekterande säkerhetsvästar; Huvudskydd för sport; Vattentäta överlevnadsdräkter för att förhindra drunkning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Маски за лице за медицинска употреба; Облекло специално за операционни зали; Маски за медицински персонал; Хирургически стерилни покривки за операции; Акушерски матраци; Мушами за болнични легла; Постелки при инконтиненция; Пристягащи облекла; Охлаждащи пластири за медицински цели; Охлаждащи компреси за първа медицинска помощ; Превръзки за акупресура; Нощници за преглед на пациенти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Roušky k lékařskému použití; Oděvy určené pro operační sály; Roušky pro lékařský personál; Operační roušky; Porodnické matrace; Podložky na nemocniční lůžka; Inkontinenční prostěradla; Kompresní oděvy; Chladivé náplasti pro lékařské účely; Chladicí polštářky pro první pomoc; Akupresurní pásy; Pláště pro vyšetřování pacientů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Ansigtsmasker til medicinske formål; Beklædning specielt til operationsstuer; Masker til brug for medicinsk personel; Kirurgiske afdækningsstykker; Fødemadrasser; Stiklagner til sygesenge; Inkontinenslagner; Kompressionsbeklædning; Kølende plastre til medicinske formål; Kølepuder til brug ved førstehjælp; Akupressurbånd; Patientundersøgelseskitler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gesichtsmasken für medizinische Zwecke; OP-Kleidung; Masken für medizinisches Personal; Operationstücher; Matratzen für Entbindungen; Krankenunterlagen; Unterlagen für Inkontinente; Kompressionsbekleidung; Kühlpflaster für medizinische Zwecke; Kühlkissen für erste Hilfe; Akupressurbänder; Patientenuntersuchungshemden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μάσκες προσώπου για ιατρική χρήση· Ενδύματα (Ειδικά για χειρουργεία -)· Μάσκες για το ιατρικό προσωπικό· Σεντόνια χειρουργικά· Στρώματα τοκετού· Καλύμματα πολυστρωματικά, αδιάβροχα, στρώματος (ασθενών)· Σεντόνια για την ακράτεια· Ενδύματα συμπίεσης· Ψυκτικά έμπλαστρα για ιατρική χρήση· Ψυκτικά επιθέματα πρώτων βοηθειών· Ταινίες βελονισμού· Ρόμπες εξέτασης ασθενών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Face masks for medical use; Clothing especially for operating rooms; Masks for use by medical personnel; Surgical drapes; Childbirth mattresses; Draw-sheets for sick beds; Incontinence sheets; Compression garments; Cooling patches for medical purposes; Cooling pads for first aid purposes; Acupressure bands; Patient examination gowns.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Máscaras faciales para uso médico; Ropa especial para quirófano; Mascarillas para personal médico; Sábanas quirúrgicas; Colchones para el parto; Protectores de colchón [salvacamas]; Sábanas para personas incontinentes [empapadores]; Prendas de compresión; Parches de enfriamiento para uso médico; Almohadillas de enfriamiento para primeros auxilios; Bandas de acupresión; Batas sanitarias para la examinación de pacientes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meditsiinilised näomaskid; Eririietus operatsioonisaalides viibimiseks, operatsiooniriietus; Maskid meditsiinipersonalile; Kirurgilised steriilsed riided; Sünnitusmadratsid; Haigevoodi vahariided; Kusepidamatushaigete linad; Surverõivad; Jahutavad meditsiinilised geelplaastrid; Jahutuspadjad esmaabiks; Akupressuurisidemed; Kitlid patsiendi läbivaatuseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kasvonaamarit lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Vaatteet leikkaussaleja varten, erikoisvalmisteiset; Suojanaamarit lääkintähenkilökuntaa varten; Leikkausliinat; Synnytyspatjat; Vetolakanat sairasvuoteita varten; Lakanat pidätyskyvyttömiä varten; Kompressiovaatteet; Viilentävät tyynyt lääkintätarkoituksiin; Viilentävät tyynyt ensiapua varten; Akupainantanauhat; Potilaantutkimusvaatteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Masques pour le visage à usage médical; Vêtements spéciaux pour salles d'opération; Masques utilisés par le personnel médical; Draps chirurgicaux; Matelas pour l'accouchement; Alaises; Draps pour incontinence; Vêtements de compression; Patchs refroidissants à usage médical; Coussinets refroidissants pour premiers soins; Bandes d'acupression; Blouses d'examen pour patients.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Maske za lice za medicinsku uporabu; Specijalna odjeća za operacijske dvorane; Maske za medicinsko osoblje; Plahte za kirurške potrebe; Madraci za porođaje; Plahte za prenošenje bolesnika za bolesničke krevete; Plahte kod nezadržavanja mokraće; Kompresijska odjeća; Flasteri za hlađenje, za medicinske potrebe; Jastučići za hlađenje za prvu pomoć; Trake za akupresuru; Košulje za pregled, za pacijente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Arcmaszkok gyógyászati használatra; Speciális műtőruházat; Maszkok egészségügyi személyzet általi használatra; Sebészeti lepedők; Matracok, szülészeti; Harántlepedők betegágyra; Inkontinencia lepedők; Kompressziós ruhák; Hűtőtapaszok gyógyászati célokra; Hűtőpárnák elsősegély-nyújtási célokra; Akupresszúrás pántok; Betegvizsgáló köpenyek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Maschere per il viso per uso medico; Vestiti speciali per sale operatorie; Maschere utilizzate dal personale medico; Lenzuola chirurgiche; Materassi per il parto; Traverse; Lenzuola per incontinenti; Indumenti di compressione; Cerotti freddi per scopi medici; Cerotti freddi per scopi di pronto soccorso; Bande di digitopressione; Camici da esame per pazienti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Veido kaukės medicinos reikmėms; Specialieji operaciniai drabužiai; Kaukės medicinos personalui; Chirurginiai drabužiai; Gimdymo čiužiniai; Ištraukiamosios paklodės (ligonių lovoms); Nelaikančiųjų paklodės; Kompresiniai drabužiai; Vėsinantys pleistrai (medicinos reikmėms); Vėsinantys paklotai (pirmosios pagalbos reikmėms); Akupresūros raiščiai; Pacientų apžiūros chalatai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Sejas maskas medicīniskām vajadzībām; Speciālie apģērbi operāciju zālēm; Medicīnas personālam paredzētās maskas; Ķirurģiskie pārklāji; Dzemdību matrači; Matraču pārklāji slimnieku gultām; Palagi personām, kas slimo ar urīna nesaturēšanu; Kompresijas apģērbs; Atvēsinoši plāksteri medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Termopakas pirmās palīdzības vajadzībām; Akupresūras saites; Pacienta izmeklēšanai paredzētie tērpi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Maskri tal-wiċċ għall-użu mediku; Ilbies speċjali għas-swali tal-operazzjonijiet; Maskri għal personal mediku; Lożor bħala għata għal waqt operazzjonijiet kirurġiċi; Saqqijiet tal-ħlas; Lożor għas-sodod tal-morda; Lożor għall-inkontinenza; Ilbies tal-kompressjoni; Irqajja' tat-tkessiħ għal skopijiet mediċi; Mħaded li jkessħu għal skopijiet tal-ewwel għajnuna; Ċineg tal-akupuntura; Ġagagi għall-eżaminazzjoni ta' pazjenti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Gezichtsmaskers voor medisch gebruik; Operatiekleding; Maskers te gebruiken door medisch personeel; Chirurgische lakens; Kraammatrassen; Steeklakens; Lakens voor incontinenten; Compressiekleding; Koelende patches voor medische doeleinden; Koudekompressen voor eerstehulp; Acupressuurbanden; Onderzoeksschorten voor patiënten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Maski na twarz do użytku medycznego; Odzież specjalna używana w salach operacyjnych; Maski stosowane przez personel medyczny; Okrycia chirurgiczne; Materace położnicze; Prześcieradła na łóżka chorych; Prześcieradła dla osób niekontrolujących czynności fizjologicznych; Odzież kompresyjna; Plastry chłodzące do celów medycznych; Poduszeczki chłodzące do udzielenia pierwszej pomocy; Opaski do akupresury; Fartuchy do badania pacjentów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máscaras faciais para uso médico; Vestuário especial para salas de operação; Máscaras para pessoal médico; Lençóis para cirurgia; Colchões para partos; Resguardos; Lençóis para incontinentes; Compressas sob a forma de vestuário; Bandas de resfriamento para uso clínico; Bolsas de resfriamento para primeiros socorros; Pulseiras de acupressão; Batas de observação de pacientes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Măşti medicale; Haine speciale pentru săli de operaţie; Măşti utilizate de personalul medical; Cearceafuri chirurgicale; Saltele pentru naştere; Aleze; Cearceafuri absorbante pentru incontinenţă; Articole de îmbrăcăminte de compresie; Bandaje de răcire pentru uz medical; Comprese de răcire de prim ajutor; Benzi pentru acupresură; Halate pentru examinarea pacienţilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Masky na tvár na lekárske účely; Odevy do operačných sál; Rúška (pre nemocničný personál); Chirurgické plachty; Pôrodnícke matrace; Nepremokavé plachty na postele; Plachty pre osoby postihnuté inkontinenciou; Sťahovacie oblečenie; Chladiace náplasti na lekárske účely; Chladiace vankúšiky na prvú pomoc; Akupresúrne pásy; Nemocničné košele na vyšetrovanie pacientov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Obrazne maske za medicinsko uporabo; Posebna oblačila za operacijske prostore; Maske za medicinsko osebje; Kirurške rjuhe; Vzmetnice za porod; Podloge za bolniške postelje; Rjuhe za inkontinentne bolnike; Kompresijska oblačila; Hladilni obliži za medicinske namene; Hladilne blazinice za prvo pomoč; Akupresurni trakovi; Halje za pregledovanje pacientov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Ansiktsmasker för medicinskt bruk; Kläder för användning i operationsrum; Munskydd för medicinsk personal; Kirurgiska skynken; Förlossningsmadrasser; Draglakan för sjuksängar; Inkontinenslakan; Kompressionskläder; Kylande plåster för medicinska ändamål; Kylkuddar för första hjälpen-ändamål; Akupressurband; Rockar för användning vid undersökning av patienter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/101</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/173</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079975</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>35172</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
