<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-20T08:10:53</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229303</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229303</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-10-19</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-20</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>APA</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Възпитание и образование, двете във връзка с астрология или космология; Развлечение, А именно изяви на тема астрология или космология.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Výchova a vzdělání, oboje pouze v souvislosti s astrologií nebo kosmologií; Zábava, Jmenovitě vystoupení k tématu astrologie nebo kosmologie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Undervisning og uddannelse, begge dele i forbindelse med astrologi eller kosmologi; Underholdningsvirksomhed, Nemlig optræden inden for emnerne astrologi eller kosmologi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Erziehung und Ausbildung, beides nur im Zusammenhang mit Astrologie oder Kosmologie; Unterhaltung, nämlich Auftritte mit dem Thema Astrologie oder Kosmologie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες εκπαίδευσης και επιμόρφωσης (επαγγελματικής κατάρτισης) στο σύνολό τους σε σχέση με την αστρολογία ή την κοσμολογία· Ψυχαγωγία, Συγκεκριμένα παρουσιάσεις με θέμα την αστρολογία ή την κοσμολογία.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Educational instruction, exclusively relating to astrology or cosmology; Entertainment, Namely presentations on the subject of astrology or cosmology.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Educación y formación exclusivamente en relación con la astrología o la cosmología; Servicios de entretenimiento, En concreto espectáculos relacionados con la astrología o la cosmología.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Haridus ja väljaõpe, mõlemad on seotud ainult astroloogia või kosmoloogiaga; Meelelahutus, Nimelt esinemised astroloogia või kosmoloogia teemal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Opetus ja koulutus, molemmat ainoastaan astrologian tai kosmologian alalla; Ajanviete, Nimittäin esitykset, joiden aiheena on astrologia tai kosmologia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Éducation et formation, les deux uniquement en relation avec l'astrologie ou la cosmologie; Divertissement, À savoir évènements avec pour thème l'astrologie ou la cosmologie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Odgoj i izobrazba, oboje samo u vezi s astrologijom ili kozmologijom; Razonoda, I to nastupi s temom astrologije ili kozmologije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nevelés és szakképzés, mindkettő csak az asztrológiával vagy kozmológiával összefüggésben; Szórakoztatás, Nevezetesen fellépések az asztrológia vagy kozmológia témájával.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Formazione didattica esclusivamente in relazione ad astrologia e cosmologia; Divertimento, Ovvero spettacoli relativi ad astrologia o cosmologia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Ugdymas ir mokymas, šios paslaugos susijusios tik su astrologija ar kosmologija; Pramogos, Būtent pasirodymai astrologijos ar kosmologijos tema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Izglītība un apmācība, abas tikai saistībā ar astroloģiju vai kosmoloģiju; Izpriecas, Respektīvi uzstāšanās par astroloģijas vai kosmoloģijas tēmām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Edukazzjoni u taħriġ, it-tnejn relatati biss mal-astroloġija jew il-kożmoloġija; Divertiment, Jiġifieri preżentazzjonijiet bis-suġġett l-astroloġija jew il-kożmoloġija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Onderwijs en opleiding, beide alleen in verband met astrologie of kosmologie; Ontspanning, Te weten optredens met als onderwerp astrologie of kosmologie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Nauczanie i kształcenie, oba wyłącznie w związku z astrologią lub kosmologią; Rozrywka, Mianowicie wystąpienia w dziedzinie astrologii lub kosmologii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de educação e formação, ambos exclusivamente relacionados com astrologia ou cosmologia; Divertimento, Nomeadamente espetáculos relacionados com astrologia ou cosmologia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Educație și instruire, ambele numai în legătură cu astrologia sau cosmologia; Divertisment, Și anume evenimente pe tema astrologiei sau cosmologiei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vzdelávanie a zabezpečovanie výcvikov, kurzov a školení, iba so zameraním na astrológiu alebo kozmológiu; Zábava, Menovite živé vystúpenia s témou astrológie alebo kozmológie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Izobraževanje in usposabljanje, oboje samo v zvezi z astrologijo ali kozmologijo; Razvedrilo, In sicer nastopi s tematiko astrologije ali kozmologije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Undervisning och utbildning, båda i samband med astrologi eller kosmologi; Underhållning, Nämligen uppträdanden avseende ämnet astrologi eller kosmologi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Промишлени анализи и проучвания; Проектиране и разработване на компютърен софтуер и хардуер; Научни и технологични услуги; Проучване в областта на технологиите; Научни услуги и дизайн свързан с тях; Технологични услуги и дизайн свързани с тях; Научни проучвания; Всички горепосочени услуги само във връзка с астрология или космология.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Analytické a výzkumné služby v průmyslu; Navrhování a vývoj počítačového hardwaru a softwaru; Vědecké a technologické služby; Výzkum vztahující se k technologiím; Vědecké služby a s nimi spojený design; Technologické služby a s nimi spojený design; Služby v oblasti výzkumu; Všechny služby pouze v souvislosti s astrologií nebo kosmologií.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Industriel analyse og forskning; Design og udvikling af computer hardware og computer software; Videnskabelige og teknologiske tjenesteydelser; Teknologiske studier; Videnskabelige tjenesteydelser og design relateret hertil; Teknologiske tjenesteydelser og design relateret hertil; Forskning; Alle førnævnte tjenesteydelser kun i forbindelse med astrologi eller kosmologi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Industrielle Analyse- und Forschungsdienstleistungen; Entwurf und Entwicklung von Computerhardware und -software; Wissenschaftliche und technologische Dienstleistungen; Technologische Forschung; Wissenschaftliche Dienstleistungen und das darauf bezogene Design; Technologische Dienstleistungen und darauf bezogenes Design; Wissenschaftliche Forschung; alle Dienstleistungen nur im Zusammenhang mit Astrologie oder Kosmologie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες βιομηχανικής ανάλυσης και έρευνας· Σχεδιασμός και ανάπτυξη υλισμικού και λογισμικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Επιστημονικές και τεχνολογικές υπηρεσίες· Τεχνολογική έρευνα· Επιστημονικές υπηρεσίες και σχετικός σχεδιασμός· Τεχνολογικές υπηρεσίες και σχετικός σχεδιασμός· Υπηρεσίες έρευνας· Στο σύνολό τους οι προαναφερόμενες υπηρεσίες μόνο σε σχέση με την αστρολογία ή την κοσμολογία.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Industrial analysis and research services; Design and development of computer hardware and software; Science and technology services; Research relating to technology; Scientific services and design relating thereto; Technological services and design relating thereto; Research services; All services exclusively relating to astrology or cosmology.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de análisis e investigaciones industriales; Diseño y desarrollo de equipos informáticos y de software; Servicios científicos y tecnológicos; Investigación relativa a la tecnología; Servicios científicos y diseño relacionado con los mismos; Servicios tecnológicos y diseño relacionado con los mismos; Servicios de investigación; Todos los servicios sólo relacionados con la astrología o la cosmología.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tööstuslikud analüüsid ja uuringud teenusena; Arvutiriistvara ja -tarkvara projekteerimine ja arendus; Teadus- ja tehnoloogiateenused; Tehnoloogilised uurimused; Teaduslikud teenused ja nende alane disain; Tehnoloogilised teenused ja nende alane disain; Uurimistööteenused; Kõik teenused on seotud ainult astroloogia või kosmoloogiaga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Teolliset analyysi- ja tutkimuspalvelut; Tietokonelaitteistojen ja -ohjelmistojen suunnittelu ja kehittäminen; Tieteelliset ja teknologiset palvelut; Teknologiaan liittyvä tutkimus; Tieteelliset palvelut ja siihen liittyvä suunnittelu; Tekniset palvelut ja siihen liittyvä suunnittelu; Tutkimuspalvelut; Kaikki palvelut liittyvät vain astrologiaan tai kosmologiaan.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d'analyses et de recherches industrielles; Conception et développement d'ordinateurs et de logiciels; Services scientifiques et technologiques; Études technologiques; Services scientifiques et de conception s'y rapportant; Services techniques et de conception s'y rapportant; Services de recherche technique; Tous les services uniquement en relation avec l'astrologie ou la cosmologie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge industrijskih analiza i istraživanja; Koncepcija i razvoj računala i računalnih programa [softvera]; Usluge znanosti i tehnologije; Tehnološka istraživanja; Znanstvene usluge i projektiranje s njima u svezi; Tehnološke usluge i projektiranje s njima u svezi; Usluge istraživanja; Sve usluge u vezi s astrologijom ili kozmologijom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ipari elemző és kutató szolgáltatások; Számítástechnikai hardver és szoftver tervezés és fejlesztés; Tudományos és technológiai szolgáltatások; Technológiai kutatás; Tudományos szolgáltatások és a hozzájuk kapcsolódó tervezés; Technológiai szolgáltatások és a hozzájuk kapcsolódó tervezés; Kutatási szolgáltatások; Az összes fent nevezett szolgáltatás asztrológiával vagy kozmológiával összefüggésben.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di analisi e di ricerche industriali; Progettazione e sviluppo di hardware e software; Servizi di scienza e tecnologia; Studi tecnologici; Servizi scientifici e progettazione relativa agli stessi; Servizi tecnologici e progettazione relativa agli stessi; Ricerca scientifica; Tutti i suddetti servizi esclusivamente in relazione ad astrologia e cosmologia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Pramoninės analizės ir tyrimų paslaugos; Kompiuterių programinės ir aparatinės įrangos projektavimas ir tobulinimas; Mokslo ir technologijų paslaugos; Technologiniai tyrimai; Mokslinės paslaugos ir su tuo susijęs projektavimas; Technologinės paslaugos ir su tuo susijęs projektavimas; Mokslinių tyrimų paslaugos; Visos paslaugos, susijusios tik su astrologija ar kosmologija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Rūpnieciskā izpēte un izstrādnes; Datoru aparatūras un programmatūras projektēšana, izstrāde un pilnveidošana; Zinātniskie un tehnoloģiskie pakalpojumi; Izpēte saistībā ar tehnoloģijām; Zinātniskie pakalpojumi un ar tiem saistītā projektēšana; Tehnoloģiskie pakalpojumi un ar tiem saistītā projektēšana; Izpētes pakalpojumi; Visi minētie pakalpojumi tikai saistībā ar astroloģiju vai kosmoloģiju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Analiżi industrijali u servizzi ta' riċerka; Disinn u żvilupp ta' ħardwer u softwer tal-kompjuter; Servizzi xjentifiċi u teknoloġiċi; Riċerka relatata mat-teknoloġija; Servizzi xjentifiċi u disinn relatat magħhom; Servizzi teknoloġiċi u disinn relatat magħhom; Servizzi ta' riċerka; Is-servizzi kollha relatati biss mal-astroloġija jew il-kożmoloġija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Dienstverlening op het gebied van industriële analyse en industrieel onderzoek; Ontwerpen en ontwikkelen van computers en van software; Wetenschappelijke en technologische diensten; Onderzoek met betrekking tot technologie; Wetenschappelijke diensten en ontwerp met betrekking tot genoemde diensten; Technologische diensten en technologisch ontwerp; Onderzoeken op wetenschappelijk gebied; Alle diensten alleen in verband met astrologie of kosmologie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przemysłowe analizy i usługi badawcze; Projektowanie i rozwój komputerowego sprzętu i oprogramowania; Usługi naukowe i technologiczne; Badania dotyczące technologii; Usługi naukowe i projektowanie w tym zakresie; Usługi technologiczne i projektowanie w tym zakresie; Usługi badawcze; Wszystkie wyżej wymienione usługi tylko w zakresie astrologii lub kosmologii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de análises e de pesquisas industriais; Concepção e desenvolvimento de computadores e de programas de computadores; Serviços de ciência e tecnologia; Investigação relacionada com tecnologia; Serviços científicos e de design relacionados com os mesmos; Serviços tecnológicos e de design relacionados com os mesmos; Serviços de investigação; Todos os serviços atrás referidos exclusivamente relacionados com astrologia ou cosmologia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de analiză şi cercetare industrială; Crearea şi dezvoltarea calculatoarelor şi a programelor de calculator; Servicii în domeniul ştiinţei şi tehnologiei; Cercetare privind tehnologia; Servicii ştiinţifice şi design privind acest domeniu; Servicii tehnologice şi design privind acest domeniu; Servicii de cercetare; Toate serviciile numai în legătură cu astrologia sau cosmologia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Priemyselné analýzy a priemyselný výskum; Návrh a vývoj počítačového hardvéru a softvéru; Vedecké a technologické služby; Technologický výskum; Vedecké služby a dizajn s nimi súvisiaci; Technologické služby a k nim sa vzťahujúci dizajn; Výskum; Všetky služby iba so zameraním na astrológiu alebo kozmológiu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Industrijske analize in raziskave; Oblikovanje in razvoj računalniške strojne in programske opreme; Znanstvene in tehnološke storitve; Raziskave v zvezi s tehnologijo; Znanstvene storitve in oblikovanje v zvezi s tem; Tehnološke storitve in oblikovanje v zvezi s tem; Raziskovalne storitve; Vse storitve samo v zvezi z astrologijo ali kozmologijo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Industriella analyser och forskningstjänster; Design och utveckling av datahårdvaror och mjukvaror; Vetenskapliga och tekniska tjänster; Forskning rörande teknik; Vetenskapliga tjänster och design relaterad därtill; Tekniska tjänster och design relaterad därtill; Forskning; Alla tjänster endast i samband med astrologi eller kosmologi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/095</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-21</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/200</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-20</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082072</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>18935</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003124457</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-06-18</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>FR</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>1596850</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>1990-06-12</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>1596850</RegistrationNumber>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>APAX</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>919225</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>44966</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
