<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-16T10:16:42</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229041</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229041</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-10-14</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-16</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>LG CHI COLORMASTER</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>7</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Електронни устройства за съхранение, претегляне, смесване, блендиране, подготовка, приготвяне и разпространение на оцветители за коса или бои за коса; Електронни устройства за съхранение, претегляне, смесване, блендиранее, подготовка, изработка и разпространение на съставки за приготвяне на оцветители за коса или бои за коса.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Elektronická zařízení pro skladování, vážení, míchání, míchání, přípravu, výrobu a distribuci barviv na vlasy nebo barev na vlasy; Elektronická zařízení pro skladování, vážení, míchání, míchání, přípravu, výrobu a distribuci složek pro výrobu barviv na vlasy nebo barev na vlasy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Elektroniske anordninger til lagring, vejning, piskning, blanding, tilberedning, fremstilling og fordeling af hårfarver eller hårfarve; Elektroniske anordninger til lagring, vejning, piskning, blanding, tilberedning, fremstilling og fordeling af ingredienser til fremstilling af hårfarver eller hårfarve.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Elektronische Geräte zum Speichern, Wiegen, Mischen, Zubereiten, Herstellen und Vertreiben von Haarfärbemitteln; Elektronische Geräte zum Speichern, Wiegen, Mischen, Zubereiten, Herstellen und Vertreiben von Zutaten zur Herstellung von Haarfärbemitteln.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ηλεκτρονικές διατάξεις για αποθήκευση, ζύγιση, ανάμειξη, πολτοποίηση, προετοιμασία, παρασκευή και διανομή χρωστικών για τα μαλλιά ή βαφών μαλλιών· Ηλεκτρονικές διατάξεις για αποθήκευση, ζύγιση, ανάμειξη, πολτοποίηση, προετοιμασία, παρασκευή και διανομή συστατικών για την παρασκευή χρωστικών για τα μαλλιά ή βαφών μαλλιών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Electronic devices for storing, weighing, mixing, blending, preparing, making and distributing hair colorants or hair dyes; electronic devices for storing, weighing, mixing, blending, preparing, making and distributing ingredients for making hair colorants or hair dyes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Dispositivos electrónicos para almacenar, pesar, mezclar, combinar, preparar, hacer y distribuir colorantes para el cabello o tintes para el cabello; Dispositivos electrónicos para almacenar, pesar, mezclar, combinar, preparar, hacer y distribuir ingredientes para hacer colorantes para el cabello o tintes para el cabello.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Juuste värvimis- ja toonimisvahendite säilitamise, kaalumise, segamise, hajutamise, ettevalmistamise, valmistamise ja levitamise elektroonikaseadmed; Juuste värvimis- ja toonimisvahendite valmistamisel koostisosade säilitamise, kaalumise, segamise, hajutamise, ettevalmistamise, valmistamise ja levitamise elektroonikaseadmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Elektroniset laitteet hiusvärien säilyttämiseen, punnitsemiseen, sekoittamiseen, valmistamiseen, tekemiseen ja annosteluun; Elektroniset laitteet hiusvärien valmistukseen tarkoitettujen ainesosien säilyttämiseen, punnitsemiseen, sekoittamiseen, valmistamiseen, tekemiseen ja annosteluun.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Dispositifs électroniques pour le stockage, le pesage, l'amalgame, le mélange, la préparation, la fabrication et la distribution de colorants pour cheveux ou teintures pour cheveux; Dispositifs électroniques pour le stockage, le pesage, l'amalgame, le mélange, la préparation, la fabrication et la distribution d'ingrédients pour la fabrication de colorants pour cheveux ou teintures pour cheveux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Elektronički uređaji za pohranu, vaganje, miksanje, miješanje, pripremu, izradu i distribuciju boja ili bojila za kosu; Elektronički uređaji za pohranu, vaganje, miksanje, miješanje, pripremu, izradu i distribuciju sastojaka za izradu boja ili bojila za kosu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Elektronikus eszközök hajfestékek vagy hajszínezők tárolására, mérésére, keverésére, összekeverésére, előkészítésére, elkészítésére és terjesztésére; Elektronikus eszközök hajszínezők vagy hajfestékek készítéséhez szükséges összetevők tárolására, mérésére, keverésére, összekeverésére, előkészítésére, elkészítésére és terjesztésére.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Dispositivi elettronici per contenere, pesare, mescolare, mischiare, preparare, fare e distribuire coloranti o tinture per capelli; Dispositivi elettronici per contenere, pesare, mescolare, mischiare, preparare, fare e distribuire ingredienti per fare coloranti o tinture per capelli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektroniniai prietaisai, skirti plaukų dažikliams ar plaukų dažams laikyti, sverti, maišyti, maišyti, ruošti, gaminti ir paskirstyti; Elektroniniai prietaisai, skirti laikyti, sverti, maišyti, maišyti, ruošti, gaminti ir paskirstyti komponentus plaukų dažikliams ar plaukų dažams gaminti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elektroniskas ierīces matu krāsvielu vai matu krāsu uzglabāšanai, svēršanai, sajaukšanai, maisīšanai, sagatavošanai, izgatavošanai un izplatīšanai; Elektroniskas ierīces sastāvdaļu glabāšanai, svēršanai, sajaukšanai, maisīšanai, sagatavošanai, izgatavošanai un izplatīšanai matu krāsvielu vai matu krāsu pagatavošanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tagħmir elettroniku għall-ħżin, l-użin, taħlit, taħlit, preparazzjoni, twettiq u distribuzzjoni ta' koloranti tax-xagħar jew żebgħa tax-xagħar; Tagħmir elettroniku għall-ħżin, l-użin, taħlit, taħlit, preparazzjoni, twettiq u distribuzzjoni ta' ingredjenti għat-twettiq tal-koloranti tax-xagħar jew żebgħa tax-xagħar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Elektronische toestellen voor het opslaan, wegen, mengen, mixen, prepareren, bereiden en distribueren van haarverven of haarkleurmiddelen; Elektronische toestellen voor het opslaan, wegen, mengen, mixen, prepareren, bereiden en distribueren van ingrediënten voor het bereiden van haarverven of haarkleurmiddelen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Elektroniczne urządzenia do przechowywania, ważenia, mieszania, mieszania, przygotowywania, wytwarzania i dystrybucji środków koloryzujących do włosów lub farb do włosów; Elektroniczne urządzenia do przechowywania, ważenia, mieszania, mieszania, przygotowywania, wytwarzania i dystrybucji składników do wytwarzania środków koloryzujących do włosów lub farb do włosów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Dispositivos eletrónicos para armazenamento, pesagem, mistura, preparação, produção e distribuição de produtos de coloração ou tintas para o cabelo; Dispositivos eletrónicos para armazenamento, pesagem, mistura, preparação, produção e distribuição de ingredientes para a produção de produtos de coloração ou tintas para o cabelo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Dispozitive electronice pentru stocarea, cântărirea, amestecarea, amestecul, prepararea, pregătirea și distribuirea coloranților pentru păr sau vopselelor de păr; Dispozitive electronice pentru stocarea, cântărirea, amestecarea, amestecul, prepararea, pregătirea și distribuirea ingredientelor pentru prepararea coloranților pentru păr sau vopselelor de păr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Elektronické prístroje na skladovanie, váženie, miešanie, prípravu, výrobu a distribúciu farbív na vlasy; Elektronické prístroje na skladovanie, váženie, miešanie, prípravu, výrobu a distribúciu prísad do farbív na vlasy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Elektronske naprave za shranjevanje, tehtanje, mešanje, kombiniranje, pripravo, izdelavo in distribucijo barvilnih sredstev za lase ali barv za lase; Elektronske naprave za shranjevanje, tehtanje, mešanje, kombiniranje, pripravo, izdelavo in distribucijo sestavin za izdelavo barvilnih sredstev za lase ali barv za lase.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Elektroniska anordningar för lagring, vägning, mixning, blandning, beredning, tillverkning och distribution av hårfärger eller hårfärger; Elektroniska anordningar för lagring, vägning, mixning, blandning, beredning, tillverkning och distribution av ingredienser för framställning av hårfärger eller hårfärger.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Устройства за измерване и анализ на цвета и състоянието на косата; Апаратура за измерване на цвета и състоянието на косата с цел съдействие за боядисване на косата (което може да се използва заедно със смартфон); Таймери; Спектрофотометри; Оптични сензори; Цифрови измервателни апарати; Измервателни устройства, електрически; 3D скенери; Цифрови входни и изходни скенери; Приложен софтуер за смарт телефон с цел съчетаване на цвета на косата за боядисване и оформяне на косата; Компютърен софтуер за подпомагане при боядисване на косата; Компютърен софтуер за съхранение, претегляне, смесване, блендиране, подготовка, изработване и разпространение на машини и апарати за оцветители за коса, бои за коса или съставки за приготвяне на оцветители или бои за коса; Компютърен софтуер за стандартизация при съчетаването на цветовете и боядисването; Софтуер за наблюдение, анализ, откриване, запис, обработка, предаване и получаване на информация, данни, звук и изображения във връзка с боядисването на косата; Софтуерна програма за изкуствен интелект с възможност за изтегляне, за безжични терминали; Софтуерни приложения за мобилни телефони; Софтуер за виртуална реалност; Софтуер за добавена реалност.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přístroje pro měření a analýzu barvy a stavu vlasů; Měřicí přístroj pro barvu a stav vlasů pro účely pomoci při barvení vlasů (který lze použít ve spojení s chytrým telefonem); Časoměřiče; Spektrofotometry; Optická čidla; Digitální měřicí přístroje; Elektrické měřicí přístroje; 3D skenery; Digitální vstupní a výstupní skenery; Aplikační software pro chytré telefony pro účely porovnávání barvy vlasů při barvení vlasů a úpravě účesu; Počítačový software pro pomoc při barvení vlasů; Počítačový software pro skladování, vážení, míchání, míchání, přípravu, výrobu a distribuci strojů a přístrojů na barviva na vlasy, barvy na vlasy nebo složky pro výrobu barviv na vlasy nebo barev na vlasy; Počítačový software pro standardizaci porovnávání barev a barvení; Software pro monitorování, analyzování, detekci, záznam, zpracování, přenos a příjem informací, dat, zvuku a obrazu ve vztahu k barvení vlasů; Aplikační softwarový program s umělou inteligencí, ke stažení pro bezdrátové terminály; Aplikační software pro mobilní telefony; Software pro virtuální realitu; Software s rozšířenou realitou.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Enheder til måling og analyse af hårfarve og -tilstand; Måleapparater til hårfarve og hårets tilstand med henblik på hjælp til hårfarvning, som kan anvendes sammen med en smartphone; Timere; Spektrofotometre; Optiske sensorer; Digitale måleapparater; Måleapparater, elektriske; 3D-scannere; Digitale ind- og udlæsningsscannere; Applikationssoftware til smartphones til matchning af hårfarve og hårstyling; Computersoftware til hjælp med hårfarvning; Elektroniske anordninger til maskiner og apparater til lagring, vejning, piskning, blanding, tilberedning, fremstilling og fordeling af hårfarver og hårfarve samt til ingredienser til fremstilling af hårfarver eller hårfarve; Computersoftware til standardisering af matchningen af hårfarver og hårfarvning; Software for overvågning, analyse, detektering, optagelse, behandling, afsendelse og modtagelse af information, data, lyd og billeder i forbindelse med hårfarvning; Downloadable applikationssoftwareprogrammer inden for kunstig intelligens til trådløse terminaler; Applikationssoftware til mobiltelefoner; Virtual reality-software; Augmenteret reality-software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Geräte zur Messung und Analyse von Haarfarbe und -zustand; Messapparate für die Haarfarbe und den Haarzustand zur Unterstützung des Haarfärbens (zur Verwendung in Verbindung mit einem Smartphone); Zeitgeber; Spektrophotometer; Optische Sensoren; Digitale Messgeräte; Elektrische Messgeräte; 3D-Scanner; Digitale Computereingabe- und -ausgabescanner; Anwendungssoftware für Smartphones zur Abstimmung von Haarfarben für das Haarfärben und Haarstyling; Computersoftware zur Unterstützung des Haarfärbens; Computersoftware zum Speichern, Wiegen, Mischen, Zubereiten, Herstellen und Vertreiben von Maschinen und Apparaten für Haarfärbemittel oder Zutaten zur Herstellung von Haarfärbemitteln; Computersoftware zur Standardisierung der Farbabstimmung und des Färbens; Software zum Überwachen, Analysieren, Erkennen, Aufzeichnen, Verarbeiten, Übermitteln und Empfangen von Informationen, Daten, Ton und Bildern in Bezug auf das Haarfärben; Anwendungssoftwareprogramme für künstliche Intelligenz, herunterladbar für drahtlose Endgeräte; Anwendungssoftware für Mobiltelefone; Virtual-Reality-Software; Software für erweiterte Realität.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές για τη μέτρηση και την ανάλυση του χρώματος και της κατάστασης των μαλλιών· Συσκευές μέτρησης χρώματος και κατάστασης μαλλιών για την παροχή βοήθειας στη βαφή μαλλιών (με δυνατότητα χρήσης σε συνδυασμό με έξυπνο τηλέφωνο)· Χρονομέτρες· Φασματοφωτόμετρο· Οπτικοί αισθητήρες· Ψηφιακές συσκευές μέτρησης· Μέτρηση (ηλεκτρικές συσκευές -ης)· Τρισδιάστατοι σαρωτές· Ψηφιακοί σαρωτές εισόδου και εξόδου· Λογισμικό εφαρμογών για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα για την αντιστοίχιση χρώματος μαλλιών με βαφές μαλλιών και για το φορμάρισμα μαλλιών· Λογισμικό ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για παροχή βοήθειας στη βαφή μαλλιών· Λογισμικό ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για αποθήκευση, ζύγιση, ανάμειξη, πολτοποίηση, προετοιμασία, παρασκευή και διανομή μηχανών και συσκευών για χρωστικές μαλλιών, βαφές μαλλιών ή συστατικά για την παρασκευή χρωστικών για τα μαλλιά ή βαφών μαλλιών· Λογισμικό ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για τυποποίηση αντιστοίχισης χρωμάτων και βαφών· Λογισμικό για παρακολούθηση, ανάλυση, ανίχνευση, καταγραφή, επεξεργασία, μετάδοση και λήψη πληροφοριών, δεδομένων, ήχου και εικόνων σε σχέση με βαφές μαλλιών· Προγράμματα λογισμικού εφαρμογών τεχνητής νοημοσύνης, τηλεφορτώσιμα για ασύρματα τερματικά· Λογισμικό εφαρμογών για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Λογισμικό εικονικής πραγματικότητας· Λογισμικό επαυξημένης πραγματικότητας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Devices for measuring and analyzing hair color and condition; measuring apparatus for hair color and condition for the purpose of hair dyeing assistance (that can be used in conjunction with a smartphone); timers; spectrophotometer; optical sensors; digital measuring apparatus; measuring devices, electric; 3D scanners; digital input and output scanners; application software for smart phone for the purpose of hair color matching of hair dyeing and hair styling; computer software for assisting hair dyeing; computer software for storing, weighing, mixing, blending, preparing, making and distributing machines and apparatus for hair colorants, hair dyes or ingredients for making hair colorants or hair dyes; computer software for standardization of color matching and dyeing; software for monitoring, analyzing, detecting, recording, processing, transmitting and receiving information, data, sound and images in relation to hair dyeing; artificial intelligence application software program, downloadable for wireless terminals; application software for smart phone; virtual reality software; augmented reality software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Dispositivos para medir y analizar el color y el estado del cabello; Aparatos para medir el color y el estado del cabello para la asistencia en el teñido del cabello (que puede usarse en conjunción con un teléfono inteligente [smartphone]; Temporizadores; Espectrofotómetros; Sensores ópticos; Aparatos de medida digitales; Aparatos eléctricos de medición; Escáneres 3D; Escáneres digitales de entrada y salida de datos; Software de aplicaciones para teléfonos inteligentes [smartphone] para determinar el color del cabello para tintar el cabello y peinar el cabello; Software para la asistencia en el teñido del cabello; Software para almacenar, pesar, mezclar, combinar, preparar, hacer y distribuir máquinas y aparatos para colorantes para el cabello, tintes para el cabello o ingredientes para hacer colorantes para el cabello o tintes para el cabello; Software para estandarizar la determinación de colores y tintes; Software para supervisar, analizar, detectar, registrar, procesar, transmitir y recibir información, datos, sonido e imágenes relacionados con el teñido del cabello; Programa de software de aplicaciones de inteligencia artificial descargable para terminales inalámbricos; Aplicaciones de software para teléfonos móviles; Software de realidad virtual; Software de realidad aumentada.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Juuste värvuse ja seisundi mõõte- ja analüüsiseadmed; Juuste värvi ja seisundi mõõtmisseadmed juuste värvimiseks (mida on võimalik kasutada koos nutiseadmega); Aegreleed; Spektrofotomeetrid; Optilised sensorid; Digitaalmõõteseadmed; Elektrilised mõõteseadmed; 3D-skannerid; Digitaalsed sisend- ja väljundskannerid; Järgmisel eesmärgil kasutatav nutitelefonide rakendustarkvara: juuksevärvide sobitamine juuste värvimiseks ja stiliseerimiseks; Arvutitarkvara juuste värvimise hõlbustamiseks; Arvutitarkvara juuksevärvide, juuste toonimisvahendite või nende koostisosade masinate ja vahendite säilitamiseks, kaalumiseks, segamiseks, hajutamiseks, ettevalmistamiseks, tootmiseks ja levitamiseks; Arvutitarkvara juuksevärvide sobitamise ja juuste värvimise standardiseerimiseks; Järgmisel eesmärgil kasutatav tarkvara: juuksevärvide teabe, andmete, heli ja piltide jälgimine, analüüsimine, tuvastamine, salvestamine, töötlemine, edastamine ja vastuvõtmine; Tehisintellekti rakendustarkvara programmid, mida on võimalik juhtmeta terminalide kaudu alla laadida; Mobiiltelefonide rakendustarkvara; Virtuaalreaalsuse tarkvara; Liitreaalsustarkvara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Laitteet hiusten värin ja hiusten kunnon mittaamiseen ja analysointiin; Hiusten värin ja kunnon mittauslaitteet hiusten värjäyksen avuksi (joita voidaan käyttää yhdessä älypuhelimen kanssa); Ajastimet; Spektrofotometrit; Optiset anturit; Digitaaliset mittauslaitteet; Mittalaitteet, sähkötoimiset; 3D-skannerit; Skannerit, joissa digitaalinen sisään- ja ulostulo; Älypuhelinten sovellusohjelmistot hiusten värjäykseen ja hiusten muotoiluun liittyvään hiusten värisävyn määrittämiseen; Tietokoneohjelmistot hiusten värjäämisen avuksi; Tietokoneohjelmistot hiusvärien ja hiusvärien valmistuksessa käytettävien ainesosien säilyttämiseen, punnitukseen, sekoittamiseen, valmistukseen, tekemiseen ja annosteluun tarkoitettuja koneita ja laitteita varten; Tietokoneohjelmistot värien sävyttämisen ja värjäämisen standardisointiin; Ohjelmistot hiusten värjäämiseen liittyvien tietojen, datan, äänen ja kuvien valvontaan, analysointiin, tunnistamiseen, tallentamiseen, käsittelyyn, lähettämiseen ja vastaanottamiseen; Tekoälyä hyödyntävä sovellusohjelma, langattomiin päätelaitteisiin ladattava; Ohjelmistosovellukset matkapuhelimiin; Virtuaalitodellisuusohjelmistot; Lisättyyn todellisuuteen liittyvät ohjelmistot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Dispositifs pour la mesure et l'analyse de la couleur et de l'état des cheveux; Appareils de mesurage de la couleur et de l'état des cheveux à des fins d'assistance pour la teinture des cheveux (pouvant être utilisés conjointement à un ordiphone [smartphone]); Minuteries; Spectrophotomètres; Capteurs optiques; Appareils de mesure numériques; Appareils électriques de mesure; Scanners tridimensionnels; Scanners d'entrée et de sortie numériques; Logiciels d'applications pour ordiphones [smartphones] aux fins de nuançage de couleurs de cheveux pour la teinture des cheveux et le coiffage; Logiciels d'assistance pour la teinture des cheveux; Logiciels pour machines et appareils de stockage, de pesage, d'amalgame, de mélange, de préparation, de fabrication et de distribution de colorants pour cheveux, teintures pour cheveux ou ingrédients pour la fabrication de colorants pour cheveux ou teintures pour cheveux; Logiciels de standardisation pour le nuançage de couleurs et la teinture; Logiciels pour la surveillance, l'analyse, la détection, l'enregistrement, le traitement, la transmission et la réception d'informations, données sons et images en lien avec la teinture des cheveux; Logiciels d'applications pour l'intelligence artificielle, téléchargeables à partir de terminaux sans fil; Logiciels applicatifs pour téléphones mobiles; Logiciels de réalité virtuelle; Logiciels de réalité augmentée.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Uređaji za mjerenje i analizu boje i stanja kose; Mjerni uređaji za boju i stanje kose za potrebe pomoći u bojenju kose (koji se mogu upotrebljavati s pametnim telefonom); Tajmeri; Spektrofotometri; Optički senzori; Uređaji za digitalno mjerenje; Električne naprave za mjerenje; 3D skeneri; Digitalni ulazni i izlazni skeneri; Aplikacijski softver za pametne telefone za potrebe usklađivanja boje kose za bojenje i oblikovanje kose; Računalni softver za pomoć u bojenju kose; Računalni softver za pohranu, vaganje, miksanje, miješanje, pripremu, izradu i distribuciju strojeva i aparata za boje za kosu, bojila za kosu ili sastojke za izradu boja ili bojila za kosu; Računalni softver za standardizaciju usklađivanja boja i bojenje; Softver za praćenje, analizu, otkrivanje, snimanje, obradu, prijenos i prijam informacija, podataka, zvuka i slika u vezi s bojenjem kose; Aplikacijski softverski program s umjetnom inteligencijom koji se može preuzeti za bežične terminale; Aplikacijski softver za mobilne telefone; Računalni program za virtualnu stvarnost; Softver „proširene stvarnosti”.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Eszközök haj színének és állapotának mérésére és elemzésére; A haj színének és állapotának mérésére szolgáló készülékek a hajfestéshez (amelyek okostelefonnal együtt használhatók); Időzítők; Spektrofotométerek; Optikai érzékelők; Digitális mérőberendezések; Mérőkészülékek, elektromos; Háromdimenziós szkennerek; Digitális bemeneti és kimeneti szkennerek; Alkalmazásszoftver okostelefonokhoz a hajfestés és a hajformázás hajszínének összehangolására; Számítógépes szoftver hajfestés elősegítésére; Számítógépes szoftverek hajfestékek, hajszínezők vagy hajfestékek vagy hajszínezők készítéséhez szükséges gépek és készülékek tárolására, mérésére, keverésére, összekeverésére, előkészítésére, elkészítésére és terjesztésére; Számítógépes szoftverek a színmegfelelőség és a festés szabványosításához; Információk, adatok, hangok és képek hajfestéssel kapcsolatos figyelésére, elemzésére, észlelésére, rögzítésére, feldolgozására, továbbítására és fogadására szolgáló szoftver; Mesterséges intelligencia-alkalmazásiszoftver, vezeték nélküli terminálok számára letölthető; Mobiltelefonos szoftveralkalmazások; Virtuális valóság szoftverek; "Kiterjesztett valóság" szoftver.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Dispositivi per la misurazione e l'analisi del colore e la condizione dei capelli; Strumenti di misura per il colore e la condizione dei capelli ai fini dell'assistenza nella tintura dei capelli (che si possono usare insieme a uno smartphone); Timer; Spettrofotometri; Sensori ottici; Apparecchi di misurazione digitali; Apparecchi elettrici di misura; Scanner 3D; Scanner ad immissione ed emissione digitale; Software applicativi per smartphone ai fini dell'abbinamento del colore dei capelli alla tintura e all'acconciatura dei capelli; Software per assistenza nella tintura dei capelli; Software per contenere, pesare, mescolare, mischiare, preparare, fare e distribuire macchine e apparecchi per coloranti per capelli, tinture per capelli o ingredienti per fare coloranti o tinture per capelli; Software per la standardizzazione dell'abbinamento di colore e tintura; Software per monitorare, analizzare, rilevare, registrare, elaborare, trasmettere e ricevere informazioni, dati, suono e immagini in relazione alla tintura dei capelli; Programma software applicativo di intelligenza artificiale, scaricabile per terminali senza filo; Software applicativi per telefoni cellulari; Software per realtà virtuale; Software di realtà aumentata.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Plaukų spalvos ir būklės matavimo ir analizės prietaisai; Plaukų spalvos ir būklės matavimo aparatai, skirti padėti dažyti plaukus (kuriuos galima naudoti kartu su išmaniuoju telefonu); Laikmačiai; Spektrofotometrai; Optiniai jutikliai; Skaitmeniniai matavimo aparatai; Elektriniai matavimo prietaisai; 3D skaitytuvai; Skaitmeniniai įvesties ir išvesties skaitytuvai; Taikomoji programinė įranga išmaniajam telefonui, siekiant suderinti plaukų spalvas su dažymu ir stiliaus formavimu; Kompiuterių programinė įranga, skirta padėti dažyti plaukus; Kompiuterių programinė įranga, skirta laikyti, sverti, maišyti, maišyti, ruošti, gaminti ir platinti mašinas ir aparatus, skirtus plaukų dažikliams, plaukų dažams ar ingredientams, skirtiems plaukų dažikliams ar plaukų dažams gaminti; Kompiuterių programinė įranga spalvų derinimui ir dažymui standartizuoti; Programinė įranga, skirta stebėti, analizuoti, aptikti, įrašyti, apdoroti, perduoti ir gauti informaciją, duomenis, garsą ir vaizdus, susijusius su plaukų dažymu; Dirbtinio intelekto taikomoji programinė įranga, atsisiunčiama belaidžiams terminalams; Mobiliųjų telefonų taikomoji programinė įranga; Virtualiosios realybės programinė įranga; Išplėstinės realybės programinė įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ierīces matu krāsas un stāvokļa mērīšanai un analīzei; Matu krāsas un stāvokļa mērīšanas aparāti, kas nepieciešami matu krāsošanai [ko var izmantot kopā ar viedtālruni]; Taimeri; Spektrofotometri; Optiskie sensori; Ciparu mērīšanas ierīces; Elektriskie mēraparāti; 3D skeneri; Ciparu ievades un izvades skeneri; Lietojumprogrammas viedtālrunim matu krāsošanas, balināšanas un veidošanai; Datoru programmatūras matu krāsošanai; Datoru programmatūras matu krāsvielu, matu krāsu vai matu krāsvielu vai matu krāsu pigmentu izgatavošanas sastāvdaļu un aparātu glabāšanai, svēršanai, sajaukšanai, maisīšanai, sagatavošanai, izgatavošanai un izplatīšanai; Datoru programmatūras krāsu saskaņošanas un krāsošanas standartizēšanai; Programmatūras informācijas, datu, skaņas un attēlu uzraudzībai, analīzei, noteikšanai, ierakstīšanai, apstrādei, pārsūtīšanai un saņemšanai saistībā ar matu krāsošanu; Mākslīgā intelekta lietojumprogrammu programma, kas lejupielādējama bezvadu termināļiem; Mobilo tālruņu lietojumprogrammatūra; Virtuālās realitātes programmatūra; Paplašinātās realitātes programmatūra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tagħmir għall-kejl u l-analiżi tal-kulur u l-kundizzjoni tax-xagħar; Apparat tal-kejl għall-kulur u l-kundizzjoni tax-xagħar għall-iskop ta' assistenza taż-żebgħa tax-xagħar (li jista' jintuża permezz ta' mowbajl); Mekkaniżmu awtomatiku biex iħaddem apparat f'ħin iffissat minn qabel; Spettrofotometru; Tagħmir sensittiv għad-dawl viżibbli; Apparat diġitali tal-kejl; Strumenti tal-kejl elettriċi; Skaners 3D; Skaners diġitali tad-dħul u l-ħruġ; Softwer ta' applikazzjoni għal smartphone għall-iskop ta' taqbil taż-żebgħa tax-xahar mal-kulur tax-xagħar u arranġament tax-xagħar; Softwer tal-kompjuter għall-assistenza taż-żebgħa tax-xagħar; Softwer tal-kompjuter għall-ħżin, l-użin, taħlit, taħlit, preparazzjoni, twettiq u magni tal-bejgħ awtomatiċi u apparat għall-koloranti tax-xagħar, żebgħa tax-xagħar jew ingredjenti għat-twettiq ta' koloranti tax-xagħar jew żebgħa tax-xagħar; Softwer tal-kompjuter għal standardizzazzjoni ta' tqabbil ta' kulur u żebgħa; Softwer għas-sorveljanza, analiżi, ditektjar, reġistrar, proċessar, trażmissjoni u r-riċevuta ta' informazzjoni, dejta, ħoss u immaġini f'relazzjoni ma' żebgħa tax-xagħar; Programm ta' softwer ta' applikazzjoni ta' intelliġenza artifiċjali li jista' jitniżżel għal terminali mingħajr fili; Sotwer tal-applikazzjonijiet għal telefowns ċellular; Softwer tar-realtà virtwali; Softwer f'ħin reali awmentat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Apparaten voor het meten en analyseren van haarkleur en -conditie; Toestellen voor het meten van de kleur en de conditie van het haar voor ondersteuning van het verven van het haar (voor gebruik in combinatie met een smartphone); Timers; Spectrofotometers; Optische sensoren; Meetapparatuur (Digitale -); Elektrische meetapparaten; 3D-scanners; Scanners voor digitale invoer en uitvoer; Applicatiesoftware voor smartphones voor het bij de haarkleur vinden van bijpassende haarkleurmiddelen en de opmaak van het haar; Software voor ondersteuning van het verven van het haar; Software voor het opslaan, wegen, mengen, mixen, prepareren, maken en distribueren van machines en apparaten voor haarverven, haarkleurmiddelen of ingrediënten voor het bereiden van haarverven of haarkleurmiddelen; Software voor het standaardiseren van het zoeken van bijpassende kleuren en kleuring; Software voor het bewaken, analyseren, opsporen, opnemen, verwerken, verzenden en ontvangen van informatie, gegevens, geluid en beelden in verband met het verven van het haar; Downloadbare applicatiesoftware met kunstmatige intelligentie voor draadloze terminals; Applicatiesoftware voor mobiele telefoons; Software voor virtual reality; Software voor toegevoegde realiteit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia do pomiaru i analizowania koloru i kondycji włosów; Urządzenia do mierzenia koloru i stanu włosów do celów pomocy przy farbowaniu włosów (które mogą być używane w połączeniu ze smartfonem); Czasomierze; Spektrofotometry; Czujniki optyczne; Cyfrowe urządzenia pomiarowe; Elektryczne urządzenia pomiarowe; Skanery 3D; Cyfrowe skanery wejścia i wyjścia; Oprogramowanie użytkowe do smartfona do dobierania koloru włosów do farbowania włosów i stylizacji włosów; Oprogramowanie komputerowe do pomocy przy farbowaniu włosów; Oprogramowanie komputerowe do maszyn i urządzeń do przechowywania, ważenia, mieszania, mieszania, przygotowywania, wytwarzania i dystrybucji środków koloryzujących do włosów, farb do włosów lub składników do wytwarzania środków do koloryzacji włosów lub farb do włosów; Oprogramowanie komputerowe do standaryzacji dobierania koloru i farbowania; Oprogramowanie do monitorowania, analizowania, wykrywania, zapisywania, przetwarzania, transmisji i odbierania informacji, danych, dźwięku i obrazów związanych z farbowaniem włosów; Komputerowy program użytkowy ze sztuczną inteligencją, do pobrania do terminali bezprzewodowych; Oprogramowanie użytkowe do telefonów komórkowych; Oprogramowanie rzeczywistości wirtualnej; Oprogramowanie do rzeczywistości rozszerzonej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Dispositivos para medição e análise da cor e do estado do cabelo; Aparelhos de medição da cor e do estado do cabelo para fins de assistência na coloração do cabelo (que podem ser utilizados em conjunto com um telefone inteligente); Temporizadores; Espetrofotómetros; Sensores óticos; Dispositivos de medida digitais; Aparelhos elétricos de medida; Digitalizadores (scanners) tridimensionais; Scanners de entrada e saída digitais; Software aplicativo para telefones inteligentes para fins de correspondência de cores para pintura do cabelo e para penteados; Software para assistência na coloração do cabelo; Software para máquinas e aparelhos de armazenamento, pesagem, mistura, preparação, produção e distribuição de produtos de coloração para o cabelo, tintas para o cabelo ou ingredientes para a produção de produtos de coloração ou tintas para o cabelo; Software para estandardização da correspondência de cores e da coloração; Software para monitorização, análise, deteção, registo, processamento, transmissão e receção de informações, dados, sons e imagens relacionados com coloração do cabelo; Programa de software aplicativo de inteligência artificial descarregável para terminais sem fios; Software aplicativo para telemóveis; Software de realidade virtual; Software de realidade aumentada.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Dispozitive pentru măsurarea și analiza culorii și stării părului; Aparate de măsurat pentru culoarea și starea părului în scopul asistenței pentru uscat părul (care pot fi folosite împreună cu un telefon inteligent); Cronometre; Spectrofotometru; Senzori optici; Aparate de măsurat digitale; Aparate electrice de măsurare; Scanere 3D; Scanere cu intrare și ieșire digitală; Software de aplicații pentru telefonul inteligent pentru potrivirea culorii părului la vopsitul părului și coafatul părului; Software de calculator pentru asistență la vopsit părul; Software de calculator pentru mașini și aparate pentru stocarea, cântărirea, amestecarea, amestecul, prepararea, pregătirea și distribuirea coloranților pentru păr, vopselelor de păr sau ingredientelor pentru preparat coloranți de păr sau vopsele de păr; Software de calculator pentru standardizarea potrivirii culorii și vopsirii; Software pentru monitorizarea, analiza, detectarea, înregistrarea, prelucrarea, transmiterea și primirea informațiilor, datelor, sunetului și imaginilor în legătură cu vopsit părul; Program software de aplicații cu inteligență artificială, descărcabil, pentru terminale fără fir; Aplicații software pentru telefoane mobile; Software de realitate virtuală; Software pentru realitate augmentată.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Prístroje na meranie a analýzy farby a stavu vlasov; Prístroje na meranie farby a stavu vlasov na účely pomoci pri farbení vlasov (ktoré možno používať so smartfónom); Časomerače; Spektrofotometre; Optické senzory; Digitálne meracie zariadenia; Elektrické meracie zariadenia; 3D skenery; Digitálne vstupné a výstupné skenery; Softvérová aplikácia pre smartfóny na účely výberu farby na vlasy; Počítačový softvér na pomoc pri farbení vlasov; Počítačový softvér pre prístroje a zariadenia na skladovanie, váženie, miešanie, prípravu, výrobu a distribúciu farbív na vlasy alebo prísad na výrobu farbív na vlasy; Počítačový softvér na štandardizáciu párovania farieb a farbenia; Softvér na monitorovanie, analýzu, detekciu, zaznamenávanie, spracovanie, prenos a príjem informácií, údajov, zvuku a obrazov v oblasti farbenia vlasov; Softvérové aplikácie s funkciami umelej inteligencie s možnosťou stiahnutia do bezdrôtových terminálov; Aplikačný softvér pre mobilné telefóny; Softvér pre virtuálnu realitu; Softvér s rozšírenou realitou.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Aparati za merjenje in analiziranje barve in stanja las; Merilni aparati za barvo in stanje las za namen pomoči pri barvanju las (ki se lahko uporabljajo v povezavi s pametnim telefonom); Štoparice, merilci časa, ure; Spektrofotometri; Optični senzorji; Digitalni merilni aparati; Električne merilne naprave; 3D skenerji; Optični čitalniki z digitalnim vhodom in izhodom; Aplikacijska programska oprema za pametni telefon za namen ujemanja barve las pri barvanju in oblikovanju las; Računalniška programska oprema za pomoč pri barvanju las; Računalniška programska oprema za shranjevanje, tehtanje, mešanje, kombiniranje, pripravo, izdelavo in distribucijo strojev ter aparatov za barvilna sredstva za lase, barve za lase ali sestavine za izdelavo barvilnih sredstev za lase ali barv za lase; Računalniška programska oprema za standardizacijo ujemanja barv in barvanja; Programska oprema za spremljanje, analizo, odkrivanje, snemanje, obdelavo, prenos in sprejemanje informacij, podatkov, zvoka ter slik v zvezi z barvanjem las; Program aplikacijske programske opreme za umetno inteligenco, prenosljiv za brezžične terminale; Namenska programska oprema za mobilne telefone; Programska oprema za navidezno resničnost; Programska oprema za razširjeno resničnost.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Enheter för att mäta och analysera hårfärg och tillstånd; Mätutrustning for hårets färg och tillstånd som hjälp vid färgning av håret (som kan användas med en smarttelefon); Timers; Spektralfotometrar; Optiska sensorer; Digitala mätapparater; Elektriska mätredskap; 3D-skannrar; Digitala skannrar för in- och utmatning; Applikationsprogramvara för smarttelefon för matchning av hårets färg med hårfärgämnen och hårfrisyr; Datorprogramvara som stöd för hårfärgning; Dataprogramvara för lagring, vägning, mixning, blandning, beredning, tillverkning och distribution av maskiner och utrustning för hårfärgämnen, hårfärgämnen eller ingredienser för framställning av hårfärgämnen eller hårfärgämnen; Datorprogramvara för standardisering av färgmatchning och färgning; Programvara för övervakning, analys, detektering, upptagning, behandling, överföring och mottagande av information, data, ljud och bilder avseende hårfärgning; Tillämpningsprogramvaruprogram med artificiell intelligens, nedladdningsbart för trådlösa terminaler; Mjukvaror i form av appar för mobiltelefoner; Virtual reality-programvara; Programvara för förstärkt verklighet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PriorityDetails>
<Priority>
<PriorityCountryCode>KR</PriorityCountryCode>
<PriorityNumber>4020200052929</PriorityNumber>
<PriorityDate>2020-03-30</PriorityDate>
<PriorityPartialIndicator>false</PriorityPartialIndicator>
<PriorityStatusCode>Claimed</PriorityStatusCode>
</Priority>
</PriorityDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/125</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-06</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/198</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>780751</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>10072</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
