<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-19T10:59:09</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229815</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229815</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-15</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-19</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>IMAXDR</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">USB памет; Калъфи, пригодени за мобилни телефони; Връзки (аксесоари) за мобилни телефони; Слушалки; Кабели за USB устройства; Аудио кабел; Кабели за предаване на данни; Поставки, пригодени за мобилни телефони; Зарядни устройства; Презареждащи се батерии; Зарядни устройства за мобилни телефони; Зарядни устройства за мобилни телефони за употреба в превозни средства; Защитно фолио за компютърни екрани; Защитни тънкослойни покрития, пригодени за смартфони; Компютърни клавиатури; Периферни устройства, пригодени за използване с компютри; Компютърни мишки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">USB flash disky; Obaly na mobilní telefony; Šňůrky na mobilní telefony; Sluchátka; USB kabely; Audio kabely; Kabely na přenos dat; Stojany přizpůsobené pro mobilní telefony; Nabíječky baterií; Dobíjecí baterie; Nabíječky baterií do mobilních telefonů; Nabíječky baterií do mobilních telefonů pro použití ve vozidlech; Ochranné fólie na počítačové obrazovky; Ochranné fólie na chytré telefony; Počítačové klávesnice; Periferní zařízení počítačů; Počítačové myši.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">USB flash drivere; Etuier til mobiltelefoner; Mobiltelefonremme; Høretelefoner; USB-kabler; Lydkabler; Kabler til datatransmission; Holdere til mobiltelefoner; Opladere til batterier; Genopladelige batterier; Batteriopladere til mobiltelefoner; Batteriopladere til mobiltelefoner til anvendelse i køretøjer; Beskyttende film tilpasset computerskærme; Beskyttelsesfilm tilpasset til smartphones; Tastaturer til computere; Perifere enheder til computere; Computermus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">USB-Sticks; Etuis für Mobiltelefone; Riemen für Mobiltelefone; Kopfhörer; USB-Kabel; Audiokabel; Kabel für die Datenübertragung; Angepasste Halter für Mobiltelefone; Ladegeräte für Batterien; Wiederaufladbare Batterien; Akkuladegeräte für Mobiltelefone; Akkuladegeräte zum Gebrauch für Mobiltelefone in Fahrzeugen; Schutzfolien für Computerbildschirme; Angepasste Schutzfolien für Smartphones; Computertastaturen; An Computer angepasste Peripheriegeräte; Computermaus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Οδηγοί USB (καθολικού σειριακού αγωγού)· Θήκες για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Λουράκια για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Ακουστικά· Καλώδια καθολικού σειριακού αγωγού (USB)· Καλώδια ήχου· Καλώδια μετάδοσης δεδομένων· Βάσεις για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Φορτιστές μπαταριών· Επαναφορτιζόμενες μπαταρίες· Φορτιστές μπαταριών για κυψελοειδή τηλέφωνα· Φορτιστές μπαταριών κυψελοειδών τηλεφώνων για χρήση σε οχήματα· Μεμβράνες προστασίας για οθόνες ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Προστατευτικές μεμβράνες προσαρμοσμένες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Πληκτρολόγια ηλεκτρονικού υπολογιστή· Περιφερειακός εξοπλισμός προσαρμοσμένος για χρήση σε ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Ποντίκια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">USB flash drives; Cell phone cases; Cell phone straps; Earphones; USB cables; Audio cables; Data cables; Stands adapted for mobile phones; Battery chargers; Chargeable batteries; Cell phone battery chargers; Cell phone battery chargers for use in vehicles; Protective films adapted for computer screens; Protective films adapted for smartphones; Computer keyboards; Computer peripheral devices; Computer mouses.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Memorias USB; Estuches adaptados para teléfonos móviles; Cordones para teléfonos celulares; Auriculares intraurales; Cables USB; Cables de audio; Cables para la transmisión de datos; Soportes adaptados para teléfonos móviles; Cargadores de pilas y baterías; Baterías recargables; Cargadores de baterías de teléfonos móviles; Cargadores de baterías de teléfonos móviles para vehículos; Láminas protectoras especiales para pantallas de ordenador; Películas de protección para teléfonos inteligentes [smartphones]; Teclados de ordenador; Dispositivos periféricos utilizados con ordenadores; Ratones de ordenador.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">USB-mälupulgad; Mobiiltelefonivutlarid; Mobiiltelefonide rihmad; Kõrvaklapid; USB-kaablid; Helijuhtmed; Andmeedastuskaablid; Mobiiltelefonide kohandatud alused; Akulaadurid, patareilaadurid; Akupatareid; Mobiiltelefonide akulaadurid; Sõidukites kasutatavad mobiiltelefonide akulaadurid; Arvutikuvarite kaitsekiled; Nutitelefonide kaitsekiled; Arvutite klaviatuurid, klahvistikud; Arvutite välisseadmed; Arvutihiired.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">USB-muistit; Matkapuhelinkotelot; Matkapuhelimen hihnat; Kuulokkeet; USB-kaapelit; Audiokaapelit; Tiedonsiirtokaapelit; Matkapuhelimille tarkoitetut telineet; Latauslaitteet sähköparistoille; Ladattavat akut; Matkapuhelinten akkujen laturit; Matkapuhelinten akkulaturit ajoneuvoissa käytettäväksi; Tietokoneen näytöille tarkoitetut suojakalvot; Älypuhelimille tarkoitetut suojakalvot; Tietokoneen näppäimistöt; Tietokoneiden oheislaitteet; Tietokonehiiret.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Clés USB; Étuis pour téléphones portables; Cordonnets pour téléphones mobiles; Casques d'écoute; Câbles USB; Câble audio; Câbles de transmission de données; Supports adaptés pour téléphones portables; Chargeurs de piles et batteries; Batteries rechargeables; Chargeurs de batterie pour téléphones cellulaires; Chargeurs de batterie de téléphones cellulaires pour véhicules; Films de protection conçus pour écrans d'ordinateur; Films de protection conçus pour ordiphones [smartphones]; Claviers d'ordinateur; Périphériques adaptés pour utilisation avec des ordinateurs; Souris d'ordinateur.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">USB uređaji [USB stickovi]; Futrole prilagođene za mobilne telefone; Trake za mobilne telefone; Slušalice; USB kablovi; Audio kablovi; Kablovi za prijenos podataka; Stalak za mobilne telefone; Akumulatori (punjači električnih akumulatora); Punjive baterije; Punjači baterija mobitela; Punjači baterija mobitela za uporabu u vozilima; Zaštitne folije prilagođene za zaslone računala; Zaštitne folije prilagođene za pametne telefone; Tipkovnice računala; Periferni uređaji prilagođeni za uporabu s računalima; Računalni miševi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">USB pendrive-ok; Mobiltelefonokhoz kialakított tokok; Szíjak, pántok mobiltelefonokhoz; Fejhallgatók; USB kábelek; Audio kábelek; Adatátviteli kábelek; Mobiltelefonokhoz kialakított állványok; Akkumulátor- és elemtöltők; Újratölthető elemek; Akkumulátortöltők mobiltelefonokhoz; Járművekben használt akkumulátortöltők mobiltelefonokhoz; Számítógép-képernyőkhöz kialakított védőfóliák; Védőfóliák okostelefonokhoz; Számítógép billentyűzetek; Számítógéphez kialakított perifériák; Számítógépes egerek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Chiavi USB; Custodie adattate per telefoni cellulari; Cinghie per cellulari; Auricolari; Cavi USB; Cavi audio; Cavi per trasmissione di dati; Supporti per telefoni cellulari; Caricabatterie; Batterie ricaricabili; Caricabatteria per telefoni cellulari; Caricabatteria da auto per telefoni cellulari; Pellicola di protezione adattata per schermo di computer; Pellicola protettiva adattata per smartphone; Tastiere del computer; Periferiche concepite per essere utilizzate con i computer; Mouse per computer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Atmintukai [USB]; Mobiliesiems telefonams pritaikyti dėklai; Mobiliųjų telefonų dirželiai; Ausinės; USB kabeliai; Garso kabeliai; Duomenų perdavimo kabeliai; Mobiliųjų telefonų laikikliai; Baterijų įkrovimo įtaisai; Įkraunamos baterijos; Mobiliojo ryšio telefonų baterijų įkrovikliai; Mobiliojo ryšio telefonų baterijų automobiliniai įkrovikliai; Kompiuterių ekranų apsauginės plėvelės; Išmaniųjų telefonų ekranų apsauginės plėvelės; Kompiuterių klaviatūros; Kompiuterių išoriniai įrenginiai; Kompiuterių pelės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">USB zibatmiņas; Mobilo tālruņu futrāļi; Mobilo telefonu aukliņas; Ieaušu austiņas; Universālo seriālo kopņu (USB) kabeļi; Audio kabeļi; Datu pārraides kabeļi; Mobilajiem tālruņiem pielāgoti statīvi; Akumulatoru uzlādes ierīces; Uzlādējamas baterijas; Mobilo tālruņu akumulatoru uzlādes ierīces; Mobilo tālruņu akumulatoru uzlādes ierīces izmantošanai transportlīdzekļos; Aizsargplēves, kas īpaši paredzētas datoru ekrāniem; Aizsargplēves, kas īpaši paredzētas viedtālruņiem; Datoru tastatūras; Datoru perifērijas ierīces; Datorpele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Flash drives tal-USB; Kaxxetti adattati għat-telefowns ċellulari; Ċineg tat-telefons ċellulari; Kuffji; Kejbil tal-USB; Linji tal-awdjo; Linji għat-trasmissjoni ta' data; Stends adattati għal telefons ċellulari; Karikaturi għal batteriji elettriċi; Batteriji li jistgħu jerġgħu jiġu ċċarġjati; Ċarġers tal-batteriji għat-telefowns ċellulari; Ċarġers tal-batteriji għat-telefowns ċellulari għall-użu fil-vetturi; Films protettivi adattati għall-iskrins tal-kompjuter; Films protettivi adattati għal smartfowns; Tastieri tal-kompjuters; Periferali addattati għall-użu mal-kompjuters; Maws tal-kompjuter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">USB-sticks; Hoesjes voor mobiele telefoons; Koordjes voor mobiele telefoons; Oortelefoons; USB kabels; Audiokabels; Datatransmissiekabels; Standaards aangepast voor mobiele telefoons; Batterij-laders; Oplaadbare batterijen; Batterijladers voor mobiele telefoons; Batterijopladers voor mobiele telefoons, voor gebruik in voertuigen; Beschermende folie aangepast voor computerschermen; Beschermende folie aangepast aan smartphones; Toetsenborden voor computers; Computerrandapparatuur; Computermuis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pamięci zewnętrzne USB; Futerały dopasowane do telefonów komórkowych; Paski do telefonów komórkowych; Słuchawki [douszne]; Kable USB; Kable audio; Kable do transmisji danych; Stojaki dostosowane do telefonów komórkowych; Ładowarki do baterii; Baterie do ponownego ładowania; Ładowarki do telefonów komórkowych; Ładowarki do telefonów komórkowych, do użytku w pojazdach; Folie ochronne przystosowane do ekranów komputerowych; Folie ochronne dostosowane do smartfonów; Klawiatury komputerowe; Sprzęt peryferyjny do komputerów; Myszki komputerowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Unidades de disco amovível [USB flash drives]; Bolsas adaptadas para telemóveis; Correias para telefones móveis; Auriculares; Cabos USB; Cabos de áudio; Cabos para a transmissão de dados; Suportes adaptados a telemóveis; Carregadores de baterias; Baterias recarregáveis; Carregadores de baterias de telemóveis; Carregadores de baterias de telemóveis para usar em veículos; Películas protetoras concebidas para ecrãs de computador; Películas protetoras adaptadas para smartphones; Teclados de computador; Periféricos adaptados para uso com computadores; Ratos para computador.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Memorii USB; Etuiuri pentru telefoane mobile; Curele pentru telefonul mobil; Căști auriculare; Cabluri USB; Cabluri audio; Cabluri pentru transmisia de date; Suporturi adaptate pentru telefoane mobile; Alimentatoare pentru acumulatoare; Baterii reîncărcabile; Încărcătoare de baterii pentru telefoane mobile; Încărcătoare de baterii de telefoane mobile destinate utilizării în vehicule; Folii de protecție adaptate pentru ecrane de calculatoare; Folii de protecție adaptate pentru telefoane inteligente; Tastaturi de calculator; Periferice adaptate pentru a fi folosite la calculatoare; Mouse-uri pentru computer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">USB kľúče; Puzdrá na mobilné telefóny; Šnúrky na mobilné telefóny; Slúchadlá; USB káble; Audio káble; Káble na prenos údajov; Stojany na mobilné telefóny; Nabíjačky batérií; Dobíjateľné batérie; Nabíjačky batérií pre mobilné telefóny; Nabíjačky batérií pre mobilné telefóny, používané vo vozidlách; Ochranné fólie na obrazovky počítačov; Ochranné fólie na smartfóny; Počítačové klávesnice; Periférne zariadenia počítačov; Počítačové myši.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">USB ključki; Etuiji za mobilne telefone; Trakovi za prenosne telefone; Slušalke; USB kabli; Avdio kabel; Kabli za prenos podatkov; Stojala, prirejena za prenosne telefone; Električni polnilniki za baterije; Baterije za ponovno polnjenje; Polnilniki za baterije, za mobilne telefone; Polnilniki za baterije mobilnih telefonov, ki se uporabljajo v vozilih; Zaščitne folije, prilagojene za računalniške zaslone; Zaščitne folije, prilagojene za pametne telefone; Računalniške tipkovnice; Zunanje enote, prilagojene za uporabo z računalniki; Računalniške miške.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">USB-minnen; Fodral anpassade för mobiltelefoner; Band för mobiltelefoner; Hörlurar; USB-kablar; Audiokablar; Kablar för dataöverföring; Ställ för mobiltelefoner; Batteriladdare; Återuppladdningsbara batterier; Batteriladdare till mobiltelefoner; Batteriladdare till mobiltelefoner för användning i fordon; Skyddsfilmer anpassade för datorskärmar; Skyddsfilm för smartphones; Tangentbord för datorer; Kringutrustning anpassade för användning med datorer; Datormusar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/085</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-07</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/156</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-18</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082624</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>91916</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018083702</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Change of name and professional address</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>91916</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-01</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
