<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-25T07:36:58</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229304</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229304</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>nl</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>RECSTAT</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>17</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Изолационни и преградни изделия и материали; Пломби, уплътнители и пълнители; Ударопоглъщащи и опаковъчни материали, вибрационни амортисьори (гасители на вибрации).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Izolační a bariérové výrobky a materiály; Těsnění, těsnicí materiál a materiál na výplně; Materiály učené k tlumení nárazů a obalové materiály, tlumiče vibrací.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Artikler og materialer til isolering og afspærring; Pakninger, tætninger og fyldmasser; Stødabsorberende og pakningsmaterialer, vibrationsdæmpere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Isolier- Dämm- und Barrierematerialien; Dichtungen, Dichtungsmittel und Füllmassen; Stoßabsorbierende- und Packungsmaterialien, Schwingungsdämpfer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Είδη και υλικά για μόνωση και για φραξιμο· Αεροστεγή σφραγίσματα,στεγανωτικά και υλικά γεμίσματος· Υλικά συσκευασίας και υλικά που απορροφούν τους κραδασμούς, αντιδονητικές βάσεις.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Insulation and barrier articles and materials; Seals, sealants and fillers; Shock-absorbing and packing materials, vibration dampers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Materiales y artículos para el aislamiento; Juntas, selladores y material de relleno; Materiales de embalaje y de absorción de impactos, amortiguadores de vibraciones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Isoleerivad tooted ja materjalid; Tihendid, hermeetikud ja täitematerjalid; Amortiseerivad ja täitematerjalid, vibratsioonisummutid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Eriste- ja sulkutuotteet ja -materiaalit; Tiivisteet, tiiviste- ja täytemateriaalit; Iskunvaimentavat materiaalit ja pakkausmateriaalit, värähtelyn vaimentimet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Articles et matériaux d'isolation et de protection; Joints, produits d'étanchéité et garnitures; Matériaux d'absorption des chocs et d'emballage, amortisseurs de vibrations.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Izolacijski i pregradni artikli i materijali; Brtve, brtvila i punila; Amortizacijski i ambalažni materijali, prigušivači vibracija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szigetelő-, és védőanyagok, eszközök; Tömítések és tömítőszerek, szűrőanyagok; Lökésgátló és csomagoló anyagok, rezgéscsillapítók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Articoli e materiali isolanti e di barriera (acustica); Guarnizioni, mastici e stucchi; Materiale per ammortizzare e imballare, smorzatori di vibrazioni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Izoliacijos ir užtvarų gaminiai ir medžiagos; Sandarikliai, tarpikliai ir užpildai; Amortizacinės medžiagos ir kamšalai, vibracijos slopintuvai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Izolācijas materiāli un aizsargbarjeras; Ielāpi, blīvējuma materiāli un pildījumi; Amortizatori un blīvēšanas materiāli, vibrāciju slāpētāji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Oġġetti u materjali għall-insulazzjoni u biex ma jgħaddix minnhom; Siġilli, siġillanti u filtri; Materjali biex jassorbu x-xokkijiet u għall-ippakkjar, umidifikaturi tal-vibrazzjoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Isolatie- en afsluitingsartikelen en -materialen.; Pakkingen, afdichtingsmiddelen en vulmiddelen; Schokabsorberende- en pakkingsmaterialen, trillingsdempers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Artykuły i materiały izolacyjne i zabezpieczające; Plomby, uszczelki i wypełnienia; Artykuły amortyzujące wstrząsy i zabezpieczające, tłumiki drgań.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Artigos e materiais isolantes e de proteção; Vedantes, selantes e enchimentos; Materiais de amortecimento e de proteção para embalagem, amortecedores de vibração.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Materiale și articole izolante și opritoare; Garnituri de etanșare, materiale de etanșare și filtre; Materiale pentru amortizare și ambalare, amortizoare pentru vibrații.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Izolačné a zábranové materiály a výrobky; Tesnenia, tesniace tmely a výplne; Nárazuvzdorné a obalové materiály, tlmiče vibrácií.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Izolacijski in pregradni proizvodi in materiali; Tesnila, tesnilna sredstva in mašilna sredstva; Materiali za blaženje udarcev in embaliranje, materiali za dušenje tresljajev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Artiklar och material för isolering och avspärrning; Tätningar, packningar och fyllnadsmedel; Stötdämpande material och förpackningsmaterial, vibrationsdämpare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/080</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/151</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-11</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/184</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>C.3.6</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-25</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>11055</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>37570</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017996003</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Proprietor - Change of name and address</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>37570</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-10</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017995823</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Change of name and professional address</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>37570</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-10</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
