<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-24T08:18:09</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229042</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229042</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-22</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-24</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>FEEL SAFE AT NH</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Франчайзингови услуги, а именно консултации и подпомагане на управлението, организиране и насърчаване на сделки, свързани със съдействие и/или управление на предприятие и хотели; Услуги, свързани с управление на хотели [за други]; Управление на хотели; Административно управление на хотели; Рекламни услуги, включително такива, които са свързани с хотели; Секретарски услуги, осигурени от хотели; Административно управление на хотели; Управление на хотели за трети лица; Консултантски услуги, свързани с ръководенето и управлението на хотели; Услуги за карти за лоялни клиенти в хотелиерския сектор.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Franšízing, a to konzultace a pomoc při řízení, organizování a propagaci obchodní činnosti vztahující se k pomoci při provozování a/nebo řízení podniků a hotelových provozoven; Služby hotelového managementu (pro třetí osoby); Hotelový management; Řízení obchodní činnosti hotelů; Propagační činnost, reklama včetně té, která se vztahuje k hotelům; Administrativní služby poskytované hotely; Řízení obchodní činnosti hotelů; Hotelový management pro třetí osoby; Poradenství v oblasti správy a řízení hotelů; Služby věrnostních karet v sektoru hotelnictví.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Franchisevirksomhed, nemlig rådgivning og konsulentbistand vedrørende ledelse, planlægning og promovering af forretninger i forbindelse med bistand ved drift og/eller ledelse af forretnings- og hotelvirksomheder; Forretningsmæssig hotelledelse (for andre); Hotelledelse; Forretningsmæssig bistand ved ledelse af hoteller; Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed, også i forbindelse med hoteller; Sekretariatsvirksomhed udbudt af hoteller; Forretningsmæssig bistand ved ledelse af hoteller; Ledelse af hoteller for andre; Konsulentbistand i forbindelse med administration og ledelse af hoteller; Kundekort inden for hotelbranchen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Franchising, nämlich Beratung und Unterstützung bei der Führung, Organisation und Entwicklung von Geschäften in Bezug auf die Hilfe beim Betrieb und/oder der Leitung von Hotelunternehmen und -einrichtungen; Geschäftsführung von Hotels [für Dritte]; Hotelmanagement; Geschäftsführung von Hotels im Auftrag Dritter; Werbung, auch in Bezug auf Hotels; Sekretariatsdienstleistungen von Hotels; Geschäftsführung von Hotels im Auftrag Dritter; Geschäftsführung in Bezug auf Hotels für Dritte; Beratung in Bezug auf Verwaltung und Leitung von Hotels; Ausgabe von Bonuskarten [Verkaufsförderung] im Hotelsektor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες δικαιοπαρόχου και, συγκεκριμένα, παροχή συμβουλών και υποστήριξης στη διεύθυνση, την οργάνωση και την προώθηση επιχειρηματικής δραστηριότητας στο πλαίσιο της παροχής βοήθειας για την εκμετάλλευση ή/και τη διεύθυνση ξενοδοχειακών επιχειρήσεων και καταστημάτων· Υπηρεσίες διαχείρισης ξενοδοχείων για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Διαχείριση ξενοδοχείων· Ξενοδοχείων διαχείρηση· Διαφημιστικές υπηρεσίες, συμπεριλαμβανομένων όσων έχουν σχέση με ξενοδοχεία· Υπηρεσίες γραμματείας παρεχόμενες από ξενοδοχεία· Ξενοδοχείων διαχείρηση· Διοίκηση επιχειρήσεων για ξενοδοχεία για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σε σχέση με τη διοίκηση και διαχείριση ξενοδοχείων· Υπηρεσίες καρτών τακτικού πελάτη στον ξενοδοχειακό κλάδο.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Franchise services, namely business promotion, organisation and management consultancy and assistance relating to assistance in the operation and/or management of hotel establishments and businesses; Hotel management service [for others]; Hotel management; Business management of hotels; Advertising, including advertising relating to hotels; Secretarial services provided by hotels; Business management of hotels; Hotel management for others; Consultancy services relating to the administration and management of hotels; Loyalty cards in the hotel sector.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">servicios de franquicias, a saber, consultas y asistencia en la dirección, organización y promoción de negocios relativas a la ayuda en la explotación y/o dirección de empresas y establecimientos hoteleros.; servicios de gestión de hoteles para terceros; servicios de gerencia administrativa de hoteles; servicios de gestión empresarial de hoteles; servicios de publicidad, incluidos aquellos relacionados con hoteles; servicios de secretariado facilitados por hoteles; gestión de negocios hoteleros; gestión hotelera para terceros; servicios de consultoría en administración y gestión hotelera; servicios de tarjetas de fidelización en el sector hotelero.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Frantsiisiteenused, st hotellide käitus- ja/või juhtimisabiga seotud äritegevuse juhtimise, korraldamise ning edendamise konsultatsioonid ja abi; Hotellide juhtimine teenusena; Hoitellijuhtimine; Hotellide ärialane juhtimine; Reklaam, sh hotellidega seotud reklaam; Hotellide sekretäriteenused; Hotellide ärialane juhtimine; Hotellide ärijuhtimisteenuse osutamine; Hotellide haldamise ja juhtimise konsultatsiooniteenused; Hotellindusega seotud püsikliendikaarditeenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Franchising-palvelut, nimittäin liikkeenjohtoa, yritysorganisaatiota ja liiketoimintaa koskevat konsultointi- ja avustuspalvelut hotelliyritysten ja -liiketoiminnan hoidon ja/tai johdon tukipalvelujen alalla; Hotellien hallintopalvelut [muille]; Hotellinjohto; Hotellien johtaminen; Mainontapalvelut, mukaan lukien hotelleihin liittyvät; Hotellien tarjoamat sihteeripalvelut; Hotellien johtaminen; Hotellien liikkeenjohto kolmansille osapuolille; Hotellien hallinnointiin ja johtamiseen liittyvät konsultointipalvelut; Kanta-asiakaskorttipalvelut hotellialalla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de franchises, à savoir conseils et assistance dans la direction, l'organisation et la promotion relatives à l'aide à l'exploitation et/ou à la direction d'entreprises et d'établissements hôteliers; Services de gestion hôtelière pour le compte de tiers; Gestion hôtelière; Gérance administrative d'hôtels; Services publicitaires, y compris ceux liés aux hôtels; Services de secrétariat fournis par des hôtels; Gérance administrative d'hôtels; Gestion commerciale d'hôtels pour le compte de tiers; Services de conseil en administration et gérance commerciale d'hôtels; Services de cartes de fidélité dans le secteur hôtelier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge franšiza, i to savjetovanje i pomoć u vođenju, organizaciji i promidžbi poslova u vezi s pomoći u radu i/ili vođenju tvrtki i hotelskih objekata; Usluga upravljanja hotelima [za druge]; Hotelske usluge; Poslovno upravljanje hotelima; Usluge oglašavanja, uključujući one u vezi s hotelima; Tajničke usluge koje pružaju hoteli; Poslovno upravljanje hotelima; Upravljanje hotelima za druge; Konzultantske usluge povezane s administracijom i upravljanjem hotelima; Usluge u vezi s karticama vjernosti u području hotelijerstva.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Franchise szolgáltatások, nevezetesen vállalatok vagy szállodai létesítmények működtetéséhez és/vagy irányításához nyújtott segítséggel kapcsolatos üzletek vezetéséhez, szervezéséhez és promóciójához nyújtott konzultáció és tanácsadás; Szállodavezetési szolgáltatások; Szállodamenedzsment; Szállodai üzletvezetés; Szállodákkal kapcsolatos reklámozási szolgáltatások; Szállodák által nyújtott titkársági szolgáltatások; Szállodai üzletvezetés; Szállodák üzletvezetése; Szállodák adminisztrálásával és üzletvezetésével kapcsolatos szaktanácsadói szolgáltatások; Hűségkártya-szolgáltatások a szállodai ágazatban.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di franchising, ovvero consulenza e assistenza nella direzione, nell'organizzazione e nella promozione di attività inerenti l'assistenza nella gestione e/o nella direzione d'imprese e attività alberghiere; Servizio di gestione di alberghi [per conto terzi]; Gestione di alberghi; Gestione amministrativa di alberghi per conto terzi; Servizi di pubblicità, inclusi quelli inerenti alberghi; Servizi di segreteria offerti da alberghi; Gestione amministrativa di alberghi per conto terzi; Gestione di alberghi per conto terzi; Servizi di consulenza inerenti l'amministrazione e la gestione di hotel; Servizi di carte fedeltà nel settore alberghiero.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Franšizių paslaugos, būtent konsultacijos ir pagalba verslo, susijusio su pagalba įmonių naudojimo ir / arba vadybos klausimais, vadybos, organizavimo ir reklamos srityje; Viešbučių valdymo paslauga [kitiems]; Viešbučių vadyba; Viešbučių verslo vadyba; Reklamos paslaugos, įskaitant paslaugas, susijusias su viešbučiais; Viešbučiuose teikiamos sekretoriaus paslaugos; Viešbučių verslo vadyba; Viešbučių verslo vadyba (kitiems); Su viešbučių administravimu ir valdymu susijusios konsultacinės paslaugos; Lojalumo kortelių paslaugos viešbučių srityje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Franšīzu pakalpojumi, proti, konsultācijas un ieteikumi uzņēmējdarbības vadībā, organizēšanā un veicināšanā saistībā ar atbalstu uzņēmumu un viesu izmitināšanas iestāžu darbībā un/vai vadībā; Viesnīcu vadības pakalpojumi [trešajām personām]; Viesnīcu vadīšana; Viesnīcu darījumu vadīšana; Reklāmas pakalpojumi, tostarp saistībā ar viesnīcām; Viesnīcu nodrošināti sekretāra pakalpojumi; Viesnīcu darījumu vadīšana; Viesnīcu vadīšana citu personu interesēs; Konsultācijas saistībā ar viesnīcu administrēšanu un pārvaldīšanu; Lojalitātes karšu pakalpojumi viesu izmitināšanas nozarē.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' frankiġja, jiġifieri, konsulenza u għajnuna fit-tmexxija, l-organizzazzjoni u l-promozzjoni ta' negozji marbuta mal-għajnuna fl-esplotazzjoni u/jew it-tmexxija ta' impriżi u stabbilimenti ta' lukandi; Servizzi ta' ġestjoni ta' lukanda [għal oħrajn]; Il-ġestjoni ta' lukandi; Il-ġestjoni tan-negozju ta' lukandi; Servizzi ta' reklamar, inkluż dawk marbuti ma' lukandi; Servizzi segretarjali pprovduti minn lukandi; Il-ġestjoni tan-negozju ta' lukandi; Ġestjoni ta' lukandi għal oħrajn; Servizzi ta' konsulenza relatata mal-amministrazzjoni u l-ġestjoni ta' lukandi; Servizzi ta' kards ta' lealtà fis-settur tal-lukandi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Franchising, te weten consultancy en hulp bij de leiding, organisatie en promotie van zaken met betrekking tot hulp bij de exploitatie en/of leiding van een ondernemingen en hotels; Beheer van hotels [voor derden]; Hotelbeheer; Professionele hotelleiding; Reclame, waaronder met betrekking tot hotels; Secretariaatsdiensten geleverd door hotels; Professionele hotelleiding; Beheer van commerciële zaken van hotels in opdracht van derden; Advisering met betrekking tot de administratie en het commercieel beheer van hotels; Diensten op het gebied van klantenkaarten in het hotelwezen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi w zakresie franczyzy, mianowicie konsultacje i wsparcie w prowadzeniu, organizacji i promocji przedsiębiorstw, związane z pomocą w eksploatacji i/lub prowadzeniu przedsiębiorstw i obiektów hotelowych; Usługi zarządzania hotelami [dla osób trzecich]; Zarządzanie hotelami; Zarządzanie hotelami; Usługi reklamowe, w tym dotyczące hoteli; Usługi sekretarskie świadczone przez hotele; Zarządzanie hotelami; Zarządzanie działalnością hoteli, dla osób trzecich; Usługi doradztwa związane z administrowaniem i zarządzaniem hotelami; Usługi kart lojalnościowych w branży hotelarskiej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de franchising, especificamente consultadoria e assistência na direção, organização e promoção de negócios, no âmbito do apoio à exploração e/ou gestão de empresas e estabelecimentos hoteleiros; Serviços de gestão hoteleira para terceiros; Gestão hoteleira; Gerência administrativa de hotéis; Serviços publicitários, incluindo os relacionados com hotéis; Serviços de secretariado fornecidos por hotéis; Gerência administrativa de hotéis; Gestão hoteleira [para terceiros]; Serviços de consultoria relacionados com administração e gestão hoteleira; Serviços de cartões de fidelização no setor hoteleiro.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de francize, şi anume, consultanţă şi asistenţă în conducerea, organizarea şi promovarea de afaceri referitoare la asistenţa în exploatarea şi/sau conducerea de societăţi şi unităţi hoteliere; Servicii de management hotelier [pentru terţi]; Management hotelier; Administrarea hotelurilor; Servicii de publicitate, inclusiv cele asociate cu hoteluri; Servicii de secretariat furnizate de hoteluri; Administrarea hotelurilor; Management hotelier pentru terţi; Servicii de consultanţă privind administrarea hotelurilor şi managementul hotelier; Servicii de carduri de fidelizare în domeniul hotelier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Služby súvisiace s udeľovaním licencií, menovite poradenské služby a pomoc pri riadení, organizovaní a propagovaní obchodnej činnosti v oblasti spojenej s pomocou pri prevádzke a/alebo riadení obchodnej alebo priemyselnej spoločnosti; Služby hotelového manažmentu pre tretie osoby; Hotelový manažment; Administratívna správa hotelov; Reklamné služby vrátane služieb spojených s hotelierstvom; Sekretárske služby poskytované hotelmi; Administratívna správa hotelov; Hotelový manažment pre tretie osoby; Konzultačné služby v oblasti riadenia a správy hotelov; Služby v oblasti vernostných kariet na využívanie hotelových služieb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve franšiz, in sicer svetovanje in pomoč pri vodenju, organizaciji in promociji poslov v zvezi s pomočjo pri upravljanju in/ali vodenju komercialnega in hotelskih obratov; Storitve upravljanja hotelov [za druge]; Upravljanje hotelov; Poslovno upravljanje hotelov; Oglasna dejavnost, vključno v zvezi s hoteli; Tajniške storitve hotelov; Poslovno upravljanje hotelov; Upravljanje hotelov za druge; Svetovalne storitve v zvezi z administracijo in upravljanjem hotelov; Storitve v zvezi s karticami zvestobe v hotelski panogi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Franchisingtjänster, nämligen konsulttjänster och assistans i företagsledning, -organisation och säljfrämjande verksamhet avseende hjälptjänster vid drift och/eller ledning av hotellföretag och -inrättningar; Managementtjänster avseende hotell [för andra]; Ledning av hotell; Företagsledning av hotell; Reklamtjänster inklusive sådana avseende hotell; Sekreterartjänster som tillhandahålls av hotell; Företagsledning av hotell; Management av hotell för andra; Rådgivningstjänster avseende administration och förvaltning av hotell; Lojalitetskort inom hotellbranschen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>43</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ресторантьорство; Временно настаняване; Услуги на хотели и мотели; Услуги за резервации за хотелско настаняване и други места за временно настаняване; Наемане и хотелски резервации и пансиони; Бюра за настаняване в хотели; Настанявания по хотели, мотели и туристически комплекси; Наемане на инсталации за събиране, конференции, изложения, спектакли, специализирани заседания, семинари, симпозиум и преподаване; Услуги за приготвяне на храна и напитки; Услуги, свързани с ресторанти, барове и кетъринг; Отдаване под наем на палатки; Отдаване под наем на преносими постройки; Отдаване под наем на столове, маси, покривки за маса и стъклени съдове.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby zajišťující stravování a nápoje; Dočasné ubytování; Hotelové služby; Rezervování hotelových pokojů a jiného dočasného ubytování; Pronájem a rezervace hotelů a penzionů; Ubytovací agentury pro hotely; Ubytování v hotelech, motelech a turistických komplexech; Pronájem zařízení pro schůze, konference, výstavy, představení, konvence, semináře, sympozia a školení; Služby přípravy jídel a nápojů; Služby v oblasti restaurací, barů a cateringu; Pronájem stanů; Pronájem přenosných staveb; Pronájem židlí, stolů, ubrusů, skleněného nádobí.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tilvejebringelse af mad og drikke; Midlertidig indkvartering; Tjenester ydet af hoteller; Reservation af hotelværelser og anden midlertidig indkvartering; Udlejning og reservation af hoteller og pensionater; Hotelindlogeringsbureau; Indkvartering på hoteller, moteller og turistkomplekser; Udlejning af faciliteter til møder, konferencer, udstillinger, shows, kongresser, seminarer, symposier og workshopper; Tilberedning af mad og drikke; Restaurations-, bar- og cateringvirksomhed; Udlejning af telte; Udlejning af transportable bygninger; Udlejning af stole, borde, duge, glasvarer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Dienstleistungen zur Verpflegung; Beherbergung von Gästen; Dienstleistungen von Hotels; Reservierung von Hotelzimmern und anderen zeitweiligen Unterkünften; Vermietung und Reservierung von Zimmern in Hotels und Pensionen; Zimmervermittlung für Hotels; Beherbergung von Gästen in Hotels, Motels und Ferienanlagen; Vermietung von Einrichtungen für Zusammenkünfte, Konferenzen, Ausstellungen, Veranstaltungen, Kongresse, Seminare, Symposien und Workshops; Dienstleistungen für die Zubereitung von Speisen und Getränken; Restaurant-, Bar- und Cateringbetrieb; Vermietung von Zelten; Vermietung von transportablen Bauten; Vermietung von Stühlen, Tischen, Tischwäsche, Gläsern.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες παροχής διατροφής και ποτών· Υπηρεσίες προσωρινής κατάλυσης· Ξενοδοχειακές υπηρεσίες· Υπηρεσίες κρατήσεων για δωμάτια ξενοδοχείων και άλλα προσωρινά καταλύματα· Ενοικίαση και κρατήσεις δωματίων σε ξενοδοχεία και σε χώρους προσωρινής διαμονής· Γραφεία ξενοδοχειακών κρατήσεων· Υπηρεσίες παροχής καταλύματος σε ξενοδοχεία, μοτέλ και τουριστικά συγκροτήματα· Εκμίσθωση εγκαταστάσεων για συνεδριάσεις, διαλέξεις, εκθέσεις, θεάματα, διασκέψεις, σεμινάρια, συμπόσια και εργαστήρια κατάρτισης· Υπηρεσίες παρασκευής τροφίμων και ποτών· Υπηρεσίες εστιατορίου, μπαρ και τροφοδοσίας· Μίσθωση σκηνών· Μίσθωση κατασκευών λυόμενων· Μίσθωση καρεκλων, τραπεζιών,τραπεζομάντηλων και γυαλικών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Services for providing food and drink; Temporary accommodation; Hotel services; Booking of hotel rooms and other temporary accommodation; Rental and booking of hotels and guesthouses; Accommodation bureaux for hotels; Accommodation in hotels, motels and tourist resorts; Rental of facilities for meetings, conferences, exhibitions, shows, conventions, seminars, symposiums and training workshops; Services for preparing food and drink; Restaurant, bar and catering services; Rental of tents; Rental of portable buildings; Rental of chairs, tables, table linen, glassware.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">servicios de restauración (alimentación); hospedaje temporal; servicios hoteleros; servicios de reserva de habitaciones de hotel y otros alojamientos temporales; alquiler y reservas de hoteles y casas de huéspedes; agencias de alojamiento en hoteles; servicios de alojamiento en hoteles, moteles y complejos turísticos; alquiler de instalaciones para reuniones, conferencias, exposiciones, espectáculos, convenciones, seminarios, simposios y talleres; servicios de preparación de comida y bebida; servicios de restaurante, bar y catering; alquiler de carpas; alquiler de construcciones transportables; alquiler de sillas, mesas, mantelerías y cristalerías.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Toitlustusteenused; Tähtajaline majutus; Hotelliteenused; Hotellitubade ja muu tähtajalise majutuse reserveerimine; Hotellikohtade ja külalismajade üürimine ja reserveerimine; Majutusbürooteenused hotellidele; Hotelli-, motelli- ja turismikuurortide majutusteenused; Koosoleku-, konverentsi-, näituse-, etenduse-, istungi-, seminari-, sümpoosioni- ja kursuseruumide üürimine; Toidu- ja joogivalmistamisteenused; Restorani-, baari- ja toitlustusteenused; Telkide üürimine, rentimine, laenutus; Teisaldatavate ehitiste üürimine, rentimine, laenutus; Toolide, laudade, laudlinade, klaasnõude üürimine, rentimine, laenutus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ravitseminen ja juomien anniskelu; Tilapäismajoitus; Hotellit; Hotellihuoneiden ja muun tilapäismajoituksen varauspalvelut; Hotellien ja täysihoitoloiden vuokraus ja varaukset; Hotellien majoitustoimistot; Hotellien, motellien ja lomakeskusten majoituspalvelut; Tilojen vuokraus kokouksia, konferensseja, näyttelyjä, näytöksiä, kokoontumisia, seminaareja, symposiumeja ja työpajoja varten; Ruokien ja juomien valmistuspalvelut; Ravintola-, baari- ja pitopalvelut; Telttojen vuokraus; Siirrettävien rakennusten vuokraus; Tuolien, pöytien, pöytäliinojen ja lasitavaroiden vuokraus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de restauration (alimentation); Hébergement temporaire; Services hôteliers; Services de réservation de chambres d'hôtel et d'autres logements temporaires; Location et réservations d'hôtels et pensions; Agences de logement pour hôtels; Services d'hébergement dans des hôtels, motels et centres de villégiature; Location d'installations pour réunions, conférences, expositions, spectacles, conventions, séminaires, symposiums et ateliers; Services de préparation d'aliments et boissons; Services de restaurant, bar et de traiteur; Location de tentes; Location de constructions transportables; Location de chaises, tables, linge de table et verrerie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge pružanja hrane i pića [okrepa]; Pružanje privremenog smještaja; Hotelske usluge; Usluge rezerviranja hotelskih soba i drugog privremenog smještaja; Iznajmljivanje i rezervacija hotela i pansiona; Agencije za smještaj u hotelima; Usluge smještaja u hotele, motele i odmarališta; Iznajmljivanje opreme za sastanke, konferencije, izložbe, priredbe, skupove, seminare, simpozije i radionice; Usluge pripreme hrane i pića; Ugostiteljske usluge restorana, barova te pripreme i dostave hrane i pića; Iznajmljivanje šatora; Iznajmljivanje prenosivih građevinskih objekata; Iznajmljivanje stolaca, stolova, stolnog rublja i staklenog posuđa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vendéglátás (élelmezés); Időleges szállásadás; Szállodai szolgáltatások; Szobafoglalási szolgáltatások hotelekben és egyéb ideiglenes szálláshelyeken; Szállodák és vendégházak bérbeadása és helyfoglalás szállodákba és vendégházakba; Szállásadó irodák hotelekhez; Szálláshelyek nyújtása szállodákban, motelekben és idegenforgalmi létesítményekben; Gyűlésekhez, konferenciákhoz, kiállításokhoz, előadásokhoz, szakmai ülésekhez, szemináriumokhoz, szimpóziumokhoz és műhelymunkákhoz való készülékek bérbeadása; Étel- és italkészítési szolgáltatások; Étteremben, bárban nyújtott és étkeztetéssel kapcsolatos szolgáltatások; Sátrak kölcsönzése; Hordozható épületek, építmények bérbeadása; Székek, asztalok, asztalterítők, üvegáruk kölcsönzése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di ristorazione (alimentazione); Alloggi temporanei; Servizi alberghieri; Servizi di prenotazioni alberghiere e altri alloggi temporanei; Noleggio e prenotazioni di alberghi e pensioni; Agenzie per alloggio in alberghi; Servizi di alloggio in alberghi, motel e complessi turistici; Noleggio di impianti per riunioni, conferenze, esposizioni, spettacoli, convegni, seminari, simposi e laboratori di formazione; Preparazione d'alimenti e bevande; Ristoranti, bar e servizi di catering; Noleggio di tende; Noleggio di costruzioni trasportabili; Noleggio di sedie, tavoli, biancheria da tavolo, bicchieri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Maisto ir gėrimų parūpinimo paslaugos; Laikinas apgyvendinimas; Viešbučių paslaugos; Viešbučių ir kitų laikino apgyvendinimo vietų rezervavimo paslaugos; Viešbučių ir pensionų nuoma bei rezervavimas; Laikino apgyvendinimo viešbučiuose biurai; Apgyvendinimo viešbučiuose, moteliuose ir turistiniuose kompleksuose paslaugos; Susirinkimų, konferencijų, parodų, spektaklių, mokslinių konferencijų, seminarų, simpoziumų ir lavinimo seminarų salių nuoma; Maisto ir gėrimų ruošimo paslaugos; Restoranų, barų ir aprūpinimo maistu ir gėrimais paslaugos; Palapinių nuoma; Kilnojamųjų statinių nuoma; Kėdžių, stalų, staltiesių, stiklo dirbinių nuoma.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apgāde ar uzturu; Viesu izmitināšana; Viesnīcu pakalpojumi; Viesnīcu un citu īslaicīgas apmešanās vietu istabu rezervēšana; Viesnīcu un pansiju noma un rezervēšana; Mājvietu biroji viesnīcām; Izmitināšanas pakalpojumi viesnīcās, moteļos un kūrortos; Iekārtu noma sanāksmēm, konferencēm, izstādēm, izrādēm, konvencijām, semināriem, simpozijiem un apmācību darbsemināriem; Pārtikas un dzērienu pagatavošanas pakalpojumi; Restorānu, bāru un piegādes pakalpojumi; Telšu iznomāšana; Pārvietojamu ēku iznomāšana; Krēslu, galdu, galda drānu, stikla trauku iznomāšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi għall-provvista ta' ikel u xorb; Akkomodazzjoni temporanja; Servizzi ta' lukanda; Servizzi ta' bbukkjar ta' akkomodazzjoni f'lukanda u akkomodazzjonijiet oħra temporanji; Kiri u prenotazzjoni ta' lukandi u pensjonijiet; Uffiċċji ta' l-akkomodazzjoni għal-lukandi; Servizzi ta' akkomodazzjoni f'lukandi, motels u kumplessi turistiċi; Kiri ta' installazzjonijiet għal tlaqqigħ mill-ġdid, konferenzi, esibizzjonijiet, wirjiet, simpożji, seminars, simpożji u werkxops; Servizzi għat-tħejjija tal-ikel u tax-xorb; Servizzi ta' restorant, bar u l-forniment ta' ikel; Kiri ta' tined; Kiri ta' bini li jista' jittieħed minn post għal ieħor; Kiri ta' siġġijiet, imwejjed, tvalji tal-imwejjed u oġġetti tal-ħġieġ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Restauratie (het verstrekken van voedsel en dranken); Tijdelijke huisvesting; Hoteldiensten; Het boeken van hotelkamers en andere tijdelijke huisvesting; Het verhuren en boeken van hotel- en pensionkamers; Bureaus voor het verstrekken van logies in hotels; Huisvesting in hotels, motels en toeristenoorden; Verhuur van faciliteiten voor vergaderingen, conferenties, tentoonstellingen, schouwspelen, congressen, seminars, symposia en workshops; Bereiding van voedsel en dranken; Diensten van een restaurant, bar en cateringbedrijf; Verhuur van tenten; Verhuur van verplaatsbare constructies; Verhuur van stoelen, tafels, tafellinnen en glaswerk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi zaopatrzenia w żywność i napoje; Tymczasowe zakwaterowanie; Usługi hotelowe; Usługi rezerwacji pokoi hotelowych oraz innego rodzaju zakwaterowania tymczasowego; Wynajem i rezerwacje hoteli i pensjonatów; Hotelowe biura zakwaterowań; Usługi w zakresie zakwaterowania w hotelach, motelach i kompleksach turystycznych; Wynajem instalacji wykorzystywanych podczas spotkań, konferencji, wystaw, spektakli, zjazdów, seminariów, sympozjów i warsztatów szkoleniowych; Usługi przygotowywania żywności i napojów; Usługi restauracji, barów i usługi cateringowe; Wypożyczanie namiotów; Wynajem budynków przenośnych; Wypożyczanie krzeseł, stołów, bielizny stołowej i szklanych naczyń.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de restauração (alimentação); Alojamento temporário; Serviços de hotéis; Serviços de reserva de quartos de hotel e outros alojamentos temporários; Aluguer e reserva de hotéis e casas de hóspedes; Agências de alojamento em hotéis; Serviços de alojamento em hotéis, motéis e complexos turísticos; Aluguer de instalações para reuniões, conferências, exposições, espetáculos, convenções, seminários, simpósios e workshops; Serviços de preparação de alimentos e bebidas; Serviços de restaurante, bar e catering; Aluguer de tendas; Aluguer de construções transportáveis; Aluguer de cadeiras, mesas, toalhas de mesa, copos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de alimentaţie publică; Servicii de cazare temporară; Servicii hoteliere; Servicii de rezervare de camere de hotel şi alte servicii de cazare temporare; Închiriere şi rezervări de hoteluri şi pensiuni; Birou de cazare hoteliera; Servicii de cazare în hoteluri, moteluri şi complexe turistice; Închiriere de instalaţii pentru reuniuni, conferinţe, expoziţii, spectacole, convenţii, seminarii, simpozioane şi ateliere de lucru; Servicii pentru pregătirea mâncării şi a băuturilor; Servicii de restaurant, bar şi catering; Închiriere de corturi; Închiriere de construcţii transportabile; Închiriere de scaune, mese, veselă şi lenjerie de masă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reštauračné služby (strava); Prechodné ubytovanie; Hotelierske služby; Služby v oblasti rezervovania hotelového ubytovania a iného prechodného ubytovania; Prenájom a rezervácia hotelov a penziónov; Ubytovacie kancelárie pre hotely; Služby hotelového ubytovania, služby motelov a letovísk; Prenájom priestorov na stretnutia, konferencie, výstavy, predstavenia, kongresy, semináre, sympóziá a tvorivé dielne; Služby v oblasti prípravy jedla a nápojov; Služby reštaurácií , barov a cateringové služby; Požičiavanie turistických stanov; Prenájom prenosných stavieb; Požičiavanie stoličiek, stolov, obrusov a nápojového skla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Nudenje hrane in pijače; Nudenje začasne nastanitve; Hotelirske storitve; Storitve v zvezi z rezervacijo hotelskih sob in druge začasne nastanitve; Dajanje v najem in rezervacija hotelov in prenočišč; Nastanitvene pisarne za hotele; Storitve v zvezi z nastanitvijo v hotelih, motelih in turističnih kompleksih; Najem instalacij za srečanja, konference, razstave, predstave, zborovanja, seminarje, simpozije in delavnice; Storitve priprave hrane in pijače; Storitve restavracij, barov ter oskrbe s hrano in pijačo; Najem šotorov; Najem prenosnih zgradb; Najem stolov, miz, namiznih prtov, steklenih posod.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Utskänkning av mat och dryck; Kortvarigt boende; Hotell; Bokning av hotellrum och annan tillfällig inkvartering; Uthyrning och bokning av hotell och pensionatrörelser; Rumsförmedling för hotell; Tjänster avseende inkvartering på hotell, motell och turistkomplex; Uthyrning av anläggningar för möten, konferenser, utställningar, shower, konvent, seminarier, symposier och arbetsgrupper; Tjänster för tillagning av mat och dryck; Restaurang-, bar- och cateringtjänster; Uthyrning av tält; Uthyrning av flyttbara byggnader; Uthyrning av stolar, bord, bordslinne och glasvaror.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/111</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-15</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/183</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-24</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>226928</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>1014</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
