<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-30T08:54:01</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229007</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229007</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-07-03</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-10-28</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-07-03</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-30</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Lumuasky</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Халки за салфетки от благородни метали; Четки за баня; Поставки за чаши; Гъби за стъргане; Дюзи за пръскане за градински маркучи; Пръскачки, прикрепени към градински маркучи; Форми за сладки; Цилиндрични чаши с дръжка; Порцеланови орнаменти; Поставки за салфетки, не от благороден метал; Произведения на изкуството, изработени от стъкло; Подложки за маса от пластични материали; Халки за салфетки, не от благороден метал; Стъклени чаши със столчета.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kroužky na ubrousky z drahých kovů; Kartáče do koupele; Držáky na šálky; Houby na čištění; Rozstřikovací trysky na zahradní hadice; Rozstřikovače připevněné k zahradním hadicím; Formy na cukrovinky; Hrnky; Dekorační předměty z porcelánu; Kroužky na ubrousky; Umělecká díla vyrobená ze skla; Jídelní podložky z plastových materiálů; Kroužky na ubrousky, jiné než z drahých kovů; Sklenice na pití.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Servietringe af ædle metaller; Badebørster; Kopholdere; Skrubbesvampe; Spraydyser til haveslanger; Sprayanordninger monteret på haveslanger; Forme til konditorbrug; Krus; Nipsting af porcelæn; Servietringe; Pyntegenstande af glas; Dækkeservietter af plastik; Servietringe, ikke af ædelmetal; Glas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Serviettenringe aus Edelmetall; Badebürsten; Becherhalter; Scheuerschwämme; Spritzen für Gartenschläuche; Sprüher zur Befestigung an Gartenschläuchen; Konditorformen; Becher; Chinoiserie aus Porzellan; Serviettenringe; Ornamentglas; Kunststoffplatzdeckchen; Serviettenringe, nicht aus Edelmetall; Stielgläser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δακτύλιοι για πετσέτες από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Βούρτσες μπάνιου· Υποδοχές για κύπελλα· Σφουγγάρια για τρίψιμο· Ψεκαστήρες εύκαμπτων σωλήνων κήπου· Ψεκαστήρες προσαρμοσμένοι σε εύκαμπτους σωλήνες κήπου· Φόρμες για ζαχαρώδη· Κούπες· Κινέζικες πορσελάνες (είδη πορσελάνης)· Υποδοχές για πετσέτες φαγητού· Είδη τέχνης φτιαγμένα από γυαλί· Επιτραπέζιες προστατευτικές βάσεις φαγητού από πλαστικό υλικό· Κρίκοι για χάρτινες ή υφασμάτινες πετσέτες σερβίτσιου, όχι από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Κολονάτα ποτήρια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Napkin rings of precious metal; Bath brushes; cup holders; Cleaning sponges; Garden hose sprayers; Sprayers attached to garden hoses; Pastry molds; Mugs; china ornaments; Serviette rings; Crystal ornaments; Plastic place mats; Napkin rings not of precious metals; Stemware.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servilleteros de aro de metales preciosos; Cepillos para el baño; Porta tazas; Estropajos [esponjas]; Rociadores para mangueras de jardín; Pulverizadores acoplados a mangueras de jardín; Moldes de confitería; Jarras para beber; Adornos de porcelana; Servilleteros de aro; Objetos de arte de cristalería; Manteles individuales de materias plásticas; Servilleteros de aro que no sean de metales preciosos; Servicios de copas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Väärismetallist salvrätirõngad; Vanniharjad; Tassihoidjad; Küürimiskäsnad; Aiavoolikute pihustusotsikud; Aiavoolikute külge kinnitatavad pihustid; Kondiitrivormid; Kruusid; Portselanornamendid; Salvrätirõngad; Klaasist kunstiesemed; Plastist taldrikualused; Salvrätirõngad [välja arvatud väärismetallist]; Jalaga joogiklaasid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Jalometalliset lautasliinarenkaat; Kylpyharjat; Kupin pidikkeet; Hankaussienet; Puutarhaletkujen sumuttimet; Puutarhaletkuihin kiinnitetyt ruiskuttimet; Leivonnaisvuoat; Mukit; Posliinikoristeet; Lautasliinarenkaat; Lasista valmistetut taide-esineet; Muoviset ruokailutabletit; Lautasliinarenkaat [muut kuin jalometalliset]; Jalalliset lasit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Ronds de serviette en métaux précieux; Brosses de bain; Porte-gobelets; Éponges à récurer; Gicleurs de tuyaux d'arrosage; Pulvérisateurs à fixer sur des tuyaux d'arrosage; Moules à pâtisserie; Mugs; Ornements en porcelaine; Ronds de serviettes; Objets d'art en verre; Sets de table en matières plastiques; Ronds de serviettes non en métaux précieux; Verres à pied.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Prsteni za ubruse od plemenitog metala; Četke za kupanje; Držači za čaše; Spužve za posuđe; Prskalice za vrtne cijevi za polijevanje; Raspršivači pričvršćeni na vrtne cijevi; Slastičarski kalupi; Šalice; Ukrasi izrađeni od porculana; Držači ubrusa; Umjetnine od stakla; Plastični podmetači; Prsteni za salvete od neplemenitih metala; Čaše s drškom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szalvétagyűrűk nemesfémből; Fürdőkefék; Csészetartók; Súrolószivacsok; Permetezőfejek kerti locsolókhoz; Kerti locsolókhoz csatlakoztatott locsolófejek; Cukrász sablonok, formák; Bögrék, korsók; Porcelándíszek; Szalvétatartók; Üvegből készült művészeti alkotások; Tányéralátétek műanyagból; Szalvétagyűrűk, nem nemesfémből; Talpas poháráru.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Anelli portatovagliolo in metallo prezioso; Spazzole da bagno; Portatazze; Spugne abrasive; Vaporizzatori per tubi flessibili da giardino; Spruzzatori collegati a tubi flessibili da giardino; Stampi per confetteria; Calici; Ornamenti in porcellana; Anelli per tovaglioli; Oggetti d'arte in vetro; Tovagliette individuali in plastica; Anelli per tovaglioli, non in metallo prezioso; Calici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Servetėlių žiedai iš brangiųjų metalų; Vonios šepečiai; Puodelių laikikliai; Šveitimo kempinės; Purškiamieji sodo žarnų antgaliai; Užmaunami sodo žarnų purkštuvai; Konditerinės formos; Bokalai; Porcelianiniai kiniški dailės mažmožiai; Servetėlių žiedai; Meno kūriniai iš stiklo; Plastikiniai valgomojo stalų patiesalai; Servetėlių žiedai, ne brangiųjų metalų; Taurelės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Salvešu gredzeni no cēlmetāliem; Vannas birstes; Krūžu turētāji; Beršanas sūkļi; Dārza šļūteņu smidzinātāji; Smidzinātāji, kas piestiprināti dārza šļūtenēm; Konditorejas izstrādājumu veidnes; Krūzes; Porcelāna dekori; Galda salvešu gredzeni; Mākslas darbi no stikla; Plastmasas galda sedziņas; Salvešu gredzeni, kas nav no dārgmetāla; Dzērienu glāzes uz kājiņas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ħoloq tas-srievet tal-metall prezzjuż; Xkupilji għall-banju; Kontenituri tal-kikkri; Sponoż għall-għorik; Bexxiexa tal-manek, tal-ġnien; Sprejers imqabbda mal-manek tal-ġnien; Forom tad-dulċiera; Maggijiet; Ornamenti magħmula mill-kina; Tagħmir li jżomm is-srievet; Xogħlijiet tal-arti magħmula mill-ħġieġ; Sottoplatti tal-mejda ta' materjal tal-plastik; Ċrieki tas-srievet, mhux tal-metall prezzjuż; Tazzi bis-sieq.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Servetringen van edelmetaal; Badborstels; Houders voor kopjes; Schuursponzen; Spuitstukken voor tuinslangen; Sproeiers bevestigd aan tuinslangen; Vormen voor suikerbakkerswaren; Drinkbekers; Chinese kunstvoorwerpen [porselein]; Servetringen; Kunstvoorwerpen van glas; Placemats van plastic materiaal; Servetringen, niet van edele metalen; Glasservies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pierścienie na serwetki z metali szlachetnych; Szczotki kąpielowe; Uchwyty na kubki; Gąbki do szorowania; Dysze zraszające do węży ogrodowych; Rozpylacze mocowane do węży ogrodowych; Formy cukiernicze; Kubki; Ozdoby z porcelany; Serwetniki; Wyroby artystyczne ze szkła; Maty obiadowe z tworzyw sztucznych; Obrączki na serwetki, nie z metali szlachetnych; Kieliszki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Argolas de guardanapos em metais preciosos; Escovas para o banho; Suportes para taças; Esponjas de esfregar; Pulverizadores para mangueiras de jardim; Pulverizadores de mangueiras de jardim; Formas de confeitaria; Canecas; Porcelanas chinesas; Argolas para guardanapos; Obras de arte em vidro; Bases para pratos em matérias plásticas; Argolas de guardanapo, não em metais preciosos; Serviços de copos de pé.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Inele din metale prețioase pentru șervețele; Perii de baie; Suporturi pentru căni; Bureți pentru frecare; Pulverizatoare pentru furtunuri de grădină; Pulverizatoare atașate la furtunurile de grădină; Forme pentru cofetărie; Căni; Bibelouri de porțelan; Inele pentru șervețele; Obiecte de artă din sticlă; Șervete din plastic pentru tacâmuri; Inele pentru șervețele, nu din metale prețioase; Pahare cu picior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Krúžky na obrúsky z drahých kovov; Kefy do kúpeľa; Držiaky na šálky; Hubky na riad; Rozprašovače pre záhradné hadice; Rozstrekovače pripevnené na záhradné hadice; Formy na cukrovinky; Hrnčeky; Čínsky porcelán; Krúžky na obrúsky; Umelecké diela vyrobené zo skla; Plastové podložky na stolovanie; Krúžky na obrúsky, s výnimkou krúžkov z drahých kovov; Poháre.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Obročki za prtičke iz žlahtnih kovin; Kopalna krtača; Držala za lončke; Gobe za razmaščevanje; Pršilne šobe za gibke vrtne cevi; Pršilni nastavki za vrtne gibke cevi; Slaščičarski modeli; Vrčki; Okraski iz porcelana; Držala za prtičke; Umetniška dela iz stekla; Plastične namizne podloge; Obročki za prtičke, ne iz žlahtnih kovin; Kozarci na peclju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Servettringar av ädelmetall; Badborstar; Kopphållare; Skursvampar; Spraymunstycken till trädgårdsslangar; Spridare för applicering på trädgårdsslangar; Formar för konfekttillverkning; Muggar; Porslinsprydnader; Servettringar; Konstföremål av glas; Bordstabletter av plastmaterial; Servettringar, inte av ädelmetall; Glas med hög fot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/135</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-20</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/208</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-30</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081919</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15066</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
