<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-10T08:16:15</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229266</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229266</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-08</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-10</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Zoeley</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Пръчици за селфи, използвани като аксесоари за смартфони; Фотографско осветително оборудване за тъмни стаи; Безжични предаватели; Поставки, пригодени за мобилни телефони; Поставки за таблети, пригодени за употреба в автомобили; Безжични слушалки; Слушалки; Стойки за фотографска апаратура; Шублери; Устройства за четене на карти; Електронни везни за кухненска употреба; USB памет; Компютърни мишки; Безжични клавиатури.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Teleskopické držáky na selfie používané jako příslušenství k chytrým telefonům; Osvětlení fotografických temných komor; Bezdrátové vysílače; Stojany přizpůsobené pro mobilní telefony; Držáky tabletů uzpůsobené pro použití v autech; Bezdrátová sluchátka; Sluchátka; Stativy pro fotografické přístroje; Posuvná měřítka; Čtečky karet; Elektronické váhy k použití v kuchyni; USB flash disky; Počítačové myši; Bezdrátové klávesnice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Selfiepinde til anvendelse som tilbehør til smartphones; Belysning til fotografiske mørkekamre; Trådløse transmittere; Holdere til mobiltelefoner; Tabletholdere tilpasset til brug i biler; Trådløse hovedtelefoner; Høretelefoner; Trebenede stativer til kameraer; Skydelære; Kortlæserudstyr; Elektroniske vægte til køkkenbrug; USB flash drivere; Computermus; Trådløse tastaturer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Selfie-Stangen zur Verwendung als Zubehör für Smartphones; Beleuchtung für Dunkelkammern; Drahtlose Sender; Angepasste Halter für Mobiltelefone; Halterungen für Tablet-Computer zur Verwendung in Fahrzeugen; Kabellose Kopfhörer; Kopfhörer; Stative für Kameras; Schieblehren; Kartenlesegeräte; Elektronische Waagen für die Küche; USB-Sticks; Computermaus; Drahtlose Tastaturen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Πτυσσόμενα μπαστούνια κάμερας ως αξεσουάρ για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Φωτισμός φωτογραφικού σκοτεινού θαλάμου· Ασύρματοι πομποί· Βάσεις για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Θήκες για ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές-ταμπλέτες προσαρμοσμένες για χρήση σε αυτοκίνητα· Ασύρματα ακουστικά· Ακουστικά· Τρίποδα φωτογραφικών μηχανών· Κυρτοσκελής διαβήτης· Εξοπλισμός ανάγνωσης καρτών· Ηλεκτρονικοί ζυγοί μαγειρικής χρήσης· Οδηγοί USB (καθολικού σειριακού αγωγού)· Ποντίκια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Ασύρματα πληκτρολόγια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Selfie sticks; Photographic darkroom lighting; Wireless transmitters; Stands adapted for mobile phones; Tablet holders adapted for use in cars; Wireless headphones; Earphones; Camera tripods; Slide calipers; Card readers; Electronic weighing scales for kitchen use; USB flash drives; Computer mouses; Wireless keyboards.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Palos para selfies utilizados como accesorios de teléfonos inteligentes; Iluminación de cuartos oscuros fotográficos; Transmisores inalámbricos; Soportes adaptados para teléfonos móviles; Soportes para tabletas adaptados para su uso en automóviles; Cascos inalámbricos; Auriculares intraurales; Trípodes para cámaras fotográficas; Compases de corredera; Equipos lectores de tarjetas; Balanzas electrónicas de cocina; Memorias USB; Ratones de ordenador; Teclados inalámbricos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Selfipulgad nutitelefoni lisaseadmetena; Pimiku valgustusseadmed; Juhtmeta saatjad; Mobiiltelefonide kohandatud alused; Autos kasutamiseks kohandatud tahvelarvutihoidikud; Juhtmeta kõrvaklapid; Kõrvaklapid; Kaamerate kolmjalad, statiivid; Nihikud, nihkmõõturid; Kaardilugejad; Elektroonilised köögikaalud; USB-mälupulgad; Arvutihiired; Juhtmeta klaviatuurid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Selfietikut älypuhelinten lisälaitteina käytettäväksi; Valokuvien kehitykseen tarkoitettujen pimiöiden valaisimet; Langattomat lähettimet; Matkapuhelimille tarkoitetut telineet; Autoissa käytettäviksi mukautetut taulutietokonetelineet; Langattomat kuulokkeet; Kuulokkeet; Kolmijalat kameroille; Mittaharpit; Kortinlukijat; Elektroniset keittiövaa'at; USB-muistit; Tietokonehiiret; Langattomat näppäimistöt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bâtonnets selfie utilisés comme accessoires de smartphone; Appareils d'éclairage pour chambre noire [photographie]; Émetteurs sans fil; Supports adaptés pour téléphones portables; Supports pour tablettes conçus pour être utilisés dans des voitures; Ecouteurs sans fil; Casques d'écoute; Trépieds pour appareils photo; Pieds à coulisse; Lecteurs de cartes; Balances électroniques de cuisine; Clés USB; Souris d'ordinateur; Claviers sans fil.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Šipke za snimanje autoportreta (selfie) kao dodatna oprema za pametne telefone; Osvjetljenje za tamne komore; Bežični odašiljači; Stalak za mobilne telefone; Držači za tablet računala adaptirani za automobile; Bežične slušalice; Slušalice; Tronožni stalci za fotografske aparate; Pomična mjerila; Oprema za čitanje kartica; Kuhinjske elektroničke vage; USB uređaji [USB stickovi]; Računalni miševi; Bežične tipkovnice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Okostelefonhoz használt szelfi botok; Fényképészeti sötétszobai világítások; Vezeték nélküli adókészülékek; Mobiltelefonokhoz kialakított állványok; Táblagéptartók gépkocsikban történő használatra; Vezeték nélküli fejhallgatók; Fejhallgatók; Háromlábú állványok fényképezőgépekhez; Tolómérők, tolómércék; Kártyaolvasó készülékek, berendezések; Elektronikus mérlegek konyhai használatra; USB pendrive-ok; Számítógépes egerek; Vezeték nélküli billentyűzet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Bastoni per gli autoscatti usati come accessori per smartphone; Illuminazione per camere oscure fotografiche; Trasmettitori senza fili; Supporti per telefoni cellulari; Supporti da tablet adattati per essere usati in automobili; Cuffie senza fili; Auricolari; Treppiedi per apparecchi fotografici; Calibri a corsoio; Apparecchiature per la lettura di schede; Bilance elettroniche da cucina; Chiavi USB; Mouse per computer; Tastiere senza filo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Teleskopinės lazdos išmaniesiems telefonams; Tamsiųjų fotografijos kambarių apšvietimo įrenginiai; Belaidžiai siųstuvai; Mobiliųjų telefonų laikikliai; Planšetinių kompiuterių laikikliai, pritaikyti naudoti automobiliuose; Belaidės ausinės; Ausinės; Filmavimo ir fotografavimo aparatų trikojai; Slankmačiai; Kortelių skaitymo įranga; Elektroninės virtuvinės svarstyklės; Atmintukai [USB]; Kompiuterių pelės; Bevielės klaviatūros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Selfiju rokas statīvi (nūjas), ko lieto kā viedtālruņu piederumus; Apgaismošanas ierīces fotolaboratorijām; Bezvadu raidītāji; Mobilajiem tālruņiem pielāgoti statīvi; Automobiļiem paredzētie planšetdatoru turētāji; Bezvadu austiņas; Ieaušu austiņas; Fotoaparātu statīvi; Bīdmērs; Karšu lasīšanas aprīkojums; Elektroniskie virtuves svari; USB zibatmiņas diski; Datorpele; Bezvadu klaviatūras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Stikek tal-istessu użati bħala aċċessorji għall-ismartfowns; Dawl għall-kamra fotografika fejn jiġu żviluppati r-ritratti; Trasmettituri mingħajr fili; Stends adattati għal telefons ċellulari; Ħowlders għal tablets adattati għall-użu f'karozzi; Kuffji tar-radju jew tat-telefon għar-ras li huma mingħajr fil; Kuffji; Apparat għaż-żamma ta' apparat fotografiku; Kalipers ta' l-islajds; Apparat għall-qari ta' kards; Imwieżen elettroniċi għall-użu fil-kċina; Flash drives tal-USB; Maws tal-kompjuter; Tastieri mingħajr fili.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Selfiestokken als toebehoren voor smartphones; Verlichting voor donkere kamers voor fotografische doeleinden; Draadloze zenders; Standaards aangepast voor mobiele telefoons; Houders voor tablets, aangepast voor gebruik in auto's; Draadloze hoofdtelefoons; Oortelefoons; Driepoten voor fototoestellen; Schuifmaten; Kaartlezers; Elektronische keukenweegschalen; USB-sticks; Computermuis; Draadloze toetsenborden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kijki do robienia selfie jako akcesoria do smartfonów; Oświetlenie do ciemni fotograficznej; Nadajniki bezprzewodowe; Stojaki dostosowane do telefonów komórkowych; Uchwyty na tablety przystosowane do użytku w samochodach; Słuchawki bezprzewodowe; Słuchawki [douszne]; Statywy do aparatów fotograficznych; Suwmiarki; Sprzęt do odczytywania kart; Elektroniczne wagi do użytku kuchennego; Pamięci zewnętrzne USB; Myszki komputerowe; Klawiatury bezprzewodowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Braços extensíveis utilizados como acessórios para smartphones; Iluminação de câmara escura fotográfica; Transmissores sem fios; Suportes adaptados a telemóveis; Suportes para "tablets" adaptados para uso em automóveis; Auscultadores sem fios; Auriculares; Tripés para câmaras fotográficas; Compassos de corrediça; Equipamento para leitura de cartões; Balanças eletrónicas para a cozinha; Unidades de disco amovível [USB flash drives]; Ratos para computador; Teclados sem fios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Suporturi pentru selfie, utilizate ca accesorii pentru telefoane inteligente; Dispozitive de iluminat pentru camere obscure fotografice; Transmiţătoare fără fir; Suporturi adaptate pentru telefoane mobile; Suporturi de tablete adaptate pentru folosirea în automobile; Casti fara fir; Căşti auriculare; Trepiede pentru aparate fotografice; Calibre reglabile; Dispozitive pentru citirea cardurilor; Cântare electronice pentru bucătărie; Memorii USB; Mouse-uri pentru computer; Tastaturi fara fir.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Teleskopické držiaky na smartfóny; Osvetlenie pre fotografické tmavé komory; Bezdrôtové vysielače; Stojany na mobilné telefóny; Držiaky na elektronické tablety do áut; Bezdrôtové slúchadlá; Slúchadlá; Trojnožky na fotoaparáty; Posuvné meradlá; Zariadenia na čítanie kariet; Elektronické váhy na kuchynské účely; USB kľúče; Počítačové myši; Bezdrôtové klávesnice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Podaljšek za fotografiranje samoportretov za uporabo s pametnimi telefoni; Razsvetljava za fotografske temnice; Brezžični oddajniki; Stojala, prirejena za prenosne telefone; Držala za tablične računalnike, prilagojena za uporabo v avtomobilih; Brezžične slušalke; Slušalke; Stojala za fotografske aparate; Kljunasta merila; Oprema za branje kartic; Elektronske tehtnice za kuhinjsko uporabo; USB ključki; Računalniške miške; Brezžične tipkovnice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Selfiepinnar för användning som tillbehör till smartphones; Belysningar för fotografiska mörkrum; Trådlösa sändare; Ställ för mobiltelefoner; Hållare för surfplattor anpassade för bilar; Trådlösa hörlurar; Öronsnäckor; Stativ för fotografiska apparater; Skjutmått; Kortläsningsutrustning; Elektroniska köksvågar; USB-minnen; Datormusar; Trådlösa tangentbord.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/101</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/173</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082018</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15173</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
