<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T09:40:08</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229242</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229242</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>EDELMALZ</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>1</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Препарати за стимулиране на топлинна обработка за промишлени цели; Химически препарати за употреба в промишлеността; Ензими за ползване в пекарната промишленост.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přípravky urychlující vaření pro průmyslové účely; Chemické přípravky pro průmyslové použití; Enzymy k použití v pekařském průmyslu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Præparater til at fremskynde kogning til industriel brug; Kemiske præparater til industrielle formål; Enzymer til anvendelse i bageriindustrien.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Back- und Kochaktivierungsmittel für gewerbliche Zwecke; Chemische Erzeugnisse für gewerbliche Zwecke; Enzyme zur Verwendung in der Backwarenindustrie..</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ψήσιμο (Προϊόντα για την επίσπευση του) για βιομηχανική χρήση· Χημικά παρασκευάσματα για χρήση στη βιομηχανία· Ένζυμα για χρήση στη βιομηχανία άρτου.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Preparations for stimulating cooking for industrial purposes; Chemical preparations for use in industry; Enzymes for use in the bakery industry.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Productos de uso industrial para activar la cocción; Preparados químicos para uso industrial; Enzimas para uso en la industria panadera.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tööstuslikud toiduvalmistamist kiirendavad ained; Tööstuslikud keemiapreparaadid; Pagaritööstuses kasutatavad ensüümid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kiehumista edistävät valmisteet teollisuuskäyttöön; Teollisuudessa käytettävät kemikaalit; Entsyymit leipomoteollisuuden käyttöön.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits pour activer la cuisson à usage industriel; Produits chimiques à usage industriel; Enzymes destinées à l'industrie de la boulangerie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sredstva za poticanje kuhanja za industrijske potrebe; Kemijski pripravci za uporabu u industriji; Enzimi za pekarsku industriju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Főzés elősegítésére szolgáló készítmények, ipari használatra; Vegyi készítmények ipari felhasználásra; Enzimek sütőipari használatra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Prodotti per attivare la cottura per uso industriale; Preparati chimici per uso industriale; Enzimi per uso nel settore della panetteria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Virimo greitinimo preparatai (pramonės reikmėms); Cheminiai preparatai pramonės reikmėms; Fermentai kepimo pramonės reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Preparāti ēdiena sagatavošanas paātrināšanai rūpnieciskiem nolūkiem; Ķīmiskie preparāti lietošanai rūpniecībā; Enzīmi, kurus izmanto maizes cepšanas rūpniecības nozarē.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tisjir [Preparazzjonijiet għall-istimulu tat- -] għal skopijiet industrijali; Preparazzjonijiet kimiċi għall-użu fl-industrija; Enzimi għall-użu fl-industrija tal-furnara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Producten voor het activeren van het kookproces, voor industrieel gebruik; Chemische preparaten voor industrieel gebruik; Enzymen voor gebruik in de bakkerijsector.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Preparaty przyspieszające gotowanie do celów przemysłowych; Preparaty chemiczne do użytku przemysłowego; Enzymy do użytku w przemyśle piekarniczym.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Preparações para ativar a cozedura para uso industrial; Preparações químicas para uso na indústria; Enzimas destinadas à indústria panificadora.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Coacere (produse de uz industrial pentru stimularea -ii); Preparate chimice destinate utilizării în industrie; Enzime folosite în panificație.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Prípravky podporujúce varenie na priemyselné použitie; Chemické prípravky na použitie v priemysle; Enzýmy pre pekárenský priemysel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pripravki za stimulacijo kuhanja za industrijske namene; Kemični pripravki za uporabo v industriji; Encimi, ki se uporabljajo v pekarski industriji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Preparat för att stimulera kokning (för industriellt bruk); Kemiska preparat för industriell användning; Enzymer för användning inom bageribranschen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>29</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Яйца; Мляко; Млечни продукти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vejce; Mléko; Mléčné výrobky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Æg; Mælk; Fødevarerpræparater bestående hovedsageligt af mælk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Eier; Milch; Milchprodukte..</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αυγά· Γάλα· Γαλακτοκομικά (- προϊόντα).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Eggs; Milk; Milk products.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Huevos; Leche; Productos lácteos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Munad; Piim; Piimatooted.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Munat; Maito; Maitotuotteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Œufs; Lait; Produits laitiers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Jaja; Mlijeko; Mliječni proizvodi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tojások; Tej; Tejtermékek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Uova; Latte; Prodotti lattieri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kiaušiniai; Pienas; Pieno produktai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Olas; Piens; Piena produkti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Bajd; Ħalib; Prodotti tal-ħalib.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Eieren; Melk; Melkproducten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Jaja; Mleko; Mleczne produkty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Ovos; Leite; Produtos lácteos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ouă; Lapte; Lactate (Produse -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vajcia; Mlieko; Mliečne výrobky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Jajca; Mleko; Mlečni proizvodi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Ägg; Mjölk; Mjölkprodukter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>30</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Хляб; Хлебни изделия; Готови смеси за пекарски изделия; Паста; Зърнени храни; Смес за кифли; Франзели; Смес за сладкиши; Бакпулвер; Смес за сладкиши; Брашно за кекс; Брашно от зърнени култури; Царевични люспи; Брашно; Готови за печене тестени продукти; Брашно, готово за печене; Брашно за сладкарски изделия; Сладкиши, кексове, торти и бисквити; Сладки бисквити за консумация от хора; Овкусени сладки; Крекери [тънки, сухи бисквити]; Меки ролца [Хляб]; Препечен хляб [Бисквити]; Кифли; Мая; Сладкиши за чай; Бонбони, приготвени от захар; Шоколадови пълнежи за пекарски изделия; Дълбокозамразени тестени изделия; Препарати за приготвяне на хлебни изделия; Сол; Сол за храни; Сладоледи и сладоледени кремове; Мед; Меласи; Малцов хляб; Малц за хранителни цели; Малцови екстракти, използвани като подправка.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Chléb; Pekárenské výrobky; Hotové směsi na pečení; Těstoviny; Přípravky z obilovin; Směs na přípravu pečiva; Bagety; Cukrářské výrobky; Kypřící prášek do pečiva; Dorty; Mouka na dorty a koláče; Obilná mouka; Kukuřičné lupínky; Mouka; Výrobky z těsta připravené k pečení; Mouka na pečení; Moučníky; Moučníky, zákusky, dorty a sušenky; Sladké sušenky pro lidskou spotřebu; Slané pečivo; Krekry; Měkké chlebové pečivo; Toasty [pečivo]; Pečivo (typu housky, rohlíky); Droždí; Čajové zákusky; Bonbóny vyrobené z cukru; Čokoládové náplně pro pekařské výrobky; Mražené pečivo; Přípravky k výrobě pečiva; Sůl; Jedlá sůl; Led na osvěžení; Med; Zlatý sirup; Sladový chléb; Sladový výtažek pro potravinářské účely; Sladové výtažky k dochucování.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Brød; Bagerivarer; Færdiglavede bageblandinger; Pasta; Kornpræparater; Bolleblanding; Flutes; Konditorkager; Bagepulver; Kager; Mel til kager; Mel af korn; Majsflager; Mel; Dejprodukter der er klar til bagning; Bagemel; Konfekturevarer af mel; Konditorivarer, kager, tærter, kiks og småkager; Søde småkager som næringsmidler til mennesker; Konditorivarer med krydret smag; Kiks; Bløde boller [brød]; Toast [kiks]; Rundstykker; Gær; Tekager; Bolsjer (sukkervarer); Chokoladefyld til bageriprodukter; Dybfrosne konditorivarer; Præparater til fremstilling af bagværk; Salt; Køkkensalt; Is til forfriskning; Honning; Lys sirup; Maltbrød; Maltekstrakter til brug som næringsmiddel; Maltekstrakt brugt som smagsstof.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Brot; Backwaren; Backmischungen; Teigwaren; Getreidepräparate; Brötchenmischungen; Baguettes; Feine Backwaren; Backpulver; Kuchen; Kuchenmehl; Getreidemehl; Cornflakes; Mehl; Backfertige Teige; Backfertiges Mehl; Konditorwaren auf Mehlbasis; Gebäck, Kuchen, Torten und Kekse; Süßes Gebäck für die menschliche Ernährung; Pikantes Gebäck; Kräcker [Gebäck]; Weiche Brötchen; Toasts [Brötchen]; Semmeln [Brötchen]; Hefe; Teegebäck; Zuckerwaren; Schokoladenfüllungen für Backwaren; Gefrorene feine Backwaren; Mischungen zur Herstellung von Backwaren; Mischungen zum Herstellen von Backwaren; Zubereitungen für die Herstellung von Backwaren; Salz; Speisesalz; Kühleis; Honig; Sirup; Malzbrot; Malzextrakte für Nahrungszwecke; Malzextrakte zur Verwendung als Aromastoff..</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Άρτος· Είδη αρτοποιίας· Έτοιμα μίγματα για ψήσιμο· Ζυμαρικά· Δημητριακά· Μείγμα για ψωμάκια· Μπαγκέτες (ψωμί γαλλικού τύπου)· Γλυκά· Ζυμωτική σκόνη· Γλυκά· Αλεύρι για κέικ· Αλεύρι δημητριακών· Νιφάδες αραβοσίτου· Αλεύρι· Έτοιμα για ψήσιμο προϊόντα ζύμης· Άλευρα έτοιμα για ψήσιμο· Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής με βάση το αλεύρι· Γλύκισματα, κέικ, τάρτες και μπισκότα· Γλυκά μπισκότα για κατανάλωση από τον άνθρωπο· Αλμυρά πιτοειδή· Κράκερ· Μαλακά ψωμάκια· Φρυγανισμένο ψωμί [μπισκότα]· Ψωμάκια· Μαγιά· Κέικ για το τσάι· Κουφέτα, καραμέλες· Γέμιση σοκολάτας για αρτοσκευάσματα· Κατεψυγμένα γλυκά· Παρασκευάσματα για προϊόντα αρτοποιίας· Αλάτι· Αλάτι φαγητού· Παγωτά και κρέμα παγωτό· Μέλι· Σιρόπια και μελάσες· Ψωμί βύνης· Βύνη για διατροφή· Εκχυλίσματα βύνης για χρήση ως αρτυματικές ύλες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Bread; Bakery goods; Ready-made baking mixtures; Pasta; Cereal preparations; Bun mix; Baguettes; Pastries; Baking powder; Cakes; Cake flour; Cereal flour; Corn flakes; Flour; Ready-to-bake dough products; Flour ready for baking; Flour confectionery; Pastries, cakes, tarts and biscuits (cookies); Sweet biscuits for human consumption; Savory pastries; Crackers; Soft rolls [bread]; Toasts [biscuits]; Bread rolls; Yeast; Tea cakes; Bonbons made of sugar; Chocolate fillings for bakery products; Frozen pastries; Preparations for making bakery products; Salt; Edible salt; Ice for refreshment; Honey; Treacle; Malt bread; Malt extract for food; Malt extracts used as flavoring.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pan; Productos de panadería; Mezclas para hornear preparadas; Pastas alimenticias; Preparaciones a base de cereales; Preparado para hacer panecillos; Baguettes; Productos de pastelería; Polvos de hornear; Pasteles; Harina pastelera; Harina de cereales; Copos de maíz; Harinas; Productos de masa listos para hornear; Harina lista para hornear; Confitería de harina; Pastas, pasteles, tartas y galletas; Galletas dulces para consumo humano; Pasteles salados; Galletas saladas [crackers]; Panecillos blandos [pan]; Tostadas [galletas]; Panecillos; Levadura; Pastas de té; Bombones hechos de azúcar; Rellenos de chocolate para productos de panadería; Pastelería congelada; Preparados para hacer productos de panadería; Sal; Sal comestible; Hielo; Miel; Jarabe de melaza; Pan de malta; Extractos de malta para uso alimenticio; Extractos de malta usados como aromatizantes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Leib, sai; Pagaritooted; Valmisküpsetussegud; Pasta (makarontooted); Teraviljasaadused; Kuklivalmistussegud; Pikad Prantsuse saiad [baguette'id]; Kondiitritooted; Küpsetuspulber; Koogid, keeksid, tordid; Koogijahu; Teraviljajahu; Maisihelbed; Jahu; Küpsetusvalmis tainatooted; Küpsetusjahu; Jahust valmistatud maiustused, kondiitritooted; Kondiitritooted, koogid, tordid ja biskviidid (küpsised); Magusad biskviidid inimtarbeks; Soolased kondiitritooted; Küpsised, kuivikud; Pehmed prantssaiad; Röstsaiad [kuivikud]; Väikesaiad; Pärm; Teekoogid; Suhkrukompvekid; Šokolaaditäidised pagaritoodetele; Külmutatud kondiitritooted; Pagaritoodete tootmisel kasutatavad preparaadid; Sool; Söögisool; Jahutusjää; Mesi; Kuldsiirup, melass; Linnaseleib; Toidulinnaseekstrakt; Linnaseekstraktid maitseainetena.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Leipä; Leipomotuotteet; Valmiit leivonta-ainekset; Pasta; Viljavalmisteet; Kuiva-aineseokset sämpylöiden valmistukseen; Patongit; Voitaikina; Leivinjauhe; Voitaikina; Jauho (Kakku -); Viljasta jauhetut jauhot; Maissihiutaleet; Jauhot; Leivontavalmiit taikinatuotteet; Jauho leivontaan; Jauhoista valmistetut konditoriatuotteet; Leivonnaiset, kakut, piirakat ja keksit; Makeat keksit ihmisravinnoksi; Suolaiset leivonnaiset; Voileipäkeksit; Pehmeät sämpylät; Paahtoleivät [keksit]; Limput; Hiiva; Teekakut; Sokerista valmistetut karamellit; Suklaatäytteet leivonnaistuotteita varten; Pakastetut leivonnaiset; Valmisteet leipomotuotteiden tekemiseen; Suola; Ruokasuola; Jäätelöt; Hunaja; Siirapit ja melassit; Mallasleipä; Maltaat ihmisravinnoksi; Makuaineina käytettävät mallasuutteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Pain; Produits de boulangerie; Mélanges prêts à cuire; Pâtes alimentaires; Préparations faites de céréales; Préparation pour brioches et petits pains; Baguettes [pain]; Pâtisserie; Poudre à lever; Gâteaux; Farine pour gâteaux; Farine de céréales; Flocons de maïs; Farine; Produits à base de pâte prête-à-cuire; Farine prête à cuire; Confiseries à base de farine; Pâtisseries, gâteaux, tartes et biscuits; Biscuits sucrés destinés à la consommation humaine; Pâtisseries salées; Crackers; Petits pains à croûte tendre [soft rolls]; Toasts [biscottes]; Petits pains; Levure; Gâteaux et petits pains pour accompagner le thé; Bonbons en sucre; Garnitures de chocolat pour produits de boulangerie-pâtisserie; Pâtisserie glacée; Préparations pour faire des produits de boulangerie; Sel; Sel comestible; Glace à rafraîchir; Miel; Sirop de mélasse; Pain à base de malt; Extraits de malt pour l'alimentation; Extraits de malt utilisés comme aromatisants.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kruh; Pekarski proizvodi; Gotove mješavine za pečenje; Prehrambena tjestenina; Žitarice; Mješavina za peciva; Francuski kruh [baguette]; Tijesto za kolače; Prašak za dizanje; Tijesto za kolače; Brašno za kolače; Brašno od žitarica; Kukuruzne pahuljice; Brašno; Proizvodi od tijesta spremni za pečenje; Brašno za pečenje; Konditorski proizvodi od brašna; Slastice, torte, pite i keksi; Slatki keksi za ljudsku konzumaciju; Slani pekarski proizvodi; Krekeri; Mekana peciva [kruh]; Tost (preprženi kruh); Pecivo (fino sitno pecivo); Pjenica [kvasac]; Čajni kolačići; Bomboni od šećera; Čokoladna punjenja za pekarske proizvode; Zamrznuta peciva; Mješavine za pripremu pekarskih proizvoda; Sol; Jestiva sol; Sladoledi i mliječni sladoledi; Med; Sirupi i melase; Kruh od slada; Ekstrakti iz slada za prehranu; Ekstrakti slada kao aroma.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kenyér; Pékáruk; Előkészített sütőkeverékek; Lisztből készült tészták; Gabonakészítmények; Tésztapor zsemléhez/molnárkához; Bagettek; Süteménytészta; Sütőpor; Süteménytészta; Süteményliszt; Gabonaliszt; Kukoricapehely; Liszt; Sütésre kész tésztatermékek; Sütőliszt; Liszt alapú sütemények; Sütemények, cukrászsütemények, torták és kekszek (aprósütemények); Édes kekszek emberi fogyasztásra; Sós sütemények; Kekszek, rágcsálnivalók; Zsemlék [kenyérfélék]; Pirítósok [kekszek]; Zsemlék; Élesztő; Teasütemények; Cukorkák; Csokoládés töltelékek pékárukhoz; Fagyasztott sütemények; Készítmények pékáruk készítéséhez; Só; Só ételízesítéshez; Fagylaltok és jégkrémek; Méz; Melaszszirup; Malátás kenyér; Maláta emberi fogyasztásra; Ízesítőként használt malátakivonatok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pane; Prodotti da forno; Miscele pronte per la cottura al forno; Paste alimentari; Preparati fatti di cereali; Miscele per panini; Baguette; Pasticcini; Lievito in polvere; Dolci; Farina per dolci; Farina di cereali; Fiocchi di mais; Farine alimentari; Prodotti di panetteria pronti da infornare; Farina pronta per la panificazione; Confetteria a base di farina; Pasticcini, torte, crostate e biscotti; Biscotti dolci per l'alimentazione umana; Pasticceria salata; Crackers; Panini morbidi; Biscotti tostati; Panini; Lievito; Dolci da tè; Confetti di zucchero; Ripieni di cioccolato per prodotti da forno; Prodotti da forno surgelati; Preparati per prodotti da forno; Sale; Sale per alimenti; Ghiaccio per rinfrescare; Miele; Sciroppo di melassa; Pane al malto; Estratti di malto per l'alimentazione; Estratti di malto da utilizzare come aromi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Duona; Duonos gaminiai; Paruošti kepimo mišiniai; Makaronų tešla; Grūdų produktai; Bandelių miltų mišinys; Prancūziškieji batonai; Miltiniai konditerijos gaminiai; Kepimo milteliai; Kepiniai; Tortų miltai; Javų miltai; Kukurūzų dribsniai; Miltai; Paruošti kepti tešlos gaminiai; Kepimui paruošti miltai; Miltiniai konditerijos gaminiai; Miltiniai konditerijos gaminiai, kepiniai, tortai ir sausainiai; Saldūs sausainiai (žmonių maistui); Sūrūs kepiniai; Krekeriai [užkandžių sausainiai]; Minkštos bandelės [duona]; Skrebučiai [sausainiai]; Bandelės; Mielės; Arbatiniai pyragai; Saldainiai iš cukraus; Šokoladiniai kepinių įdarai; Šaldyti pyragaičiai; Duonos gaminių kepimo mišiniai; Druska; Maistinė druska; Ledas (šaldymui); Medus; Melasos sirupas; Salyklinė duona; Salyklo ekstraktas (maistui); Salyklo ekstraktai [aromatinė medžiaga].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Maize; Maizes ceptuvju produkcija; Gatavi cepšanas maisījumi; Pasta (makaronu izstrādājumi vai ēdieni); Graudaugu produkti; Maisījumi smalkmaizīšu pagatavošanai; Bagetes (franču baltmaize); Maizes izstrādājumi; Cepamais pulveris; Kūkas; Kūku milti; Labības milti; Kukurūzas pārslas; Milti; Cepšanai gatavi mīklas izstrādājumi; Milti cepšanai; Miltu konditoreja; Konditorejas izstrādājumi, kūkas, tortes un cepumi; Saldi cepumi cilvēku patēriņam; Sāļie maizes konditorejas izstrādājumi; Krekeri; Mīkstas, apaļas maizītes; Grauzdiņi [biskvīti]; Maizītes; Raugs; Tējas kūkas; No cukura gatavotas konfektes; Šokolādes pildījumi maizes izstrādājumiem; Saldēti miltu konditorejas izstrādājumi; Konditorejas izstrādājumu izgatavošanai paredzētie maisījumi; Sāls; Pārtikas sāls; Pārtikas ledus; Medus; Melase; Iesala maize; Iesala ekstrakts pārtikai; Iesala ekstrakti, kurus lieto kā aromatizētājus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ħobż; Prodotti tal-ħami; Taħlitiet tal-ħami lesti; Għaġin; Ċereali; Taħlita tal-panini; Ħobż forma ta' bezzun; Għaġina tal-kejk; Trab tal-ħami; Għaġina tal-kejk; Dqiq tal-kejkijiet; Dqiq taċ-ċereali; Kornflejks; Dqiq; Prodotti tal-għaġina lesti għall-ħami; Dqiq lest għall-ħami; Ħelu tad-dqiq; Pasti, kejkijiet, torti u gallettini (cookies); Gallettini tal-ħelu għall-konsum uman; Ikel tal-għaġina [mhux tal-ħelu]; Kràkers; Ħobż artab [imgerbeb]; Gallettini mixwijin; Ftajjar rotob; Ħmira; Kejkijiet ta' mat-te; Kunfetti magħmula miz-zokkor; Mili taċ-ċikkulata għall-prodotti tal-ħami; Għaġina iffriżata; Preparazzjonijiet biex tagħmel prodotti għall-ħami; Melħ; Melħ għall-ikel; Silġ għar-rinfreskar; Għasel; Xiropp u għasel iswed; Ħobż mix-xgħir jew qamħ ġeneralment bârli; Xgħir għall-konsum mill-bniedem; Estratti tax-xgħir jew qamħ użati bħala essenzi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Brood; Bakkerijproducten; Kant-en-klare bakmengsels; Deegwaren; Graanpreparaten; Mengsels voor broodjes; Baguettes; Banketbakkerswaren; Bakpoeder; Taarten; Cakemeel; Granenbloem; Maïsvlokken [cornflakes]; Meel; Deegproducten (Bakklare -); Bakmeel; Suikergoed op basis van meel; Banketbakkerswaren, cakes, taarten en biscuits (koekjes); Biscuits (Zoete -) voor menselijke consumptie; Hartig gebak; Crackers; Zachte broodjes; Toast [koekjes]; Broodjes; Gist; Theebroodjes; Bonbons gemaakt van suiker; Chocoladevullingen voor bakkerswaren; Bevroren banketbakkerswaren; Preparaten voor het bereiden van bakkerswaren; Zout; Zout voor voedingsdoeleinden; Koelijs; Honing; Melassestroop; Brood (Mout -); Moutextracten voor voedingsdoeleinden; Moutextracten voor gebruik als smaakstof.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Chleb; Wyroby piekarnicze; Gotowe mieszanki do pieczenia; Makarony; Zboża; Mieszanki do pieczenia bułek; Bagietki; Ciastka; Proszek do pieczenia; Ciasta; Mąka do pieczenia; Mąka zbożowe; Płatki kukurydziane; Mąka; Ciasta gotowe do pieczenia; Mąka gotowa do pieczenia; Wyroby cukiernicze z mąki; Wyroby cukiernicze, ciasta, tarty i ciasteczka; Słodkie herbatniki do spożycia przez ludzi; Solone wyroby piekarnicze; Krakersy; Miękkie bułeczki; Grzanki [sucharki]; Bułki; Drożdże; Ciastka herbaciane; Czekoladki wykonane z cukru; Nadzienia czekoladowe do wyrobów piekarniczych; Mrożone wyroby piekarnicze; Preparaty do wyrobu produktów piekarniczych; Sól; Sól spożywcza; Lody; Miód; Melasa; Chleb słodowy; Słód do celów spożywczych; Wyciągi słodowe stosowane jako aromaty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Pão; Produtos de padaria; Misturas preparadas para cozinhar no forno; Massas alimentares; Preparações à base de cereais; Mistura para pãezinhos; Baguetes; Produtos de pastelaria; Fermento em pó; Bolos; Farinha para bolos; Farinha de cereais; Flocos de milho; Farinhas alimentares; Massa pronta a cozer; Farinhas prontas para cozedura no forno; Confeitaria de farinha; Pastelaria, bolos, tartes e biscoitos (bolachas); Biscoitos doces para consumo humano; Pastelaria salgada; Bolachas de água e sal; Brioches [Pãezinhos]; Bolachas tostadas; Pãezinhos; Levedura; Bolinhos de chá; Bombons de açúcar; Recheios de chocolate para produtos de padaria; Pastelaria congelada; Preparações para a confeção de produtos de padaria; Sal; Sal comestível; Gelo para refrescar; Mel; Xarope de melaço; Pão de malte; Extrato de malte para a alimentação; Extratos de malte utilizados como aromatizantes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Pâine; Produse de brutărie; Amestecuri de copt gata preparate; Paste alimentare făinoase; Cereale; Amestec pentru chifle cu lapte; Baghete; Torturi; Praf de copt; Torturi; Făină pentru prăjituri; Făină de cereale; Fulgi de porumb; Făină; Produse din aluat gata de copt; Făină de copt; Produse de cofetărie pe bază de făină; Produse de patiserie, prăjituri, tarte și biscuiți (prăjiturele); Biscuiți dulci pentru consum uman; Produse de patiserie aromate; Biscuiți sărați; Chifle moi [Pâine]; Pâine prăjită [Biscuiți]; Chifle; Drojdie; Prăjituri pentru ceai; Bomboane preparate din zahăr; Umpluturi din ciocolată pentru produse de brutărie; Produse de patiserie congelate; Amestecuri pentru produse de brutărie; Sare; Sare pentru condimentarea mâncării; Înghețată; Miere; Siropuri și melasă; Pâine de malț; Malț pentru alimentație; Extracte de malț utilizate ca arome.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Chlieb; Pekárske výrobky; Hotové [pripravené] zmesi na pečenie; Cestoviny; Prípravky z obilnín; Zmesi na žemle; Bagety; Jemné pečivárske výrobky; Práškové droždie; Zákusky, koláče; Múka na koláče; Obilná múka; Kukuričné vločky; Múka; Výrobky z cesta pripravené na pečenie; Múka na okamžité použitie do pečenia; Cukrovinky z múky; Jemné pečivo, koláče, torty, sušienky; Sladké sušienky na ľudskú spotrebu; Lahôdkové pečivo; Slané pečivo (krekery); Žemle z krehkého cesta [pečivo]; Hrianky [pečivo]; Pečivo (rožky); Droždie; Čajové pečivo; Bonbóny z cukru; Čokoládové plnky na výrobu pekárenských výrobkov; Mrazené pečivo; Prípravky na výrobu pekárenských výrobkov; Soľ; Jedlá soľ; Ľad do nápojov; Med; Melasový sirup; Sladový chlieb; Sladové výťažky (potraviny); Sladové výťažky používané ako príchuti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kruh; Pekovski izdelki; Pripravljene mešanice za peko; Testenine; Žitarice; Mešanica za štručke; Francoske štruce; Testo za torte; Pecilni praški; Testo za torte; Moka za torto; Žitna moka; Koruzni kosmiči; Moka; Izdelki iz testa, pripravljeni za peko; Moka za peko; Slaščice iz moke; Fino pecivo, torte, kolači in piškoti; Sladki piškoti za človeško prehrano; Pikantno pecivo; Krekerji; Mehki kruhovi zvitki; Popečenec [piškoti]; Drobno kruhovo pecivo; Kvas; Čajno pecivo; Bonboni iz sladkorja; Čokoladni nadevi za pekovske izdelke; Zamrznjeno pecivo; Mešanice za pripravo pekarskih proizvodov; Sol; Jedilna sol; Led; Med; Sirupi, melasni sirupi; Sladni kruh; Slad za človeško prehrano; Sladni ekstrakti za aromatiziranje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bröd; Bagerivaror; Färdiga bakningsmixer; Pasta; Spannmålspreparat; Bullmixer; Baguetter; Bakverk; Bakpulver; Kakor; Mjöl för kakbak; Mjöl av brödsäd; Majsflingor; Mjöl; Gräddningsfärdiga degprodukter; Färdiga mjölmixer för bakning; Mjölbaserade godsaker; Bakverk, kakor, tårtor och kex (småkakor); Söta kex för mänsklig konsumtion; Kryddade bakverk; Crackers (smörgåskex); Mjuka kuvertbröd; Rostade kex; Kuvertbröd; Jäst; Tekakor; Sockerkarameller; Chokladfyllningar för bakvaror; Frysta konditorivaror; Preparat för att tillverka bageriprodukter; Salt; Ätliga salter; Is för förfriskningar; Honung; Sirap; Maltbröd; Maltextrakt för livsmedel; Maltextrakt för användning som smaktillsatser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/080</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/151</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-11</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>957271</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>20350</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
