<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-18T14:29:20</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229844</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229844</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-13</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-18</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Suntapower</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>12</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Въздушни помпи за велосипеди за напомпване на гуми; Въздушни помпи за двуколесни моторни превозни средства или велосипеди; Въздушни помпи [аксесоари на превозни средства]; Въздушни помпи за мотоциклети; Въздушни помпи за автомобили; Нагнетателни помпи [принадлежности за превозни средства].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vzduchové pumpičky na nafukování pneumatik jízdních kol; Vzduchové pumpy pro dvojkolová motorová vozidla a jízdní kola; Hustilky [výbava vozidel]; Vzduchové pumpičky pro motocykly; Vzduchové pumpy pro automobily; Čerpadla na stlačený vzduch (příslušenství vozidel).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Cykelpumper [til luftpumpning af cykeldæk]; Luftpumper til tohjulede motorkøretøjer eller cykler; Luftpumper [tilbehør til køretøjer]; Luftpumper til motorcykler; Luftpumper til biler; Trykluftspumper [tilbehør til køretøjer].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Luftpumpen zum Aufpumpen von Fahrradreifen; Luftpumpen für motorisierte Zweiräder oder Fahrräder; Luftpumpen [Fahrzeugzubehör]; Luftpumpen für Motorräder; Luftpumpen für Automobile; Luftdruckpumpen als Fahrzeugzubehör.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αεραντλίες για τα ελαστικά ποδηλάτων· Αεραντλίες για δίτροχα μηχανοκίνητα οχήματα ή ποδήλατα· Αντλίες αέρα [εξαρτήματα οχημάτων]· Αντλίες αέρα για μοτοσυκλέτες· Αεραντλίες για αυτοκίνητα· Αντλίες πίεσης αέρα [εξαρτήματα οχημάτων].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Air pumps for bicycles for the inflation of tyres; Air pumps for two-wheeled motor vehicles or bicycles; Air pumps [vehicle accessories]; Air pumps for motorcycles; Air pumps for automobiles; Air pressure pumps [vehicle accessories].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bombas de aire para hinchar neumáticos de bicicleta; Bombas de aire para vehículos de motor de dos ruedas o bicicletas; Bombas de aire [accesorios para vehículos]; Bombas de aire para motocicletas; Bombas de aire para automóviles; Bombas de aire a presión [accesorios para vehículos].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Õhupumbad jalgratta rehvide täispumpamiseks; Kaherattaliste mootorsõidukite või jalgrataste õhupumbad; Õhupumbad [sõidukiseadised]; Mootorrataste õhupumbad; Autode õhupumbad; Suruõhupumbad [sõidukitarvikud].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Polkupyörien ilmapumput renkaiden täyttämiseen; Kaksipyöräisten moottoriajoneuvojen tai polkupyörien ilmapumput; Ilmapumput [ajoneuvojen apuvälineinä]; Moottoripyörien ilmapumput; Autojen ilmapumput; Ilmanpainepumput [ajoneuvojen varusteet].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Pompes à air pour gonfler les pneus de bicyclettes; Pompes à air pour véhicules à moteur à deux roues ou bicyclettes; Pompes à air [accessoires de véhicules]; Pompes à air pour motocycles; Pompes à air pour véhicules automobiles; Pompes à air comprimé [accessoires pour véhicules].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Zračne pumpe za pumpanje guma bicikla; Zračne pumpe za motorna vozila na dva kotača ili za bicikle; Zračne pumpe [oprema za vozila]; Zračne pumpe za motocikle; Zračne pumpe za automobile; Pumpe na tlačni zrak [oprema vozila].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kerékpár abroncsok felfújására szolgáló pumpák, levegőpumpák; Légszivattyúk kétkerekű gépjárművekhez vagy kerékpárokhoz; Légszivattyúk, légpumpák [járműtartozékok]; Légpumpák motorkerékpárokhoz; Légszivattyúk autókba; Légpumpák [jármű tartozékok].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pompe ad aria per biciclette per gonfiare i pneumatici; Pompe ad aria per biciclette o veicoli a motore a due ruote; Pompe ad aria [accessori di veicoli]; Pompe ad aria per motociclette; Pompe ad aria per automobili; Pompe a pressione d'aria [accessori per veicoli].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Oro pompos dviračių padangoms pripūsti; Dviračių motorinių transporto priemonių ar dviračių oro pompos; Oro siurbliai [transporto priemonių reikmenys]; Oro pompos motociklams; Automobilių oro pompos; Suslėgto oro siurbliai [transporto priemonių priedai].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Gaisa sūkņi velosipēdu riepu piepūšanai; Gaisa sūkņi mototransportam vai velosipēdiem; Gaisa sūkņi (transportlīdzekļu piederumi); Gaisa sūkņi motocikliem; Gaisa sūkņi automobiļiem; Gaisa spiediena sūkņi (transportlīdzekļu piederumi).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pompi għall-infiħ ta' roti tar-roti; Pompi tal-arja għall-vetturi bil-mutur b'żewġ roti jew għar-roti; Arja [Pompi tal- -] (aċċessorji tal-vetturi); Pompi tal-arja għall-muturi; Pompi tal-arja għall-karozzi; Pompi tal-arja kkompressata [aċċessorji għall-vetturi].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Luchtpompen voor fietsen voor het oppompen van banden; Luchtpompen voor gemotoriseerde tweewielers of fietsen; Luchtpompen [voor voertuigen]; Luchtpompen voor motorrijwielen; Luchtpompen voor auto's; Luchtperspompen [voor voertuigen].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pompki do pompowania opon rowerowych; Pompy powietrza do dwukołowych pojazdów silnikowych lub rowerów; Pompy powietrzne [akcesoria do pojazdów]; Pompy powietrza do motocykli; Pompy powietrza do samochodów; Pompy na sprężone powietrze [akcesoria do pojazdów].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Bombas de ar para encher pneus de bicicletas; Bombas de ar para veículos motorizados de duas rodas ou bicicletas; Bombas de ar [acessórios para veículos]; Bombas de ar para motociclos; Bombas de ar para automóveis; Bombas de pressão de ar [acessórios de veículos].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Pompe de aer pentru umflarea cauciucurilor de bicicletă; Pompe de aer pentru vehicule cu motor pe două roți sau biciclete; Pompe de aer [accesorii pentru vehicule]; Pompe de aer pentru motociclete; Pompe de aer pentru automobile; Pompe cu aer comprimat [accesorii pentru vehicule].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Pumpy na hustenie pneumatík pre bicykle; Pumpy pre dvojkolesové motorové vozidlá alebo bicykle; Vzduchové pumpy (výbava automobilov); Vzduchové pumpy pre motocykle; Vzduchové pumpy pre automobily; Tlakové vzduchové pumpy [ príslušenstvo vozidiel].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zračne tlačilke za polnjenje pnevmatik koles; Zračne tlačilke za motorizirana dvokolesa ali kolesa; Zračne tlačilke [oprema vozil]; Zračne tlačilke za motorna kolesa; Zračne tlačilke za avtomobile; Črpalke na zračni tak [dodatna oprema za vozila].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Luftpumpar för uppumpning av cykeldäck; Luftpumpar för tvåhjuliga motorfordon eller cyklar; Luftpumpar [fordonstillbehör]; Luftpumpar för motorcyklar; Luftpumpar för bilar; Tryckluftspumpar [tillbehör till fordon och farkoster].</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>26</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ширити; Копчета; Резбонарезни глави; Копчета за облекло; Перуки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Prýmky; Knoflíky; Navlékače jehel; Knoflíky na oděvy; Paruky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kantebånd; Knapper; Nåletrædere; Nitter til beklædningsgenstande; Parykker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Tressen, Soutachen, Litzen, Borten [Besatzwaren]; Knöpfe; Nadeleinfädler; Knöpfe für Bekleidungsstücke; Perücken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Γαλόνια· Κουμπιά· Βελονοπεραστές· Καρφιά για ενδύματα· Περούκες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">braids; Buttons; needle-threaders; buttons for clothing; wigs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cordones; Botones; Enhebradores de agujas; Tachuelas para la ropa; Pelucas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Punutised; Nööbid; Nõelapoisid [niidi nõelasilmast läbiajamise vahendid]; Rõivanööbid; Parukad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Punokset; Napit; Langanpujottimet; Vaatteiden napit; Peruukit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Lacets [cordons]; Boutons; Enfile-aiguilles; Boutons pour vêtements; Perruques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Uzice [konopčići]; Dugmad [puceta]; Naprave za uvlačenje konca u igle; Dugmad za odjeću; Vlasulje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szalagok, fonatok, zsinórok; Gombok; Tűbefűzők; Ruhagombok; Parókák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cordoni trecciati; Bottoni; Infila-aghi; Bottoni per indumenti; Parrucche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Juostelės; Sagos; Adatų siūlo vertuvai; Drabužių sagos; Perukai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pītas lentes; Pogas; Diegu ievērēji adatām; Apģērbu pogas; Parūkas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tberfil; Buttuni; Dammiema għal-labar; Buttuni b'żewġt irjus għall-ilbies; Parrokki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Boordsel; Knopen; Instrumentjes voor het trekken van garen door het oog van een naald; Knopen voor kleding; Pruiken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Galony; Guziki; Nawlekacze do igieł; Guziki do odzieży; Peruki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cordões [laços]; Botões; Enfia-agulhas; Botões para vestuário; Perucas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Trese; Nasturi; Mașini de filetat cu ac; Butoni pentru haine; Peruci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Pletené šnúry; Gombíky; Navliekače nití; Gombíky pre odevy; Parochne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Okrasne vrvice; Gumbi; Vdevalniki niti; Gumbi za oblačila; Lasulje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tränsar; Knappar; Nålpåträdare; Knappar för kläder; Peruker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Джой-стикове за игрови конзоли; Игли за помпи за надуване на топки за игри; Помпи, специално приспособени за употреба с топки за игри; Снегоходки; Пристягащи колани за кръста за упражнения; Пояси за плуване; Ръкавици за батъри [аксесоари за игри]; Наколенки [спортни артикули].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Ovladače herních konzolí; Jehly do pumpiček na nafukování míčů na míčové hry; Pumpičky speciálně upravené pro nafukování míčů na míčové hry; Sněžnice; Stahovací cvičební pásy; Kruhy na plavání; Pálkařské rukavice [vybavení pro hry]; Kolení chrániče [sportovní potřeby].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Controllere til spillekonsoller; Nåle til pumper til oppustning af bolde til spil; Pumper særligt tilpasset bolde til spil; Snesko; Træningsbælter til trimning af taljen; Svømmeringe; Slåhandsker til cricket; Knæbeskyttere [sportsartikler].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Steuergeräte für Spielkonsolen; Nadeln für Pumpen zum Aufblasen von Spielbällen; Spezialpumpen für Spielbälle; Schneeschuhe; Trainingsgürtel zur Reduzierung der Taillenweite; Schwimmreifen; Schlägerhandschuhe [Spielzubehör]; Knieschützer [Sportartikel].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ελεγκτές για κονσόλες παιχνιδιών· Βελόνες για αεραντλίες για το φούσκωμα μπαλών παιχνιδιού· Αντλίες ειδικά προσαρμοσμένες για χρήση με μπάλες παιχνιδιού· Παπούτσια για το χιόνι· Ζώνες άσκησης για την σύσφιξη της μέσης· Κυκλικά σωσίβια· Αθλητικά γάντια (- μποξ) [εξαρτήματα παιχνιδιού]· Επιγονατίδες [αθλητικά είδη].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">controllers for game consoles; needles for pumps for inflating balls for games; pumps specially adapted for use with balls for games; snowshoes; Waist trimmer exercise belts; swimming rings; Batting gloves; Knee pads for athletic use.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Mandos para consolas de juego; Agujas de infladores para pelotas de juego; Infladores especiales para pelotas de juego; Raquetas de nieve; Correas de ejercicio para reducir la cintura; Flotadores de aro; Guantes de bateador [accesorios para juegos]; Rodilleras [artículos de deporte].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Mängukonsoolide kontrollerid; Pallipumpade nõelad; Pallide pumbad; Räätsad; Harjutusvööd piha salendamiseks; Ujumisrõngad; Kriketikindad [sportmänguvahendid]; Põlvekaitsmed [sporditarbed].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Pelikonsoleiden ohjaimet; Peleissä käytettävien pallojen täyttämiseen käytettävät neulat; Erityisesti peleissä käytettäviä palloja varten tarkoitetut pumput; Lumikengät; Keskivartalonharjoitusvyöt; Uimarenkaat; Lyömäkäsineet [pallopeleihin]; Polvisuojukset [urheiluun].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Commandes pour consoles de jeu; Aiguilles de pompe de gonflage pour balles de jeu; Pompes spécialement conçues pour balles de jeu; Raquettes à neige; Ceintures d'exercice pour affiner la taille; Bouées gonflables; Gants pour batteurs [accessoires de jeux]; Protège-genoux [articles de sport].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kontrolori za igraće konzole; Igle za pumpe za napuhivanje lopti za igru; Pumpe posebno prilagođene za uporabu s loptama za igru; Cipele za snijeg; Remenje za tjelovježbu za smanjenje obujma struka; Koluti za plivanje; Rukavice za udaranje palicom; Zaštita za koljena [sportski artikli].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vezérlők játékkonzolokhoz; Szeleptűk játéklabdák felfújására szolgáló pumpákhoz; Kifejezetten játéklabdákhoz használandó pumpák; Hótalpak; Testedző övek a derék karcsúsítására; Úszókarikák; Baseball kesztyűk ütőjátékosoknak [játékfelszerelések]; Térdvédők [sportcikkek].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Comandi per console di gioco; Anelli di pompaggio per gonfiare palle da gioco; Pompe da usare per palloni da gioco; Racchette da neve; Cinture per l'esercizio fisico, per il girovita; Braccioli per nuotare; Guanti per battitori [accessori per giochi]; Paraginocchi [articoli sportivi].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Žaidimų valdymo pultai; Pompų adatos (žaidimų kamuoliams pripūsti); Žaidimų kamuolių pompos; Sniegpadžiai (neklimpti einant per sniegą); Liekninantys juosmens pratimų diržai; Plaukimo ratai; Padavimo pirštinės [sportinių žaidimų reikmenys]; Antkeliai [sporto reikmenys].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Spēļu konsoļu vadības ierīces; Spēļu bumbu sūkņu adatas; Spēļu bumbu sūkņi; Sniega kurpes; Vidukļa apmēra samazināšanai paredzētas treniņu jostas; Peldriņķi; Sporta cimdi; Ceļgalu aizsargi sportistiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kontrolluri għall-konsoli tal-logħob; Labar għal pompi biex jintefħu l-blalen għal logħob; Pompi adatti speċjalment għall-użu mal-blalen għal-logħob; Żraben għas-silġ; Ċinturini tal-eżerċizzji għat-tnaqqis tal-wisa' tal-qadd; Ċrieki għall-għawm; Ingwanti tal-battituri [aċċessorji għal-logħob]; Kuxxinetti għall-protezzjoni tal-irkoppa (oġġetti tal-isports).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Besturingen voor spelconsoles; Naalden voor pompen voor opblaasbare ballen voor spellen; Pompen speciaal aangepast voor gebruik ballen voor spellen; Sneeuwschoenen; Trainingsgordels voor de taille om af te slanken; Zwembanden; Handschoenen voor slagmannen [spelaccessoires]; Kniebeschermers [sportartikelen].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kontrolery do konsoli gier; Igły do pompek do pompowania piłek do gier; Pompki specjalnie przystosowane do pompowania piłek do gier; Rakiety śnieżne; Pasy na talię, do ćwiczeń; Koła do pływania; Rękawice dla pałkarzy [akcesoria do gier]; Nakolanniki [artykuły sportowe].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Comandos para consolas de jogos; Agulhas para bombas para insuflar bolas de jogar; Bombas especialmente adaptadas para uso com bolas de jogar; Raquetes para a neve; Cintas adelgaçantes para a prática de exercício; Boias de natação; Luvas para batedores [acessórios de jogos]; Joelheiras [artigos de desporto].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Controlere pentru console de jocuri; Ace pentru pompe de umflat mingi de joc; Pompe adaptate special pentru a fi utilizate cu mingi de joc; Rachete de zăpadă; Curele pentru exerciţii pentru abdomen; Colaci de înot; Mănuși de protecție pentru jocuri cu crosă sau bâtă [accesorii de joc]; Apărători de genunchi [articole de sport].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ovládače hracích konzol; Ihly do púmp na nafukovanie hracích lôpt; Pumpy prispôsobené hracím loptám; Snežnice; Sťahovacie opasky na cvičenie; Plávacie kolesá; Kriketové rukavice; Chrániče na kolená (športový tovar).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Krmilniki za igralne konzole; Igle za tlačilke za napihovanje žog za igro; Tlačilke, posebej prilagojene za uporabo z žogami za igro; Snežne krplje; Vadbeni pasovi za zmanjšanje obsega pasu; Plavalni obroči; Rokavice udarjanje s palicami [pripomočki za igre]; Ščitniki za kolena [športni artikli].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Handkontroller för spelkonsoler; Munstycken till pumpar för pumpning av bollar för spel; Pumpar som särskilt anpassats för bollar för spel; Snöskor; Korsetter för midjeträning; Badringar; Slagspelshandskar; Knäskydd [sportartiklar].</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/083</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/155</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-17</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082693</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15066</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
