<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-15T09:20:14</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229235</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229235</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-12</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-15</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Dor Mibao</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162455998</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229235/000162455998.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>26.01.03</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.05</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.19</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.08</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.07</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>29.01.96</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>27</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Килими, черги и изтривалки; Килими, черги и изтривалки; Рогозки,черги, килимчета; Тръстикови рогозки; Килими, черги и изтривалки; Сламени рогозки; Килимчета за баня; Подови настилки; Изкуствен чим; Постелки за гимнастически салони; Постелки за гимнастически салони; Рогозки,черги, килимчета; Стелки и килими за превозни средства; Черги, рогозки, килимчета, които не се хлъзгат; Линолеум; Подложки на килими; Подови настилки от винил; Настилки от преплетени въжета за ски писти; Подови постелки, огнеупорни, за камини и скари; Постелки за йога; Рогозки,черги, килимчета; Гумени подложки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Koberce; Koberce; Rohože; Rákosové rohože; Koberce, předložky, rohožky; Slaměné rohože; Koupelnové rohožky a předložky; Podlahové krytiny; Umělé trávníky; Žíněnky; Žíněnky; Rohožky před dveře; Autokoberce; Protiskluzové podložky; Linoleum; Podložky pod koberce; Vinylové podlahové krytiny; Rohože z tkaného lana pro lyžařské sjezdové tratě; Nehořlavé rohože ke krbům a grilům; Podložky na jógu; Rohože; Gumové rohože.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tæpper; Tæpper; Måtter; Stråmåtter; Tæpper og måtter; Stråmåtter [halmmåtter]; Bademåtter; Gulvbeklædning; Kunstige græsplæner; Gymnastikmåtter; Gymnastikmåtter; Dørmåtter; Tæpper til automobiler; Skridhindrende måtter; Linoleum; Tæppeunderlag; Gulvbeklædning af vinyl; Måtter af vævet tovværk til skibakker; Brandhæmmende gulvmåtter til pejse og udendørs grill; Yogamåtter; Måtter; Gummimåtter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Vorleger; Vorleger; Matten; Schilfmatten; Teppiche, Vorleger und Matten; Strohmatten; Badematten; Bodenbeläge [Oberböden]; Kunstrasen; Turnmatten; Turnmatten; Fußmatten; Automatten; Gleitschutzteppiche; Linoleum; Teppichunterlagen; Bodenbeläge aus Vinyl; Matten für Skipisten, aus Seilen gewoben; Feuerfeste Bodenmatten für offene Kamine und Grills; Yogamatten; Matten; Gummimatten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Τάπητες, ψάθες και χαλάκια· Τάπητες, ψάθες και χαλάκια· Ψάθες· Καλάμι (Ψάθες από -)· Τάπητες, ψάθες και χαλάκια· Ψάθινα χαλάκια· Χαλάκια μπάνιου· Επιστρώσεις δαπέδου· Τεχνητός χλοοτάπητας· Τάπητες γυμναστικής· Τάπητες γυμναστικής· Ψάθες· Καλύμματα και χαλάκια οχημάτων· Αντιολισθητικοί τάπητες· Λινοτάπητες· Υποστρώματα χαλιών· Επικαλύψεις επιφανειών από βινύλιο· Τάπητες από υφασμένα σκοινιά για πίστες του σκι· Χαλάκια δαπέδου, πυράντοχα, για τζάκια και ψησταριές (μπάρμπεκιου)· Χαλάκια για γιόγκα· Ψάθες· Χαλάκια από καουτσούκ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Carpets; Rugs; Mats; Reed mats; Carpets, rugs and mats; Straw mats; Bath mats; Floor coverings; Artificial turf; Gymnastic mats; Gymnasium mats; Door mats; Carpets for automobiles; Non-slip mats; Linoleum; Carpet underlay; Vinyl floor coverings; Mats of woven rope for ski slopes; Floor mats, fire-resistant, for fireplaces and barbecues; Yoga mats; Floor mats; Rubber mats.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Alfombras; Alfombras; Esteras; Esteras de junco; Alfombras, alfombrillas y tapetes; Alfombrillas de paja; Alfombrillas de baño; Revestimientos de pisos; Césped artificial; Colchonetas de gimnasia; Colchonetas de gimnasia; Felpudos; Alfombrillas para automóviles; Alfombras antideslizantes; Linóleo; Bajo alfombras; Revestimientos de vinilo para suelos; Alfombras de cuerda trenzada para pistas de esquí; Alfombras ignífugas para chimeneas y barbacoas; Esteras de yoga; Esteras; Esteras de goma.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Vaibad; Vaibad; Matid; Roogmatid; Vaibad ja matid; Õlgmatid; Vannitoamatid; Põrandakatted; Tehismuru; Võimlemismatid; Võimlemismatid; Uksematid; Autovaibad; Libisemisvastased matid; Linoleum; Vaiba alusmaterjal; Vinüülpõrandakatted; Suusamägede punutud köismatid; Tulekindlad põrandamatid kaminate ja grillide juurde; Joogamatid; Matid; Kummimatid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Matot; Matot; Kynnysmatot; Kaislamatot; Matot; Olkimatot; Kylpyhuonematot; Lattianpäällysteet; Keinonurmi; Voimistelumatot; Voimistelumatot; Kynnysmatot; Ajoneuvojen matot; Liukuestematot; Linoleumi; Mattoalustat; Vinyyliset lattianpäällysteet; Köysimatot laskettelurinteisiin; Tulenkestävät edusmatot takkoja ja grillejä varten; Joogamatot; Kynnysmatot; Kumimatot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Carpettes; Carpettes; Nattes; Nattes de roseau; Tapis, paillassons et nattes; Nattes de paille; Tapis de bain; Revêtements de sol; Gazon artificiel; Tapis de gymnastique; Tapis de gymnastique; Paillassons; Tapis pour automobiles; Tapis antiglisse; Linoléum; Sous-tapis; Revêtements de sols en vinyle; Nattes de corde tissée pour pistes de ski; Tapis de sol antifeu pour cheminées et barbecues; Tapis de yoga; Nattes; Tapis en caoutchouc.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Tepisi, sagovi i otirači; Tepisi, sagovi i otirači; Otirači; Hasure od trske; Tepisi, sagovi i otirači; Slamnati podmetači; Prostirači pred kadama za kupanje; Prekrivači za podove; Umjetni travnjak; Gimnastički prostirači; Gimnastički prostirači; Otirači; Otirači i tepisi za vozila; Nesklizajući sagovi; Linoleum [voštano platno]; Podloge za sagove; Podne obloge od vinila; Hasure od užeta za skijaške staze; Podni podmetači, vatrootporni, za kamine i roštilje; Podloge za jogu; Otirači; Gumeni otirači.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szőnyegek, pokrócok, lábtörlők; Szőnyegek, pokrócok, lábtörlők; Lábtörlők [gyékények]; Nádszőnyegek; Szőnyegek, pokrócok, lábtörlők; Szalmaszőnyegek; Fürdőszobaszőnyegek, kilépők; Padlóburkolatok; Mesterséges gyep, műgyep; Tornaszőnyegek, tornatermi padlóburkolatok; Tornaszőnyegek, tornatermi padlóburkolatok; Lábtörlők [gyékények]; Szőnyegek járművekhez; Csúszásmentes gyékények; Linóleum; Szőnyegalátétek; Vinil padlóburkolatok; Szőnyegek fonott kötélből sípályákra; Tűzálló szőnyegek kandallókhoz és grillsütőkhöz; Jógaszőnyegek; Lábtörlők [gyékények]; Gumiszőnyegek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Tappetini; Tappetini; Stuoie; Stuoie di giunco; Tappeti, zerbini e stuoie; Tappetini in paglia; Tappeti da bagno; Rivestimenti di pavimenti; Prato artificiale; Tappeti per ginnastica; Tappeti per ginnastica; Pulisci-piedi [zerbini]; Tappetini per automobili; Tappeti antisdrucciolevoli; Tela cerata [linoleum]; Sottotappeti; Rivestimenti per pavimenti in vinile; Trecce di corde tessute per piste da sci; Tappetini ignifughi per caminetti o barbecue; Tappetini da yoga; Stuoie; Tappetini di gomma.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kilimai; Kilimai; Patiesalai; Dembliai; Kilimai, kilimėliai, patiesalai; Šiaudiniai kilimėliai; Vonios kambario patiesalai; Grindų dangos; Dirbtinės vejos; Gimnastikos salių patiesalai; Gimnastikos salių patiesalai; Priedurio patiesalai; Automobilių patiesalai; Neslidžios kiliminės dangos; Linoleumas; Pokilimiai; Vinilo grindų dangos; Slidžių trasų virveliniai dembliai; Ugniai atsparūs grindų kilimėliai (namų židiniams ir kepimo rėmams); Jogos kilimėliai; Patiesalai; Guminiai patiesalai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Paklāji, grīdsegas un pīteņi; Paklāji, grīdsegas un pīteņi; Mašas; Niedru paklājiņi; Paklāji, grīdsegas un pīteņi; Salmu paklāji; Vannas istabu paklājiņi; Grīdas segumi; Mākslīgais zālājs; Vingrošanas paklājiņi; Vingrošanas paklājiņi; Mašas; Paklāji un grīdsegas transportlīdzekļiem; Neslīdoši paklāji; Linolejs; Paklāju pamatnes; Vinila grīdas segumi; Austu auklu paklājiņi slēpošanas trasēm; Paklājiņi, ugunsizturīgi, kamīnam un grilam; Jogas paklāji; Mašas; Gumijas paklājiņi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Twapet; Twapet; Twapet żgħar; Twapet żgħar tal-qasab; Twapet; Tapiti żgħar tat-tibna; Twapet tal-banju; Kisi tal-paviment; Ħaxix artifiċjali; Twapet tal-ġinnastika; Twapet tal-ġinnastika; Twapet żgħar; Twapet għall-vetturi; Twapet li ma jiżolqux; Linolju; Tapit (Materjali li jitwaħħlu mal-qiegħ tat- -); Kisi tal-art tal-vinil; Twapet tal-ħabel minsuġ għaż-żrieżaq tal-iski; Twapet tal-art, reżistenti għan-nar, għal fuklari u barbikjus; Mattijiet tal-joga; Twapet żgħar; Twapet tal-lastku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Vloerkleden; Vloerkleden; Matten; Rietmatten; Tapijten. vloerkleden en matten; Stromatten; Badmatten; Vloerbedekking; Kunstgras; Gymnastiekmatten; Gymnastiekmatten; Deurmatten; Automatten; Antislipmatten; Linoleum; Ondertapijt; Vloerbedekking van vinyl; Matten van geweven touw voor skipistes; Vloermatten, vuurbestendig, voor open haarden en barbecues; Yogamatten; Matten; Matten (Rubberen -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dywany, chodniki i maty; Dywany, chodniki i maty; Maty; Maty z trzciny; Dywany, chodniki i maty; Słomiane maty; Maty łazienkowe [dywaniki]; Pokrycia podłogowe; Darń sztuczna; Maty gimnastyczne; Maty gimnastyczne; Maty; Dywaniki i maty samochodowe; Maty antypoślizgowe; Linoleum; Podkładki pod dywany; Pokrycia podłogowe winylowe; Maty z plecionej liny na stoki narciarskie; Maty podłogowe, ognioodporne, do kominków i grillów; Maty do jogi; Maty; Maty z kauczuku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Carpetes; Carpetes; Esteiras [tapetes]; Esteiras de cana [esteiras de junco]; Tapetes, carpetes e esteiras; Esteiras de palha; Tapetes de banho; Revestimentos para chão; Relva artificial; Tapetes para ginástica; Tapetes para ginástica; Tapetes de entrada; Carpetes para automóveis; Tapetes anti-deslizantes; Linóleo; Protetores de carpetes; Revestimentos para chão em vinil; Esteiras de corda trançada para pistas de ski; Tapetes de chão, resistentes a fogo, para lareiras e churrascos; Esteiras para ioga; Esteiras [tapetes]; Esteiras de borracha.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Covoare, carpete şi preşuri; Covoare, carpete şi preşuri; Covoare pentru uşă; Rogojini din stuf; Covoare, carpete şi preşuri; Rogojine de paie; Covoraşe de baie; Învelitori pentru pardoseli; Gazon artificial; Saltele de gimnastică; Saltele de gimnastică; Covoare pentru uşă; Preşuri şi covoare de maşină; Covoare antiglisante; Linoleum; Substrat de covoare; Căptuşeli de răşină din vinil pentru pardoseli; Covoare din sfoară ţesută pentru pârtiile de schi; Preşuri, rezistente la foc, pentru şemineuri şi grătare; Covoraşe de yoga; Covoare pentru uşă; Covoare de cauciuc.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Koberce; Koberce; Rohožky; Trstinové rohože; Koberce, koberčeky a rohožky; Slamené rohožky; Kúpeľňové koberčeky (rohožky); Podlahové krytiny; Umelé trávniky; Gymnastické žinenky; Gymnastické žinenky; Dverové rohožky; Koberčeky do automobilov; Protišmykové rohože; Linoleum; Kobercové podložky; Vinylové podlahové krytiny; Rohože z tkaných povrazov na lyžiarske svahy; Ohňovzdorné predložky ku kozubom a grilom; Podložky na jogu; Rohožky; Gumené rohožky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Preproge, tekači in predpražniki; Preproge, tekači in predpražniki; Predpražniki; Rogoznice iz trsja; Preproge, tekači in predpražniki; Slamnata rogoznica; Kopalniške preproge; Talne obloge; Umetna trata; Blazine za telovadnico; Blazine za telovadnico; Predpražniki; Predpražniki in preproge za vozila; Protizdrsne preproge; Linolej; Podloge za preproge; Vinilne talne obloge; Preproge iz pletene vrvi za smučišča; Predpražniki, ognjevarni, za kamine in žare; Blazine za jogo; Predpražniki; Predpražniki iz gume.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Mattor, inkluderande dörrmattor och heltäckningsmattor; Mattor, inkluderande dörrmattor och heltäckningsmattor; Mattor; Vassmattor; Mattor, inkluderande dörrmattor och heltäckningsmattor; Halmmattor; Badkarsmattor; Golvbeläggningar; Konstgjort gräs; Gymnastiksalsmattor; Gymnastiksalsmattor; Mattor; Fordonsmattor; Halkningsförhindrande mattor; Linoleum; Mattunderlägg; Golvbeläggningar av vinyl; Mattor av vävt rep för skidbackar (underlag); Golvmattor, brandsäkra, för öppna spisar och grillar; Yogamattor; Mattor; Gummimattor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/105</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/176</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-15</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081950</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>37556</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
