<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-10T08:16:13</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229293</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229293</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-08</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-10</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162459976</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229293/000162459976.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>28.03</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Медицински апарати и инструменти; Изкуствено дишане (Апарати за -); Респираторни маски за изкуствено дишане; Терапевтични маски за лице; Глюкомер; Песари; Облекло специално за операционни зали; Оборудване за физиотерапия; Слухови апарати; Подложки за медицински цели; Надуваеми подложки за медицински цели; Маски за медицински персонал; Охлаждащи пластири за медицински цели; Санитарни маски за медицински цели; Високофилтърни хирургични маски; Бебешки шишета; Биберони за шишета за хранене; Изкуствена кожа за хирургически цели; Чорапи за разширени вени; Пристягащи облекла.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Lékařské přístroje a nástroje; Přístroje pro umělé dýchání; Respirační masky pro umělé dýchání; Terapeutické obličejové masky; Glykemická pravítka; Pesary; Oděvy určené pro operační sály; Fyzioterapeutické přístroje; Naslouchátka; Podušky pro lékařské účely; Nafukovací podušky pro lékařské účely; Roušky pro lékařský personál; Chladivé náplasti pro lékařské účely; Hygienické masky pro lékařské účely; Chirurgické masky vysokofiltrační; Dětské láhve; Dudlíky na kojenecké lahve; Umělá kůže pro chirurgické účely; Punčochy na křečové žíly; Kompresní oděvy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Medicinske apparater og instrumenter; Apparater til kunstigt åndedræt; Respirationsmasker til kunstig respiration; Terapeutiske ansigtsmasker; Indretninger til måling af blodsukker; Pessarer; Beklædning specielt til operationsstuer; Udstyr til fysisk terapi; Hjælpemidler for hørelsen; Puder til medicinske formål; Oppustelige puder til medicinske formål; Masker til brug for medicinsk personel; Kølende plastre til medicinske formål; Sanitære masker til medicinske formål; Højfiltrerende masker til kirurgiske formål; Sutteflasker; Sutter til sutteflasker; Kunstig hud til kirurgiske formål; Strømper mod åreknuder; Kompressionsbeklædning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Medizinische Apparate und Instrumente; Apparate für die künstliche Beatmung; Atemmasken für künstliche Beatmung; Therapeutische Gesichtsmasken; Blutzucker-Lineale; Pessare; OP-Kleidung; Geräte für physikalische Therapie; Hörgeräte; Kissen für medizinische Zwecke; Luftkissen für medizinische Zwecke; Masken für medizinisches Personal; Kühlpflaster für medizinische Zwecke; Mundschutz für medizinische Zwecke; Chirurgische Masken mit hoher Filterwirkung; Babyflaschen; Flaschensauger; Künstliche Haut für chirurgische Zwecke; Krampfaderstrümpfe; Kompressionsbekleidung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ιατρικά (Συσκευές και όργανα -)· Αναπνευστήρες· Αναπνευστικές μάσκες για τεχνητή αναπνοή· Θεραπευτικές μάσκες προσώπου· Συσκευή μέτρησης της γλυκαιμίας· Πεσσοί· Ενδύματα (Ειδικά για χειρουργεία -)· Εξοπλισμός φυσικοθεραπείας· Βοηθήματα ακοής· Μαξιλάρια για χρήση ιατρική· Αέρα (Μαξιλάρια -) για ιατρική χρήση· Μάσκες για το ιατρικό προσωπικό· Ψυκτικά έμπλαστρα για ιατρική χρήση· Μάσκες υγιεινής για ιατρική χρήση· Χειρουργικές μάσκες υψηλής διήθησης· Υποδοχείς για θήλαστρα· Θηλές για μπιμπερό· Δέρμα τεχνητό για χρήση χειρουργική· Κάλτσες για κιρσούς· Ενδύματα συμπίεσης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">medical apparatus and instruments; apparatus for artificial respiration; respiratory masks for artificial respiration; therapeutic facial masks; glucometers; pessaries; clothing especially for operating rooms; physiotherapy apparatus; hearing aids; cushions for medical purposes; air cushions for medical purposes; masks for use by medical personnel; cooling patches for medical purposes; sanitary masks for medical purposes; high filter surgical masks; feeding bottles; feeding bottle teats; artificial skin for surgical purposes; stockings for varices; compression garments.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos e instrumentos médicos; Aparatos para la respiración artificial; Mascarillas respiratorias para la respiración artificial; Máscaras faciales terapéuticas; Medidores de glucosa en sangre; Pesarios; Ropa especial para quirófano; Equipos de terapia física; Audífonos de corrección auditiva; Cojines para uso médico; Cojines de aire para uso médico; Mascarillas para personal médico; Parches de enfriamiento para uso médico; Mascarillas sanitarias para uso médico; Mascarillas quirúrgicas de alta filtración; Biberones; Tetinas de biberones; Piel artificial para uso quirúrgico; Medias para varices; Prendas de compresión.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meditsiiniseadmed ja -riistad; Kunstliku hingamise aparaadid; Kunstliku hingamise respiraatormaskid; Ravinäomaskid; Glükomeetrid; Pessaarid, emakarõngad; Eririietus operatsioonisaalides viibimiseks, operatsiooniriietus; Füsioteraapiaseadmed; Kuuldeaparaadid; Meditsiinilised padjad; Meditsiinilised õhkpadjad; Maskid meditsiinipersonalile; Jahutavad meditsiinilised geelplaastrid; Meditsiinilised hügieenilised maskid; Peenfiltreerivad kirurgimaskid; Lutipudelid; Pudelilutid; Kirurgiline tehisnahk; Veenilaiendisukad; Surverõivad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Tekohengityslaitteet; Hengitysnaamarit tekohengitykseen; Hoitavat kasvonaamiot; Verensokerin viitearvokortit; Pessaarit; Vaatteet leikkaussaleja varten, erikoisvalmisteiset; Fysioterapiassa käytettävät välineet; Kuulolaitteet; Tyynyt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Ilmatyynyt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Suojanaamarit lääkintähenkilökuntaa varten; Viilentävät tyynyt lääkintätarkoituksiin; Saniteettinaamarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Vaimennussuodattimet kirurgisiin kasvosuojuksiin; Tuttipullojen säilytysastiat; Tuttipullojen tutit; Keinoiho ihonsiirtoa varten; Sukat suonikohjujen hoitoon; Kompressiovaatteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils et instruments médicaux; Appareils pour la respiration artificielle; Masques respiratoires pour la respiration artificielle; Masques thérapeutiques à porter sur le visage; Règles à glycémie; Pessaires; Vêtements spéciaux pour salles d'opération; Équipement de thérapie physique; Appareils auditifs; Coussins à usage médical; Coussins à air à usage médical; Masques utilisés par le personnel médical; Patchs refroidissants à usage médical; Masques hygiéniques à usage médical; Masques chirurgicaux avec filtres à grand débit; Supports pour biberons; Tétines de biberons; Peau artificielle à usage chirurgical; Bas pour les varices; Vêtements de compression.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Medicinski uređaji i instrumenti; Uređaji za umjetno disanje; Respiracijske maske za umjetno disanje; Terapeutske maske za lice; Glukometri; Pesari; Specijalna odjeća za operacijske dvorane; Oprema za fizikalnu terapiju; Slušna pomagala; Jastuci za medicinske potrebe; Zračni jastuci za medicinske potrebe; Maske za medicinsko osoblje; Flasteri za hlađenje, za medicinske potrebe; Sanitarne maske za medicinske svrhe; Kirurške maske visoke filtracije; Spremnici dječjih bočica; Dude za bočice; Umjetna koža za kirurške potrebe; Čarape za proširene vene; Kompresijska odjeća.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Gyógyászati készülékek és eszközök; Mesterséges lélegeztető készülékek; Légzőmaszkok mesterséges lélegeztetéshez; Terápiás arcmaszkok; Vércukorszint-mérők; Pesszáriumok; Speciális műtőruházat; Fizikoterápiás készülékek; Hallókészülékek; Párnák gyógyászati használatra; Levegővel töltött párnák gyógyászati célokra; Maszkok egészségügyi személyzet általi használatra; Hűtőtapaszok gyógyászati célokra; Gyógyászati célú egészségügyi maszkok; Nagy hatékonyságú sebészeti szűrőmaszkok; Cumisüvegtartók; Cumik cumisüvegekhez; Mesterséges bőr sebészeti használatra; Visszér harisnyák; Kompressziós ruhák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi e strumenti medici; Apparecchi per la respirazione artificiale; Maschere respiratorie per la respirazione artificiale; Maschere facciali terapeutiche; Strisce misura glicemia; Pessari; Vestiti speciali per sale operatorie; Attrezzatura per terapie fisiche; Sussidi per l'udito; Cuscini per uso medico; Cuscini ad aria per uso medico; Maschere utilizzate dal personale medico; Cerotti freddi per scopi medici; Maschere igieniche per uso medico; Maschere ad alta filtrazione per uso chirurgico; Recipienti per biberon; Tettarelle per poppatoi; Pelle artificiale per uso chirurgico; Calze per le vene varicose; Indumenti di compressione.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Medicinos aparatai ir instrumentai; Dirbtinio kvėpavimo aparatai; Respiratorių kaukės (dirbtinio kvėpavimo reikmėms); Terapinės veido kaukės; Glikemijos liniuotės; Pesarai; Specialieji operaciniai drabužiai; Fizioterapijos įranga; Klausos aparatai; Medicininės pagalvėlės; Pripučiamos pagalvėlės (medicinos reikmėms); Kaukės medicinos personalui; Vėsinantys pleistrai (medicinos reikmėms); Sanitarinės kaukės medicinos reikmėms; Aukštos filtracijos chirurginės kaukės; Žindymo buteliukai; Buteliukų žindukai; Dirbtinė oda (chirurgijos reikmėms); Kojinės nuo venų išsiplėtimo; Kompresiniai drabužiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Medicīniskā aparatūra un instrumenti; Mākslīgās elpināšanas ierīces; Respiratoru maskas, kas paredzētas mākslīgajai elpināšanai; Ārstnieciskas sejas maskas; Glikometri; Pesāriji (dzemdes gredzeni); Speciālie apģērbi operāciju zālēm; Fizikālās terapijas iekārtas; Dzirdes aparāti; Medicīnā izmantojamie spilveni; Gaisa spilveni medicīniskai lietošanai; Medicīnas personālam paredzētās maskas; Atvēsinoši plāksteri medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Sanitārās maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Ķirurģiskās maskas ar stipru filtru; Barošanas pudelīšu turētāji; Barošanas pudeļu knupīši; Mākslīgā āda ķirurģiskiem nolūkiem; Zeķes varikozām vēnām; Kompresijas apģērbs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat u strumenti mediċi; Apparat għar-respirazzjoni artifiċjali; Maskri respiratorji għan-nifs artifiċjali; Masks tal-wiċċ terapewtiċi; Glukometri; Pessarji; Ilbies speċjali għas-swali tal-operazzjonijiet; Tagħmir għat-terapija fiżika; Mezzi għall-għajnuna fis-smigħ; Kuxxini għal skopijiet mediċi; Kuxxini tal-arja għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri għal personal mediku; Irqajja' tat-tkessiħ għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri sanitarji għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri kirurġiċi b'filtru qawwi; Reċipjenti bħala fliexken għat-tmigħ tat-trabi; Gażażi tal-fliexken tal-ħalib; Ġilda artifiċjali għal skopijiet kirurġiċi; Kalzetti twal għall-variċi; Ilbies tal-kompressjoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Medische apparaten en instrumenten; Apparaten voor kunstmatige ademhaling; Ademhalingsmaskers voor kunstmatige beademing; Therapeutische gezichtsmaskers; Glykemiemeters; Pessaria; Operatiekleding; Apparaten voor lichamelijke behandeling; Hoorapparaten; Kussens voor medisch gebruik; Luchtkussens voor medisch gebruik; Maskers te gebruiken door medisch personeel; Koelende patches voor medische doeleinden; Hygiënische maskers voor medische doeleinden; Chirurgische maskers met hoge filtercapaciteiten; Reservoirs voor zuigflessen; Spenen voor zuigflessen; Kunsthuid voor geneeskundig gebruik; Kousen tegen spataderen; Compressiekleding.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia i instrumenty medyczne; Urządzenia do sztucznego oddychania; Maski do sztucznego oddychania; Maski terapeutyczne na twarz; Glukometry; Pesaria; Odzież specjalna używana w salach operacyjnych; Urządzenia i przyrządy do fizjoterapii; Aparaty słuchowe; Poduszki do celów medycznych; Dmuchane poduszki do celów medycznych; Maski stosowane przez personel medyczny; Plastry chłodzące do celów medycznych; Maski sanitarne do celów medycznych; Maski chirurgiczne z wysokim współczynnikiem filtracji; Pojemniki na butelki do karmienia; Smoczki do butelek do karmienia; Sztuczna skóra do celów chirurgicznych; Pończochy przeciwżylakowe; Odzież kompresyjna.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos e instrumentos médicos; Aparelhos para a respiração artificial; Máscaras para respiração artificial; Máscaras faciais terapêuticas; Medidores de glicemia; Pessários; Vestuário especial para salas de operação; Equipamento de fisioterapia; Auxiliares auditivos; Almofadas para uso medicinal; Almofadas de ar para uso médico; Máscaras para pessoal médico; Bandas de resfriamento para uso clínico; Máscaras higiénicas para uso médico; Máscaras cirúrgicas de elevada filtração; Biberons [biberões]; Tetinas de biberão para alimentação; Pele artificial para cirurgia; Meias para as varizes; Compressas sob a forma de vestuário.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate şi instrumente medicale; Respiraţie artificială (Aparate pentru -); Măşti respiratorii, altele decât cele pentru respiraţie artificială; Măști faciale terapeutice; Aparate de reglare a glicemiei; Pesare; Haine speciale pentru săli de operaţie; Echipament pentru exerciţii fizice; Dispozitive auditive; Perne de uz medical; Perne cu aer pentru uz medical; Măşti utilizate de personalul medical; Bandaje de răcire pentru uz medical; Măşti sanitare de uz medical; Măşti chirurgicale cu filtru de înaltă protecţie; Recipiente pentru biberoane; Tetine de biberon; Piele artificială pentru uz chirurgical; Ciorapi pentru varice; Articole de îmbrăcăminte de compresie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Lekárske prístroje a nástroje; Umelé dýchanie (Prístroje na -); Dýchacie masky na umelé dýchanie; Terapeutické masky na tvár; Stupnice na meranie krvného cukru; Pesary; Odevy do operačných sál; Fyzioterapeutické zariadenia; Načúvacie pomôcky; Podušky na lekárske použitie; Nafukovacie podušky na lekárske použitie; Rúška (pre nemocničný personál); Chladiace náplasti na lekárske účely; Sanitárne masky na lekárske účely; Chirurgické masky s vysokoúčinným filtrom; Detské fľaše; Cumle na detské fľaše; Umelá koža na chirurgické použitie; Pančuchy na kŕčové žily; Sťahovacie oblečenie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Medicinski aparati in instrumenti; Aparati za umetno dihanje; Dihalne maske za umetno dihanje; Terapevtske maske za obraz; Merilniki krvnega sladkorja; Pesarji; Posebna oblačila za operacijske prostore; Naprave za fizikalno terapijo; Slušni pripomočki; Blazine za medicinske namene; Zračne blazine za medicinske namene; Maske za medicinsko osebje; Hladilni obliži za medicinske namene; Higienske maske za medicinske namene; Kirurške maske z močnimi filtri; Posodice za stekleničke za hranjenje; Cuclji za stekleničke za hranjenje dojenčkov; Umetna koža za kirurške namene; Nogavice za krčne žile; Kompresijska oblačila.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Medicinska apparater och instrument; Apparater för konstgjord andning; Andningsmasker för konstgjord andning; Terapeutiska ansiktsmasker; Glykemisk mätsticka; Pessar; Kläder för användning i operationsrum; Utrustning för fysioterapi; Hörselhjälpmedel; Kuddar för medicinska ändamål; Luftdynor för medicinska ändamål; Munskydd för medicinsk personal; Kylande plåster för medicinska ändamål; Sanitetsmasker för medicinska ändamål; Starka filter för kirurgiska masker; Nappflaskor; Nappar för nappflaskor; Konstgjord hud för kirurgiska ändamål; Strumpor för åderbråck; Kompressionskläder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/101</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/173</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081987</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>956</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
