<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-12T08:41:12</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229850</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229850</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-11</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-12</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>JIANDI</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162504965</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229850/000162504965.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>26.05.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.05.22</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Защитни работни маски за лице; Защитни очила; Защитни маски; Защитно облекло против химическо въздействие; Компютърни програми, записани; Апарати за разпознаване на лицето; Смарт часовници; Компютъризирани часовници с разпознаване на пръстови отпечатъци; Термометри, с изключение на такива за медицински цели; Инсталации, предпазващи от кражба, електрически; Защитни маски срещу прах.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pracovní ochranné obličejové štíty; Bezpečnostní brýle; Ochranné masky; Oděvy na ochranu proti chemickým látkám; Počítačový software (nahraný); Zařízení na rozpoznávání obličeje; Chytré hodinky; Počítačové časovače s rozpoznáváním otisků prstů; Teploměry, ne lékařské; Elektrická zabezpečovací zařízení proti krádeži; Masky proti prachu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beskyttende ansigtsskærme til arbejdere; Beskyttelsesbriller; Beskyttelsesmasker; Beskyttelsesbeklædning mod kemikalier; Software til computere, optaget; Apparater til ansigtsgenkendelse; Smartwatches; Computerbaseret tidsregistrering med fingeraftryksgenkendelse; Termometre [ikke til medicinsk brug]; Tyverihindrende installationer, elektriske; Støvmasker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gesichtsschutzschirme für Arbeiter; Korbbrille; Schutzmasken; Bekleidung zum Schutz gegen Chemikalien; Gespeicherte Computersoftware; Geräte zur Gesichtserkennung; Smartwatches; Computerisierte Stempeluhren mit Fingerabdruckerkennung; Thermometer, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Elektrische Diebstahlalarmanlagen; Staubschutzmasken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Προστατευτικές ασπίδες προσώπου· Προστατευτικά γυαλιά· Προστατευτικές μάσκες· Ενδύματα για προστασία από χημικές ουσίες· Η/Υ (Προγράμματα -) εγγεγραμμένα· Συσκευές αναγνώρισης προσώπου· Έξυπνα ρολόγια χειρός· Ηλεκτρονικοποιημένα ρολόγια χρονομέτρησης με αναγνώριση δακτυλικών αποτυπωμάτων· Θερμόμετρα όχι ιατρικά· Αντικλεπτικές εγκαταστάσεις ηλεκτρικές· Προσωπίδες προστασίας από τη σκόνη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Workmen's protective face-shields; goggles; protective masks; clothing for protection against chemicals; recorded computer software; facial recognition apparatus; smart watches; computerized time clocks with fingerprint recognition; thermometers, not for medical purposes; theft prevention installations, electric; dust masks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pantallas de protección facial para obreros; Gafas protectoras; Máscaras de protección; Ropa para la protección química; Software [programas grabados]; Aparatos de reconocimiento facial; Relojes inteligentes; Relojes de fichar informatizados con función de reconocimiento dactilar; Termómetros que no sean para uso médico; Instalaciones eléctricas antirrobo; Máscaras antipolvo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tööliste näokaitsesirmid; Ohutusprillid; Kaitsemaskid; Kemikaalikindlad kaitserõivad; Salvestatud arvutitarkvara; Näotuvastusseadmed; Nutikellad; Sõrmejälgede tuvastamise süsteemiga arvutipõhised ajakellad; Termomeetrid, v.a meditsiinilised; Elektrilised vargust ennetavad seadmed; Tolmumaskid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Työntekijöiden kasvonsuojukset; Turvasuojalasit; Suojanaamarit; Suojavaatteet kemiallista altistusta vastaan; Tietokoneohjelmat [tallennetut]; Kasvojentunnistuslaitteet; Älykellot; Tietokoneistetut kellokorttilaitteet, joissa on sormenjäljen tunnistus; Lämpömittarit, ei-lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Varkaudenestolaitteet, sähkökäyttöiset; Pölysuojanaamarit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Écrans de protection faciaux pour ouvriers; Lunettes de protection; Masques de protection; Vêtements de protection contre les produits chimiques; Logiciels [programmes enregistrés]; Appareils de reconnaissance faciale; Montres intelligentes; Pointeuses informatisées à reconnaissance digitale; Thermomètres, non à usage médical; Installations électriques pour préserver du vol; Masques anti-poussières.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Zasloni za zaštitu lica radnika; Zaštitne naočale; Zaštitne maske; Odjeća za zaštitu od kemikalija; Računalni programi [snimljeni]; Uređaji za prepoznavanje lica; Pametni ručni satovi; Kompjuterizirani uređaji za računanje radnog vremena s prepoznavanjem otiska prsta; Toplomjeri nisu za medicinsku uporabu; Električne instalacije protiv krađe; Maske za zaštitu od prašine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Munkavédelmi arcvédő pajzsok; Védőszemüvegek; Védőálarcok/-maszkok; Vegyszerek elleni védőruházat; Számítógépes programok, rögzített; Arcfelismerő készülékek; Okoskarórák; Ujjlenyomat-felismerő számítógépes blokkoló órák; Hőmérők, nem gyógyászati használatra; Lopásgátló berendezések, elektromos; Porvédő maszkok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Schermi per la protezione del viso degli operai; Occhiali di protezione; Maschere di protezione; Abiti per la protezione chimica; Software [programmi registrati]; Apparecchi per il riconoscimento del viso; Orologi intelligenti [smartwatch]; Orologi da controllo computerizzati con riconoscimento delle impronte digitali; Termometri non per uso medico; Impianti di allarme antifurto elettrici; Maschere per la polvere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Apsauginiai darbininkų veido skydeliai; Apsauginiai akiniai; Apsauginės kaukės; Apsauginiai drabužiai nuo chemikalų; Kompiuterių programinė įranga [įrašyta]; Veidų atpažinimo įranga; Išmanieji laikrodžiai; Kompiuterizuoti laikrodžiai su pirštų atspaudų atpažinimo funkcija; Termometrai (išskyrus medicininius); Elektriniai įrenginiai nuo vagystės; Kaukės nuo dulkių.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Aizsargmaskas strādniekiem; Brilles acu aizsardzībai; Aizsargmaskas; Aizsargapģērbs pret ķīmiskām vielām; Ierakstīta programmatūra; Sejas atpazīšanas ierīces; Viedie rokaspulksteņi; Datorizēta darba laika uzskaites iekārta ar pirkstu nospieduma atpazīšanu; Termometri, ne medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Elektriskās iekārtas zādzību novēršanai; Putekļu maskas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Lqugħ protettiv tal-wiċċ għal ħaddiema; Nuċċalijiet protettivi; Maskri protettivi; Ilbies għall-protezzjoni mis-sustanzi kimiċi; Programmi tal-kompjuter irrekordjati; Apparat għar-rikonoxximent tal-uċuħ; Arloġġi tal-idejn tat-tip smart; Arloġġi tal-ħin kompjuterizzati li jagħrfu l-marki tas-swaba'; Termometri [mhux għal skopijiet mediċi]; Installazzjonijiet li jipprevjenu s-serq, tal-elettriku; Maskri tat-trab.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Gezichtsbeschermers [schermen] voor werklieden; Beschermende brillen; Beschermende maskers; Kleding voor bescherming tegen chemische stoffen; Software [geregistreerde programma's]; Apparatuur voor gezichtsherkenning; Smartwatches; Geautomatiseerde stempelklokken met vingerafdrukherkenning; Thermometers, niet voor medisch gebruik; Elektrische installaties voor diefstalpreventie; Stofmaskers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Osłony ochronne na twarz dla robotników; Okulary ochronne; Maski ochronne; Odzież do ochrony przed działaniem środków chemicznych; Programy komputerowe nagrane; Urządzenia rozpoznające twarz; Zegarki inteligentne; Skomputeryzowane zegary z funkcją rozpoznawania linii papilarnych; Termometry nie do celów medycznych; Elektryczne instalacje przeciwwłamaniowe; Maski przeciwpyłowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Telas para a proteção do rosto de operários; Óculos de proteção; Máscaras de proteção; Vestuário para a proteção contra substâncias químicas; Software [programas de computador gravados]; Aparelhos de reconhecimento facial; Relógios inteligentes; Relógios de ponto informatizados com reconhecimento de impressão digital; Termómetros, não sendo para uso médico; Instalações elétricas antirroubo; Máscaras contra o pó.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Măști de protecție pentru muncitori; Ochelari de protecție; Măști de protecție; Îmbrăcăminte de protecție contra substanțelor chimice; Programe de calculator înregistrate; Aparate de recunoaștere facială; Ceasuri inteligente; Ceasuri computerizate cu funcție de recunoaștere a amprentei; Termometre, altele decât cele de uz medical; Instalații electrice antifurt; Măști de protecție împotriva prafului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Tvárové štíty (ochranné pracovné prostriedky); Bezpečnostné okuliare; Ochranné masky; Ochranné odevy proti chemikáliám; Počítačový softvér (nahraté počítačové programy); Prístroje na rozpoznávanie tváre; Inteligentné hodinky; Počítačové hodiny s rozpoznávaním odtlačkov prstov; Teplomery (nie na lekárske použitie); Elektrické zariadenia proti krádežiam; Masky proti prachu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zaščita za obraz za delavce; Zaščitni naočniki; Zaščitne maske; Oblačila za zaščito pred kemikalijami; Računalniški programi, posneti; Naprave za prepoznavanje obraza; Pametne zapestne ure; Računalniška ura s prepoznavanjem prstnih odtisov; Termometri, ne za medicinske namene; Protivlomne napeljave, električne; Maske za zaščito pred prahom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Skyddsvisir för arbetare; Skyddsglasögon; Skyddsmasker; Skyddskläder mot kemikalier; Registrerade datormjukvaror; Apparater för ansiktsigenkänning; Smarta klockor; Datoriserade klockor med fingeravtryckssensorer; Termometrar, inte för medicinska ändamål; Elektriska stöldförhindrande installationer; Skyddsmask mot damm.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Респираторни маски за изкуствено дишане; Маски за дишане за медицинска употреба; Респиратори за медицински цели; Инфрачервени термометри за медицински цели; Цели Ортопедични обувки за медицински цели; Ръкавици за медицински цели; Санитарни маски за медицински цели; Маски за лице за медицинска употреба; Защитно облекло за медицински цели; Секс играчки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Respirační masky pro umělé dýchání; Respirační masky k lékařskému použití; Respirátory k lékařskému použití; Infračervené teploměry pro lékařské účely; Boty pro lékařské účely; Rukavice pro lékařské účely; Hygienické masky pro lékařské účely; Roušky k lékařskému použití; Ochranné oděvy pro lékařské účely; Erotické hračky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Respirationsmasker til kunstig respiration; Åndedrætsværn til medicinske formål; Respiratorer til medicinske formål; Infrarøde termometre til medicinske formål; Støvler til medicinske formål; Handsker til medicinske formål; Sanitære masker til medicinske formål; Ansigtsmasker til medicinske formål; Beskyttelsesbeklædning til medicinske formål; Sexlegetøj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Atemmasken für künstliche Beatmung; Atemmasken für medizinische Zwecke; Atemgeräte für medizinische Zwecke; Infrarotthermometer für medizinische Zwecke; Stiefel für medizinische Zwecke; Handschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Mundschutz für medizinische Zwecke; Gesichtsmasken für medizinische Zwecke; Schutzbekleidung für medizinische Zwecke; Sexspielzeug.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αναπνευστικές μάσκες για τεχνητή αναπνοή· Αναπνευστικές μάσκες για ιατρικές χρήσεις· Αναπνευστήρες για ιατρική χρήση· Θερμόμετρα υπερύθρων για ιατρική χρήση· Μπότες για χρήση ιατρική· Γάντια ιατρικής χρήσης· Μάσκες υγιεινής για ιατρική χρήση· Μάσκες προσώπου για ιατρική χρήση· Προστατευτικά ενδύματα για ιατρική χρήση· Σεξουαλικά παιχνίδια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Respiratory masks for artificial respiration; respiratory masks for medical purposes; respirators for medical purposes; infrared thermometers for medical purposes; boots for medical purposes; gloves for medical purposes; sanitary masks for medical purposes; face masks for medical use; protective clothing for medical purposes; sex toys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Mascarillas respiratorias para la respiración artificial; Mascarillas respiratorias para uso médico; Respiradores para uso médico; Termómetros de infrarrojos para uso médico; Botas para uso médico; Guantes para uso médico; Mascarillas sanitarias para uso médico; Máscaras faciales para uso médico; Ropa protectora para fines médicos; Juguetes sexuales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kunstliku hingamise respiraatormaskid; Meditsiinilised hingamismaskid; Meditsiiniotstarbelised respiraatorid; Meditsiinilised infrapunatermomeetrid; Meditsiinilised saapad; Meditsiinilised kindad; Meditsiinilised hügieenilised maskid; Meditsiinilised näomaskid; Meditsiinis kasutatavad kaitserõivad; Sekslelud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hengitysnaamarit tekohengitykseen; Hengitysnaamarit lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Hengityslaitteet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Infrapunakuumemittarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Saappaat lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Käsineet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Saniteettinaamarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Kasvonaamarit lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Suojavaatteet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Seksilelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Masques respiratoires pour la respiration artificielle; Masques respiratoires à usage médical; Respirateurs à usage médical; Thermomètres à infrarouges à usage médical; Bottes à usage médical; Gants à usage médical; Masques d'hygiène à usage médical; Masques pour le visage à usage médical; Vêtements de protection à usage médical; Jouets sexuels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Respiracijske maske za umjetno disanje; Maske za disanje za medicinske namjene; Respiratori za medicinske namjene; Infracrveni termometri za medicinske potrebe; Čizme za medicinske potrebe; Rukavice za medicinsku uporabu; Sanitarne maske za medicinske svrhe; Maske za lice za medicinsku uporabu; Zaštitna odjeća za medicinske namjene; Seksualne igračke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Légzőmaszkok mesterséges lélegeztetéshez; Légzőmaszkok orvosi célokra; Lélegeztető készülékek orvosi használatra; Infravörös hőmérők gyógyászati célokra; Csizmák gyógyászati használatra; Kesztyűk gyógyászati használatra; Gyógyászati célú egészségügyi maszkok; Arcmaszkok gyógyászati használatra; Védőruházat orvosi célokra; Szexuális játékszerek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Maschere respiratorie per la respirazione artificiale; Maschere respiratorie per uso medico; Respiratori per uso medico; Termometri a raggi infrarossi per uso medico; Stivali per uso medico; Guanti per uso medico; Maschere igieniche per uso medico; Maschere per il viso per uso medico; Abbigliamento protettivo per uso medico; Giocattoli del sesso [sex toys].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Respiratorių kaukės (dirbtinio kvėpavimo reikmėms); Kvėpavimo kaukės medicinos reikmėms; Respiratoriai medicinos reikmėms; Medicininiai infraraudonųjų spindulių termometrai; Batai (medicinos reikmėms); Pirštinės (medicinos reikmėms); Higieninės kaukės (medicinos reikmėms); Veido kaukės medicinos reikmėms; Apsauginiai drabužiai medicininėms reikmėms; Sekso žaislai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Respiratoru maskas mākslīgajai elpināšanai; Elpošanas maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Respiratori medicīniskam nolūkam; Infrasarkano staru termometri izmantošanai medicīnā; Zābaki medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Cimdi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Sanitārās maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Sejas maskas medicīniskām vajadzībām; Aizsargtērpi medicīniskām vajadzībām; Seksa rotaļlietas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Maskri respiratorji għan-nifs artifiċjali; Maskri respiratorji għal skopijiet mediċi; Respiraturi għal skopijiet mediċi; Termometri infraħomor għal skopijiet mediċi; Stvali għal skopijiet mediċi; Ingwanti għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri sanitarji għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri tal-wiċċ għall-użu mediku; Ħwejjeġ protettivi għall-użu mediku; Ġugarelli tas-sess.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Ademhalingsmaskers voor kunstmatige beademing; Ademhalingsmaskers voor medische doeleinden; Ademhalingstoestellen voor medische doeleinden; Infraroodthermometers voor medische doeleinden; Laarzen voor medisch gebruik; Handschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Hygiënische maskers voor medisch gebruik; Gezichtsmaskers voor medisch gebruik; Beschermende kledingstukken voor medische doeleinden; Seksspeeltjes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Maski do sztucznego oddychania; Maski oddechowe do celów medycznych; Respiratory do celów medycznych; Termometry na podczerwień do celów medycznych; Boty do celów medycznych; Rękawice do celów medycznych; Maski sanitarne do celów medycznych; Maski na twarz do użytku medycznego; Odzież ochronna do celów medycznych; Zabawki erotyczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máscaras para respiração artificial; Máscaras respiratórias para uso médico; Respiradores para uso médico; Termómetros de infravermelhos para uso médico; Botas para uso médico; Luvas para uso médico; Máscaras higiénicas para uso médico; Máscaras faciais para uso médico; Vestuário de proteção para uso médico; Brinquedos sexuais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Măști respiratorii, altele decât cele pentru respirație artificială; Măști respiratorii de uz medical; Aparate de respirat de uz medical; Termometre cu infraroșu de uz medical; Ghete de uz medical; Mănuși de uz medical; Măşti sanitare de uz medical; Măști medicale; Îmbrăcăminte de protecție de uz medical; Jucării erotice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Dýchacie masky na umelé dýchanie; Respiračné masky na lekárske účely; Respirátory na lekárske účely; Infračervené lekárske teplomery; Zdravotná obuv; Rukavice na lekárske použitie; Sanitárne masky na lekárske účely; Masky na tvár na lekárske účely; Ochranné odevy na lekárske účely; Erotické pomôcky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Dihalne maske za umetno dihanje; Dihalne maske za medicinske namene; Respiratorji za medicinske namene; Infrardeči termometri za medicinske namene; Škornji za medicinske namene; Rokavice za medicinske namene; Higienske maske za medicinske namene; Obrazne maske za medicinsko uporabo; Zaščitna oblačila za medicinske namene; Spolni pripomočki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Andningsmasker för konstgjord andning; Andningsmasker för medicinska ändamål; Respiratorer för medicinska ändamål; Infraröda termometrar för medicinska ändamål; Stövlar för medicinska ändamål; Handskar för medicinska ändamål; Sanitetsmasker för medicinska ändamål; Ansiktsmasker för medicinskt bruk; Skyddskläder för medicinska ändamål; Sexleksaker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Рекламиране и рекламни услуги; Онлайн реклама в компютърна мрежа; Представяне на стоки с цел продажаба на дребно чрез всички средства за комуникация; Рекламиране чрез афиши; Подпомагане в областта на търговския франчайзингов мениджмънт; Агенции за внос и износ; Насърчаване на продажбите [за трети лица]; Снабдяване за сметка на трети лица [закупуване на стоки или услуги за други предприятия]; Систематизиране на информация в компютърни бази данни; Търговия на дребно и едро с фармацевтични, ветеринарни, санитарни и медицински препарати.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Propagace; Online inzerce v počítačové síti; Prezentace výrobků v komunikačních médiích pro účely maloobchodu; Venkovní reklama; Asistence při řízení obchodních franšízových společností; Zprostředkování dovozu a vývozu; Podpora prodeje jiných osob; Zásobovací služby pro jiné osoby [nákup zboží a služeb pro jiné podniky]; Systematizace údajů do počítačových databází; Služby pro maloobchod nebo velkoobchod s farmaceutickými, veterinárními a sanitárními přípravky a zdravotnickým materiálem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Reklamevirksomhed; Online-annoncering på et computernetværk; Præsentation af varer på kommunikationsmedier til detailhandelsmæssige formål; Udendørs avertering; Bistand ved forretningsledelse i franchisevirksomheder; Import- og eksportagenturer; Salgsfremmende foranstaltninger for andre; Indkøbsbistand til andre ved køb af varer og tjenesteydelser; Sortering og redigering af informationer computerdatabaser; Detail- eller engroshandel med farmaceutiske, veterinære og hygiejniske præparater og medicinske artikler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werbung; Online-Werbung in einem Computernetzwerk; Präsentation von Waren in Kommunikations-Medien für den Einzelhandel; Außenwerbung; Hilfe bei der Führung von gewerblichen Franchise-Unternehmen; Dienstleistungen einer Im- und Exportagentur; Verkaufsförderung [Sales promotion] für Dritte; Beschaffungsdienstleistungen für Dritte [Erwerb von Waren und Dienstleistungen für andere Unternehmen]; Systematisierung von Daten in Computerdatenbanken; Einzelhandels- oder Großhandelsdienstleistungen für pharmazeutische, veterinärmedizinische Artikel, Hygienepräparate sowie medizinische Artikel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαφήμιση· Διαφήμιση on line σε δίκτυο πληροφορικής· Παρουσίαση αγαθών σε μέσα επικοινωνίας με σκοπό τη λιανική πώληση· Αφισοκόλληση· Υποστήριξη στη διαχείριση εμπορικών επιχειρήσεων υπό καθεστώς δικαιόχρησης· Πρακτορεία εισαγωγών-εξαγωγών· Προώθηση πωλήσεων [για τρίτους]· Εφοδιασμού για τρίτους (υπηρεσίες -) [αγορά προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για άλλες επιχειρήσεις]· Συστηματοποίηση δεδομένων σε βάσεις δεδομένων· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής ή χονδρικής για προμήθειες φαρμακευτικών, κτηνιατικών, ιατρικών και ειδών υγιεινής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Advertising; online advertising on a computer network; presentation of goods on communication media, for retail purposes; outdoor advertising; assistance in franchised commercial business management; import-export agency services; sales promotion for others; procurement services for others [purchasing goods and services for other businesses]; systemization of information into computer databases; retail or wholesale services for pharmaceutical, veterinary and sanitary preparations and medical supplies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicidad; Publicidad en línea por una red informática; Presentación de productos en cualquier medio de comunicación para su venta minorista; Publicidad exterior; Asistencia en la gestión de negocios comerciales franquiciados; Servicios de agencias de importación-exportación; Promoción de ventas para terceros; Servicios de abastecimiento para terceros [compra de productos y servicios para otras empresas]; Sistematización de información en bases de datos informáticas; Venta minorista o mayorista de preparaciones farmacéuticas, veterinarias y sanitarias, así como de suministros médicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reklaam; Arvutivõrgureklaam; Kaupade jaemüügi reklaam meediakanalites; Välireklaam; Frantsiisi korras tegutsevate kaubandusettevõtete juhtimisabi; Ekspordi- ja impordiagentuuride teenused; Müügikampaaniad, -reklaam teenusena; Hanketeenused teistele ettevõtetele [kaupade ja teenuste ostmine]; Info süstematiseerimine arvuti andmebaasides; Farmaatsia- ja veterinaariapreparaatide ning hügieeni- ja meditsiinitarvete jae- ja hulgimüük.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mainonta; Online-mainonta tietoverkoissa; Tavaraesittely tiedotusvälineissä vähittäismyyntiä varten; Ulkomainonta; Franchising-toimintaa koskevaan kaupalliseen liikkeenjohtoon liittyvä avustaminen; Tuonti- ja vientiagentuuripalvelut; Myynninedistäminen [muille]; Hankintapalvelut muille [tavaroiden ja palveluiden osto muille yrityksille]; Tietokantatietojen systematisointi; Farmaseuttisten ja eläinlääkinnällisten valmisteiden, saniteettivalmisteiden sekä lääkintätarvikkeiden vähittäiskauppa- tai tukkukauppapalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publicité; Publicité en ligne sur un réseau informatique; Présentation de produits sur tout moyen de communication pour la vente au détail; Publicité extérieure; Assistance en gestion de franchise commerciale; Services d'agences d'import-export; Promotion des ventes pour des tiers; Services d'approvisionnement pour des tiers [achat de produits et de services pour d'autres entreprises]; Systématisation d'informations dans des bases de données informatiques; Services de vente au détail ou en gros de préparations pharmaceutiques, vétérinaires et hygiéniques ainsi que de fournitures médicales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Oglašavanje; Online oglašavanje na računalnim mrežama; Prezentacija robe putem komunikacijskih medija, u maloprodajne svrhe; Plakatiranje [oglašavanje]; Potpora u upravljanju komercijalnom poslovnom djelatnošću u obliku franšize; Agencije za uvoz-izvoz; Promicanje prodaje za treće osobe; Nabava za treće osobe [usluge kupnje proizvoda i usluga za druga poduzeća]; Sistematiziranje podataka za središnju kartoteku; Usluge maloprodaje ili veleprodaje za farmaceutske, veterinarske i sanitarne pripravke i za medicinske potrepštine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hirdetési- és reklámszolgáltatások; On-line hirdetői tevékenység számítógépes hálózaton; Áruk bemutatása kommunikációs médiában, kiskereskedelmi célokból; Szabadtéri reklámozás, hirdetés; Segítségnyújtás franchise rendszerű kereskedelmi üzletvitelhez; Import-export ügynökségek; Értékesítési promóciós szolgáltatások; Beszerzői szolgáltatások [áruk illetve szolgáltatások beszerzése más cégeknek]; Információk számítógépes adatbázisokba való rendezése; Gyógyszerészeti, állatgyógyászati és higiéniai készítmények valamint gyógyászati eszközök kis- és nagykereskedelme.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicità; Pubblicità online su rete informatica; Presentazione di prodotti con mezzi di comunicazione per la vendita al dettaglio; Pubblicità esterna; Assistenza nella gestione di imprese commerciali in franchising; Servizi di agenzie per l'importazione e l'esportazione; Promozione delle vendite per i terzi; Servizi di approvvigionamento per conto terzi [acquisto di prodotti e di servizi per altre imprese]; Sistemazione di informazioni in banche dati informatiche; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio o all'ingrosso di preparati farmaceutici, veterinari e sanitari e di forniture mediche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Reklama; Viešasis elektroninis reklamavimas kompiuterių tinkle; Prekių pateikimas žiniasklaidoje pardavimo reikmėms; Viešasis reklamavimas; Franšizės komercijos verslo vadybos pagalba; Importo ir eksporto agentūrų paslaugos; Prekių pardavimo skatinimas [kitiems]; Tiekimo paslaugos kitiems [prekių ir paslaugų pirkimas kitiems verslams]; Informacijos sisteminimas kompiuterinėse duomenų bazėse; Mažmeninė ar didmeninė prekyba farmacijos, veterinarijos ir higienos preparatais bei medicinos reikmenimis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reklāma; Reklāma tiešsaistē ar datortīklu starpniecību; Preču demonstrēšana komunikācijas līdzekļos mazumtirdzniecības nolūkiem; Afišu izvietošana; Atbalsts franšīzes tirdzniecības uzņēmumu vadībā; Importa-eksporta aģentūru pakalpojumi; Preču noieta veicināšana; Uzņēmumu apgāde (preču un pakalpojumu sagāde trešo personu interesēs); Informācijas sistematizēšana datoru datubāzēs; Farmaceitisko, veterināro un higiēnas preparātu un medicīnisko preču mazumtirdzniecība un vairumtirdzniecība.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reklamar; Reklamar onlajn fuq netwerk tal-kompjuters; Il-preżentazzjoni ta' oġġetti fuq mezzi tal-komunikazzjoni, għal skopijiet ta' bejgħ bl-imnut; Reklamar fuq barra; Assistenza fil-ġestjoni kummerċjali ta' negozju ta' frankiġja; Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-importazzjoni u esportazzjoni; Il-promozzjoni tal-bejgħ għal oħrajn; Servizzi ta' akkwist għal oħrajn [xiri ta' prodotti u servizzi għal negozji oħra]; Is-sistematizzazzjoni ta' informazzjoni f'dejtabejżis tal-kompjuter; Servizzi kemm bl-imnut jew bl-ingrossa għall-forniment ta' oġġetti farmaċewtiċi, veterinarji, medikali u preparazzjonijiet sanitarji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Publiciteit; Online reclame op een computernetwerk; Presentatie van goederen op communicatiemedia, voor verkoopdoeleinden; Reclame door aanplakbiljetten; Hulp bij de leiding van commerciële franchiseondernemingen; Diensten van import- en exportagentschappen; Verkooppromotie [voor derden]; Aankoop voor andere bedrijven; Systematisering in een centraal bestand van gegevens; Detailhandels- of groothandelsdiensten in farmaceutische, veterinaire en hygiënische preparaten en medische hulpmiddelen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Reklama; Reklama online za pośrednictwem sieci komputerowej; Prezentowanie produktów w mediach dla celów sprzedaży detalicznej; Reklama zewnętrzna; Pomoc w zarządzaniu przedsiębiorstwami zarządzanymi na zasadach franchisingu; Usługi agencji importowo-eksportowych; Promocja sprzedaży dla osób trzecich; Usługi w zakresie nabywania dla osób trzecich [zakupy produktów i usług dla innych przedsiębiorstw]; Systematyzacja danych w komputerowych bazach danych; Sprzedaż detaliczna lub hurtowa środków farmaceutycznych, weterynaryjnych i sanitarnych oraz zaopatrzenia medycznego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicidade; Publicidade online numa rede informática; Apresentação de produtos nos meios de comunicação, para fins de venda a retalho; Serviços de publicidade de exterior; Assistência na gestão de negócios comerciais de franchising; Serviços de agências de importação-exportação; Promoção de vendas [prestada a terceiros]; Serviços de fornecimento para terceiros [compra de produtos e serviços para outras empresas]; Sistematização de informação numa base de dados informática; Serviços de venda a retalho ou a grosso de preparações farmacêuticas, veterinárias e higiénicas e provisões médicas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicitate; Publicitate on-line într-o rețea informatizată; Prezentarea produselor prin toate mijloacele de comunicare pentru vânzarea cu amănuntul; Afișaj; Asistență în gestiunea comercială a firmelor în sistem de franciză; Agenții de import-export; Promovarea vânzărilor pentru terți; Servicii de aprovizionare pentru terți [achiziții de bunuri și servicii pentru alte întreprinderi]; Sistematizarea informațiilor în fișiere electronice; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul sau en-gros pentru preparate farmaceutice, veterinare și sanitare și produse medicale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reklama; Online reklama na počítačovej komunikačnej sieti; Prezentácia výrobkov v komunikačných médiách pre maloobchod; Vonkajšia reklama; Pomoc pri riadení franchisingových obchodných podnikov; Kancelárie zaoberajúce sa dovozom a vývozom; Podpora predaja (pre tretie osoby); Zásobovacie služby pre tretie osoby (nákup tovarov a služieb pre iné podniky); Zoraďovanie údajov v počítačových databázach; Maloobchodné alebo veľkoobchodné služby s farmaceutickými, zverolekárskymi a zdravotníckymi prípravkami a s lekárskymi potrebami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oglaševanje in oglaševalske storitve; Spletno oglaševanje preko računalniškega omrežja; Predstavitev blaga v komunikacijskih medijih (prodaja na drobno); Plakatiranje; Pomoč pri upravljanju trgovskega podjetja v franšiznem režimu; Uvozno - izvozne agencije; Pospeševanje prodaje (za druge); Prokuratorske storitve [nabava blaga in storitev za druga podjetja]; Sistematizacija informacij v računalniške baze podatkov; Maloprodajne ali veleprodajne storitve za farmacevtske, veterinarske in sanitarne proizvode in medicinske potrebščine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Reklam; Annonsering online via datanätverk; Presentation av varor på kommersiella media, för försäljningsändamål; Utomhusreklam; Assistans vid företagsledning för kommersiell franchising; Import-exportagenturer; Sales promotiontjänster; Inköp av varor och tjänster för annans räkning; Systematisering av information i databaser; Återförsäljning eller detaljhandelstjänster för farmaceutiska, veterinära och sanitära preparat och medicinska varor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/082</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/152</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-12</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082711</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>14539</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
