<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-17T09:59:27</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229813</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229813</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-13</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-17</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>xianggan</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162496997</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229813/000162496997.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.01</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Секс играчки; Галванични терапевтични прибори; Санитарни маски за медицински цели; Изкуствени гърди [бюст]; Бебешки шишета; Ортопедични изделия; Стоматологично оборудване; Презервативи; Медицински апарати и инструменти; Апарати за масаж.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Erotické hračky; Galvanické terapeutické přístroje; Hygienické masky pro lékařské účely; Umělá poprsí; Dětské láhve; Ortopedické potřeby; Zařízení pro zubní lékařství; Kondomy; Lékařské přístroje a nástroje; Masážní přístroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sexlegetøj; Galvaniske terapeutiske apparater; Sanitære masker til medicinske formål; Brystproteser; Sutteflasker; Ortopædiske artikler; Tandlægeapparater og -instrumenter; Kondomer; Medicinske apparater og instrumenter; Massageapparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Sexspielzeug; Galvanische Therapiegeräte; Mundschutz für medizinische Zwecke; Brustprothesen; Saugflaschen; Orthopädische Artikel; Zahnärztliche Apparate und Instrumente; Präservative [Kondome]; Medizinische Apparate und Instrumente; Massagegeräte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Σεξουαλικά παιχνίδια· Γαλβανικές (- θεραπευτικές συσκευές)· Μάσκες υγιεινής για ιατρική χρήση· Τεχνητές προσθήκες στήθους· Υποδοχείς για θήλαστρα· Ορθοπεδικά είδη· Οδοντιατρικός εξοπλισμός· Προφυλακτικά· Ιατρικά (Συσκευές και όργανα -)· Συσκευές μασαζ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Sex toys; Galvanic therapeutic appliances; Sanitary masks for medical purposes; Artificial breasts; Feeding bottles; Orthopaedic articles; Dental apparatus and instruments; Condoms; Medical apparatus and instruments; Massage apparatus..</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Juguetes sexuales; Aparatos galvánicos para uso terapéutico; Mascarillas sanitarias para uso médico; Prótesis mamarias; Biberones; Artículos ortopédicos; Aparatos e instrumentos odontológicos; Preservativos; Aparatos e instrumentos médicos; Aparatos de masaje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sekslelud; Galvanoteraapiaseadmed; Meditsiinilised hügieenilised maskid; Rinnaproteesid; Lutipudelid; Ortopeediatooted, ortopeedilised tooted; Hambaraviseadmed ja -riistad; Kondoomid, preservatiivid; Meditsiiniseadmed ja -riistad; Massaažiaparaadid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Seksilelut; Galvanoterapeuttiset laitteet; Saniteettinaamarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Tekorinnat; Tuttipullot; Ortopediset välineet; Hammaslääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Kondomit; Lääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Hierontalaitteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Jouets sexuels; Appareils thérapeutiques galvaniques; Masques d'hygiène à usage médical; Seins artificiels; Biberons; Articles orthopédiques; Appareils et instruments dentaires; Préservatifs; Appareils et instruments médicaux; Appareils de massage.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Seksualne igračke; Galvanski terapeutski uređaji; Sanitarne maske za medicinske svrhe; Umjetne dojke; Spremnici dječjih bočica; Ortopedski artikli; Stomatološka oprema; Kondomi; Medicinski uređaji i instrumenti; Uređaji za masažu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szexuális játékszerek; Galvánterápiás készülékek; Gyógyászati célú egészségügyi maszkok; Műmellek; Cumisüvegtartók; Ortopédiai cikkek; Fogászati berendezések; Óvszerek; Gyógyászati készülékek és eszközök; Masszázsberendezések.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Giocattoli del sesso [sex toys]; Apparecchi terapeutici galvanici; Maschere igieniche per uso medico; Seni artificiali; Poppatoi; Articoli ortopedici; Apparecchi e strumenti dentari; Preservativi; Apparecchi e strumenti medici; Apparecchi per il massaggio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Sekso žaislai; Galvanoterapijos aparatūra; Higieninės kaukės (medicinos reikmėms); Krūtų protezai; Žindymo buteliukai; Ortopedijos gaminiai; Odontologijos aparatūra ir instrumentai; Prezervatyvai; Medicinos aparatai ir instrumentai; Masažavimo aparatai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Seksa rotaļlietas; Galvaniskās ierīces terapeitiskiem nolūkiem; Sanitārās maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Krūts protēzes; Barošanas pudelītes; Ortopēdiskās preces; Zobārstniecības ierīces un instrumenti; Prezervatīvi; Medicīniskā aparatūra un instrumenti; Masāžas aparāti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ġugarelli tas-sess; Tagħmir terapewtiku galvaniku; Maskri sanitarji għal skopijiet mediċi; Sider artifiċjali; Reċipjenti bħala fliexken għat-tmigħ tat-trabi; Oġġetti ortopediċi; Tagħmir dentali; Kondoms; Apparat u strumenti mediċi; Apparat għall-massaġġi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Seksspeeltjes; Galvanische apparaten voor therapeutisch gebruik; Hygiënische maskers voor medisch gebruik; Borstprothesen; Zuigflessen; Orthopedische artikelen; Tandheelkundige apparaten en instrumenten; Condooms; Medische apparaten en instrumenten; Massageapparaten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Zabawki erotyczne; Galwaniczna aparatura terapeutyczna; Maski sanitarne do celów medycznych; Sztuczne piersi; Pojemniki na butelki do karmienia; Artykuły ortopedyczne; Przyrządy i przybory dentystyczne; Prezerwatywy; Urządzenia i instrumenty medyczne; Urządzenia do masażu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Brinquedos sexuais; Aparelhos terapêuticos galvânicos; Máscaras higiénicas para uso médico; Seios artificiais; Biberons [biberões]; Artigos ortopédicos; Aparelhos e instrumentos dentários; Preservativos; Aparelhos e instrumentos médicos; Aparelhos de massagem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Jucării erotice; Aparate pentru terapie galvanică; Măşti sanitare de uz medical; Proteze mamare; Recipiente pentru biberoane; Articole ortopedice; Echipament stomatologic; Prezervative; Aparate și instrumente medicale; Aparate de masaj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Erotické pomôcky; Galvanické terapeutické zariadenia; Sanitárne masky na lekárske účely; Umelé prsníky; Detské fľaše; Ortopedické pomôcky; Zubárske prístroje a nástroje; Kondómy, prezervatívy; Lekárske prístroje a nástroje; Masážne prístroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Spolni pripomočki; Terapevtske naprave z galvanskim tokom; Higienske maske za medicinske namene; Umetne dojke; Posodice za stekleničke za hranjenje; Ortopedski izdelki; Zobozdravstveni aparati in instrumenti; Kondomi; Medicinski aparati in instrumenti; Masažne naprave.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Sexleksaker; Galvaniska terapiapparater; Sanitetsmasker för medicinska ändamål; Bröstproteser; Nappflaskor; Konstgjorda lemmar, ögon och tänder; Dentala apparater och instrument; Kondomer; Medicinska apparater och instrument; Massageapparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/084</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-06</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/154</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-14</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082563</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>26721</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
