<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-12T09:10:12</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229816</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229816</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-11</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-12</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Loco Charmz</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Съдове за пиене; Козметични и тоалетни принадлежности; Домакински изделия за почистване, четки и материали за изработване на четки; Изделия за грижа за облекла и обувки; Сервизи и прибори за маса, кухненска посуда и съдини; Съдове за домакински или кухненски цели [с изключение на такива от благороден метал]; Статуи, статуетки, плакети и произведения на изкуството, изработени от материали като порцелан, глина или стъкло, включени в този клас.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nádoby na pití; Kosmetické a toaletní potřeby; Domácí náčiní k úklidu, kartáče a materiály na výrobu kartáčů; Výrobky pro péči o oděvy a obuv; Nádobí, kuchyňské náčiní a nádoby; Dózy, boxy a nádoby pro použití v domácnosti a kuchyni; Sochy, figurky, plakety a medaile a umělecké předměty vyrobené z materiálů jako porcelán, terakota nebo sklo, zahrnuté v této třídě.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Drikkebeholdere; Redskaber til kosmetisk brug og toiletredskaber; Redskaber til rengøring i hjemmet, børster og børstenbindermateriale; Artikler til pleje af beklædningsgenstande og fodtøj; Bordservice, køkkengrej og beholdere; Beholdere til husholdnings- eller køkkenbrug; Statuer, statuetter, plaketter og kunstværker fremstillet af materialer såsom porcelæn, terra-cotta eller glas, indeholdt i klassen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Trinkgefäße; Kosmetik- und Toiletteutensilien; Haushaltsreinigungsgegenstände, Bürsten und Bürstenmachermaterialien; Haushaltsgegenstände für die Pflege von Bekleidung und Schuhwaren; Geschirr, Kochgeschirr und Behälter; Gefäße für Haushalt oder Küche; Statuen, Figuren, Schilder und Kunstwerke aus Materialien wie Porzellan, Keramik, Steingut und Glas, soweit in dieser Klasse enthalten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Πόσης (Δοχεία -)· Σύνεργα καλλωπισμού και ατομικής περιποίησης· Οικιακά σύνεργα καθαρισμού, βούρτσες και υλικά ψηκτροποιίας· Είδη περιποίησης ενδυμάτων και υποδημάτων· Επιτραπέζια σκεύη, μαγειρικά σκεύη και δοχεία· Δοχεία οικιακά ή μαγειρικά· Αγάλματα, αγαλματίδια, κορνίζες και έργα τέχνης, από υλικά όπως πορσελάνη, τερακότα ή γυαλί, που περιλαμβάνονται στην κλάση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Drinking vessels; Cosmetic and toilet utensils; Household utensils for cleaning, brushes and brush-making materials; Articles for the care of clothing and footwear; Tableware, cookware and containers; Containers for household or kitchen use; Statues, figurines, plaques and works of art, made of materials such as porcelain, terra-cotta or glass, included in the class.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Recipientes para beber; Utensilios de cosméticos y de tocador; Utensilios domésticos de limpieza, cepillos y materiales para fabricar cepillos; Artículos para el cuidado de prendas de vestir y calzado; Vajillas, baterías de cocina y recipientes; Recipientes para uso doméstico o culinario; Estatuas, estatuillas, placas y objetos de arte, fabricados de materiales como porcelana, terracota o vidrio, incluidos en esta clase.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Jooginõud; Kosmeetika- ja tualett-tarvikud; Puhastusvahendid majatarvetena, harjad ja harjamaterjalid; Rõivaste ja jalatsite hooldustooted; Lauanõud, toiduvalmistusnõud ja mahutid; Köögi- või majapidamismahutid; Antud klassi kuuluvad kujud, kujukesed, tahvlid ja plaadid, mis on valmistatud materjalidest, nagu portselan, terrakota või klaas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Juoma-astiat; Kosmetiikka- ja toilettitarvikkeet; Kodinpuhdistusvälineet, harjat ja harjanvalmistusaineet; Tarvikkeet vaatteiden ja jalkineiden hoitoon; Pöytäastiat, keittoastiat ja säiliöt; Säiliöt koti- tai keittiökäyttöön; Patsaat, pienoisveistokset, muistolaatat ja taideteokset luokkaan sisältyvistä materiaaleista kuten posliini, keramiikka tai lasi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Récipients à boire; Ustensiles cosmétiques et de toilette; Ustensiles de nettoyage, brosses et matériaux pour la brosserie; Articles pour l'entretien de vêtements et de chaussures; Vaisselle, ustensiles de cuisine et récipients pour la cuisine ou le ménage; Récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine; Statues, figurines, plaques et œuvres d'art, faites de matériaux comme la porcelaine, la terre cuite ou le verre, compris dans la classe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Posude za pića; Kozmetički i toaletni pribor; Kućanski pribor za čišćenje, četke i materijali za izradu četki; Artikli za održavanje odjeće i obuće; Pribor za jelo, kuhinjski pribor i spremnici; Posude za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju; Kipovi, figurice, ploče i umjetnička djela, od materijala kao što su porculan, terakota ili staklo, obuhvačeni ovim razredom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ivóedények; Kozmetikai és piperecikkek; Háztartási tisztítóeszközök, kefék és kefekészítő anyagok; Árucikkek ruhák és lábbelik ápolásához; Asztalneműk, főzőedények és tárolók; Tárolók, tároló edények háztartási vagy konyhai célokra; Szobrok, kisplasztikák, dísztáblák és művészeti alkotások porcelánból, terrakottából vagy üvegből, amelyek ebbe az osztályba tartoznak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Recipienti per bere; Utensili per uso cosmetico e per la toilette; Utensili per le pulizie domestiche, spazzole e materiali per la fabbricazione di spazzole; Articoli per la cura di capi di abbigliamento e calzature; Vasellame, pentole e recipienti; Recipienti per la casa o per la cucina; Statue, statuette, targhe e opere d'arte, fatte in porcellana, terracotta o vetro, incluse in questa classe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Geriamieji indai; Kosmetiniai ir tualetiniai reikmenys; Namų apyvokos valymo reikmenys, šepečiai ir šepečių darymo medžiagos; Drabužių ir avalynės prižiūros reikmenys; Valgomieji reikmenys, virtuvės reikmenys ir buitinės talpyklos; Buitinės ar virtuvinės talpyklos; Porceliano, keramikos ar stiklo statulos, figūrėlės, lentelės ir meno dirbiniai, priskirti prie šios klasės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Dzērienu trauki; Kosmētikas un tualetes piederumi; Mājsaimniecības piederumi tīrīšanai, birstes un birstu izgatavošanas materiāli; Preces apģērbu un apavu kopšanai; Galda un virtuves piederumi, tilpnes un trauki; Tilpnes mājturības vai virtuves nolūkiem; Porcelāna, terakotas vai stikla statujas, statuetes, plaketes un mākslas darbi, kas ietverti šajā klasē.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reċipjenti għax-xorb; Għodod kosmetiċi u tat-twaletta; Utensili domestiċi għat-tindif, xkupilji u materjali biex tagħmel l-ixkupilji u l-pniezel; Artikli għall-kura ta' ħwejjeġ u ta' xedd is-saqajn; Oġġetti għal fuq il-mejda, oġġetti li ssajjar bihom u kontenituri; Kontenituri għal użu domestiku jew għal użu fil-kċina; Statwi, figurini, plakki u xogħolijiet tal-arti, magħmula minn materjali bħall-porċellana, t-terrakotta jew il-ħġieġ, inklużi fil-klassi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Drinkgerei; Cosmetisch gerei en toiletgerei; Huishoudelijk schoonmaakgerei, borstels en materialen voor de borstelfabricage; Artikelen voor het verzorgen van kleding en schoeisel; Vaatwerk, kookgerei en houders voor de keuken of de huishouding; Houders voor de huishouding of de keuken; Beelden, beeldjes, plaquettes en kunstwerken van materialen zoals porselein, terracotta of glas, begrepen in deze klasse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Naczynia na napoje; Przybory kosmetyczne i toaletowe; Przybory do użytku domowego do czyszczenia, szczotki i materiały do wytwarzania szczotek; Artykuły do pielęgnacji odzieży i obuwia; Zastawa stołowa, przybory kuchenne i pojemniki; Pojemniki do użytku domowego lub kuchennego; Statuetki, figurki, tabliczki i dzieła sztuki wykonane z takich materiałów, jak porcelana, terakota lub szkło, zawarte w tej klasie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Recipientes para bebidas; Utensílios cosméticos e de toilette; Utensílios domésticos para a limpeza, escovas e materiais para o fabrico de escovas; Artigos para a conservação de vestuário e calçado; Utensílios de mesa, cozinha e recipientes; Recipientes para uso doméstico ou para cozinha; Estátuas, estatuetas, placas e obras de arte, feitos de materiais tais como porcelana, terracota ou vidro, incluídos na classe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Recipiente de băut; Ustensile cosmetice și de toaletă; Ustensile de uz menajer pentru curățat, perii și materiale pentru perii; Material pentru îngrijirea articolelor de îmbrăcăminte şi încălţăminte; Veselă, articole de bucătărie şi recipiente; Recipiente pentru menaj sau bucătărie; Statui, figurine, plăci şi obiecte de artă din materiale ca porţelan, teracotă sau sticlă, incluse în această clasă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Poháre, šálky, hrnčeky na pitie; Kozmetické a toaletné potreby; Domáce alebo kuchynské potreby na čistenie, kefy a materiály na výrobu kief; Výrobky pre starostlivosť o odevy a obuv; Stolovacie potreby, kuchynský riad a nádoby; Nádoby na použitie v domácnosti alebo v kuchyni; Sochy, figúrky, plakety a umelecké diela z materiálov ako sú porcelán,terakota alebo sklo, patriace do tejto triedy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Posode za pitje; Kozmetični in toaletni pripomočki; Gospodinjski pripomočki za čiščenje, krtače in materiali za ščetkarstvo; Izdelki za nego oblačil in obutve; Namizna posoda, posoda za kuhanje in shranjevalna posoda; Posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo; Kipi, figurice, okrasne ploščice in umetniška dela iz materialov, kot so porcelan, glina ali steklo, vključenih v ta razred.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Dryckeskärl; Kosmetiska redskap och toalettredskap; Hushållsredskap för rengöringsändamål, borstar och borstmakerimaterial; Artiklar för vård av kläder och fotbeklädnader; Bordsserviser, köksredskap och behållare; Behållare för hushålls- eller köksändamål; Statyer, figuriner, plaketter och konstföremål, gjorda av material som porslin, terrakotta eller glas, ingående i klassen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Облекло; Обувки; Шапки и други принадлежности за глава.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Oděvy; Obuv; Pokrývky hlavy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beklædningsgenstande; Fodtøj; Hovedbeklædning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bekleidungsstücke; Schuhwaren; Kopfbedeckungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ενδύματα· Υποδήματα· Είδη πιλοποιίας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Clothing; Footwear; Headgear.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Prendas de vestir; Calzado; Artículos de sombrerería.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rõivad; Jalatsid; Peakatted.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatteet; Jalkineet; Päähineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vêtements; Chaussures; Chapellerie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Odjeća; Obuća; Pokrivala za glavu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ruházati cikkek; Lábbelik; Kalapáruk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Abbigliamento; Calzature; Cappelleria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Drabužiai, apranga; Apavas; Galvos apdangalai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apģērbi; Kurpes; Galvassegas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ilbies; Xedd is-saqajn; Xedd ir-ras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kleding; Schoeisel; Hoofddeksels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odzież; Obuwie; Nakrycia głowy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vestuário; Calçado; Chapelaria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole de îmbrăcăminte; Articole de încălţăminte; Articole pentru acoperirea capului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Odevy, oblečenie; Obuv; Pokrývky hlavy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oblačila; Obutev; Pokrivala.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kläder; Fotbeklädnader; Huvudbonader.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>30</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Сладкарски изделия; Хлебни изделия; Шоколад; Немедицински сладкарски продукти; Бонбони, близалки и дъвки; Сладкарски блокчета; Сосове [подправки за ястия]; Лед, сладолед, замразен йогурт и сорбети; Кафе, чай и какао и техни заместители; Обработени зърнени храни, нишестета и стоки от тях, смеси за тестени изделия и кваси; Зърнени храни; Брашно; Зърнени храни; Хляб; Сол; Горчица; Оцет; Пикантни подправки; Подправки; Подправки; Снаксови храни на зърнена основа; Продукти за снаксове, направени от картофено брашно; Леки закуски на оризова основа; Смес за сладкиши; Ориз; Пайове с пастет; Нишестени храни; Сандвичи; Пици.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Cukrovinky; Pekárenské výrobky; Čokoláda; Sladkosti bez léčivých přísad; Sladkosti (bonbóny), sladké tyčinky a žvýkačky; Tyčinky (cukrovinky); Omáčky [dochucovadla]; Led, zmrzliny, mražené jogurty a sorbety; Káva, čaj, kakao a jejich náhražky; Zpracované obilí, škrob a produkty z nich vyrobené, pečicí přípravky a droždí; Cereálie; Mouka; Přípravky z obilovin; Chléb; Sůl; Hořčice; Ocet; Ochucovadla; Koření; Dochucovadla; Svačinové občerstvení na bázi cereálií; Pochutiny vyrobené z bramborové mouky; Svačinové občerstvení na bázi rýže; Sušenky; Rýže; Paštiky zapečené v těstě; Moučná jídla; Sendviče; Pizza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Konfekturevarer; Bagerivarer; Chokolade; Konfektureslik [uden lægemidler]; Slik, slikbarer og tyggegummi; Konfekturestænger; Kryddersaucer; Is, spiseis, frossen yoghurt, og sorbet; Kaffe, te, kakao og erstatninger herfor; Forarbejdet korn, stivelse og varer fremstillet deraf, bagepræparater og gær; Kornprodukter; Mel; Kornpræparater; Brød; Salt; Sennep; Eddike; Krydderier; Krydderier; Smagsstoffer [krydderier]; Kornbaserede snacks; Snackvarer fremstillet af kartoffelmel; Snacks baseret på ris; Biscuits [søde kiks og småkager]; Ris; Postej; Retter tilberedt på basis af mel; Sandwiches; Pizzaer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Süßigkeiten; Backwaren; Schokolade; Süßwaren [nicht medizinisch]; Süßwaren [Bonbons], Schokoriegel und Kaugummi; Süßwarenriegel; Saucen [Würzmittel]; Eis, Eiscreme, gefrorener Joghurt, Sorbets; Kaffee, Tee, Kakao und Ersatzstoffe hierfür; verarbeitetes Getreide und Stärken für Nahrungsmittel sowie Waren hieraus, Backzubereitungen und Hefe; Cerealien; Mehle; Getreidepräparate; Brot; Salz; Senf; Essig; Würzmittel; Gewürze; Gewürzmischungen; Snacks auf Getreidebasis; Snacks aus Kartoffelmehl; Snacks auf Reisbasis; Kekse; Reis; Pasteten; Mehlspeisen; Sandwiches; Pizzas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ζαχαρώδη· Είδη αρτοποιίας· Σοκολάτα· Ζαχαρωτά για μη φαρμακευτική χρήση· Ζαχαρωτά, ραβδοι ζαχαρωτών και τσίχλες· Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής σε μορφή ράβδου· Σάλτσες [καρυκεύματα]· Πάγος, παγωτά, παγωμένο γιαούρτι και γρανίτες· Καφές, τσάι και κακάο και υποκατάστατα αυτών· Επεξεργασμένα δημητριακά, άμυλα και προϊόντα που κατασκευάζονται από αυτά, ψημένα παρασκευάσματα και μαγιά· Δημητριακά· Αλεύρι· Δημητριακά· Άρτος· Αλάτι· Μουστάρδα· Ξύδι· Μαγειρικά βότανα, μπαχαρικά· Μπαχαρικά· Καρυκεύματα· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) με βάση τα δημητριακά· Προϊόντα μικρογευμάτων (σνακ) από πατατάλευρο· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) με βάση το ρύζι· Γλυκά· Ρύζι· Ηπατοπολτοί (πατέ) με κρούστα από ζύμη· Τρόφιμα με βάση το αλεύρι· Σάντουιτς· Πίτσες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Confectionery; Bakery goods; Chocolate; Non-medicated confectionery candy; Sweets (candy), candy bars and chewing gum; Confectionery bars; Sauces [condiments]; Ice, ice creams, frozen yogurts and sorbets; Coffee, teas and cocoa and substitutes therefor; Processed grains, starches, and goods made thereof, baking preparations and yeasts; Cereals; Flour; Cereal preparations; Bread; Salt; Mustard; Vinegar; Seasonings; Spices; Condiments; Cereal-based snack food; Snack food products made from potato flour; Rice-based snack food; Cookies; Rice; Pâtés en croûte; Farinaceous foods; Sandwiches; Pizza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Productos de confitería; Productos de panadería; Chocolate; Golosinas no medicinales; Caramelos, golosinas y chicles; Barras de golosina; Salsas [condimentos]; Hielo, helados, yogures helados y sorbetes; Café, té, cacao y sucedáneos de los mismos; Granos preparados, almidones y productos fabricados con los mismos, productos para panadería y levaduras; Cereales; Harinas; Preparaciones a base de cereales; Pan; Sal; Mostaza; Vinagres; Productos para sazonar; Especias; Condimentos; Refrigerios a base de cereales; Productos de aperitivo hechos de harina de patata; Refrigerios a base de arroz; Galletas; Arroz; Patés en costra; Alimentos a base de harina; Bocadillos y sándwiches; Pizza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Maiustused; Pagaritooted; Šokolaad; Ravitoimeta kompvekid; Kompvekid, maiustused (batoonid) ja närimiskumm; Maiustusetahvlid; Maitsekastmed; Jäätis, piima- ja koorejäätised, külmutatud jogurtid ja sorbetid; Kohv, tee ja kakao ning nende aseained; Töödeldud teraviljad, tärklis ning nendest valmistatud kaubad, küpsetuspulbrid ja pärm; Teraviljad; Jahu; Teraviljasaadused; Leib, sai; Sool; Sinep; Äädikas; Vürtsid, maitsetaimed; Vürtsid; Maitseained; Teraviljast valmistatud suupisted; Kartulijahust valmistatud suupisted; Riisist valmistatud suupisted; Biskviidid, küpsised; Riis; Tainas küpsetatud pasteedid (patés en croute); Jahutoidud; Võileivad; Pitsad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sokerimakeiset; Leipomotuotteet; Suklaa; Lääkeaineita sisältämättömät karamellit; Makeiset (karamellit), makeispatukat ja purukumi; Makeispatukat; Kastikkeet (Mauste -); Jää, jäätelöt, jäädytetyt jugurtit ja sorbetit; Kahvi, tee ja kaakao ja niiden korvikkeet; Jalostetut viljat, tärkkelykset ja niistä tehdyt tuotteet, leivontavalmisteet ja hiivat; Viljavalmisteet; Jauhot; Viljavalmisteet; Leipä; Suola; Sinappi; Etikka; Maustesekoitukset; Mausteet; Mausteet; Viljapohjainen pikaruoka; Perunajauhosta tehdyt välipalat; Pikaruoka, riisipohjainen; Keksit; Riisi; Pasteijat; Ruoat, jauhopohjaiset; Voileivät; Pizza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Confiserie; Produits de boulangerie; Chocolat; Bonbons non médicinaux [confiseries]; Bonbons (sucreries), friandises et gomme à mâcher; Confiseries en barre; Sauces [condiments]; Glace, crèmes glacées, yaourts glacés et sorbets; Café, thés, cacao et leurs succédanés; Grains transformés, amidons et dérivés, préparations pour boulangerie et levures; Céréales; Farine; Préparations faites de céréales; Pain; Sel; Moutarde; Vinaigres; Assaisonnements; Épices; Condiments; En-cas à base de céréales; En-cas à base de farine de pommes de terre; En-cas à base de riz; Biscuits; Riz; Pâtés en croûte; Mets à base de farine; Sandwiches; Pizzas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Slastice; Pekarski proizvodi; Čokolada; Nemedicinski konditorski bomboni; Slatkiši (bomboni), čokoladice i guma za žvakanje; Konditorske pločice; Umaci (začinski); Led, sladoledi, zamrznuti jogurti i sorbeti; Kava, čajevi, kakao i njihovi nadomjesci; Prerađene žitarice, škrobovi i njihovi proizvodi, pripravci za pečenje i kvasci; Žitarice; Brašno; Žitarice; Kruh; Sol; Senf; Ocat; Mirodije; Začini; Začinski dodaci; Grickalice na bazi žitarica; Grickalice od brašna krumpira; Grickalice od riže; Tijesto za kolače; Riža; Pâtés en croute; Jela od brašna; Sendviči; Pizza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kandiscukor; Pékáruk; Csokoládé; Nem gyógyhatású cukorka; Édességek (cukorkák), csokoládés szeletek, rágógumi; Édesség szeletek; Szószok [ízesítőszerek, fűszeres mártások]; Jég, fagylalt, fagyasztott joghurtok és sörbetek; Kávé, tea, kakaó és helyettesítőik; Feldolgozott gabonák, keményítő és az ezekből készült áruk, pékáruk és élesztők; Gabonakészítmények; Liszt; Gabonakészítmények; Kenyér; Só; Mustár; Ecet; Fűszerek; Fűszerek; Fűszerek, ízesítők; Snack ételek (Gabona alapú -); Burgonyalisztből készült rágcsálnivaló termékek; Rizs alapú rágcsálnivalók; Süteménytészta; Rizs; Tésztában sült pástétom; Liszttartalmú ételek; Szendvicsek; Pizza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Confetteria; Prodotti da forno; Cioccolato; Confetteria e caramelle non medicinali; Dolci (caramelle) e gomme da masticare; Prodotti dolciari in barrette; Salse salate; Ghiaccio, gelati, yogurt gelati e sorbetti; Caffè, tè e cacao e loro succedanei; Cereali lavorati, amidi e prodotti da essi derivati, preparati da forno e lieviti; Cereali; Farine alimentari; Preparati fatti di cereali; Pane; Sale; Senape; Aceto; Aromatizzanti; Spezie; Condimenti; Snack a base di cereali; Snack a base di farina di patate; Snack a base di riso; Biscotti; Riso; Paté in crosta; Alimenti a base di farina; Sandwiches; Pizze.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Konditerijos gaminiai; Kepiniai; Šokoladas ir šokoladiniai saldainiai; Konditeriniai saldainiai (nevaistiniai); Saldainiai, batonėliai ir kramtomoji guma; Konditeriniai batonėliai; Padažai [uždarai]; Ledas, ledai, šaldytas jogurtas ir šerbetas; Kava, arbata ir kakava bei jų pakaitalai; Apdoroti grūdai, krakmolas ir jų gaminiai, preparatai kepimo reikmėms ir mielės; Grūdai; Miltai; Grūdų produktai; Duona; Druska; Garstyčios; Actas; Prieskoniai [kvapieji]; Prieskoniai; Prieskoniai; Javiniai užkandžiai; Užkandiniai gaminiai iš bulvių miltų; Ryžių užkandžiai; Biskvitai; Ryžiai; Pyragai su pašteto įdaru; Miltiniai maisto produktai; Sumuštiniai; Picos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Konditorejas izstrādājumi; Maizes produkti; Šokolāde; Konditorejas saldumi bez ārstnieciskām piedevām; Saldumi (konfektes), konfekšu tāfelītes un košļājamās gumijas; Saldumu tāfelītes; Mērces [garšvielu mērces]; Pārtikas ledus, saldējums, saldēts jogurts un sorbets; Kafija, tēja, kakao un to aizstājēji; Apstrādāti graudi, ciete un no tiem ražoti produkti, piedevas cepšanai un raugs; Graudaugu produkti; Milti; Graudaugu produkti; Maize; Sāls; Sinepes; Etiķis; Garšaugi; Garšvielas; Garšvielu mērces; Uzkodas uz graudaugu bāzes; No kartupeļu miltiem pagatavoti uzkodu pārtikas produkti; Uzkodas uz rīsu bāzes; Toršu mīkla; Rīsi; Pastēte mīklā; Miltu ēdieni; Sviestmaizes; Picas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ħelu; Prodotti tal-ħami; Ċikkulata; Ħlewwiet tal-kandju mhux immedikati; Ħelu (kandju), bars tal-kandju u chewing gum; Biċċiet solidi tal-ħelu; Zlazi [kondimenti]; Silġ, ġelati, jogurts iffriżati u sorbets; Kafè, te u kawkaw u sostituti tagħhom; Qamħ proċessat, lamtu, u prodotti magħmula minnhom, preparazzjonijiet għall-ħami u ħmira; Ċereali; Dqiq; Ċereali; Ħobż; Melħ; Mustarda; Ħall; Ħwawar; Ħwawar; Kondimenti; Ikel ħafif magħmul miċ-ċereali; Prodotti tal-ikel ħfief magħmula mid-dqiq tal-patata; Ikliet ħfief ibbażati fuq ir-ross; Għaġina tal-kejk; Ross; Patè bl-għaġina; Ikel dqiqi; Sandwiċis; Pizez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Suikergoed; Bakkerijproducten; Chocolade; Niet-medicinaal suikersnoepgoed; Zoetigheden (snoep), snoeprepen en kauwgom; Snoepgoedrepen; Kruidensausen; Ijs, roomijs, yoghurtijs en waterijs; Koffie, thee en cacao en vervangingsmiddelen hiervoor; Bewerkte granen, zetmeel en producten hiervan, preparaten voor het bakken en gist; Granen; Meel; Graanpreparaten; Brood; Zout; Mosterd; Azijn; Kruiderijen; Specerijen; Kruiden [specerijen]; Versnaperingen op basis van granen; Snacks gemaakt van aardappelmeel; Versnaperingen op basis van rijst; Koekjes; Rijst; Vleespasteien; Gerechten op basis van meel; Belegde broodjes; Pizza's.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Wyroby cukiernicze; Wyroby piekarnicze; Czekolada; Nielecznicze słodycze [wyroby cukiernicze]; Cukierki, batony i guma do żucia; Batoniki cukiernicze; Sosy [przyprawy]; Lód, lody spożywcze, mrożone jogurty i sorbety; Kawa, herbata, kakao i namiastki tych towarów; Ziarna przetworzone, skrobia i wyroby z tych towarów, preparaty do pieczenia i drożdze; Zboża; Mąka; Zboża; Chleb; Sól; Musztarda; Ocet; Przyprawy korzenne; Przyprawy; Przyprawy; Przekąski na bazie zbóż; Przekąski przyrządzone z mąki ziemniaczanej; Przekąski na bazie ryżu; Ciasto na wypieki; Ryż; Pasztet w cieście (pâté en croute); Potrawy na bazie mąki; Kanapki; Pizza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Produtos de confeitaria; Produtos de padaria; Chocolate; Guloseimas não medicinais; Doces (guloseimas), barras de chocolate e pastilhas elásticas; Barras de confeitaria; Molhos [condimentos]; Gelo, gelados, iogurtes gelados e sorvetes; Café, chás e cacau e substitutos dos mesmos; Grãos processados, amidos, e produtos feitos a partir dos mesmos, preparações de cozedura e leveduras; Cereais; Farinhas alimentares; Preparações à base de cereais; Pão; Sal; Mostarda; Vinagres; Temperos; Especiarias; Condimentos; Snacks à base de cereais; Aperitivos feitos com farinha de batata; Snacks à base de arroz; Biscoitos [bolinhos]; Arroz; Patés; Alimentos à base de farinha [farináceos]; Sandwiches; Pizzas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Dulciuri; Produse de brutărie; Ciocolată; Bomboane nemedicinale (cofetărie); Dulciuri (bomboane), tablete de ciocolată şi gumă de mestecat; Batoane dulci; Sosuri [condimente]; Gheaţă, îngheţată, iaurt îngheţat şi şerbeturi; Cafea, ceaiuri, cacao şi înlocuitori ai acestora; Seminţe procesate, amidon şi produsele acestora, preparate coapte şi drojdie; Cereale; Făină; Cereale; Pâine; Sare; Muştar; Oţet; Mirodenii; Mirodenii; Condimente; Gustări pe bază de cereale; Produse pentru gustări preparate din făină de cartofi; Gustări pe bază de orez; Torturi; Orez; Pâtés en croute; Mâncăruri pe bază de făină; Sandvişuri; Pizza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Cukrovinky; Pekárske výrobky; Čokoláda; Neliečivé cukrárske cukrovinky; Cukríky, sladké tyčinky a žuvačky; Cukrovinky vo forme tyčiniek; Omáčky (chuťové prísady); Potravinársky ľad, zmrzliny, mrazené jogurty a sorbety; Káva, čaj, kakao a ich náhradky; Spracované semená, škroby a produkty z nich vyrobené, prípravky na pečenie a droždia; Prípravky z obilnín; Múka; Prípravky z obilnín; Chlieb; Soľ; Horčica; Ocot; Koreniny; Korenie; Chuťové prísady; Obilninové chuťovky; Chuťovky vyrobené zo zemiakovej múky; Ryžové chuťovky; Jemné pečivárske výrobky; Ryža; Paštéty zapekané v ceste; Múčne jedlá; Sendviče; Pizza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Slaščice; Pekovski izdelki; Čokolada; Bomboni brez zdravilnih učinkovin; Sladkarije (bonboni), sladke ploščice in žvečilni gumi; Slaščice v obliki ploščic; Omake [začimbe]; Led, sladoledi, zamrznjeni jogurti in sorbeti; Kava, čaji in kakav ter nadomestki naštetega; Predelano zrnje, škrobi, in proizvodi narejeni iz naštetega, sredstva za peko in kvasila; Žitarice; Moka; Žitarice; Kruh; Sol; Gorčica; Kis; Dišave, začimbe (rastlinskega izvora, največkrat v prahu); Začimbe; Začimbni dodatki jedem (sol, kis, gorčica); Prigrizki iz žitaric; Prigrizki izdelani iz krompirjeve moke; Prigrizki na riževi osnovi; Testo za torte; Riž; Pasteta v testu; Močnate jedi; Sendviči; Pice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Konfekt; Bagerivaror; Choklad; Icke-medicinsk konfekt och godsaker; Godis, konfektyrbitar och tuggummi; Godisbitar; Såser [smaktillsatser]; Is, glass, fryst yoghurt och sorbet; Kaffe, te och kakao och ersättningar därtill; Bearbetat korn, stärkelse samt varor framställda av dessa, preparat för bakning samt jäst; Spannmål; Mjöl; Spannmål; Bröd; Salt; Senap; Vinäger; Kryddor; Kryddor; Smaktillsatser (såser); Sädesbaserade tilltugg; Snackmatsprodukter gjorda av potatismjöl; Risbaserade tilltugg; Kakdeg; Ris; Piroger; Mjölbaserade maträtter; Smörgåsar; Pizzor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/082</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/152</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-12</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080668</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>12102</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
