<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T11:10:28</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229221</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229221</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Qililandiy</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Шивашка креда; Модели на бродерии [образци, мостри]; Шнурове за подвързване на книги; Хартия; Копринена хартия; Картон; Книжки за дейности със стикери; Кламери; Тъкани за подвързване на книги; Декоративни хартиени украси за маса; Декоративни стикери за шлемове; Хартиени украси за партита; Знамена [от хартия]; Декоративни гирлянди от хартия за партита; Платна за рисуване на картини; Висящи етикети от хартия; Комплекти за бюра; Канцеларски офис материали; Модели за плетене; Японска ръчно изработена хартия.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Krejčovské křídy; Vzory na vyšívání; Provázky a nitě pro knižní vazby; Papír; Hedvábný papír; Lepenka; Pracovní sešity s nálepkami; Sponky na papír; Látky na knižní vazby; Papírové ozdoby na stůl; Ozdobné nálepky na přilby; Papírové ozdoby na večírky; Papírové vlajky; Papírové dekorativní girlandy na večírky; Šablony; Papírové závěsné štítky; Stolní sady; Kancelářské potřeby; Pletací vzory; Japonský ručně dělaný papír.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Skrædderkridt; Broderimønstre; Tråd til bogbinding; Papir; Silkepapir; Pap; Aktivitetsbøger med klistermærker; Papirclips; Stof til bogbinding; Borddekorationer af papir; Pynteklistermærker til hjelme; Festdekorationer af papir; Flag af papir; Dekorative papirguirlander til fester; Stencilplader; Hængemærkater af papir; Skrivebordssæt; Papirhandlervarer til kontorbrug; Strikkemønstre; Japansk papir til kunsthåndværk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Schneiderkreide; Stickmuster; Buchbindegarn; Papier; Taschentuchpapier; Pappe; Stickeralben für Kinder; Notizklemmen [Papeteriewaren]; Buchbinderstoffe; Papiermittelstücke für Dekorationszwecke; Dekorative Aufkleber für Helme; Partydekorationen aus Papier; Fahnen aus Papier; Dekorative Papiergirlanden für Partys; Schriftschablonen; Papieranhängeetiketten; Schreibtisch-Sets; Papier- und Schreibwaren für Büros; Strickmuster; Japanische Kunsthandwerksstücke aus Papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κιμωλία μοδιστρικής· Κεντήματος (Σχέδια -)· Σύρματα για βιβλιοδεσίες· Χαρτί· Λεπτό χαρτί, μεταξύ άλλων για προϊόντα υγιεινής· Χαρτόνι· Βιβλία δραστηριοτήτων με αυτοκόλλητα· Συνδετήρες εγγράφων· Υφάσματα βιβλιοδεσίας· Χάρτινα διακοσμητικά για το κέντρο του τραπεζιού· Διακοσμητικά αυτοκόλλητα για κράνη· Χάρτινα διακοσμητικά για πάρτι· Σημαίες [από χαρτί]· Διακοσμητικές γιρλάντες από χαρτί για πάρτι· Καμβάς ζωγραφικής· Χάρτινες κρεμαστές ετικέτες· Σετ γραφείου· Γραφική ύλη γραφείου· Σχέδια πλεκτικής· Ιαπωνικό χαρτί χειροτεχνίας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Tailors' chalk; embroidery designs [patterns]; cords for bookbinding; paper; tissue paper; cardboard; sticker books; paper-clips; fabrics for bookbinding; decorative paper centerpieces; decorative stickers for helmets; party ornaments of paper; flags of paper; Decorative paper garlands for parties; stencil plates; paper hangtags; desk sets; office stationery; knitting patterns; Japanese handicraft paper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Jabón de sastre; Patrones de bordado; Hilos de encuadernación; Papel; Papel de seda; Cartón; Libros de actividades con pegatinas; Pinzas para sujetar papeles; Tejidos de encuadernación; Centros de mesa decorativos de papel; Pegatinas decorativas para cascos; Decoraciones de papel para fiestas; Banderas de papel; Guirnaldas decorativas de papel para fiestas; Plantillas de estarcir; Etiquetas colgantes de papel; Sets de escritorio; Material de papelería para oficinas; Patrones para punto; Papel de manualidades japonés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rätsepakriit; Tikandite mustrilehed; Raamatuköitmisnöörid; Paber; Kosmeetiliste salvrätikute paber; Papp, kartong; Kleebistega tegevusraamatud; Kirjaklambrid; Raamatuköiteriie; Dekoratiivsed paberkaunistused; Dekoratiivkleebised kiivritele; Paberist peokaunistused; Paberist lipud, plagud; Pidudel kasutatavad paberist dekoratiivvanikud; Joonestustrafaretid; Paberist rippsildid; Kirjutustarvete komplektid töölaudadele; Kantseleitarbed; Kudumismustrid; Jaapani käsitööpaber.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatturinliitu; Koruompelumallit; Kirjansidontapunokset; Paperi; Käärinpaperi; Pahvi; Tarroja sisältävät puuhakirjat; Paperiklemmarit; Kankaat kirjansidontaan; Paperiset koristeet pöydän keskelle; Koristetarrat kypäröihin; Paperiset juhlakoristeet; Liput (Paperi -); Paperiset koristeköynnökset juhliin; Kangas öljyvärimaalaukseen; Paperiset ripustettavat nimilaput; Työpöytätarvikesarjat; Toimistojen paperitarvikkeet; Neulekaavat; Japanilainen käsityöpaperi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Craie pour tailleurs; Modèles de broderie; Fils pour reliures; Papier; Papier de soie; Carton; Livres d'activités avec autocollants; Pince-notes; Étoffes pour reliures; Centres de table décoratifs en papier; Autocollants décoratifs pour casques; Décorations de fête en papier; Drapeaux en papier; Guirlandes décoratives en papier pour fêtes; Pochoirs; Étiquettes volantes en papier; Parures de bureau; Fournitures de bureau; Patrons pour tricot; Papier japonais pour travaux manuels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Krojačke krede; Modeli za vezenje; Kanap za uvezivanje knjiga; Papir; Svileni papir; Ljepenka [karton]; Knjige aktivnosti s naljepnicama; Spajalice za papir; Tkanina za uvezivanje; Ukrasi od papira za sredinu stola; Ukrasne naljepnice za kacige; Papirnate dekoracije za zabave; Papirnate zastavice; Ukrasne papirnate girlande za proslave; Platno za slike; Papirnate viseće etikete; Stolni setovi; Uredski pisaći pribor; Uzorci za pletenje; Japanski papir za rukotvorine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szabókréta; Hímzőminták; Könyvkötő fonalak; Papír; Selyempapír; Karton; Matricás foglalkoztató könyvek; Gémkapocs; Könyvkötő szövetek; Papír asztaldíszek; Díszítő matricák sisakokra; Ünnepi papír dekorációk [partikra]; Zászlók papírból; Dekoratív papír girlandok partikra; Festővásznak; Papírból készült függőcímkék; Íróasztali szettek; Irodaszerek; Kötésminták; Japán kézművespapír.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Gessetti per sarti; Modelli di ricamo; Fili per rilegature; Carta; Carta velina; Cartone; Libri-gioco con adesivi; Graffette da ufficio; Stoffe per legatorie; Centrotavola decorativi di carta; Adesivi ornamentali per caschi; Decorazioni in carta per feste; Gagliardetti di carta; Ghirlande decorative in carta per feste; Maschere per la pittura; Targhette pendenti di carta; Set da scrivania; Articoli di cartoleria per ufficio; Modelli per maglieria; Carta giapponese per artigianato.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Siuvėjų kreida; Siuvinėjamų piešinių pavyzdžiai; Knygų įrišimo siūlai, virvutės; Popierius; Plonasis popierius; Kartonas; Užduočių knygelės su lipdukais; Popieriaus sąvaržėlės; Knygų įrišimo siūlai; Dekoratyviniai popieriniai papuošimai; Dekoratyviniai šalmo lipdukai; Popierinės švenčių dekoracijos; Popierinės vėliavėlės; Dekoratyvinės šventinės girliandos iš popieriaus; Estampai; Popierinės pakabinamos etiketės; Rašomojo stalo komplektai; Biuro reikmenys; Mezgimo raštų pavyzdžiai; Japoniškas rankdarbių popierius.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Drēbnieku krītiņi; Izšūšanas raksti (paraugi); Auklas grāmatu iesiešanai; Papīrs; Papīrs salvetēm; Kartons; Uzlīmju darba burtnīcas; Papīra saspraudes; Audumi grāmatu iesiešanai; Novietošanai galda centrā paredzēti rotājumi no papīra; Dekoratīvas uzlīmes ķiverēm; Svinību dekorācijas no papīra; Papīra karodziņi; Dekoratīvas papīra virtenes ballītēm; Trafaretu plāksnes; Piekaramās birkas no papīra; Rakstāmgalda piederumu komplekti; Kancelejas preces birojam; Adīšanas rakstu paraugi; Japāņu rokdarbu papīrs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ġibs tal-ħajjata; Disinni tar-rakkmu; Spag għal-legatura tal-kotba; Karti; Karta tat-tixù; Kartunċin; Kotba li fuqhom jitwaħħlu l-istikers; Klipps tal-karti; Drapp għall-użu fil-legatura; Dekorazzjonijiet għal fuq il-mejda magħmula mill-karti; Stikers dekorattivi għall-elmi; Dekorazzjonijiet tal-karti għal festini; Bnadar tal-karti; Girlandi dekorattivi tal-karti għall-festini; Kanvas għat-tpinġija; Tikketti tal-karti li jiddendlu; Settijiet tal-iskrivanija; Materjal tal-kartolerija għall-uffiċċju; Mudelli għall-innittjar; Karta Ġappuniża tax-xogħol tal-artiġjanat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kleermakerskrijt; Borduurpatronen; Draad voor het boekbinden; Papier; Zijdepapier; Karton; Activiteitenboeken met stickers; Paperclips; Stoffen voor het boekbinden; Decoratieve middenstukjes van papier; Decoratieve stickers voor helmen; Papieren feestdecoraties; Vlaggen van papier; Decoratieve slingers van papier voor feestjes; Tekensjablonen; Losse etiketten van papier; Bureausets; Kantoorartikelen; Breipatronen; Knutselpapier (Japans -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kreda krawiecka; Wzory do haftowania; Sznurek introligatorski; Papier; Bibułka; Karton; Zeszyty ćwiczeń z naklejkami; Spinacze do papieru; Tkaniny introligatorskie; Dekoracje na środek stołu z papieru; Dekoracyjne naklejki na kaski; Ozdoby papierowe na przyjęcia; Chorągiewki papierowe; Papierowe dekoracyjne girlandy na przyjęcia; Płótna malarskie; Papierowe metki [zawieszki]; Zestawy na biurko; Artykuły biurowe; Szablony do dziergania; Japoński papier rękodzielniczy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Giz para alfaiates; Modelos de bordados [padrões]; Fios para encadernações; Papel; Papel de seda; Cartão; Livros de atividades à base de autocolantes; Clips para papéis; Tecidos para encadernações; Centros de mesa decorativos de papel; Autocolantes decorativos para capacetes; Decorações em papel para festas; Bandeiras em papel; Grinaldas decorativas de papel para festas; Pochoirs [moldes recortados para pintar]; Etiquetas de papel; Conjuntos para secretária; Artigos de papelaria para escritório; Padrões para tricô; Papel japonês para trabalhos manuais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cretă pentru croitorie; Modele de broderie; Sfoară de legătorie; Hârtie; Hârtie pentru șervețele; Carton; Cărți cu abțibilduri pentru activități; Agrafe de birou pentru hârtie; Pânză pentru legătorie; Articole decorative din hârtie pentru centrul mesei; Abțibilduri decorative pentru căști; Decorațiuni din hârtie pentru petreceri; Stegulețe din hârtie; Ghirlande decorative din hârtie pentru petreceri; Plăcute pentru șabloane; Etichete de agățat din hârtie; Seturi de birou; Articole de papetărie pentru birou; Modele pentru tricotat; Hârtie japoneză pentru lucrări de artizanat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Krajčírska krieda; Výšivkové vzory; Knihárske nite; Papier; Hodvábny papier; Kartón, lepenka; Pracovné zošity so samolepkami; Kancelárske sponky; Knihárske textílie; Dekoratívne papierové ozdoby na stred stola; Dekoratívne nálepky pre helmy; Papierové ozdoby na oslavy; Papierové zástavy; Papierové ozdobné girlandy na oslavy; Šablóny na kreslenie a maľovanie; Papierové štítky; Stojanové súpravy na stoly; Kancelárske potreby; Pletacie vzory; Japonský remeselnícky papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Krojaška kreda; Vzorci za vezenje; Vrvice za vezavo knjig; Papir; Svileni papir; Lepenka; Igralne knjige z nalepkami; Papirne sponke; Blago za vezavo knjig; Papirnate dekoracije za na mizo; Okrasne nalepke za čelade; Papirnati okraski za zabave; Zastavice (papirnate); Okrasne girlande iz papirja, za zabave; Slikarsko platno; Viseče oznake iz papirja; Namizni seti; Pisarniški material; Vzorci za pletenje; Papir za japonska ročna dela.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Skräddarkritor; Broderimönster; Bokbinderigarn; Papper; Silkespapper; Kartong; Klistermärkesböcker; Pappersgem; Väv för bokbindning; Pappersdekorationer för bord; Dekorativa klistermärken för hjälmar; Festdekorationer av papper; Flaggor av papper; Dekorativa pappersgirlanger för fester; Stencilplåtar; Hängetiketter av papper; Skrivbordsset; Pappersvaror för kontorsändamål; Mönster för stickning; Japanskt hantverkspapper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/081</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-30</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/150</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081922</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017950422</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-05-27</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
