<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-20T08:29:23</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229309</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229309</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-19</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-20</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>2R</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>36</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Финансови сделки; Финансови сделки; Управление на активи; Управление на инвестиции; Съвети по управление на имущество; Инвестиционно управление и консултантски услуги; Информационни, административни и консултантски услуги, свързани с всички горепосочени услуги.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby finanční; Služby finanční; Správa aktiv; Investiční management; Poradenství zaměřené na zprávu majetku; Správa investic a konzultační služby; Informační, administrativní a poradenské služby vztahující se ke všem výše uvedeným službám.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Finansiel virksomhed; Finansiel virksomhed; Forvaltning af aktiver; Forvaltning af investeringer; Rådgivning vedrørende formueforvaltning; Investeringsforvaltning og rådgivning; Tjenester i form af information, administration og rådgivning vedrørende alle førnævnte tjenester.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Finanzwesen; Finanzwesen; Anlagenverwaltung; Kapitalanlagenmanagement; Beratung in Fragen der Vermögensverwaltung; Anlageverwaltung und -beratung; Information, Verwaltung und Beratung in Bezug auf alle vorstehend genannten Dienstleistungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Χρηματοπιστωτικές υποθέσεις· Οικονομικές υπηρεσίες· Διαχείριση στοιχείων ενεργητικού· Διαχείριση επενδύσεων· Παροχή συμβουλών σε θέματα διαχείρισης περιουσίας· Διαχείριση επενδύσεων και υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών· Υπηρεσίες παροχής πληροφοριών, διοίκησης και παροχής συμβουλών και διαχείρισης σε σχέση με το σύνολο των προαναφερόμενων υπηρεσιών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Financial affairs; financial services; asset management; investment management; asset management consultancy; investment management consultancy; information, administration and advisory services relating to all the aforementioned services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Operaciones financieras; Servicios financieros; Gestión de activos; Gestión de inversiones; Asesoramiento en gestión de patrimonio; Gestión de inversiones y servicios de asesoramiento; Servicios de información, administración y asesoramiento en relación con todos los servicios mencionados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rahalised tehingud; Finantsteenused; Varahaldus; Investeeringute haldamine; Pärandi haldamise alane nõustamine; Investeeringute haldus- ja nõustamisteenused; Teabe-, haldus- ja nõustamisteenused kõikide eespool nimetatud teenuste alal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Rahatalousasiat; Rahoituspalvelut; Varainhoito; Sijoitusten hallinta; Omaisuuden hallintaan liittyvä neuvonta; Sijoitusten hallinta ja neuvontapalvelut; Tiedotus-, hallinnointi- ja neuvontapalvelut, jotka liittyvät kaikkiin edellä mainittuihin palveluihin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Affaires financières; Services financiers; Gestion d'actifs; Gestion d'investissements; Conseil en gestion de patrimoine; Gestion d'investissements et services de conseils; Services d'informations, d'assistance et de conseils relatifs à tous les services précités.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Financijski poslovi; Financijske usluge; Upravljanje aktivom; Upravljanje ulaganjem; Savjetovanje o upravljanju imovinom; Upravljanje investicijama i savjetodavne usluge; Informacijske, administrativne i savjetodavne usluge u vezi sa svim gore navedenim uslugama.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Pénzügyi ügyletek; Pénzügyi szolgáltatások; Vagyonkezelési szolgáltatások; Befektetés menedzsment; Tanácsadás vagyonkezeléssel kapcsolatban; Befektetésőrzési szolgáltatások és szaktanácsadási szolgáltatások; Információs, adminisztrációs és tanácsadási szolgáltatások az összes fent említett szolgáltatással kapcsolatban.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Affari finanziari; Affari finanziari; Servizi di gestione patrimoniale; Gestione di investimenti; Consulenza in materia di gestione di patrimoni; Gestione d'investimenti e consulenza; Servizi d'informazione, amministrazione e consulenza relativi a tutti i servizi summenzionati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Finansinės operacijos; Finansinės paslaugos; Turto valdymas; Investicijų valdymas; Konsultavimas paveldo administravimo klausimais; Investicijų valdymas ir konsultavimas; Informacijos, administravimo ir patariamosios paslaugos, susijusios su visomis anksčiau paminėtomis paslaugomis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Finanšu lietas; Finanšu pakalpojumi; Aktīvu pārvaldes pakalpojumi; Ieguldījumu pārvaldība; Ieteikumi par īpašuma vadīšanu; Ieguldījumu pārvaldība un konsultāciju pakalpojumi; Informācijas, administrēšanas un konsultāciju pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar visiem iepriekšminētajiem pakalpojumiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Affarijiet finanzjarji; Servizzi f'finanzi; Il-ġestjoni ta' assi; Il-ġestjoni ta' investimenti; Pariri dwar il-ġestjoni finanzjarja; Żamma ta' investimenti u servizzi ta' konsulenza; Servizzi ta' informazzjoni, amministrazzjoni u għoti ta' pariri marbuta mas-servizzi kollha msemmija qabel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Financiële zaken; Financiële diensten; Vermogensbeheer; Beheer van investeringen; Adviezen op het gebied van vermogensbeheer; beleggingsbeheer en adviesdiensten; Informatie, raadgeving en administratie met betrekking tot alle voornoemde diensten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Działalność finansowa; Usługi finansowe; Zarządzanie aktywami; Zarządzanie inwestycjami; Doradztwo związane z zarządzaniem dziedzictwem; Zarządzanie inwestycjami finansowymi i usługi doradcze; Usługi informacyjne, administracyjne i doradcze związane ze wszystkimi wyżej wymienionymi usługami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Negócios financeiros; Serviços financeiros; Gestão de ativos; Gestão de investimentos; Consultadoria em matéria de gestão de património; Gestão de investimentos e serviços de consultoria; Serviços de informações, administração e assessoria relacionados com todos os serviços atrás referidos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Afaceri financiare; Servicii financiare; Gestionare a activelor; Gestiunea investiţiilor; Consultanta in gestionarea patrimoniului; Gestionarea investiţiilor şi servicii de consultanţă; Servicii de informații, administrare și asistență referitoare la toate serviciile susmenționate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Finančné služby; Služby v oblasti finančníctva; Manažment aktív; Investičný manažment; Poradenstvo v oblasti správy majetku; Správa investícií a poradenské služby; Poradenské, administratívne a poradenské služby súvisiace s vyššie uvedenými službami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Finančni posli; Finančne storitve; Upravljanje premoženja; Upravljanje investicij; Svetovanje pri upravljanju premoženja; Nadzor naložb in svetovalne storitve; Storitve informacij, administracije in svetovanja v zvezi z vsemi prej navedenimi storitvami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Finansiella tjänster; Finansiella tjänster; Förvaltning av tillgångar; Förvaltning av investeringar; Rådgivning avseende förmögenhetsförvaltning; Investeringsförvaltning och konsulttjänster; Information, administration och rådgivning rörande ovannämnda tjänster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/088</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-12</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/158</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-20</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1082062</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>88472</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
