<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-10T08:51:51</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229616</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229616</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-25</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>es</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-28</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ADAGIO CERAMICAS</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Уреди за осветление, отопление, парогенериране, готвене, охлаждане, сушене, вентилация, водоснабдяване и за санитарни цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přístroje pro osvětlení, topení, výrobu páry, pro vaření, přístroje chladicí, pro sušení, ventilaci, rozvod vody a sanitární zařízení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Apparater til belysning, opvarmning, dampdannelse, madlavning, køling, tørring, ventilation og vandforsyning, samt til sanitære formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Beleuchtungs-, Heizungs-, Dampferzeugungs-, Koch-, Kühl-, Trocken-, Lüftungs- und Wasserleitungsgeräte sowie sanitäre Anlagen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές και συστήματα φωτισμού, θέρμανσης, παραγωγής ατμού, μαγειρέματος, ψύξης, αποξήρανσης, αερισμού, υδροδότησης και εγκαταστάσεις υγειϊνής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Apparatus for lighting, heating, steam generating, cooking, refrigerating, drying, ventilating, water supply and sanitary purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de alumbrado, calefacción, producción de vapor, cocción, refrigeración, secado, ventilación y distribución de agua, así como instalaciones sanitarias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Valgustus-, kütteseadmed, aurugeneraatorid, toiduainete kuumtöötlusseadmed, jahutusseadmed, kuivatus-, ventilatsiooni-, veevarustus- ja sanitaarseadmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Valaistus-, lämmitys-, höyrynkehitys-, keitto-, jäähdytys-, kuivatus-, ilmastointi-, vesihuolto- ja saniteettilaitteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils d'éclairage, de chauffage, de production de vapeur, de cuisson, de réfrigération, de séchage, de ventilation, de distribution d'eau et installations sanitaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Uređaji za rasvjetu, grijanje, proizvodnju pare, kuhanje, hlađenje, sušenje, ventilaciju, vodoopskrbu i sanitarna oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Világító-, fűtő-, gőzfejlesztő, főző-, hűtő-, szárító-, szellőztető-, vízszolgáltató és egészségügyi berendezések.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi di illuminazione, di riscaldamento, di produzione di vapore, di cottura, di refrigerazione, di essiccamento, di ventilazione, di distribuzione d'acqua e impianti sanitari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Apšvietimo, šildymo, garų gamybos, valgio virimo, šaldymo, džiovinimo, vėdinimo, vandens tiekimo ir sanitariniai įrenginiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apgaismošanas, apsildes, tvaika ražošanas, ēdiena termiskās apstrādes, dzesēšanas, žāvēšanas, vēdināšanas, ūdensapgādes un sanitārtehniskās ierīces un aparāti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat li jagħti d-dawl, li jsaħħan, li jiġġenera l-fwar, li jsajjar, li jkessaħ, li jnixxef, li jagħti ventilazzjoni, li jipprovdi l-ilma u għal użu sanitarju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verlichtings-, verwarmings-, stoomopwekkings-, kook-, koel-, droog-, ventilatie- en waterleidingsapparaten en sanitaire installaties.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia do oświetlania, ogrzewania, wytwarzania pary, gotowania, chłodzenia, suszenia, wentylacji, zaopatrzenia w wodę oraz instalacje sanitarne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos de iluminação, de aquecimento, de produção de vapor, de cozedura, de refrigeração, de secagem, de ventilação, de distribuição de água e instalações sanitárias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate de iluminat, de incălzit, de producere a vaporilor, de coacere, de refrigerare, de uscare, de ventilare, de distribuire a apei şi instalaţii sanitare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zariadenia na osvetľovanie, vykurovanie, parné kotly, zariadenia na varenie, chladenie a sušenie, vetracie, vodárenské a sanitárne zariadenia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Naprave za osvetljevanje, ogrevanje, proizvodnjo pare, kuhanje, hlajenje, sušenje, prezračevanje, vodovodne in sanitarne instalacije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Apparater för belysning, uppvärmning, ångalstring, kokning, kylning, torkning, ventilation, vattenförsörjning och sanitära ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>19</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Фаянсови плочки, подови плочки, материали за облицоване на стени и полагане на подови настилки, керамични материали, смес от глина и кварцов пясък, и порцелан.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Glazované obkladové dlaždice, podlahové dlaždice, materiál pro obložení stěn a na podlahové krytiny z keramiky, pískovce a porcelánu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kakler, fliser, materialer til vægbeklædning og gulvbelægning, materialer af keramik, sandsten og porcelæn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Fliesen, Kacheln, Materialien für die Wandverkleidung und Fußbodenbeläge, aus Keramik, Sandstein und Porzellan.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εφυαλωμένα κεραμικά πλακίδια, λιθόπλακες, υλικά επένδυσης τοίχων και επίστρωσης δαπέδων, από κεραμικά υλικά, ψαμμίτη και πορσελάνη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Glazed ceramic tiles, tiles, materials for wall surfacing and floor paving of ceramic, sandstone or porcelain.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Azulejos, baldosas, materiales de revestimientos de paredes y pavimentación de suelos, de materiales cerámicos, de gres y porcelánicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Glasuurplaadid, põrandakivid, seina- ja põrandakattematerjalid, kõik valmistatuna keraamilistest, savi- või portselanmaterjalidest.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lasitiilet, laatat sekä keramiikasta, savesta ja posliinista valmistetut tarvikkeet seinien pinnoittamiseen ja lattioiden päällystämiseen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Carreaux vernissés, dalles, matériaux pour revêtement mural et pavement des sols, matériaux céramiques, en grès et porcelaine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pločice, podne pločice, materijali za oblaganje zidova i popločavanje podova od keramičkih materijala, opeke i porculanskih materijala.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Mázas kerámia csempe, padlóburkoló lapok, fal- és padlóburkolatok, kerámiából, homokkőből és porcelánból.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Piastrelle in ceramica vetrinate, mattonelle, materiali per rivestimento di pareti e per pavimentazione, materiali in ceramica, grès e porcellana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Glazūruotos keraminės plytelės, grindų plytelės, sienų ir grindų dangų medžiagos, iš keraminių medžiagų, smiltainio ir porceliano.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Glazētas flīzes, grīdas flīzes, sienu pārklājuma un grīdas seguma materiāli no keramikas, smilšakmens un porcelāna.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tajls, madum, materjal għall-kisi ta' ħitan u pavimentazzjoni ta' l-art, ta' materjal taċ-ċeramika, tal-fuħħar u tal-kina.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Tegels, plavuizen, materiaal voor muurbekleding en vloertegels, van keramiek, gres en porselein.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kafelki, płytki, materiały do pokrywania ścian i układania posadzek, z materiałów ceramicznych, gresu i porcelany.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Azulejos, ladrilhos, material de revestimento de paredes e pavimentação de soalhos, de materiais cerâmicos, de grés e porcelana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Dale de ceramica vitrificata, gresie, materiale pentru imbracarea peretilor si pardosire, de materiale ceramice, de gresie si portelanuri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Obkladačky, obkladačky, materiály pre obklady stien, dlaždenie podláh, z keramickýxh materiálov, kameniny a porcelánové.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Glazirane keramične ploščice, talne ploščice, materiali za stenske in talne obloge iz keramike, iz peščenjaka in porcelana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kakel, kakelplattor, väggbeklädnadsmaterial och golvbeläggning, material av keramik, sandsten och porslin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Реклама; Управление на търговски сделки; Търговска администрация; Административна дейност; Снабдяване за сметка на трети лица [закупуване на стоки или услуги за други предприятия]; Актуализиране на рекламни материали; Проучване на пазара; Търсене на спонсори; Бизнес проучвания; Подреждане на витрини; Представяне на стоки; Разпространение на реклами; Разпространение на мостри; Съставяне на извлечения от сметки; Проучване на пазара; Услуги за наемане на подизпълнители [търговско съдействие]; Фактуриране; Организиране на търговски панаири с търговска или рекламна цел; Търговско управление при лицензиране на стоки и услуги за трети лица; Управление на компютърни файлове; Информация в областта на бизнеса; Предоставяне на търговска информация и съвети за клиенти [център за потребителски съвети]; Изследвания с търговска цел; Изготвяне на ведомости; Психологическо тестване за подбор на кадри; Представяне на стоки с цел продажаба на дребно чрез всички средства за комуникация; Набиране на кадри; Експертни услуги по бизнес експедитивност; Проучване на общественото мнение; Услуги за продажба на едро и дребно в търговската мрежа и чрез световната компютърна мрежа на фаянс, теракот, материали за облицовка на стени и настилки за подове, керамични материали, гранит и порцелан, на апарати за осветление, настилки за баня от керамика.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Propagační činnost, reklama; Pomoc při řízení obchodní činnosti; Obchodní administrativa; Kancelářské práce; Dodavatelské služby pro třetí osoby [nákup výrobků a služeb pro jiné podniky]; Aktualizace reklamních materiálů; Průzkum trhu; Vyhledávání sponzorů; Obchodní průzkum; Aranžování výkladů; Předvádění zboží; Šíření reklam; Šíření vzorků; Vyhotovování výpisů z účtu; Průzkum trhu; Subdodavatelské služby [pomoc v obchodní činnosti]; Fakturace; Pořádání veletrhů pro obchodní či reklamní účely; Obchodní správa licencí k výrobkům a službám jiných osob; Vedení počítačové evidence; Obchodní nebo podnikatelské informace; Komerční informace a rady pro spotřebitele [spotřebitelská poradna]; Obchodní nebo podnikatelský průzkum; Příprava výplatních listin; Psychologické testování pro výběr zaměstnanců; Prezentace výrobků v komunikačních médiích pro účely maloobchodu; Nábor zaměstnanců; Služby odborníka na výkonnost podniku; Průzkum veřejného mínění; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní prodej obkládaček, dlaždic, obkladových materiálů na zeď, obkladů podlah, keramických materiálů, kameniny a porcelánu, přístrojů pro osvětlení a svícení, obkladů koupelen, umělecké keramiky v obchodech a prostřednictvím světových počítačových sítí.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed; Forretningsledelse; Forretningsadministration; Varetagelse af kontoropgaver; Bistand ved køb af varer og tjenesteydelser for andre; Ajourføring af reklamemateriale; Marketingsundersøgelser; Søgning efter sponsorater; Forretningsresearch; Dekoration af butiksvinduer; Demonstration af varer; Spredning af reklamemateriale; Distribution af vareprøver; Udarbejdelse af kontoopgørelser; Markedsforskning; Outsourcing [forretningsmæssig bistand]; Fakturering; Organisering af varemesser med kommercielle eller reklamemæssige formål; Kommerciel administration ved licensering af andres varer og tjenesteydelser; Administration af datastyrede arkiver; Information vedrørende forretningsvirksomhed; Kommerciel information og rådgivning til forbrugere [forbrugerrådgivning]; Forretningsundersøgelser; Udarbejdelse af lønningslister; Psykologiske tests ved udvælgelse af personale; Præsentation af varer på kommunikationsmedier til detailhandelsmæssige formål; Personalerekruttering; Tjenesteydelser udbudt af rationaliseringseksperter indenfor forretningsvirksomhed; Opinionsundersøgelser; Detail- og engrossalg i forretninger og via globale computernetværk af kakler, fliser, materialer til væg- og gulvbeklædning, materialer af keramik, sandsten og porcelæn, belysningsapparater, beklædning til bade af kunstnerisk keramik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werbung; Geschäftsführung; Unternehmensverwaltung; Büroarbeiten; Beschaffungsdienstleistungen für Dritte [Erwerb von Waren und Dienstleistungen für andere Unternehmen]; Aktualisierung von Werbematerial; Marktforschung; Sponsorensuche; Betriebswirtschaftliche Recherche; Dekorieren von Schaufenstern; Vorführung von Waren für Werbezwecke; Verbreitung von Werbeanzeigen; Verteilung von Warenproben zu Werbezwecken; Erstellung von Rechnungsauszügen; Marktforschung; Outsourcing-Dienste [Hilfe bei Geschäftsangelegenheiten]; Fakturierung; Veranstaltung von Messen zu gewerblichen oder zu Werbezwecken; Kommerzielle Verwaltung der Lizenzierung von Waren und Dienstleistungen für Dritte; Dateienverwaltung mittels Computer; Informationen in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Erteilung von Auskünften (Information) und Beratung für Verbraucher in Handels- und Geschäftsangelegenheiten [Verbraucherberatung]; Ermittlungen in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Lohn- und Gehaltsabrechnung; Personalauswahl mit Hilfe von psychologischen Eignungstests; Präsentation von Waren in Kommunikations-Medien, für den Einzelhandel; Personalanwerbung; Erstellung von Geschäftsgutachten; Meinungsforschung; Groß- und Einzelhandelsverkauf in Geschäften und über weltweite Computernetze von Fliesen, Kacheln, Materialien für Wandverkleidungen, Bodenbelägen, Materialien aus Keramik, Sandstein und Porzellan, Beleuchtungsgeräten, Verkleidungen für Badezimmer, Kunstgegenständen aus Keramik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαφήμιση· Διοίκηση επιχειρήσεων· Διαχείριση επιχειρήσεων· Εργασίες γραφείου· Εφοδιασμού για τρίτους (υπηρεσίες -) [αγορά προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για άλλες επιχειρήσεις]· Ενημέρωση για υλικό διαφημιστικό· Έρευνα αγοράς· Αναζήτηση χορηγίας· Επιχειρηματική έρευνα· Διακόσμηση βιτρινών· Επίδειξη προϊόντων· Διάδοση διαφημιστικού υλικού· Διανομή δειγμάτων· Κατάρτιση λογιστικών καταστάσεων· Έρευνα αγοράς· Υπηρεσίες υπεργολαβίας [παροχή βοηθείας σε επιχειρήσεις]· Εργασίες έκδοσης τιμολογίων· Οργάνωση εκθέσεων εμπορικών για σκοπούς εμπορικούς ή διαφημιστικούς· Εμπορική διοίκηση αδειών εκμετάλλευσης προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Διαχείρηση αρχείων πληροφορικής· Πληροφόρηση για επιχειρήσεις· Παροχή εμπορικών πληροφοριών και παροχή συμβουλών σε καταναλωτές [καταστήματα παροχής συμβουλών σε καταναλωτές]· Επιχειρηματική πραγματογνωμοσύνη· Κατάρτιση καταστάσεων μισθοδοσίας· Μέθοδοι ψυχοτεχνικές για επιλογή προσωπικού· Παρουσίαση αγαθών σε μέσα επικοινωνίας με σκοπό τη λιανική πώληση· Πρόσληψη προσωπικού· Υπηρεσίες ειδικού στην αποδοτικότητα των επιχειρήσεων· Δημοσκόπηση· Υπηρεσίες χονδρικής και λιανικής πώλησης, σε εμπορικά καταστήματα και μέσω παγκόσμιων ηλεκτρονικών δικτύων, οι οποίες αφορούν πλακίδια τοίχου, λιθόπλακες, υλικά επένδυσης τοίχων και επίστρωσης δαπέδων από κεραμικά υλικά, ψαμμίτη και πορσελάνη, συσκευές φωτισμού και φωταγώγησης, υλικά επίστρωσης λουτρών από καλλιτεχνική πορσελάνη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Advertising; Business management; Business administration; Office functions; Procurement services for others [purchasing goods and services for other businesses]; Updating of advertising material; Market research; Sponsorship search; Business research; Shop window dressing; Demonstration of goods; Dissemination of advertising matter; Sample distribution; Drawing up statements of account; Marketing studies; Outsourcing services [business assistance]; Invoicing; Organisation of trade fairs for commercial or advertising purposes; Commercial administration of the licensing of the goods and services of others; Computerized file management; Business information; Commercial information and advice for consumers [consumer advice shop]; Business investigation; Payroll preparation; Psychological testing for the selection of personnel; Presentation of goods on communication media, for retail purposes; Personnel recruitment; Business efficiency expert services; Opinion polling; Wholesaling and retailing in shops, and sale via global computer networks of tiles for building, wall lining and floor paving materials made of ceramic, sandstone and porcelain, lighting apparatus, bathroom linings, artistic ceramic.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicidad; Gestión de negocios comerciales; Administración comercial; Trabajos de oficina; Abastecimiento para terceros (servicios de -) [abastecimiento de productos y servicios para otras empresas]; Actualización de documentación publicitaria; Búsqueda de mercados; Búsqueda de patrocinadores; Búsquedas de negocios; Decoración de escaparates; Demostración de productos; Difusión de anuncios publicitarios; Distribución de muestras; Estados de cuenta (Elaboración de -); Estudio de mercados; Externalización (servicios de -) [asistencia comercial]; Facturación; Ferias (Organización de -) con fines comerciales o publicitarios; Gestión comercial de licencias de productos y servicios para terceros; Gestión de archivos informáticos; Información sobre negocios; Información y asesoramiento comerciales al consumidor; Investigación comercial; Nóminas (Preparación de -); Personal (Tests psicotécnicos para la selección de -); Presentación de productos en cualquier medio de comunicación para su venta al por menor; Selección de personal; Servicios de expertos en eficiencia empresarial; Sondeos de opinión; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor en comercios y a través de redes informáticas mundiales de azulejos, baldosas, materiales de revestimiento de paredes, pavimentación de suelos, de materiales cerámicos, de gres y porcelánicos, de aparatos de alumbrado e iluminación, de revestimientos para baño, de cerámica artística.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reklaam; Ärijuhtimine; Ärikorraldus; Kontoriteenused; Hanketeenused teistele ettevõtetele [kaupade ja teenuste ostmine]; Reklaammaterjalide ajakohastamine, moderniseerimine; Turu-uuringud; Sponsorite otsimine; Ärialased uuringud; Poeakende (vaateakende) kaunistamine, dekoreerimine; Kaupade demonstreerimine; Reklaammaterjalide levitamine; Näidiste (proovide) levitamine; Arvete seisu, bilansi koostamine; Turu-uuringud; Allhanketeenused [ärialane abi]; Arvete esitamine; Messide korraldamine äri või reklaami eesmärgil; Teiste omanike kaupade ja teenuste litsentsimise korraldamine äri eesmärgil; Arvutipõhine dokumendihaldus; Äriinfo, -teave; Äriteave ja klientide nõustamine [klientide nõustamiskeskus]; Ärialased uuringud; Palgalehtede koostamine; Psühholoogiline testimine personali valikuks; Kaupade jaemüügi reklaam meediakanalites; Tööjõu värbamine; Äri efektiivsuse ekspertiisid; Arvamusküsitlused; Keraamiliste plaatide, kivitahvlite, seina- ja põrandakattematerjalide, keraamiliste, fajanss- ja portselanmaterjalide, valgustusseadmete, vannitoa kattematerjalide, kunstkeraamika hulgi- ja jaemüük kauplustes ja ülemaailmse arvutivõrgu kaudu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mainonta; Liikkeenjohto; Yrityshallinto; Toimistotehtävät; Hankintapalvelut muille [tavaroiden ja palveluiden osto muille yrityksille]; Mainosmateriaalin päivitys; Markkinatutkimus; Sponsoroinnin etsintäpalvelut; Liikkeenhoitoa koskeva tutkimus; Näyteikkunoiden somistelu; Tavaroiden esittely; Mainosten jakelu; Tavaranäytteiden jakelu; Tilinpitoselvitys; Markkinatutkimus; Ulkoistamispalvelut [yritystoiminnan avustamisena]; Laskutus; Messujen järjestäminen kaupallisiin tai mainontatarkoituksiin; Kaupallinen hallinnointi koskien toisten tavaroiden ja palveluiden lisensointia; Tietokonetiedostojen hallinta; Informaatio (Liiketoiminta -); Kaupallinen kuluttajaneuvonta; Tutkimus liittyen liikkeenhoitoon; Palkkalistojen laadinta; Psykologinen testaus työhönoton yhteydessä; Tavaraesittely tietoliikennevälineissä vähittäismyyntiä varten; Henkilöstörekrytointi; Yritystehokkuutta koskevat asiantuntijapalvelut; Mielipidetutkimukset; Kaakelien, laattojen, keramiikasta, savesta ja posliinista valmistettujen seinien ja lattioiden päällystysmateriaalien, valaistuslaitteiden ja valaisimien, kylpyhuoneen päällystysmateriaalien taidekeramiikan tukku- ja vähittäismyyntipalvelut liikkeissä ja maailmanlaajuisten tietoverkkojen välityksellä.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publicité; Gestion des affaires commerciales; Administration commerciale; Travaux de bureau; Services d'approvisionnement pour des tiers [achat de produits et de services pour d'autres entreprises]; Mise à jour de documentation publicitaire; Étude de marché; Recherche de parraineurs; Recherches pour affaires; Décoration de vitrines; Démonstration de produits; Diffusion d'annonces publicitaires; Diffusion d'échantillons; Établissement de relevés de comptes; Étude de marché; Services de sous-traitance [assistance commerciale]; Facturation; Organisation de foires à buts commerciaux ou de publicité; Administration commerciale de licences de produits et de services de tiers; Services de gestion informatisée de fichiers; Informations d'affaires; Informations et conseils commerciaux aux consommateurs; Investigations pour affaires; Préparation de feuilles de paye; Sélection du personnel par procédés psychotechniques; Présentation de produits sur tout moyen de communication pour la vente au détail; Recrutement de personnel; Services d'expertise en productivité d'entreprise; Sondage d'opinion; Services de vente en gros et au détail dans les commerces, ainsi que via des réseaux informatiques mondiaux, de carreaux vernissés, dalles, matériaux de revêtement mural et pavement des sols, de matériaux en céramique, grès et porcelaine, et d'appareils d'éclairage, de revêtements pour salles de bains, de céramique artistique.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Oglašavanje; Vođenje komercijalnih poslova; Komercijalna administracija; Uredski poslovi; Nabava za treće osobe [usluge kupnje proizvoda i usluga za druga poduzeća]; Ažuriranje reklamnog materijala; Istraživanje tržišta; Traženje sponzorstva; Poslovna istraživanja; Uređenje izloga; Demonstracija proizvoda; Distribucija reklamnog materijala; Podjela [distribucija] uzoraka; Izrada izvoda računa; Istraživanje tržišta; Vanjske usluge [komercijalna pomoć]; Fakturiranje; Organiziranje trgovačkih sajmova u komercijalne ili reklamne svrhe; Komercijalno upravljanje u svezi licenci proizvoda i usluga trećih osoba; Vođenje informatičkih kartoteka; Poslovne obavijesti; Potrošači [pružanje komercijalni savjeta i informacija potrošačima]; Istraživanja za poslove; Priprema platnih paketa; Psihotehnički odabir osoblja; Prezentacija proizvoda na svim komunikacijskim sredstvima u svrhu prodaje na malo; Selekcija osoblja; Usluge stručnjaka za poslovnu učinkovitost; Ispitivanje javnog mnijenja; Usluge veleprodaje i maloprodaje u trgovinama i putem globalnih računalnih mreža pločica, podnih pločica, materijala za oblaganje zidova, podnih obloga, keramičkih, kamenih i porculanskih materijala, rasvjetnih uređaja i rasvjete, obloga za kupaonice, umjetničke keramike.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Reklámozás; Kereskedelmi ügyletek; Kereskedelmi adminisztráció; Irodai munkák; Beszerzői szolgáltatások [áruk illetve szolgáltatások beszerzése] mások számára; Reklámanyag frissítése; Piackutatás; Szponzorok felkutatása; Kutatások ügyletekkel kapcsolatban; Kirakatrendezés; Árubemutatás; Reklámterjesztés; Termékminták, áruminták terjesztése; Számlakivonatok összeállítása; Piackutatás; Outsourcing szolgáltatások [üzleti segítségnyújtás]; Számlázás; Kereskedelmi- vagy reklámcélú vásárok szervezése; Áruk és szolgáltatások engedélyezésének kereskedelmi ügyintézése; Számítógépes fájlkezelés, adatkezelés; Üzleti információk; Információ és tanácsadás fogyasztóknak [fogyasztói tanácsadás]; Üzleti vizsgálatok, kutatások; Bérszámfejtés; Személyzet kiválasztása pszichológiai eljárásokkal; Áruk bemutatása kommunikációs médiában, kiskereskedelmi célokból; Munkaerő-toborzás; Üzleti hatékonysági szakértő szolgáltatásai; Közvélemény-kutatás; Csempék, járólapok, kerámia-, homokkő- és porcelán falburkoló és padlóburkoló anyagok, valamint padlóburkolatok,kerámiák, kőlapok és porcelán anyagok, fűtő és világító készülékek, fürdőszobai burkolók, művészi kerámiák bolti kis- és nagykereskedelme, valamint eladása a számítógépes világhálón keresztül.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicità; Gestione di affari commerciali; Amministrazione commerciale; Lavori di ufficio; Servizi di approvvigionamento per conto terzi [acquisto di prodotti e di servizi par altre imprese]; Aggiornamento di materiale pubblicitario; Indagini di mercato; Ricerca di sponsor; Ricerche per affari; Decorazione di vetrine; Dimostrazione pratica di prodotti per scopi pubblicitari; Diffusione di annunci pubblicitari; Distribuzione di campioni per scopi pubblicitari; Stesura di estratti di conti; Ricerche di mercato; Servizi di subappalto [assistenza commerciale]; Fatturazione; Organizzazione di fiere per scopi commerciali o di pubblicità; Amministrazione commerciale di licenze di prodotti e di servizi di terzi; Servizi di gestione di archivi informatici; Informazioni di affari; Informazioni e consulenza commerciale ai consumatori; Investigazioni per affari; Preparazione di fogli di paga; Selezione di personale con procedimenti psicotecnici; Presentazione di prodotti con qualsiasi mezzo di comunicazione per la vendita al dettaglio; Reclutamento di personale; Servizi per la (ri) progettazione dei processi aziendali; Sondaggio di opinione; Servizi di vendita all'ingrosso e al dettaglio in negozi e tramite reti informatiche mondiali di piastrelle in ceramica vetrinate, mattonelle, materiali per rivestimento di pareti e per pavimentazione, materiali in ceramica, grès e porcellana, apparecchi di illuminazione, rivestimenti per bagni, ceramica artistica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Reklama; Verslo vadyba; Verslo tvarkyba; Įstaigų veikla; Tiekimo paslaugos kitiems [prekių ir paslaugų pirkimas kitiems verslams]; Reklaminės medžiagos tobulinimas; Rinkotyra; Rėmėjų paieška; Verslo tyrimai; Parduotuvių vitrinų puošimas [tvarkymas]; Prekių rodymas; Reklaminių skelbimų platinimas; Pavyzdžių platinimas; Sąskaitų būklės apyskaitų sudarymas; Rinkos tyrimai; Paslaugų nuoma [verslo pagalba]; Sąskaitų-faktūrų išrašymas; Mugių rengimas (komercijos ar reklamos reikmėms); Trečiųjų asmenų prekių ir paslaugų licencijavimo komercinis administravimas; Kompiuterizuotų rinkmenų tvarkymas; Verslo informacija; Komercinė informacija ir patarimai vartotojams [konsultacijų teikimas]; Verslo nagrinėjimas; Algalapių parengimas; Psichologinis testavimas personalo parinkimo reikmėms; Prekių pateikimas žiniasklaidoje pardavimo reikmėms; Personalo komplektavimas; Verslo efektyvumo (veiksmingumo) specialistų paslaugos; Nuomonių tyrimas; Didmeninės ir mažmeninės prekybos parduotuvėse ir per pasaulinius kompiuterių tinklus plytelėmis, keraminėmis plytelėmis, sienų dangos medžiagomis, grindų dangos medžiagomis, keraminėmis, smiltainio ir porceliano medžiagomis, apšvietimo aparatais, vonios kambario dangomis, meniniais keramikos dirbiniais paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reklāma; Darījumu vadīšana; Uzņēmumu pārvaldīšana; Biroja darbi; Uzņēmumu apgāde [preču un pakalpojumu sagāde trešo personu interesēs]; Reklāmas materiālu aktualizēšana; Tirgus izpēte; Sponsoru meklēšana; Darījumu izpēte; Veikalu skatlogu noformēšana; Preču demonstrēšanas pakalpojumi; Reklāmas izplatīšana; Paraugu izplatīšana; Aktu par savstarpējo norēķinu salīdzināšanu sagatavošana; Tirgus izpēte; Ārpakalpojumi (palīdzība uzņēmējdarbībā); Rēķinu izrakstīšanas pakalpojumi; Gadatirgu organizēšana komerciāliem un reklāmas nolūkiem; Preču un pakalpojumu licencēšanas komerciālā vadība citu personu labā; Datorizēta datņu (failu) pārvaldība; Darījumu informācijas sniegšana; Komerciāla informācija un padomi patērētājiem; Darījumu izpēte; Algu sarakstu sagatavošana; Psiholoģiskā testēšana personāla atlasei; Preču demonstrēšana komunikācijas līdzekļos mazumtirdzniecības vajadzībām; Personāla atlase; Ekspertu pakalpojumi uzņēmējdarbības efektivitātes noteikšanā; Aptauju veikšana; Glazētu flīžu, grīdas flīžu, sienu pārklājumu un grīdas segumu, keramikas, celtniecības mālu un porcelāna materiālu, apgaismošanas un izgaismošanas ierīču, vannas pārklājumu, dekoratīvo keramikas pārklājumu vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi veikalos un globālajos datortīklos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reklamar; Il-ġestjoni ta' negozju; L-amministrazzjoni ta' negozju; Funzjonijiet ta' uffiċċju; Servizzi ta' ksib għal oħrajn [xiri ta' prodotti u servizzi għal negozji oħra]; L-aġġornament ta' materjal tar-reklamar; Riċerka tas-suq; Tiftix għal sponsorizzazzjoni; Riċerka dwar negozju; Arranġament ta' vetrini tal-ħwienet; Dimostrazzjoni ta' prodotti; Tixrid ta' reklami; Distribuzzjoni ta' kampjuni; It-tħejjija ta' dikjarazzjonijiet ta' kontijiet; Riċerka tas-suq; Servizzi ta' esternalizzazzjoni [assistenza fin-negozju]; Fatturazzjoni; L-organizzazzjoni ta' fieri tal-kummerċ għal skopijiet kummerċjali jew ta' reklamar; Servizzi ta' amministrazzjoni kummerċjali ta' ħaddieħor, għal-liċenzjar ta' oġġetti u servizzi; Il-ġestjoni kompjuterizzata ta' fajls; Informazzjoni dwar negozju; Tagħrif kummerċjali u pariri għal konsumaturi [għoti ta' pariri lill-konsumatur]; Investigazzjonijiet dwar negozju; Il-preparazzjoni ta' listi tal-impjegati kollha mħallsa mill-impriża; Testijiet psikoloġiċi għas-selezzjoni ta' personàl; Preżentazzjoni ta' oġġetti fuq il-mezzi tal-komunikazzjoni, għal skopijiet ta' bejgħ; Ir-reklutaġġ ta' personàl; Servizzi esperti dwar l-effiċjenza tan-negozju; Il-votazzjoni tal-opinjonijiet; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut fi ħwienet u permezz ta' netwerks mondjali tal-informatika ta' madum, madum taċ-ċeramika igglejżjat, madum, materjal għall-kisi ta' ħitan u iċċangar tal-pavimenti, ta' materjali taċ-ċeramika, tal-fuħħar u tal-porċellana, ta' apparat tad-dawl u tidwil, ta' kisi għall-banju, ta' ċeramika artistika.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reclame; Beheer van commerciële zaken; Zakelijke administratie; Administratieve diensten; Aankoop voor andere bedrijven; Bijhouden van reclamedocumentatie; Marketing onderzoek; Werving van sponsors; Zakelijk onderzoek; Decoratie van etalages; Demonstratie van producten; Verspreiding van reclameboodschappen; Verspreiding van monsters; Opstellen van rekeningoverzichten; Marktstudie; Outsourcing [zakelijke assistentie]; Facturering; Organisatie van beurzen voor commerciële of publicitaire doeleinden; Zakelijke administratie van licenties op producten en diensten van derden; Beheer van gegevensbestanden; Informatie over zaken; Handelsinformatie en -adviezen voor consumenten; Onderzoek op zakelijk gebied; Salarisadministratie; Personeelsselectie via psychotechnisch onderzoek; Presentatie van goederen op communicatiemedia, voor verkoopdoeleinden; Personeelswerving; Expertises in bedrijfsefficiëntie; Opiniepeiling; Groothandel- en detailverkoop in winkels en via wereldwijde computernetwerken van wandtegels, vloertegels, materialen voor de bekleding van wanden en het plaveien van vloeren, materialen van keramiek, zandsteen en porselein, verlichtingsapparaten, badkamerbekledingen, kunstvoorwerpen van keramiek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Reklama; Zarządzanie w działalności gospodarczej; Administrowanie działalności gospodarczej; Prace biurowe; Zaopatrzenie osób trzecich (usługi -) [zakupy produktów i usług dla innych przedsiębiorstw]; Uaktualnianie materiałów reklamowych; Badania rynkowe; Poszukiwania w zakresie patronatu; Badania w dziedzinie działalności gospodarczej; Dekoracja wystaw sklepowych; Pokazy towarów; Rozpowszechnianie reklam; Kolportaż próbek; Sporządzanie wyciągów z konta; Badania rynkowe; Outsourcing [doradztwo biznesowe]; Fakturowanie; Organizowanie targów w celach handlowych lub reklamowych; Zarządzanie handlowe w zakresie koncesjonowania dóbr i usług na rzecz osób trzecich; Komputerowe zarządzanie plikami; Informacja o działalności gospodarczej; Handlowe informacje i porady udzielane konsumentom [punkty informacji konsumenckiej]; Badania biznesowe; Przygotowanie listy płac; Dobór personelu za pomocą metod psychotechnicznych; Prezentowanie produktów w mediach dla celów sprzedaży detalicznej; Rekrutacja personelu; Usługi ekspertów w zakresie efektywności biznesowej; Badania opinii publicznej; Usługi sprzedaży hurtowej i detalicznej prowadzonej w sklepach oraz za pośrednictwem światowych sieci informatycznych w zakresie glazury, płytek, materiałów okładzinowych do ścian, do układania posadzek, materiałów ceramicznych, gresu i porcelany, urządzeń oświetleniowych, okładzin stosowanych do łazienek, artystycznych wyrobów ceramicznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicidade; Gestão de negócios comerciais; Administração comercial; Trabalhos de escritório; Serviços de fornecimento para terceiros [compra de produtos e serviços para outras empresas]; Atualização de documentação publicitária; Estudos de mercado; Procura de patrocínios; Pesquisas comerciais; Decoração de montras; Demonstração de produtos; Difusão de anúncios publicitários; Distribuição de amostras; Elaboração de extratos de contas; Estudo de mercados; Serviços de outsourcing [assistência em negócios comerciais]; Faturação; Organização de feiras com fins comerciais ou de publicidade; Administração comercial do licenciamento de produtos e serviços para terceiros [serviços de]; Gestão de ficheiros informáticos; Informações comerciais; Serviços de aconselhamento e informação comercial aos consumidores [loja do consumidor]; Investigações em negócios comerciais; Preparação de folhas de pagamento; Seleção de pessoal por meio de testes psicotécnicos; Apresentação de produtos nos meios de comunicação, para fins de venda a retalho; Recrutamento de pessoal; Serviços de peritagens em negócios comerciais; Sondagem de opinião; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, em estabelecimentos comerciais e através de redes informáticas mundiais, de azulejos, ladrilhos, materiais de revestimento de paredes e pavimentos, materiais cerâmicos, de grés e de porcelana, aparelhos de iluminação, revestimentos para casas de banho, cerâmica artística.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicitate; Gestiunea afacerilor comerciale; Administraţie comercială; Lucrări de birou; Aprovizionare pentru terţi (servicii de -) [achiziţie de bunuri şi servicii pentru alte întreprinderi]; Reactualizarea materialelor publicitare; Studii de piaţă; Căutare de sponsorizare; Cercetări pentru afaceri; Decorarea vitrinelor; Prezentare de produse; Difuzare de anunţuri publicitare; Distribuţie de mostre; Întocmire de extrase de cont; Studii de piaţă; Servicii de externalizare [asistenţă în afaceri]; Facturare; Organizarea de târguri în scopuri comerciale şi publicitare; Administrarea comercială a licenţelor produselor şi a serviciilor pentru terţi; Gestionare de fişiere informatice; Informaţii pentru afaceri; Informaţii şi sfaturi comerciale pentru consumatori; Investigaţii pentru afaceri; Întocmirea statelor de salarii; Selectarea personalului prin teste psihologice; Prezentarea produselor prin toate mijloacele de comunicare pentru vânzarea cu amănuntul; Recrutare de personal; Servicii de expertiză în materie de eficienţa afacerilor; Sondaje de opinie; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul în magazine şi prin intermediul reţelelor informatice mondiale de plăci de ceramică, gresie, materiale pentru îmbrăcarea pereţilor, acoperirea pardoselilor, de materiale ceramice, de gresie şi porţelan, de aparate de iluminat şi iluminat, de produse de acoperire pentru baie din ceramică artistică.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reklamné služby; Obchodný manažment, obchodná správa; Obchodná administratíva; Kancelárske práce; Zásobovacie služby pre tretie osoby [nákup tovarov a služieb pre iné podniky]; Aktualizovanie reklamných materiálov; Marketingový prieskum; Vyhľadávanie sponzorov; Obchodný alebo podnikateľský výskum; Aranžovanie výkladov; Predvádzanie tovaru; Rozširovanie reklamných oznamov; Rozširovanie vzoriek tovarov; Výpisy z účtu (Zostavovanie -); Marketingový prieskum; Subdodávateľské služby (obchodné služby); Fakturácie; Organizovanie obchodných alebo reklamných veľtrhov; Obchodná správa licencií výrobkov a služieb (pre tretie osoby); Správa počítačových súborov; Obchodné alebo podnikateľské informácie; Obchodné informácie a rady spotrebiteľom; Obchodný alebo podnikateľský prieskum; Príprava miezd a výplatných listín; Výber zamestnancov pomocou psychologických testov; Prezentácia výrobkov v komunikačných médiách pre maloobchod; Nábor zamestnancov; Odborné posudky efektívnosti podnikov; Prieskum verejnej mienky; Predaj dlaždíc, obkladačiek, nástenných krytín, podlahových krytín, z keramiky, kameniny a porcelánu, zariadení na osvetľovanie, kúpeľňových obkladov, umeleckej keramiky, prostredníctvom veľkoobchodnej a maloobchodnej činnosti v predajniach a na celosvetových počítačových sieťach.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oglasna dejavnost; Vodenje komercialnih poslov; Poslovna administracija; Pisarniški posli; Prokuratorske storitve [nabava blaga in storitev za druga podjetja]; Izpopolnjevanje reklamnega gradiva; Tržne raziskave; Iskanje sponzorstva; Poslovne študije; Aranžiranje izložb; Predstavitev izdelkov; Širjenje oglasov; Distribucija vzorcev; Saldakonti; Tržne raziskave; Storitve zunanjih izvajalcev (poslovna pomoč); Fakturiranje; Organizacija trgovskih sejmov za komercialne ali oglasne namene; Poslovna administracija licenciranja blaga in storitev drugih; Vodenje podatkovnih baz; Poslovne informacije; Poslovne informacije in nasveti za potrošnike; Poslovne preiskave; Priprava plačilne liste; Psihološko testiranje za potrebe kadrovanja; Predstavitev blaga v komunikacijskih medijih (prodaja na drobno); Zaposlovanje osebja; Strokovne storitve na področju poslovne učinkovitosti; Javnomnenjske raziskave; Storitve veleprodaje in maloprodaje v trgovinah in preko svetovnih računalniških omrežij stenskih ploščic, talnih ploščic, materialov za prekrivanje sten in tlakovanje tal, materialov iz keramike, peščenjaka in porcelana, svetilnih aparatov in aparatov za osvetljevanje, kopalniških oblog, umetniške keramike.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Annons- och reklamverksamhet; Företagsledning; Företagsadministration; Kontorstjänster; Inköp av varor och tjänster för annans räkning; Uppdatering av annons- och reklammaterial; Marknadsundersökningar; Sökande av sponsorskap; Företagsundersökningar; Skyltning av skyltfönster; Varudemonstrationer; Spridning av reklamannonser; Utdelning av varuprover; Räkenskapsredovisning; Marknadsundersökningar; Outsourcingtjänster [affärsassistans]; Faktureringstjänster; Anordnande av mässor för kommersiella eller reklamändamål; Kommersiell administration av licensiering av varor och tjänster för andra; Registerhantering (Datoriserad -); Företagsinformation; Kommersiell information och rådgivning för konsumenter [konsumentrådgivningsbutik]; Företagsutredningar; Färdigställande av lönelistor; Psykologisk testning vid rekrytering; Presentation av varor på kommersiella media, för försäljningsändamål; Personalrekrytering; Experttjänster i företagseffektivitet; Opinionsundersökningar; Partihandelsförsäljning och detaljförsäljning i butik och via globala datanät av kakel, kakelplattor, väggbeklädnadsmaterial och golvbeläggningsmaterial av keramiskt material, sandsten och porslin, apparater för belysning, beläggning av badrumsgolv, av konstnärlig keramik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/091</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-15</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/163</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-27</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/214</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>C.1.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-11-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1136191</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>43804</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018728629</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Proprietor - Total transfers</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>43804</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-11-10</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
