<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T11:10:28</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229227</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229227</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>HAWKEYE</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162455537</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/229/018229227/000162455537.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>03.07.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>03.07.24</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>03.07.99</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Осветление за автомобили; Фарове за автомобили; Лампи; Фенери за осветление; Светлини за велосипеди; Електрически фенерчета; Лампи за мотоциклети; Таванно осветление; Обезопасени лампи за рудници; Светлини, електрически, за коледни елхи; Фарове за автомобили; Рефлектори за превозни средства; Осветление за автомобили; Осветление за автомобили; Лампи с нажежаема жичка за пътепоказатели за превозни средства; Лампиони; Насочени светлини за велосипеди; Водопроводни кранове за тръби.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Světla pro vozidla; Světlomety pro automobily; Svítidla; Lucerny; Světla pro jízdní kola; Baterky (elektrické svítilny); Světla pro motocykly; Stropní svítidla; Bezpečnostní lampy; Elektrická osvětlení na vánoční stromky; Světlomety pro vozidla; Reflektory pro vozidla; Osvětlovací zařízení pro vozidla; Světla pro automobily; Žárovky pro směrová světla vozidel; Světelné řetězy pro slavnostní dekorace; Světla na směrové ukazatele jízdních kol; Kohouty a kohoutky do potrubí.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Lygter til befordringsmidler; Forlygter til biler; Lamper; Lanterner til belysning; Cykellygter; Elektriske lygter; Lygter til motorcykler; Loftsbelysning; Sikkerhedslamper; Juletræslys, elektriske; Forlygter til befordringsmidler; Reflektorer til befordringsmidler; Belysningsapparater til befordringsmidler; Lygter til automobiler; Elektriske pærer til retningssignaler i befordringsmidler; Kulørte lamper til festdekoration; Retningsvisende lygter til cykler; Taphaner til rørsystemer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Leuchten für Fahrzeuge; Scheinwerfer für Kraftfahrzeuge; Beleuchtungslampen; Laternen; Fahrradleuchten; Elektrische Taschenlampen; Motorradleuchten; Deckenlampen; Sicherheitslampen; Elektrische Christbaumbeleuchtungen; Fahrzeugscheinwerfer; Fahrzeugrückstrahler; Beleuchtungsgeräte für Fahrzeuge; Leuchten für Kraftfahrzeuge; Lampen für Fahrtrichtungsanzeiger von Fahrzeugen; Lichterketten für die Festtagsdekoration; Fahrradblinker; Hähne für Rohrleitungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Οχημάτων φανάρια· Προβολείς για αυτοκίνητα· Φωτισμός (λαμπτήρες -ού)· Φανοί φωτισμού· Δικύκλων φανάρια· Ηλεκτρικοί φορητοί φανοί· Φώτα μοτοσικλέτας· Οροφής φωτισμοί· Λυχνίες ασφαλείας· Λαμπάκια ηλεκτρικά για δένδρα χριστουγεννιάτικα· Προβολείς για αυτοκίνητα· Ανακλαστήρες οχημάτων· Οχημάτων φανάρια· Οχημάτων φανάρια· Λυχνίες ενδεικτικές κατεύθυνσης για αυτοκίνητα· Λαμπιόνια χρωματιστά διακοσμητικά για γιορτινές διακοσμήσεις· Δείκτες αλλαγής πορείας για ποδήλατα (όπου περιλαμβάνονται λαμπτήρες)· Διοχέτευσης (Στρόφιγγες -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Lights for vehicles; Headlights for automobiles; Lamps; Lanterns for lighting; Bicycle lights; Electric flashlights; Motorcycle lights; Ceiling lights; Safety lamps; Electric lights for Christmas trees; Vehicle headlights; Vehicle reflectors; Lighting apparatus for vehicles; Automobile lights; Light bulbs for directional signals for vehicles; String lights for festive decoration; Directional lights for bicycles; Faucets for pipes and pipelines; Cocks for pipes and pipelines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Luces para vehículos; Faros para automóviles; Lámparas [aparatos de iluminación]; Faroles de alumbrado; Luces para bicicletas; Linternas eléctricas; Luces de motocicleta; Plafones [lámparas]; Lámparas de seguridad; Luces eléctricas para árboles de Navidad; Faros para vehículos; Reflectores para vehículos; Aparatos de iluminación para vehículos; Luces para automóviles; Bombillas de indicadores de dirección para vehículos; Guirnaldas de luces decorativas para fiestas; Luces indicadoras de dirección para bicicletas; Grifos para tuberías y canalizaciones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sõidukilaternad; Autode esilaternad; Lambid [valgustid]; Valgustuslaternad; Jalgrattalaternad; Elektrilised taskulambid; Mootorrattatuled; Laevalgustid; Turvalambid; Jõulupuu elektriküünlad; Sõidukite esilaternad; Sõidukihelkurid; Sõidukite valgustusseadmed; Autolaternad; Sõidukite suunatulepirnid; Dekoreertuled, ehistuled, ilutuled pidulikuks kaunistamiseks; Jalgrataste suunatuled; Torujuhtmekraanid, torukraanid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ajoneuvojen valaisimet; Ajovalaisimet autoihin; Lamput; Lyhdyt valaistukseen; Lamput polkupyöriin; Sähkökäyttöiset käsivalaisimet; Moottoripyörien valot; Kattovalaisimet; Turvalamput; Joulukuusten sähkövalaisimet; Ajovalaisimet autoihin; Heijastimet ajoneuvoille; Ajoneuvojen valaisimet; Ajoneuvojen valaisimet; Hehkulamput ajoneuvojen suuntavilkkuihin; Värilliset lamput koristeluun; Polkupyörien suuntavilkut; Putkihanat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Feux pour véhicules; Phares pour automobiles; Lampes d'éclairage; Lanternes d'éclairage; Feux pour bicyclettes; Torches électriques; Feux de motocycle; Plafonniers; Lampes de sûreté; Lampes électriques pour arbres de Noël; Phares de véhicules; Réflecteurs pour véhicules; Appareils d'éclairage pour véhicules; Feux pour automobiles; Ampoules d'indicateurs de direction pour véhicules; Guirlandes lumineuses pour décoration de fête; Feux indicateurs de direction pour bicyclettes; Robinets pour tuyaux et canalisations.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Svjetla za automobile; Farovi za vozila; Rasvjetne svjetiljke; Rasvjetni fenjeri; Svjetla za bicikle; Električne baterijske svjetiljke; Svjetla na motociklima; Stropna svjetla; Svjetiljke, sigurnosne; Svjećice (električne svjećice za božićna drvca); Farovi za vozila; Reflektori za vozila; Svjetla za automobile; Svjetla za automobile; Žaruljice pokazivača smjera vožnje za vozila; Lampioni za svečane dekoracije; Svjetla za pokazivače smjera za bicikle; Slavine za cjevovode.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Lámpák járművekhez; Fényszórók, reflektorok gépkocsikhoz; Lámpák; Lámpások világításra; Kerékpár lámpák; Elektromos zseblámpák; Lámpák motorkerékpárokhoz; Mennyezetvilágítások, mennyezeti lámpák; Biztonsági lámpák; Lámpák karácsonyfákhoz, elektromos; Fényszórók, reflektorok gépkocsikhoz; Reflektorok járművekhez; Lámpák járművekhez; Lámpák járművekhez; Irányjelző izzólámpák járművekhez; Lámpák, égők ünnepi díszkivilágításhoz; Kerékpár irányjelző lámpák; Csapok [vízcsapok] csövekhez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Fanali per veicoli; Fari per automobili; Lampade per illuminazione; Lanterne per illuminazione; Fanali per biciclette; Torce elettriche; Fanali per motocicli; Plafoniere; Lampade di sicurezza; Lampadine elettriche per alberi di natale; Fari per veicoli; Riflettori per veicoli; Apparecchi di illuminazione per veicoli; Fanali per automobili; Lampadine per indicatori di direzione per veicoli; Ghirlande luminose decorative per le feste; Luci direzionali per biciclette; Rubinetti per tubi e condotte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Transporto priemonių lempos; Priekiniai automobilių žibintai; Lempos; Apšvietimo žibintai; Dviračių žibintai; Elektriniai žibintuvėliai; Motociklų lempos; Pakabinamieji šviestuvai; Saugiosios lempos; Kalėdų eglučių elektros lemputės; Transporto priemonių priekiniai žibintai; Transporto priemonių atšvaitai; Transporto priemonių apšvietimo prietaisai; Automobilių žibintai; Automobilių krypties signalizatorių lemputės; Šventinių lempučių girliandos; Dviračių posūkių lemputės; Vamzdžių čiaupai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Transportlīdzekļu lukturi; Automobiļu priekšējie lukturi; Lampas; Lukturi apgaismošanai; Velosipēdu lukturi; Elektriskie lukturīši; Motociklu lukturi; Griestu lampas; Eksplozijdrošas raktuvju lampas; Elektriskās spuldzītes Ziemassvētku eglītēm; Transportlīdzekļu priekšējie lukturi; Transportlīdzekļu atstarotāji; Transportlīdzekļu apgaismes ierīces; Automobiļu lukturi; Virziena maiņas signāllampas automobiļiem; Lampiņu virtenes svētku dekorācijām; Velosipēdu virzienrādītāju lampas; Cauruļvadu aizbīdņi (krāni).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Dwal għall-vetturi; Fanali għal karrozzi; Lampi; Fanali għad-dawl; Dwal tar-roti; Torċi elettriċi; Fanali tal-muturi; Dwal tas-soqfa; Lampi tas-sigurtà; Dwal elettriċi għas-siġar tal-Milied; Fanali għal karrozzi; Rifletturi tal-vetturi; Dwal għall-vetturi; Dwal għall-vetturi; Bozoz tad-dawl għal sinjali tad-direzzjoni għal vetturi; Lampi żgħar tat-tiżjin għad-dekorazzjoni festivi; Indikaturi tad-direzzjoni għar-roti (Lampi għal -); Vitien speċifiċi [valvi, kavilji] jew ġenerali għall-kanen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Lichten voor voertuigen; Koplampen voor automobielen; Lampen voor verlichting; Lantaarns voor verlichting; Fietslampen; Elektrische zaklampen; Motorrijwielverlichting; Plafondlampen; Veiligheidslampen; Elektrische lampen voor kerstbomen; Koplampen voor voertuigen; Reflectoren voor voertuigen; Verlichtingsapparatuur voor voertuigen; Lichten voor automobielen; Lampjes voor richtingaanwijzers voor voertuigen; Lampions; Richtingaanwijzers voor fietsers; Kranen voor waterleidingen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Światła do pojazdów; Reflektory samochodowe; Lampy oświetleniowe; Latarnie oświetleniowe; Światła rowerowe; Latarki kieszonkowe, elektryczne; Oświetlenie do motocykli; Światła sufitowe; Lampy bezpieczeństwa; Lampki elektryczne na choinki; Reflektory samochodowe; Reflektory do pojazdów; Światła do pojazdów; Światła do pojazdów; Żarówki do kierunkowskazów w pojazdach; Kolorowe światełka do dekoracji świątecznych; Lampy kierunkowe do rowerów; Zawory do rur i rurociągów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Luzes para veículos; Faróis para automóveis; Lâmpadas; Lanternas de iluminação; Luzes para bicicletas; Lanternas elétricas; Luzes para motociclos; Candeeiros de teto; Lâmpadas de segurança; Lâmpadas elétricas para árvores de natal; Faróis de veículos; Refletores para veículos; Aparelhos de iluminação para veículos; Luzes para automóveis; Lâmpadas de indicadores de direção para veículos; Correntes de luzes para decorações festivas; Faróis indicadores de direção para bicicletas; Torneiras para canalização.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate de iluminat pentru vehicule; Automobile (Faruri pentru -); Lămpi de iluminat; Lanterne de iluminat; Lanterne de biciclete; Lămpi electrice; Lumini pentru motociclete; Plafoniere; Lămpi de siguranță; Instalații luminoase pentru pomul de Crăciun; Automobile (Faruri pentru -); Proiectoare pentru vehicule; Aparate de iluminat pentru vehicule; Aparate de iluminat pentru vehicule; Automobile (Becuri indicatoare de direcție pentru -); Ghirlande luminoase pentru decorațiuni festive; Becuri pentru indicatoare de direcție de biciclete; Robinete de canalizare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Svetlá na dopravné prostriedky; Automobilové reflektory; Lampy; Lampáše; Svietidlá na bicykle; Elektrické vreckové baterky; Svetlá na motocykle; Stropné svetlá; Bezpečnostné lampy; Elektrické svetlá na vianočné stromčeky; Reflektory na vozidlá; Reflektory vozidiel; Osvetľovacie zariadenia na dopravné prostriedky; Svetlá na automobily; Žiarovky do smeroviek na vozidlá; Dekoračné svetelné reťaze; Smerovkové lampy pre bicykle; Kohútiky a kohúty na potrubia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Naprave za osvetlitev za vozila; Prednje luči za avtomobile; Svetilke; Lanterne za razsvetljavo; Kolesarske luči; Električne baterijske svetilke; Luči za motorna kolesa; Stropne luči; Varnostne svetilke; Električne lučke za božična drevesca; Prednje luči za avtomobile; Reflektorji za vozila; Naprave za osvetlitev za vozila; Naprave za osvetlitev za vozila; Žarnice za smerne kazalce pri vozilih; Lučke za praznično okrasitev; Luči za smerne svetilke za kolesa; Pipe za dovodne cevi [vodovodne].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Lyktor för fordon och farkoster; Strålkastare för bilar; Lampor; Lanternor för belysning; Cykelbelysning; Ficklampor; Belysning för motorcyklar; Innertaksbelysningar; Säkerhetslampor; Elektriska belysningar för julgranar; Strålkastare för fordon och farkoster; Reflektorer för fordon och farkoster; Belysningsanordningar för fordon och farkoster; Lyktor för bilar; Glödlampor för körriktningsvisare för fordon och farkoster; Ljusslingor för dekoration; Lampor för körriktningsvisare för cyklar; Kranar för rör.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>12</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Вилични кари високоповдигачи; Прикачващи устройства за сухопътни превозни средства; Скачване на ремаркета за превозни средства; Туристически автобуси; Туристически автобуси; Камиони; Аларми при заден ход на превозни средства; Капаци за превозни средства; Ремаркета [превозни средства]; Трактори; Мотоциклети; Огледала за обратно виждане; Коли [автомобили]; Каросерии на превозни средства; Автокаравани; Запалки за цигари за автомобили; Камиони с ремаркета; Велосипедни звънци; Алармени инсталации против кражба на превозни средства.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vysokozdvižné vozíky; Tažné spojky pro pozemní vozidla; Tažná zařízení na vozidla; Autobusy; Autokary; Kamiony; Zařízení pro signalizaci zpětné jízdy pro vozidla; Kapoty pro vozidla; Přívěsy [vozidla]; Traktory; Motocykly; Zpětná zrcátka; Automobily; Karoserie pro vozidla; Obytné vozy; Cigaretové zapalovače do vozidel; Tažné nákladní automobily; Zvonky pro jízdní kola; Zabezpečovací poplašná zařízení pro vozidla (proti krádeži).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Gaffeltrucks; Koblinger til befordringsmidler til brug på land; Anhængertræk til befordringsmidler; Busser; Rutebiler; Lastvogne; Bakgearsadvarsler til befordringsmidler; Kalecher til befordringsmidler; Påhængsvogne; Traktorer; Motorcykler; Bakspejle; Biler; Karosseri til befordringsmidler; Autocampere; Cigartændere til automobiler; Lastbiler med anhængere; Klokker til cykler; Tyverialarmer til befordringsmidler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gabelstapler; Kupplungen [Verbindungen] für Landfahrzeuge; Anhängerkupplungen für Fahrzeuge; Autobusse; Reiseomnibusse; Lastwagen; Rückfahrwarngeräte für Fahrzeuge; Fahrzeugverdecke; Anhänger [Fahrzeuge]; Traktoren; Motorräder; Rückspiegel; Automobile; Fahrzeugkarosserien; Campingwagen; Zigarrenanzünder für Automobile; Abschleppfahrzeuge; Fahrradklingeln; Diebstahlwarngeräte für Fahrzeuge.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Περονοφόρα οχήματα· Συμπλέκτες για χερσαία οχήματα· Ζεύξεις ρυμουλκών για οχήματα· Λεωφορεία τουριστικά· Λεωφορεία τουριστικά· Φορτηγά· Δείκτες οπισθοπορείας για οχήματα· Κουκούλες οχημάτων· Ρυμουλκά [οχήματα]· Ελκυστήρες· Μοτοσυκλέτες· Καθρέπτες οχημάτων οπισθοπορείας· Αυτοκίνητα· Αμαξώματα οχημάτων· Μηχανοκίνητα τροχόσπιτα· Αναπτήρες πούρων για οχήματα· Φορτηγά ρυμούλκησης· Δικύκλων κουδούνια· Συναγερμοί αντικλεπτικοί για οχήματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Forklift trucks; Couplings for land vehicles; Trailer hitches for vehicles; Motor buses; Motor coaches; Lorries; Reversing alarms for vehicles; Hoods for vehicles; Trailers [vehicles]; Tractors; Motorcycles; Rearview mirrors; Automobiles; Bodies for vehicles; Camping cars; Cigar lighters for automobiles; Tow trucks; Wreckers for transport; Bicycle bells; Anti-theft alarms for vehicles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Carretillas elevadoras; Acoplamientos para vehículos terrestres; Enganches de remolque para vehículos; Autobuses; Autocares; Camiones; Avisadores acústicos de marcha atrás para vehículos; Capotas para vehículos; Remolques [vehículos]; Tractores; Motocicletas; Retrovisores; Coches; Carrocerías; Autocaravanas; Encendedores de cigarrillos para automóviles; Grúas remolque; Timbres para bicicletas; Alarmas antirrobo para vehículos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kahveltõstukid; Maismaasõidukite sidurid; Sõidukite haakeseadmed; Autobussid; Reisibussid; Veoautod; Sõidukite tagurdusalarmid; Sõidukite lükandkatused; Treilerid, raskeveohaagised; Traktorid; Mootorrattad; Tahavaatepeeglid; Autod; Sõidukikered; Autoelamud, vagunelamud; Sigaretisüütlid autodele; Puksiirautod; Jalgrattakellad; Sõidukite ärandamisvastased alarmiseadmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Haarukkatrukit; Kytkinlaitteet maa-ajoneuvoihin; Ajoneuvojen hinauskoukut; Bussit; Bussit; Kuorma-autot; Peruutushälyttimet ajoneuvoihin; Konepellit ajoneuvoihin; Perävaunut; Traktorit; Moottoripyörät; Taustapeilit; Autot; Korit ajoneuvoihin; Matkailuautot; Savukkeensytyttimet autoihin; Hinausautot; Polkupyörän soittokellot; Varashälyttimet ajoneuvoihin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Chariots élévateurs; Accouplements pour véhicules terrestres; Attelages de remorques pour véhicules; Autobus; Autocars; Camions; Avertisseurs de marche arrière pour véhicules; Capotes de véhicules; Remorques [véhicules]; Tracteurs; Motocyclettes; Rétroviseurs; Voitures; Carrosseries; Autocaravanes; Allume-cigares pour automobiles; Dépanneuses; Sonnettes de bicyclettes; Alarmes antivol pour véhicules.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Viljuškari; Spojke za kopnena vozila; Spojnice prikolice za vozila; Autobusi; Autobusi; Motorna teretna vozila; Signalizatori za kretanje vozila unatrag; Poklopci, preklopni za vozila; Prikolice [vozila]; Traktori; Motocikli; Retrovizori; Automobili; Karoserije vozila; Autokaravane; Automobilski upaljači za cigare; Vučni kamioni; Zvona za bicikle; Protuprovalni alarmi za vozila.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Villás targoncák; Tengelykapcsolók szárazföldi járművekhez; Utánfutó horgok járművekhez; Távolsági autóbuszok; Távolsági autóbuszok; Tehergépkocsik, teherautók, kamionok; Tolatásjelzők járművekhez; Lenyitható tetők járművekhez; Pótkocsik, utánfutók [járművek]; Traktorok; Motorkerékpárok; Visszapillantó tükrök; Gépkocsik; Jármű karosszériák; Lakóautók; Szivargyújtók gépkocsikba; Vontató tehergépkocsik; Kerékpárcsengők; Lopásgátló riasztók járművekhez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Carrelli elevatori; Accoppiamenti per veicoli terrestri; Attacchi di rimorchi per veicoli; Autobus; Autocarri; Camions; Segnalatori di retromarcia per veicoli; Cappotte di veicoli; Rimorchi [veicoli]; Trattori; Motociclette; Retrovisori; Autovetture; Carrozzerie; Autocaravan; Accendisigari per automobili; Carri attrezzi; Campanelli per biciclette; Allarmi antifurto per automobili.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Šakiniai krautuvai; Antžeminių transporto priemonių sukabintuvai; Transporto priemonių prikabinimo įtaisai; Autobusai; Turistiniai autobusai; Sunkvežimiai; Transporto priemonių atbulinės eigos signaliniai įtaisai; Transporto priemonių gaubtai; Priekabos [transporto priemonės]; Traktoriai; Motociklai; Užpakalinio vaizdo veidrodžiai; Lengvieji automobiliai; Transporto priemonių kėbulai; Iškylavimo automobiliai; Cigarų žiebtuvėliai (automobiliams); Nutempimo furgonai; Dviračių skambučiai; Transporto priemonių signalizacija nuo vagysčių.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Autokrāvēji; Sajūgi, kas paredzēti sauszemes transporta līdzekļiem; Pacēlāji transportlīdzekļiem; Motorizēti autobusi; Tūristu autobusi; Kravas automobiļi; Transportlīdzekļu atpakaļgaitas signālierīces; Transportlīdzekļu pārsegi; Transportlīdzekļu piekabes; Traktori; Motocikli; Atpakaļskata spoguļi; Automobiļi; Transportlīdzekļu virsbūves; Kempinga auto; Cigarešu aizdedzināšanas ierīces automobiļiem; Vilcējautomobiļi; Velosipēdu zvaniņi; Transportlīdzekļu pretaizdzīšanas signalizācijas ierīces.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Trakkijiet tal-forklifter; Tagħmir ta' gganċjar għall-vetturi tal-art; Ganċijiet tal-irmonk għall-vetturi; Karozzi tal-linja motorizzati; Karozzi tal-linja motorizzati; Trakkijiet; Allarmi għas-sewqan b'lura tal-vetturi; Għata għall-vetturi; Karrijiet [vetturi]; Tratturi; Muturi; Mirja għall-veduta ta' wara; Karozzi; Struttura ta' barra għal vetturi; Vetturi karavani; Qabbada tas-sigarri għall-karozzi; Trakkijiet tal-irmonkar; Qniepen għar-roti; Allarm ta' kontra s-serq, għal vetturi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Heftrucks; Koppelingen [aanhaakinrichtingen] voor voertuigen; Koppelingen [aanhaakinrichtingen] voor aanhangwagens; Autobussen; Touringcars; Vrachtauto's; Achteruitrij-signaalapparaten voor voertuigen; Kappen voor voertuigen; Aanhangwagens [voertuigen]; Tractoren; Motorrijwielen; Achteruitkijkspiegels; Voertuigen; Carrosserieën; Campers; Sigarenaanstekers voor automobielen; Vrachtwagens met opleggers; Fietsbellen; Alarmapparaten tegen diefstal van voertuigen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Wózki jezdniowe widłowe; Urządzenia sprzęgające do pojazdów lądowych; Złącza do przyczep do pojazdów; Autokary; Autokary; Ciężarówki; Sygnalizatory jazdy wstecz do pojazdów; Maski do pojazdów; Przyczepy [pojazdy]; Ciągniki; Motocykle; Lusterka wsteczne; Samochody; Nadwozia pojazdów; Samochody kempingowe; Zapalniczki samochodowe; Samochody holownicze [pomocy drogowej]; Dzwonki do rowerów; Alarmy antywłamaniowe do pojazdów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Empilhadoras; Acoplamentos para veículos terrestres; Ganchos de reboques para veículos; Autocarros; Camionetas; Camiões (tratores); Avisadores de marcha atrás para veículos; Capotas para veículos; Reboques [veículos]; Tratores; Motociclos; Espelhos retrovisores; Viaturas [carros]; Carroçarias para veículos; Autocaravanas; Isqueiros para automóveis; Reboques; Campainhas de bicicletas; Alarmes antirroubo para veículos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Camioane motostivuitoare; Cuplaje pentru vehicule terestre; Dispozitive de remorcare pentru vehicule; Autocare; Autocare; Camioane; Avertizoare acustice de marșarier pentru vehicule; Capote de vehicule; Remorci [vehicule]; Tractoare; Motociclete; Retrovizoare; Mașini; Caroserii; Autorulote; Brichete pentru automobile; Autocamioane de remorcat; Bicicletă (Clopoței de -); Alarme antifurt pentru vehicule.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zdvíhacie vozíky; Spriahadlá pozemných vozidiel; Ťažné zariadenia vozidiel; Autobusy; Autokary; Nákladné autá, kamióny; Signalizačné zariadenia pri spätnom chode automobilov; Kapoty na vozidlá; Vlečné vozidlá, ťahače; Traktory; Motocykle; Spätné zrkadlá; Osobné automobily; Karosérie dopravných prostriedkov; Karavany (obytné prívesy); Zapaľovače cigariet do automobilov; Odťahovacie nákladné vozidlá; Zvončeky na bicykle; Zabezpečovacie poplašné zariadenia proti odcudzeniu vozidiel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Viličarji; Spojke za kopenska vozila; Vlečne kljuke za vozila; Avtobusi; Avtobusi; Tovornjaki; Alarmi za vzvratno vožnjo vozil; Ponjave za vozila; Prikolice [vozila]; Traktorji; Motorna kolesa; Vzvratna ogledala; Avtomobili; Karoserije za vozila; Avtodomovi; Vžigalniki za cigarete za avtomobile; Vlečni tovornjaki; Zvonci za kolesa; Protivlomni alarmi za vozila.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Gaffeltruckar; Kopplingsanordningar för landfordon; Dragkrokar för fordon och farkoster; Bussar; Turistbussar; Lastbilar; Backningssignaler för fordon och farkoster; Suffletter för fordon och farkoster; Släpvagnar; Traktorer; Motoriserade cyklar; Backspeglar; Bilar; Karosserier för fordon och farkoster; Husbilar för camping; Cigarrtändare för bilar; Bärgningsbilar; Cykelringklockor; Stöldskyddslarm för fordon och farkoster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/081</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-30</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/150</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1081932</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>89731</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017763825</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>89731</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-04-24</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
