<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T11:10:21</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018229823</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018229823</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-27</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-27</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>CHOOYOU</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Колани за щангисти; Уреди за упражнения за трениране на тялото; Бодиборд [вид дъски за сърф]; Уреди за трениране на тялото; Протектори за гръдния кош за спортна употреба; Налакътници [спортни артикули]; Топки за упражнения; Ленти за упражнения; Лостове за упражнения; Гимнастически уреди; Гимнастически и спортни артикули; Гимнастика (Уреди за -); Халки за гимнастика; Въжета за скачане; Наколенки [спортни артикули]; Топки за лакрос (северноамериканска игра на топка); Тежести за крака за упражнения; Йога блокчета; Ремъци за йога.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vzpěračské pásy [sportovní výstroj]; Přístroje na fyzický trénink (cvičení); Prkna na bodyboarding; Posilovací stroje; Chrániče hrudníku pro sportovní účely; Loketní chrániče [sportovní potřeby]; Míče na cvičení; Pásy na cvičení; Cvičební tyče; Posilovače prsních svalů (expandéry); Gymnastické a sportovní zboží; Gymnastická nářadí; Gymnastické kruhy; Švihadla; Kolení chrániče [sportovní potřeby]; Lakrosové míče; Závaží na cvičení nohou; Bloky (pomůcky) na cvičení jógy; Pásy na cvičení jógy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Nyrebælter [sportsartikler]; Apparater til kropstræning [motion]; Bodyboards; Apparater til bodybuilding; Brystbeskyttere til sportsbrug; Albuebeskyttere [sportsartikler]; Træningsbolde; Træningsbånd; Træningsstænger; Ekspandere [muskelstrækkere]; Gymnastik- og sportsartikler; Gymnastikredskaber; Ringe til gymnastik; Sjippetov; Knæbeskyttere [sportsartikler]; Lacrossebolde; Ankelvægte til træningsbrug; Yogablokke; Yogastropper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gewichthebergürtel [Sportartikel]; Körpertrainingsgeräte [für Übungszwecke]; Bodyboards; Bodybuilding-Geräte; Brustschutz für Sportler; Ellbogenschützer [Sportartikel]; Trainingsbälle; Fitnessbänder; Übungsstab; Expander; Turn- und Sportartikel; Gymnastik- und Turngeräte; Ringe zum Turnen; Springseile; Knieschützer [Sportartikel]; Lacrosse-Bälle; Beingewichte für Trainingszwecke; Yogablöcke; Yoga-Gurte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Άρση βαρών (ζώνες για -) [αθλητικά είδη]· Συσκευές σωματικής προπόνησης (σωματικής άσκησης)· Ιστιοσανίδα σώματος· Αποκατάστασης σώματος συσκευές· Προστατευτικά θώρακα για αθλητική χρήση· Προστατευτικά αγκώνων [αθλητικά είδη]· Μπάλες σωματικής άσκησης· Ελαστικές ταινίες σωματικής άσκησης· Ζυγοί άσκησης· Ανάπτυξης-όργανα· Είδη γυμναστικής και αθλητισμού· Είδη γυμναστικής· Κρίκοι γυμναστικής· Σχοινάκια για υπερπηδήσεις· Επιγονατίδες [αθλητικά είδη]· Μπάλες του λακρός· Βάρη ποδιών για άσκηση· Κύβοι για γιόγκα· Ιμάντες για γιόγκα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Belts (Weight lifting -) [sports articles]; Body training apparatus [exercise]; Bodyboards; Body-training apparatus; Chest protectors for sports use; Elbow guards [sports articles]; Exercise balls; Exercise bands; Exercise bars; Exercisers [expanders]; Gymnastic and sporting articles; Gymnastics (Appliances for -); Gymnastics rings; Jump ropes; Knee guards [sports articles]; Lacrosse balls; Leg weights for exercising; Rings for gymnastics; Yoga blocks; Yoga straps.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cinturones de halterofilia; Aparatos de entrenamiento corporal [ejercicio físico]; Tablas de bodyboard; Aparatos de culturismo; Petos protectores para deportes; Coderas [artículos de deporte]; Pelotas para hacer ejercicio; Bandas de entrenamiento; Barras de gimnasia; Extensores para pectorales; Artículos de deporte y gimnasia; Aparatos de gimnasia; Aros para gimnasia; Cuerdas para saltar a la comba; Rodilleras [artículos de deporte]; Pelotas de lacrosse; Pesas para ejercitar las piernas; Bloques para yoga; Cintas para yoga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tõstevööd [sporditarbed]; Kehalise treeningu seadmed [harjutusseadmed]; Kõhulauad; Füüsilise vormi parandamise/taastamise seadmed; Rinnakaitsmed spordis kasutamiseks; Küünarnukikaitsmed [sporditarbed]; Võimlemispallid; Venitusrihmad [spordivahendid]; Võimlemiskangid; Ekspandrid, tõmmitsad; Võimlemis- ja sportimistarbed; Võimlemisriistad; Võimlemisrõngad; Hüppenöörid; Põlvekaitsmed [sporditarbed]; Kahvpalli- ehk lakrossipallid; Jalaraskused treenimiseks; Joogas kasutatavad klotsid; Joogarihmad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vyöt (painonnosto -) [urheiluun]; Kuntosalilaitteet (kuntoiluun); Kelluntalaudat; Kehonrakennusvälineet; Rintasuojat urheilukäyttöön; Kyynärsuojat [urheiluun]; Harjoittelupallot; Vastuskuminauhat; Harjoitustangot; Voimaharjoitusvälineet [venytyslaitteet]; Voimistelu- ja urheiluvälineet; Voimisteluvälineet; Voimistelurenkaat; Hyppynarut; Polvisuojukset [urheiluun]; Haavipallot; Jalkapainot harjoitteluun; Joogapalikat; Joogahihnat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Ceintures d'haltérophilie [articles de sport]; Appareils de musculation corporelle [exercice physique]; Body boards; Appareils pour le culturisme; Plastrons de protection pour le sport; Protège-coudes [articles de sport]; Balles d'exercice; Bandes d’entraînement; Barres d'exercice physique; Exerciseurs [extenseurs]; Articles de gymnastique et de sport; Appareils de gymnastique; Anneaux de gymnastique; Cordes à sauter; Protège-genoux [articles de sport]; Balles de lacrosse; Poids pour exercer les jambes; Blocs de yoga; Sangles de yoga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Remenje za dizanje utega [sportski artikli]; Naprave za tjelovježbu; Daske za potrbušno plivanje; Sprave za body building; Sportski štitnici za prsa; Štitnici za laktove [sportski artikli]; Lopte za vježbanje; Trake za vježbanje; Šipke za vježbanje; Ekspanderi za prsa; Gimnastička i sportska oprema; Gimnastički aparati; Gimnastičke karike; Užad za preskakanje; Zaštita za koljena [sportski artikli]; Lakros loptice; Utezi za noge za tjelovježbu; Kocke za jogu; Remenje za jogu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Súlyemelő övek [sportcikkek]; Testedző eszközök; Bodyboard deszkák; Testedző berendezések; Mellkasvédők sportoláshoz; Könyökvédők [sportcikkek]; Fitness labdák; Edzőszalagok; Edző rudak; Mellkas expanderek [edzőeszközök]; Torna- és sporttermékek; Tornaeszközök; Tornagyűrűk; Ugrálókötelek; Térdvédők [sportcikkek]; Lacrosse labdák; Lábsúlyok testedzéshez; Jógablokkok; Jógaszalagok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cinture per sollevatore di pesi [articoli sportivi]; Apparecchi per allenare il corpo [esercizio fisico]; Body boards; Apparecchi per il culturismo; Protezioni per il torace per lo sport; Paragomiti [articoli sportivi]; Palloni per esercizi; Fasce per esercizio fisico; Barre per allenamento; Estensori [attrezzi ginnici]; Articoli per la ginnastica e lo sport; Apparecchi per la cultura fisica; Anelli per la ginnastica; Corde per fare saltelli; Paraginocchi [articoli sportivi]; Palle da lacrosse; Pesi per le gambe per l'esercizio fisico; Blocchetti per lo yoga; Cinghie per yoga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Sunkumų kilnojimo diržai [sporto reikmenys]; Kūno treniravimo prietaisai [mankštos reikmėms]; Gulimosios banglentės; Fizinių pratimų prietaisai [kūnui treniruoti]; Krūtinės apsaugos sporto reikmėms; Antalkūniai [sporto reikmenys]; Fizinių pratimų kamuoliai; Mankštos juostos; Pratimų skersiniai; Krūtinės treniravimo espanderiai; Gimnastikos ir sporto reikmenys; Gimnastikos reikmenys; Gimnastikos žiedai; Šokdynės; Antkeliai [sporto reikmenys]; Vartinio teniso kamuoliukai; Kojų svarmenys mankštos reikmėms; Jogos kaladėlės; Jogos diržai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Svarcēlāju jostas (sporta piederumi); Ķermeņa trenažieri (vingrošanas rīki); Dēļi sērfošanai guļus; Atlētiskās vingrošanas ierīces; Krūškurvja aizsargi izmantošanai sportā; Elkoņu aizsargi sportistiem; Treniņu bumbas; Slodzes gumijas vingrošanai; Vingrošanas stieņi; Espanderi; Vingrošanas un sporta preces; Vingrošanas ierīces; Vingrošanas riņķi; Lecamauklas; Ceļgalu aizsargi sportistiem; Lakrosa bumbiņas; Kāju atsvari vingrinājumiem; Klucīši jogas nodarbībām; Siksnas jogas nodarbībām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ċinturini għall-irfigħ tal-piżijiet [oġġetti sportivi]; Apparat għall-eżerċizzju tal-ġisem; Bords għall-għawm [Body boards]; Apparat għat-taħriġ tal-muskoli; Protetturi tas-sider għall-użu sportiv; Protezzjoni għall-minkbejn [oġġetti sportivi]; Blalen ta' l-eżerċizzju; Ċineg għall-eżerċizzju; Bars tal-eżerċizzju; Wessiegħa tas-sider [apparat għall-eżerċizzji fiżiċi]; Artikli tal-ġinnastika u ta' l-isports; Tagħmir tal-ġinnastika; Ċrieki tal-ġinnastika; Ħbula tal-qbiż; Kuxxinetti għall-protezzjoni tal-irkoppa (oġġetti tal-isports); Blalen tal-lakross; Piżijiet għal mas-saqajn għall-eżerċizzju; Blokki tal-joga; Ċineg tal-Joga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Gewichtheffersgordels; Oefentoestellen voor lichaamstraining; Body boards; Fitnesstoestellen; Borstbeschermers voor sportgebruik; Elleboogbeschermers [sportartikelen]; Trainingsballen; Trainingsbanden; Oefenstaven; Trekveren voor spieroefeningen; Gymnastiek- en sportartikelen; Gymnastiekapparaten; Ringen voor gymnastiek; Springtouwen; Kniebeschermers [sportartikelen]; Lacrosseballen; Beengewichten voor oefendoeleinden; Yogablokken; Yogariemen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pasy do podnoszenia ciężarów [artykuły sportowe]; Urządzenia do ćwiczeń fizycznych [ćwiczenia]; Bodyboard; Przyrządy stosowane do ćwiczeń fizycznych; Ochraniacze na klatkę piersiową do użytku sportowego; Ochraniacze na łokcie [artykuły sportowe]; Piłki do ćwiczeń; Taśmy do ćwiczeń; Drążki do ćwiczeń; Ekspandery [ćwiczenia]; Artykuły gimnastyczne i sportowe; Artykuły gimnastyczne; Obręcze gimnastyczne; Skakanki; Nakolanniki [artykuły sportowe]; Piłki do lacrosse; Treningowe obciążniki na nogi; Bloczki do jogi; Paski do jogi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cintos para levantamento de pesos [artigos desportivos]; Aparelhos para exercícios físicos de treino muscular; Pranchas de bodyboard; Aparelhos para o culturismo; Protetores de tórax para uso desportivo; Cotoveleiras [artigos de desporto]; Bolas de exercício; Bandas para exercício; Barras de exercício; Exercitadores [extensores]; Artigos de ginástica e desporto; Aparelhos de ginástica; Argolas para ginástica; Cordas de saltar; Joelheiras [artigos de desporto]; Bolas de lacrosse; Pesos para as pernas para fazer exercício; Plataformas para ioga; Cordas para ioga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Centuri pentru halterofili [articole de sport]; Aparate pentru antrenamente [exerciții fizice]; Plăci de bodyboarding; Aparate pentru culturism; Protecții de piept pentru sport; Apărători de cot [articole de sport]; Mingi de antrenament; Benzi pentru exerciții; Bare pentru exerciții; Extensoare; Articole de gimnastică și de sport; Articole de gimnastică; Inele pentru gimnastică; Coarde de sărit; Apărători de genunchi [articole de sport]; Mingi pentru lacrosse; Greutăți pentru picioare pentru exerciții; Blocuri yoga; Benzi elastice pentru yoga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Opasky pre vzpieračov (športové potreby); Zariadenia a stroje na precvičovanie tela; Dosky na tréning vo vode; Posilňovacie stroje; Chrániče hrude používané pri športe; Chrániče na lakte (športové potreby); Cvičebné lopty; Pásy na cvičenie; Tyče na cvičenie; Cvičebné náradie na posilňovanie hrudníka; Gymnastické a športové predmety; Gymnastické zariadenia; Gymnastické kruhy; Švihadlá; Chrániče na kolená (športový tovar); Lakrosové loptičky; Závažia na nohy na cvičenie; Bloky na cvičenie jogy; Pásy na cvičenie jogy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pasovi za dvigovanje uteži (izdelki za šport); Naprave za telesno vadbo [telovadba]; Plavalne deske; Naprave za telovadbo; Ščitniki za prsi za uporabo pri športu; Ščitniki za komolce [športni artikli]; Žoge za vadbo; Trakovi za vadbo; Palice za vadbo; Ekspanderji [za raztegovanje prsnih mišic]; Gimnastične in športne potrebščine; Izdelki za telovadbo; Obroči za gimnastiko; Kolebnice; Ščitniki za kolena [športni artikli]; Lacrosse žoga; Uteži za noge za vadbo; Bloki za jogo; Trakovi za jogo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tyngdlyftningsbälten [sportartiklar]; Apparater för kroppsträning [träning]; Bodyboard (små surfbrädor); Träningsapparater; Bröstskydd för sportbruk; Armbågsskydd [sportartiklar]; Bollar för träning; Träningsband; Träningsstänger; Muskelstärkare; Gymnastik- och sportartiklar; Redskap för gymnastik; Ringar för gymnastik; Hopprep; Knäskydd [sportartiklar]; Lacrossebollar; Benvikter för motion; Yogablock; Remmar för användning med yoga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/081</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-30</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/150</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>979648</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>39103</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
