<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-17T08:58:42</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018222913</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018222913</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-08</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-13</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>fr</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-08</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-17</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>LINKLIFT</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>6</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Метални строителни материали; Преносими метални конструкции; Подвижни метални конструкции; Верижки от метал; Колони от метал за сгради; Метални дръжки за натискане; Сцена за спектакли, състояща се основно от метални материали; Метални стъпала; Метални подови плоскости; Преносими стойки от метал за използване при наблюдение.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kovové stavební materiály; Přenosné kovové konstrukce; Mobilní kovové konstrukce posuvné; Kovové řetězy; Kovové sloupy pro stavebnictví; Kovové tlačné tyče; Pódia pro představení, především z kovových materiálů; Kovové lavice (na sportovištích); Kovové podlahové desky; Přenosné kovové tribuny pro diváky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Byggematerialer af metal; Bygninger, transportable, af metal; Mobile, flytbare konstruktioner af metal; Kæder af metal; Søjler af metal til bygningsbrug; Frontstænger af metal; Scener til shows bestående hovedsageligt af materialer af metal; Metaltribuner; Gulvplanker af metal; Transportable tilskuertribuner af metal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Baumaterialien aus Metall; Transportable Bauten aus Metall; Verschiebbare Bauten aus Metall; Metallketten; Säulen aus Metall [Bauteile]; Metallgriffe; Bühnen für Aufführungen, die vorwiegend aus metallischen Werkstoffen bestehen; Metallstufen; Bodenbleche aus Metall; Tragbare Gestelle aus Metall zur Verwendung durch Zuschauer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μεταλλικά υλικά οικοδομών· Κατασκευές λυόμενες μεταλλικές· Μετατοπιζόμενες φορητές μεταλλικές κατασκευές· Αλυσίδες μεταλλικές· Στήλες μεταλλικές [μέρη οικοδομών]· Μεταλλικοί στρόφαλοι ώσεως· Σκηνές για θεάματα κατασκευασμένες κυρίως από μεταλλικά υλικά· Μεταλλικές κερκίδες· Μεταλλικές σανίδες δαπέδου· Φορητές μεταλλικές βάσεις για χρήση από θεατές.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Metal building materials; Transportable structures of metal; Transferable mobile metal constructions; Chains of metal; Pillars of metal for buildings; Metal push bars; Stages for shows composed predominantly of materials of metal; Stands of metal; Floor boards of metal; Portable stands of metal for use by spectators.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Materiales de construcción metálicos; Estructuras metálicas transportables; Construcciones metálicas móviles en traslación; Cadenas metálicas; Columnas metálicas [partes de construcciones]; Barras de empuje metálicas; Escenario para espectáculos conformado principalmente por materiales metálicos; Gradas metálicas; Placas metálicas para el suelo; Bases portátiles de metal para su uso por parte de espectadores.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Metallehitusmaterjalid; Teisaldatavad metallehitised, -tarindid; Teisaldatavad metallehitised; Metallist ketid; Metallist ehituspiilarid; Metallist tõukerauad; Peamiselt metallmaterjalidest koosnevad lavad etendusteks; Metalltribüünid; Metallpõrandaplaadid; Vaatajatele mõeldud teisaldatavad metallist alused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Metalliset rakennustarvikkeet; Siirrettävät metalliset rakennukset; Siirrettävät metallirakenteet; Ketjut (Metalli -); Pylväät (Metalli -), rakennuksiin; Metalliset työntötangot; Esityksiin tarkoitetut näyttämöt, jotka koostuvat pääosin metallisista materiaaleista; Metalliset avokatsomot; Metalliset lattialevyt; Siirrettävät metalliset telineet yleisöä varten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Matériaux de construction métalliques; Constructions métalliques transportables; Constructions métalliques mobiles en translation; Chaînes métalliques; Colonnes métalliques (partie de constructions); Barres de poussée métalliques; Scènes pour spectacles se composant principalement de matériaux métalliques; Gradins métalliques; Planchers métalliques; tribunes mobiles en métal pour spectateurs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Metalni građevinski materijali; Prenosive građevinske metalne strukture; Mobilne metalne konstrukcije u prijenosu; Lanci (metalni lani); Metalne kolone [dijelovi građevinskih konstrukcija]; Metalni elementi za otvaranje; Pozornice za priredbe koje se sastoje uglavnom od metalnih materijala; Metalne tribine; Metalne podne ploče; Prenosiva metalna stajališta za gledatelje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Fém építőanyagok; Hordozható, mobil fémszerkezetek; Eltolható mobil fémszerkezetek; Fémláncok; Fémoszlopok [építmények részei]; Fém tolórudak; Főként fémes anyagokból álló színpad előadásokhoz; Lépcsőzetes fém padsorok; Padlóburkolatok fémből; Mobil lelátók fémből.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Materiali per costruzione metallici; Strutture metalliche trasportabili; Costruzioni metalliche mobili in traslazione; Catene metalliche; Colonne metalliche [parti di costruzioni]; Maniglie di spinta metalliche; Scenari per spettacoli composti principalmente da materiali metallici; Gradini metallici; Assi per pavimenti di metallo; Tribune portatili per spettatori in metallo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Metalinės statybinės medžiagos; Kilnojamosios metalinės struktūros; Kilnojamos metalinės konstrukcijos vertimo reikmėms; Grandinės (Metalinės -); Metalinės statybinės atramos; Stumiamosios metalinės juostos; Renginių scenos, daugiausia iš metalinių medžiagų; Metaliniai žiūrovų suolai; Metalinės grindų lentos; Kilnojamos metalinės žiūrovų tribūnos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Būvmateriāli no metāla; Pārvietojamas metāla struktūras; Pārvietojamas metāla būves pārvietošanai; Metāla ķēdes; Metāla kolonnas (būvdetaļas); Metāla stumšanas stieņi; Skatuves izrādēm, kas veidotas galvenokārt no metāla materiāliem; Metāla tribīnes; Grīdas dēļi no metāla; Pārvietojami metāla podesti skatītājiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Materjal tal-metall għall-bini; Strutturi trasportabbli tal-metall; Kostruzzjonijiet tal-metall li jistgħu jinġarru minn post għall-ieħor; Ktajjen tal-metall; Kolonni tal-metall għall-bini; Vireg għall-imbuttar magħmula mill-metall; Palkijiet għall-ispettakli magħmula l-aktar minn materjali tal-metall; Sedili twal tal-istejdjums tal-metall; Bordijiet tal-metall tal-art; Stends li jinġarru tal-metall għall-użu minn spettaturi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Bouwmaterialen van metaal; Verplaatsbare constructies van metaal; Mobiele parallel verplaatsende constructies van metaal; Kettingen van metaal; Kolommen van metaal [bouwonderdelen]; Stootbalken van metaal; Podia voor voorstellingen, voornamelijk bestaande uit metalen materialen; Rijen banken van metaal; Vloerplaten van metaal; Tribunes (Verplaatsbare -) van metaal voor toeschouwers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Budowlane materiały metalowe; Przenośne struktury metalowe; Konstrukcje metalowe do przenoszenia równoległego; Łańcuchy metalowe; Słupy metalowe [elementy konstrukcyjne]; Metalowe elementy umożliwiające popychanie; Scena do widowisk zbudowana głównie z materiałów metalowych; Trybuny metalowe; Metalowe płyty podłogowe; Przenośne trybuny metalowe do użytku przez widzów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Materiais de construção metálicos; Construções transportáveis metálicas; Construções metálicas móveis em translação; Correntes metálicas; Colunas metálicas para construções; Puxadores de portas metálicos; Palcos para espetáculos compostos principalmente por materiais metálicos; Bancadas metálicas; Soalhos metálicos; Plataformas portáteis em metal para uso de espetadores.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Materiale de construcţie metalice; Structuri metalice transportabile; Construcții metalice mobile în translație; Lanţuri metalice; Stâlpi de metal [părti de construcţie]; Bare de tracțiune din metal; Scene pentru spectacole alcătuite în principal din materiale metalice; Tribune metalice; Scânduri din metal pentru podea; Tribune mobile din metal pentru spectatori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Stavebný materiál z kovu; Prenosné konštrukcie z kovu; Kovové prenosné stavby s pohybom dopredu; Kovové reťaze; Kovové stĺpy pre stavebníctvo; Kovové tyče na tlačenie; Javiská na predstavenia, ktoré sa skladajú predovšetkým z materiálov z kovu; Kovové tribúny; Kovové podlahové panely; Prenosné kovové tribúny pre divákov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kovinski gradbeni materiali; Prenosne kovinske strukture; Prenosne premične kovinske zgradbe; Kovinske verige; Kovinski nosilci za gradnjo; Kovinski potisni drogovi; Odri za predstave, sestavljeni pretežno iz kovinskih materialov; Kovinske montažne tribune; Kovinske talne plošče; Prenosne kovinske tribune.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Byggnadsmaterial av metall; Flyttbara byggnadskonstruktioner av metall; Mobila metallkonstruktioner under förflyttning; Kedjor av metall; Pelare av metall för byggnader; Stötstänger av metall; Scener för shower som huvudsakligen består av metallmaterial; Metall-terrasser; Golvpaneler av metall; Bärbara ställningar av metall för användning av åskådare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>7</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Инструменти за машини; Повдигащи апарати, елеватори [лифтове], ескалатори, асансьори, подемници; Повдигащи машини за обработка на товари; Повдигателни съоръжения за обработка на товари; Подемни колони; Повдигащи или въздушни платформи (включително и мобилни); Подемни повърхности; Поставки за повдигане на плоскости; Плъзгачи за супорти [части на машини]; Подвижни повдигащи се платформи; Уреди за преместване на структури; Машини за транспорт и вертикален пренос на товари; Механизми за вертикално преместване; Задвижващи устройства за асансьори; Механизъм за преобразуване на редици седалки чрез автоматизирана система; Механизъм за ръководене на преместването на седалки за промяна на обзавеждането на зали; Устройства за съхраняване на вериги за машинни инструменти; Устройства за съхранение (части за машини); Предавателни вериги, с изключение на такива за сухопътни превозни средства; Твърди тласкащи вериги за машини; Твърди вериги за машинни инструменти; Ремъци за елеватори; Подемни устройства [машинни]; Предавателни съединители (машини); Машинни автомобилни крикове; Гъвкави жакове (електрически); Линеен задвижващ механизъм; Телескопични задвижващи механизми; Телескопични задвижващи механизми (механични); Рампи (машини); Повдигащи рампи; Механизми за преместване на дъното на плувен басейн.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Obráběcí stroje; Zdvihací zařízení, elevátory, eskalátory, pohyblivá schodiště, výtahy, zdviže; Zvedací stroje pro manipulaci s nákladem; Zvedací náčiní pro manipulaci s nákladem; Zvedací kolony; Zdvižné nebo zvedací plošiny (včetně mobilních); Zdvihací stoly; Stojany na zvedací stoly; Saně (suporty) [části strojů]; Zdvihací plošiny pro nákladní auta; Zařízení pro přemísťování konstrukcí; Stroje na vertikální dopravu a přenos břemen; Mechanismy pro vertikální přemísťování; Hnací zařízení pro výtahy; Mechanismus pro přeskupení řad sedadel pomocí automatizovaného systému; Vodicí mechanismus pro přemísťování sedadel za účelem změny uspořádání sálů; Úložná zařízení pro řetězy obráběcích strojů; Úložná zařízení [části strojů]; Převodové řetězy, jiné než pro pozemní vozidla; Neohebné tlačné řetězy pro stroje; Neohebné řetězy pro obráběcí stroje; Řemeny pro výtahy; Hevery [stroje]; Pohonové zdviháky (stroje); Strojní zvedáky pro vozidla; Pružné zvedáky (elektrické); Lineární aktuátory; Teleskopické pohony; Teleskopické pohony (mechanické); Rampy jako stroje; Zdvihací rampy; Mechanismy pro posunování den bazénů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Maskinværktøjer; Løfteanordninger, elevatorer, rulletrapper, lifte, hejseapparater; Løftemaskiner til håndtering af last; Løftegrej til håndtering af last; Løftesøjler; Elevations- eller løfteplatforme (inklusive mobile); Løfteborde; Stativer til løfteborde; Værktøjsslæder [dele af maskiner]; Lifte monteret på ladvogne; Apparater til flytning af konstruktioner; Maskiner til transport og vertikal overførsel af laster; Mekanismer til vertikal transport; Drev til hejseværk; Mekanismer til omdannelse af sæderækker via et automatiseret system; Mekanismer til styring og flytning af sæder til ændring af lokalers indretning; Udstyr til kædestyring af værktøjsmaskiner; Lagerenheder (maskindele); Transmissionskæder, ikke til befordringsmidler til brug på land; Stive anslagskæder til maskiner; Stive kæder til værktøjsmaskiner; Elevatordrivremme; Løftemaskiner; Donkrafte til kraftoverførsel (maskiner); Maskindrevne donkrafte; Fleksible donkrafte (Elektriske); Lineære aktuatorer; Teleskopaktuatorer; Teleskopaktuatorer (mekaniske); Ramper i form af maskiner; Løfteramper; Bundrensere til svømmebassiner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werkzeugmaschinen; Hubgeräte, Elevatoren, Rolltreppen, Lifte [Aufzüge], Lastenaufzüge; Hebemaschinen für den Lastenumschlag; Hebegeräte zum Handhaben von Lasten; Hebesilos; Hub- oder Hebebühnen (einschließlich mobile); Hubtische; Ständer für Hebetische; Schlittensupporte [Maschinenteile]; Hochhubwagen; Geräte zum Bewegen von Konstruktionen; Maschinen für den Transport und die vertikale Beförderung von Lasten; Mechanismen zum vertikalen Bewegen; Antriebsgeräte für Aufzuganlagen; Mechanismen zum Umbau von Sitzreihen über ein automatisiertes System; Mechanismen zur Steuerung des Versetzens von Sitzplätzen zur Änderung der Raumgestaltung; Kettenlagervorrichtungen für Werkzeugmaschinen; Lagerungsvorrichtungen (Maschinenteile); Antriebsketten, ausgenommen für Landfahrzeuge; Starre Schubketten für Maschinen; Starre Ketten für Werkzeugmaschinen; Elevatorgurte; Hebewinden [Maschinen]; Hebevorrichtungen für Getriebe (Maschinen); Maschinelle Wagenheber; Kraftbetätigte Gelenkwagenheber; Linearaktoren; Teleskopaktoren; (mechanische) Teleskopaktoren; Rampen als Maschinen; Hubrampen; Mechanismen zum Bewegen von Schwimmbeckenböden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εργαλειομηχανές· Συσκευές ανύψωσης, ανυψωτήρες, κυλιόμενες κλίμακες, ανελκυστήρες, ανυψωτήρες φορτίου· Μηχανές ανύψωσης για τον χειρισμό φορτίων· Μηχανισμοί ανύψωσης για τον χειρισμό φορτίων· Στήλες ανύψωσης· Ανύψωση ή άρση πλατφόρμων (όπου περιλαμβάνονται κινητές)· Πίνακες ανελκυστήρα· Βάσεις για ανυψωτικές τράπεζες· Ολισθαίνοντα έδρανα [μέρη μηχανών]· Ανυψωτικά οχήματα-πλατφόρμες· Συσκευές μετακίνησης κατασκευών· Μηχανές για κατακόρυφη μεταφορά και μετακίνηση φορτίων· Μηχανισμοί κατακόρυφης μετατόπισης· Κινητήριοι μηχανισμοί για εγκαταστάσεις ανελκυστήρων· Μηχανισμός για μετατροπή σειρών καθισμάτων με χρήση συστήματος αυτόματης λειτουργίας· Μηχανισμός οδήγησης της μετακίνησης καθισμάτων με σκοπό την αλλαγή της διαρρύθμισης αιθουσών· Μηχανισμός αποθήκευσης αλυσίδων για χρήση σε εργαλειομηχανές· Μηχανισμοί αποθήκευσης (μέρη μηχανών)· Αλυσίδες κινητήρων, εκτός αυτών που προορίζονται για χερσαία οχήματα· Άκαμπτες αλυσίδες ώθησης για μηχανές· Άκαμπτες αλυσίδες για χρήση σε εργαλειομηχανές· Ιμάντες ανελκυστήρων· Βαρούλκα [μηχανές]· Γρύλοι μετάδοσης κίνησης (μηχανές)· Μηχανικοί ανυψωτές οχημάτων· Ηλεκτροκίνητοι εύκαμπτοι γρύλοι· Γραμμικοί ενεργοποιητές· Τηλεσκοπικά εξαρτήματα ενεργοποίησης· Τηλεσκοπικοί μηχανικοί μηχανισμοί ενεργοποίησης· Ράμπες ως μηχανές· Ράμπες ανύψωσης· Μηχανισμοί μετατόπισης πυθμένα πισίνας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Machine tools; Lifting apparatus, lifts, escalators, elevators, hoists; Lifting machines for handling loads; Lifting gear for handling loads; Lifting columns; Elevating or lifting platforms (including mobile); Lifting tables; Stands for lifting tables; Slide rests [parts of machines]; Platform truck lifts; Apparatus for moving structures; Machines for the transport and vertical transfer of loads; Vertical movement mechanisms; Driving devices for lifts; Mechanism for transforming rows of seats via an automated system; Mechanism for guiding the moving of seats for modifying room layout; Device for storing chains for machine tools; Storage devices (parts of machines); Transmission chains other than for land vehicles; Rigid push chains for machines; Rigid chains for machine tools; Elevator belts; Jacks [machines]; Transmission jacks (machines); Mechanical jacks; Flexible jacks (Power operated -); Linear actuators; Telescopic actuators; Telescopic actuators (mechanical); Ramps being machines; Lifting ramps; Mechanisms for moving swimming pool floors.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Máquinas herramientas; Aparatos de elevación, elevadores, escaleras mecánicas, ascensores, montacargas; Máquinas de elevación para manipular cargamentos; Engranajes de elevación para manipular cargas; Columnas de elevación; Plataformas de elevación (incluyendo móviles); Mesas elevadoras; Bases para elevar mesas; Carros (soportes de -) [partes de máquinas]; Elevadores de camiones con plataforma; Aparatos de desplazamiento de estructuras; Máquinas para el transporte y transferencia vertical de cargas; Mecanismos de desplazamiento vertical; Dispositivos de accionamiento para elevadores; Máquinas de transformación de filas de asientos mediante un sistema automático; Mecanismo de guía de desplazamiento de asientos para la modificación de planificación de salas; Dispositivo de almacenamiento de cadenas para máquinas herramienta; Dispositivos de almacenamiento (partes de máquinas); Cadenas motrices que no sean para vehículos terrestres; Cadenas de empuje rígidas para máquinas; Cadenas rígidas para máquinas herramienta; Correas para elevadores; Crics; Cilindros de transmisión (máquinas); Gatos mecánicos; Gatos flexibles eléctricos; Actuadores lineales; Accionadores telescópicos; Accionadores telescópicos (mecánicos); Rampas que sean máquinas; Rampas de elevación; Mecanismos de desplazamiento de fondos de piscinas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tööpingid; Tõsteseadmed, elevaatorid, eskalaatorid, liftid, kaubaliftid; Tõstemasinad laadungite käsitsemiseks; Tõstemehhanism laadungite käsitsemiseks; Tõstetorud; Lifti-või tõsteplatvormid (sh mobiilsed); Tõsteplaadid; Tõsteplaatide alused; Supordid [masinaosad]; Madelauto-tõstukid; Ehituskonstruktsioonide teisaldamise seadmed; Raskuste vertikaalseks transpordiks ja edasi viimiseks ette nähtud masinad; Mehhanismid asjade vertikaalseks liigutamiseks; Liftide käiturseadmed; Automatiseeritud süsteemi abil istmeridade muutmise mehhanismid; Istmete liigutamise juhtimise mehhanismid saalide sisseseade muutmiseks; Konveierladustuse seadmed tööpinkidele; Laoseadmed (masinaosad); Ülekandeketid, v.a maismaasõidukite; Masinatele ette nähtud jäigad konveierilindid (töötavad tõukemeetodi abil); Tööpinkidele ette nähtud jäigad konveierilindid; Tõstukirihmad; Tungrauad [masinad]; Tõsteseadmed (masinad); Masinlikud autotõstukid; Painduvad elektrilised tungrauad; Lineaarajamid; Teleskoopseadmed; Mehaanilised teleskoopseadmed; Rambid [masinad]; Tõsterambid; Basseinipõhjade liigutamise mehhanismid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Konetyökalut; Nostolaitteet, nostimet, liukuportaat, hissit, kuormannostolaitteet; Nostokoneet kuorman käsittelyyn; Nostokoneistot kuorman käsittelyyn; Nostopylväät; Nostolavat (mukaan lukien siirrettävät); Nostopöydät; Telineet nostopöytiä varten; Teränpitimet [koneiden osina]; Hissilavatrukit; Rakenteiden siirtolaitteet; Koneet kuromien pystykuljetukseen ja -siirtoon; Pystysiirtomekanismit; Hissien ajolaitteet; Mekanismit istuinrivien muuntamiseen automatisoidun järjestelmän välityksellä; Istuinten siirron ohjausmekanismit tilojen kalustuksen muuntamiseen; Ketjujen säilytyslaitteet työstökoneita varten; Säilytyslaitteet (koneiden osat); Vaihdeketjut, paitsi maa-ajoneuvoihin; Jäykät työntöketjut koneisiin; Jäykät ketjut työstökoneisiin; Hissien hihnat; Tunkit [koneina]; Voimansiirtosylinterit (koneet); Konekäyttöiset autonnostovivut; Taipuisat (sähkökäyttöiset) tunkit; Lineaarikäyttölaitteet; Teleskooppiset toimilaitteet; Teleskooppiset toimilaitteet (mekaaniset); Rampit koneina; Nostorampit; Uima-altaiden pohjien siirtomekanismit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Machines-outils; Appareils de levage, élévateurs, escaliers roulants, ascenseurs, monte-charge; Machines de levage pour manutention de charges; Mécanismes de levage pour manutention de charges; Colonnes de levage; Plates-formes élévatrices ou de levage y compris mobiles; Table de levage; Supports de tables élévatrices; Supports à chariot (parties de machines); Chariots à plate-forme élévatrice; Appareils de déplacement de structures; Machines pour le transport et le transfert vertical de charges; Mécanismes de déplacement vertical; Dispositifs d'entraînement pour élévateurs; Mécanisme de transformation de rangées de sièges via un système automatisé; Mécanisme de guidage de déplacement de sièges pour modification d'aménagement de salles; dispositif de stockage de chaînes pour machines-outils; dispositifs de stockage (parties de machines); chaînes motrices autres que pour véhicules terrestres; Chaînes de poussée rigides pour machines; Chaînes rigides pour machines-outils; Courroies d'élévateurs; Vérins (machines); Vérins de transmission (machines); Vérins mécaniques; Vérins flexibles électriques; Actionneurs linéaires; Actionneurs télescopiques; Actionneurs télescopiques (mécaniques); rampes sous forme de machines; Rampes de levage; mécanismes de déplacement de fonds de piscines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Alatni strojevi; Strojevi za dizanje, dizala, pokretne stube, liftovi, povlačne dizalice; Strojevi za dizanje za rukovanje tereta; Uređaji za dizanje i rukovanje teretom; Uređaji u obliku stupova za dizanje; Podizne platforme ili platforme za podizanje, uključujući i mobilne; Platforme za dizanje; Stalci za dizanje stolova; Klizna postolja [dijelovi strojeva]; Pokretna platforma za podizanje tereta; Uređaji za premještanje struktura; Strojevi za prijevoz i vertikalni prijenos tereta; Mehanizmi za vertikalni prijenos; Pogonske naprave za dizala; Mehanizam za preobrazbu redova sjedala automatiziranim sustavom; Mehanizam za navođenje premještanja sjedala radi izmjene uređenja prostorija; Uređaji za skladištenje lanaca za alatne strojeve; Spremnici za skladištenje (dijelovi strojeva); Prijenosni lanci [osim za kopnena vozila]; Kruti udarni lanci za strojeve; Kruti lanci za alatne strojeve; Remeni uređaja za dizanje [elevatora]; Dizalice za vozila [strojevi]; Prijenosne dizalice (strojevi); Strojne dizalice za vozila; Fleksibilne dizalice (Električne -); Linearni aktuatori; Teleskopski aktuatori; Teleskopski aktuatori (mehanički); Rampe kao strojevi; Rampe za dizanje; Mehanizmi za kretanje na dnu bazena.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szerszámgépek; Emelőberendezések, felvonók, mozgólépcsők, liftek, teherliftek; Rakomány kezeléséhez használt emelőgépek; Terhek kezelésére szolgáló felvonószerkezetek; Emelő oszlopok; Felvonó vagy emelő platformok (többek között mozgatható); Emelőasztalok; Emelőasztal-állványok; Keresztszánok [géprészek]; Emelők platformos teherautókhoz; Készülékek szerkezetek mozgatásához; Gépek terhek szállítására és függőleges elmozdítására; Függőleges mozgatásra szolgáló szerkezetek; Liftek hajtóeszközei; Üléssorok automatizált rendszeren keresztüli átalakítására szolgáló szerkezet; Székek elmozdítását vezérlő szerkezet, termek elrendezésének módosításához; Lánctároló eszköz szerszámgépekhez; Tárolóeszközök (géprészek); Erőátviteli láncok, nem szárazföldi járművekhez; Merev nyomóláncok gépekhez; Merev láncok szerszámgépekhez; Felvonó hevederek; Emelőszerkezetek [gépek]; Erőátviteli hengerek (gépek); Gépi kocsiemelők; Flexibilis elektromos emelők; Lineáris aktuátorok; Teleszkópos hajtóművek; Teleszkópos hajtóművek (szerkezetek); Rámpák, mint gépek; Emelőrámpák; Mozgó szerkezetek úszómedencék aljához.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Macchine utensili; Apparecchi di sollevamento, elevatori, scale mobili, ascensori, montacarichi; Macchine di sollevamento per la movimentazione di carichi; Meccanismi di sollevamento per la manipolazione di carichi; Colonne sollevatrici; Piattaforme di sollevamento (anche mobili); Tavole di sollevamento; Supporti per tavole elevatrici; Lunette mobili [parti di macchine]; Carrelli elevatori a piattaforma; Apparecchi di spostamento di strutture; Macchine per il trasporto e il trasferimento verticale di carichi; Meccanismi di spostamento verticale; Dispositivi di guida per ascensori; Meccanismo di trasformazione di file di sedili tramite un sistema automatizzato; Meccanismo di guida di spostamento di sedili per la modifica della sistemazione di sale; Dispositivo di deposito di catene per macchine-utensili; Dispositivi di deposito (parti di macchine); Catene motrici, diverse da quelle per veicoli terrestri; Catene di spinta rigide per macchine; Catene rigide per macchine utensili; Cinghie per elevatori; Martinetti [macchine]; Martinetti di trasmissione (macchine); Martinetti meccanici; Martinetti flessibili (Elettrici -); Attuatori lineari; Azionatori telescopici; Dispositivi d'azionamento telescopici (meccanici); Rampe che sono macchine; Rampe di sollevamento; Meccanismi di spostamento per fondi di piscine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Metalo apdirbimo staklės; Kėlimo aparatai, liftai, eskalatoriai, keltuvai, keltuvai; Keliamosios krovinių tvarkymo mašinos; Krovinių pakrovimo-iškrovimo įrenginiai; Keliančiosios kolonos; Kėlimo platformos (įskaitant nešiojamąsias); Kėlimo stalai; Kėlimo stalų stovai; Suportai su pasukamomis pavažomis [mašinų dalys]; Platforminiai sunkvežimių keltuvai; Judančių konstrukcijų aparatai; Krovinių gabenimo ir vertikalaus perdavimo mašinos; Vertikalaus poslinkio mechanizmai; Liftų varomieji prietaisai; Sėdynių eilių pertvarkymo per automatizuotą sistemą mechanizmas; Sėdynės poslinkio kreipiamasis mechanizmas kambario išdėstymui modifikuoti; Staklių grandininis laikymo įtaisas; Laikymo įtaisai (mašinų dalys); Pavaros grandinės (ne antžeminio transporto priemonėms); Standžios mašinų stūmimo grandinės; Standžios staklių grandinės; Elevatorių diržai; Keltuvai [mašinos]; Transmisijos cilindrai (mašinos); Automobilių kėlimo platformos; Elektriniai lankstieji kėlikliai; Tiesiaeigiai vykdomieji įtaisai; Teleskopinės pavaros; Teleskopinės pavaros (mechaninės); Rampos (mašinos); Kėlimo rampos; Baseinų dugnų judėjimo mechanizmai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Darbgaldi; Pacelšanas ierīces, lifti, eskalatori, lifti, telferceltņi; Cēlējmašīnas manipulācijām ar kravām; Pacēlējmehānismi manipulācijām ar kravām; Paceļošas piltuves; Pacelšanas vai celšanas platformas (tostarp pārvietojamas); Pacelšanas virsmas; Galdu celšanas statīvi; Suporta kamanas [mašīnu daļas]; Kravas automobiļu pacēlājplatformas; Aparāti konstrukciju pārvietošanai; Mašīnas vertikālas kravas pārvietošanai; Vertikālo pārvietojumu mehānismi; Liftu piedziņas mehānismi; Sēdekļu rindu pārveidošanas mehānisms, izmantojot automatizētu sistēmu; Sēdekļa pārvietošanas vadības mehānisms telpas izkārtojuma modificēšanai; Darbgaldu ķēdes glabāšanas ierīce; Uzglabāšanas ierīces (mašīnu daļas); Pārvada ķēdes, izņemot sauszemes transportlīdzekļiem paredzētās; Stingras mašīnbūves ķēdes; Stingras darbgaldu ķēdes; Elevatoru siksnas; Domkrati [mašīnas]; Transmisijas domkrati (mašīnas); Mehāniski domkrati; Pielāgojami elektriskie domkrati; Lineārie aktuatori; Teleskopiskās piedziņas; Teleskopiskās (mehāniskās) piedziņas; Uzbrauktuves (rampas), kas ir mašīnas; Pacelšanas rampas; Baseinu dibena pārvietošanas mehānismi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Għodda tal-magni; Apparat ta' rfigħ, elevaturi, skalaturi, liftijiet, magni tal-irfigħ; Magni tal-irfigħ għall-ġestjoni tat-tagħbijiet; Tagħmir għall-irfigħ għat-tqandil tat-tagħbijiet; Tagħmir tal-irfigħ; Pjattaformi elevati jew għal skop ta' olzar (li jinkludu dawk mobbli); Imwejjed tal-irfigħ; Stends għall-imwejjed tal-irfigħ; Sapporti għaż-żrieżaq (partijiet ta' magni); Trakkijiet bil-pjattaformi tal-irfigħ; Apparat għall-ġarr ta' strutturi; Magni għat-trasport u t-trasferiment vertikali tat-tagħbija; Mekkaniżmi għall-ġarr vertikali; Tagħmir li jħaddem għal lifts; Mekkaniżmu għat-trasformazzjoni tar-ringieli tas-siġġijiet permezz ta' sistema awtomatika; Mekkaniżmu ta' gwida għall-ġarr tas-siġġijiet għall-modifikazzjoni tat-tqassim tas-sali; Tagħmir tal-ħżin tal-ktajjen għall-għodda tal-magni; Tagħmir tal-ħżin (partijiet ta' magni),; Ktajjen tat-trasmissjoni, minbarra għal vetturi tal-art; Ktajjen ibsin tal-imbuttar għall-magni; Ktajjen ibsin għall-għodda tal-magni; Ċineg tal-liftijiet; Ġakkijiet [magni]; Ġakkijiet tat-trażmissjoni (magni); Ġakkijiet mekkaniċi; Ġakkijiet elettriċi (li jaħdmu bid-dawl); Attwaturi lineari; Attwaturi teleskopiċi; Attwaturi teleskopiċi (mekkaniċi); Rampi li huma magni; Rampi tal-irfigħ; Mekkaniżmi għall-ġarr tal-fondi tal-pixxini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Werktuigmachines; Hefapparaten, elevatoren, roltrappen, liften, goederenliften; Hefwerktuigen voor het verladen van vracht; Heftoestellen voor het verladen van vracht; Hefkolommen; Hijstoestellen of hefplatforms (waaronder mobiele); Heftafels voor machines; Stellingen voor heftafels; Slede-steunen [machine-onderdelen]; Platformwagenliften; Apparaten voor het verplaatsen van constructies; Machines voor transport en verticale overbrenging van ladingen; Mechanismen voor verticale verplaatsing; Aandrijfmotoren voor liftinstallaties; Mechanismen voor het veranderen van stoelenrijen via een geautomatiseerd systeem; Mechanismen voor het verplaatsen van stoelen voor het veranderen van de inrichting van zalen; Opslaginrichtingen voor kettingen voor werktuigmachines; Opslaginrichtingen (machineonderdelen); Transmissiekettingen, anders dan voor landvoertuigen; Onbuigzame aandrijfkettingen voor machines; Onbuigzame kettingen voor werktuigmachines; Riemen voor liftapparatuur; Kriks [machines]; Overbrengingsvijzels (machines); Machinale krikken; Krikken (Elektrisch bediende buigzame -); Lineaire actuatoren; Telescopische aandrijfmechanismen; Telescopische aandrijfmechanismen (mechanisch); Hellingbanen, zijnde machines; Liftplatforms; Verplaatsingsmechanismen voor zwembadbodems.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Obrabiarki; Urządzenia podnośnikowe, podnośniki, ruchome schody, windy, wyciągi; Maszyny podnośnikowe do transportu bliskiego ładunków; Sprzęt podnośnikowy do transportu bliskiego ładunków; Kolumny podnoszące; Platformy unoszące lub podnoszące (w tym mobilne); Stoły podnośnikowe; Stojaki do stołów podnośnikowych; Suporty [części maszyn]; Podnośniki do ciężarówek platformowych; Urządzenia do przenoszenia struktur; Maszyny do transportu i do pionowego przenoszenia ładunków; Mechanizmy do przenoszenia poziomego; Urządzenia napędowe do wind; Mechanizmy do przekształcania rzędów siedzeń za pomocą zautomatyzowanego systemu; Mechanizmy prowadzące do przenoszenia siedzeń w celu zmiany urządzenia sal; Urządzenia do przechowywania łańcuchów obrabiarek; Urządzenia do przechowywania (części maszyn); Łańcuchy napędowe, inne niż do pojazdów lądowych; Sztywne łańcuchy pchające do maszyn; Sztywne łańcuchy do obrabiarek; Pasy do podnośników; Podnośniki [urządzenia]; Podnośniki transmisyjne (maszyny); Mechaniczne podnośniki samochodowe; Dźwigniki elastyczne obsługiwane elektrycznie; Siłowniki liniowe; Siłowniki teleskopowe; Siłowniki teleskopowe (mechaniczne); Rampy w postaci maszyn; Rampy do podnoszenia; Mechanizmy do przenoszenia den basenów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máquinas-ferramentas; Aparelhos de elevação, elevadores, escadas rolantes, ascensores, monta-cargas; Máquinas de elevação para manuseamento de cargas; Engrenagens de elevação para manuseamento de cargas; Torres elevatórias; Plataformas elevatórias (incluindo móveis); Mesas elevadoras; Suportes para mesas de elevação; Suportes para carretas; Plataformas de elevação para camiões; Aparelhos de deslocação de estruturas; Máquinas para o transporte e a transferência vertical de cargas; Mecanismos de deslocação vertical; Dispositivos de acionamento para elevadores; Mecanismos de transformação de filas de assentos através de um sistema automatizado; Mecanismos de orientação de deslocação de assentos para modificação de organização de salas; Dispositivos de armazenamento de correntes para máquinas-ferramentas; Dispositivos de armazenamento (partes de máquinas); Correntes de transmissão, não sendo para veículos terrestres; Correntes rígidas de impulso para máquinas; Correntes rígidas para máquinas-ferramentas; Correias de elevadores; Macacos [máquinas]; Macacos de transmissão (máquinas); Macacos mecânicos; Macacos flexíveis elétricos; Atuadores lineares; Acionadores telescópicos; Acionadores telescópicos (mecânicos); Rampas enquanto máquinas; Rampas elevatórias; Mecanismos de deslocação de fundos de piscinas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Maşini-unelte; Aparate de ridicat, elevatoare, scări rulante, lifturi, mașini de ridicat; Echipamente de ridicare pentru manipularea încărcăturilor; Utilaj de ridicare pentru manevrarea încărcăturilor; Coloane elevatoare; Platforme de elevare sau de ridicare (inclusiv mobile); Mese de ridicare; Suporturi pentru mese de ridicare; Sănii portcuţit [organe de maşini]; Stivuitoare pentru paleţi; Aparate de deplasare de structuri; Mașini pentru transportul și transferul vertical al încărcăturilor; Mecanisme de deplasare verticală; Dispozitive de acţionare pentru lifturi; Mecanism de transformare de rânduri de scaune printr-un sistem automatizat; Mecanism de ghidare de deplasare de scaune pentru modificarea amenajării sălilor; Dispozitiv de stocare de lanțuri pentru mașini-unelte; Dispozitive de stocare (părți de mașini); Lanţuri de transmisie, altele decât cele pentru vehicule terestre; Lanțuri de tracțiune rigide pentru mașini; Lanțuri rigide pentru mașini-unelte; Elevatoare (Benzi de -); Cricuri [maşini]; Balansiere de transmisie (mașini); Cricuri mecanice de ridicat vehicule; Vinciuri flexibile acţionate electric; Mecanisme de acţionare liniare; Aparate de acționare telescopice; Aparate de acționare telescopice (mecanice); Rampe sub formă de maşini; Rampe de ridicare; Mecanisme de deplasare de funduri de piscină.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Obrábacie stroje; Zdvíhacie zariadenia, elevátory, pohyblivé schodištia, výťahy, nákladné výťahy; Zdvíhacie stroje pre manipulovanie s nákladmi; Zdvíhacie zariadenia pre manipulovanie s nákladmi; Zdvíhacie stĺpy; Zdvíhacie plošiny (vrátane mobilných); Zdvíhacie stoly; Stojany na zdvíhacie stoly; Klzné podstavce (časti strojov); Zdvíhacie plošiny pre nákladné vozidlá; Zariadenia na premiestňovanie konštrukcií; Stroje na prepravu a vertikálne presúvanie nákladu; Mechanizmy na vertikálne premiestňovanie; Pohonné zariadenia pre výťahy; Mechanizmus na transformáciu radov sedadiel prostredníctvom automatizovaného systému; Mechanizmus na riadenie premiestnenia sedadiel na úpravu usporiadania miestností; Zariadenia na ukladanie reťazí do obrábacích strojov; Skladovacie zariadenia (časti strojov); Prevodové reťaze (nie na pozemné vozidlá); Pevné ťahacie reťaze do strojov; Pevné reťaze do obrábacích strojov; Remene elevátorov; Zdviháky (stroje); Prevodové zdviháky (stroje); Strojové zdvíhače vozidiel; Pružné zdviháky na elektrický pohon; Lineárne ovládače; Teleskopické pohonné prístroje; Teleskopické pohonné prístroje (mechanické); Rampy v podobe strojov; Zdvíhacie rampy; Mechanizmy na premiestnenie základov bazénov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Obdelovalni stroji; Dvižne naprave, elevatorji, tekoče stopnice, osebna dvigala, tovorna dvigala; Dvižni stroji za manipulacijo s tovorom; Dvižna oprema za delo s tovorom; Dvižni stolpci; Dvižne ploščadi (vključno z mobilnimi); Dvižne mize; Stojala za dvižne mize; Drsne opore [deli strojev]; Dvižne ploščadi na tovornjakih; Naprave za premeščanje struktur; Stroji za transport in navpično prenašanje tovorov; Mehanizmi za navpično premikanje; Pogonske naprave za dvigala; Mehanizem za preoblikovanje vrst sedežev prek samodejnega sistema; Mehanizem za upravljanje premikanja sedežev za spreminjanje ureditve dvoran; Shranjevalnik verig za orodne stroje; Shranjevalniki (strojni deli); Transmisijske verige, razen za kopenska vozila; Toge potisne verige za stroje; Toge verige za orodne stroje; Jermeni za dvigala; Dvigalke [stroji]; Prenosni vitli (stroji); Strojne dvigalke za vozila; Električne fleksibilne dvigalke; Linearni aktuatorji; Teleskopski aktuatorji; Teleskopski aktuatorji (mehanski); Rampe, ki so stroji; Dvižne rampe; Mehanizmi za premikanje dnov plavalnih bazenov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Maskinverktyg; Lyftverktyg (maskiner), hissar, rulltrappor, hissar, lyftanordningar för gods; Lyftmaskiner för lasthantering; Lyftanordningar för godshantering; Lyftkolumner; Hiss- eller lyftplattformar (även flyttbara); Lyftbord; Stativ för lyftbord; Verktygssupporter [maskindelar]; Plattformslyfttruckar; Apparater för förflyttning av konstruktioner; Maskiner för vertikal transport och förflyttning av laster; Mekanismer för vertikal förflyttning; Drivmaskiner för hissanläggningar; Mekanism för omvandling av stolsrader via ett automatiserat system; Styrmekanism för förflyttning av stolar för modifiering av inredning av salar; Kedjelagringsanordning för maskinverktyg; Lagringsanordningar (maskindelar); Transmissionskedjor, inte för landfordon; Styva stötkedjor för maskiner; Styva kedjor för maskinverktyg; Hissremmar; Domkrafter [maskiner]; Transmissionskolvar (maskiner); Maskinella domkrafter; (motordrivna) ledbara domkrafter; Linjära manöverdon; Teleskopiska manöverdon; Teleskopiska manöverdon (mekaniska); Ramper utgörande maskiner; Lyftramper; Mekanismer för förflyttning av bassängbottnar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>37</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за инсталиране, поддръжка и поправка на системи за преместване и пренос на товари; Услуги за инсталиране, поддръжка и поправка на подемно оборудване; Услуги за инсталиране, поддръжка и поправка на оборудвания за преместване и обработка на товари; Монтажни услуги, ремонт и поддръжка на машини.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Instalace, údržba a opravy systémů pro přemísťování a přenos břemen; Instalace, údržba a opravy zdvihacích zařízení; Instalace, údržba a opravy zařízení pro přemísťování a manipulaci; Instalace, opravy a údržba obráběcích strojů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Installation, vedligeholdelse og reparation af systemer til flytning og overførsel af laster; Installation, vedligeholdelse og reparation af løfteudstyr; Installation, vedligeholdelse og reparation af udstyr til flytning og vedligehold; Installation, reparation og vedligeholdelse af værktøjsmaskiner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Installation, Wartung und Reparatur von Anlagen zum Bewegen und Befördern von Lasten; Installation, Wartung und Reparatur von Hebeausrüstungen; Installation, Wartung und Reparatur von Ausrüstungen zum Bewegen und Transportieren; Installation, Reparatur und Wartung von Werkzeugmaschinen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες εγκατάστασης, συντήρησης και επισκευής συστημάτων μετατόπισης και μεταφοράς φορτίων· Υπηρεσίες εγκατάστασης, συντήρησης και επισκευής εξοπλισμού ανύψωσης· Υπηρεσίες εγκατάστασης, συντήρησης και επισκευής εξοπλισμού μετατόπισης και χειρισμού· Υπηρεσίες εγκατάστασης, επισκευής και συντήρησης εργαλειομηχανών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Installation, maintenance and repair of load movement and transfer systems; Installation, maintenance and repair of lifting equipment; Installation, maintenance and repair of moving and handling equipment; Installation, repair and maintenance of machine tools.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de instalación, mantenimiento y reparación de sistemas de desplazamiento y transferencia de cargas; Servicios de instalación, mantenimiento y reparación de equipos de elevación; Servicios de instalación, mantenimiento y reparación de equipos de desplazamiento y de manutención; Servicios de instalación, reparación y mantenimiento de máquinasherramienta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Raskuste liigutamise ja edasi viimise süsteemide paigaldamine, hooldamine ja remontimine; Tõsteseadmete paigaldamine, hooldamine ja remontimine; Kaupade liigutamiseks ja käsitsemiseks ette nähtud seadmete paigaldamine, hooldamine ja remontimine; Tööpinkide paigaldamine, remontimine ja hooldamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kuormien liikuttamis- ja siirtojärjestelmien asennus-, kunnossapito. ja korjauspalvelut; Nostolaitteiden asennus-, kunnossapito. ja korjauspalvelut; Siirto- ja käsittelylaitteiden asennus-, kunnossapito. ja korjauspalvelut; Työstökoneiden asennus-, korjaus- ja huoltopalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d'installation, maintenance et réparation de systèmes de déplacement et de transfert de charges; Services d'installation, maintenance et réparation d'équipements de levage; Services d'installation, maintenance et réparation d'équipements de déplacement et de manutention; Services d'installation, maintenance et réparation de machines-outils.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge postavljanja, održavanja i popravljanja sustava za kretanje i prijenos tereta; Usluge postavljanja, održavanja i popravljanja opreme za podizanje; Usluge postavljanja, održavanja i popravljanja opreme za kretanje i rukovanje; Usluge postavljanja, popravaka i održavanja alatnih strojeva.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Terhek elmozdítására és továbbítására szolgáló rendszerek üzembe helyezése, karbantartása és javítása; Emelőberendezések üzembe helyezése, karbantartása és javítása; Mozgató és kezelő berendezések üzembe helyezése, karbantartása és javítása; Szerszámgépek felszerelési, javítási és karbantartási szolgáltatásai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi d'installazione, manutenzione e riparazione di sistemi di spostamento e trasferimento di carichi; Servizi d'installazione, manutenzione e riparazione di apparecchiature di sollevamento; Servizi d'installazione, manutenzione e riparazione di apparecchiature di spostamento e manutenzione; Servizi di installazione, riparazione e manutenzione di macchine utensili.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Poslinkio ir krovinio perkėlimo sistemų įrengimo, priežiūros ir remonto paslaugos; Kėlimo įrangos montavimas, techninė priežiūra ir remontas; Kilnojamosios ir krovimo įrangos montavimo, priežiūros ir taisymo paslaugos; Staklių įrengimo, taisymo ir priežiūros paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pārvietošanas un kravas pārvietošanas sistēmu uzstādīšanas, apkopes un remonta pakalpojumi; Celšanas aprīkojuma uzstādīšana, apkope un remonts; Iekārtu pārnešanas un pārvietošanas ierīču uzstādīšanas, apkopes un remonta pakalpojumi; Darbmašīnu uzstādīšanas, remonta un apkopes pakalpojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' installazzjoni, manutenzjoni u tiswija ta' sistemi ta' ġarr u ta' trasferiment tat-tagħbija; Servizzi ta' installazzjoni, manutenzjoni u tiswija ta' tagħmir tal-irfigħ; Servizzi ta' installazzjoni, manutenzjoni u tiswija ta' tagħmir ta' ġarr u tal-manutenzjoni; Servizzi ta' installazzjoni, tiswija u manutenzjoni ta' għodod tal-magni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Installatie, onderhoud en reparatie van systemen voor verplaatsing en overbrengen van ladingen; Installatie, onderhoud en reparatie van hefapparatuur; Installatie, onderhoud en reparatie van verplaatsings- en verladingsapparatuur; Installatie, reparatie en onderhoud van werktuigmachines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi w zakresie instalacji, konserwacji i naprawy systemów przemieszczania i przenoszenia ładunków; Usługi w zakresie instalacji, konserwacji i naprawy sprzętu podnośnikowego; Usługi w zakresie instalacji, konserwacji i naprawy sprzętu do przenoszenia i do transportu bliskiego; Usługi instalacyjne, naprawcze i konserwacyjne w zakresie obrabiarek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de instalação, manutenção e reparação de sistemas de deslocação e de transferência de cargas; Serviços de instalação, manutenção e reparação de equipamentos de elevação; Serviços de instalação, manutenção e reparação de equipamentos de deslocação e de manutenção; Serviços de instalação, reparação e manutenção de máquinas-ferramentas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de instalare, întreținere și reparație de sisteme de deplasare și de transfer de încărcături; Servicii de instalare, întreținere și reparație de echipamente de ridicare; Servicii de instalare, întreținere și reparare de echipamente de deplasare și de manipulare; Servicii de instalare, reparare şi întreţinere de maşini-unelte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Inštalácia, údržba a opravy systémov na premiestnenie a presun nákladu; Inštalácia, údržba a opravy zdvíhacích zariadení; Inštalácia, údržba a opravy zariadení na premiestňovanie a manipulačných zariadení; Inštalačné služby, oprava a údržba obrábacích strojov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve v zvezi z montažo, vzdrževanje in popravila sistemov za premikanje in prenašanje tovorov; Storitve v zvezi z montažo, vzdrževanje in popravila dvižne opreme; Storitve v zvezi z montažo, vzdrževanje in popravila premikalne in manipulacijske opreme; Storitve na področju montaže, popravila in vzdrževanja orodnih strojev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Installation, underhåll och reparation av system för förflyttning och överföring av laster; Installation, underhåll och reparation av tvättutrustning; Installation, underhåll och reparation av utrustning för förflyttning och lagerhantering; Installation, reparation och underhåll av maskinverktyg.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PriorityDetails>
<Priority>
<PriorityCountryCode>FR</PriorityCountryCode>
<PriorityNumber>4590228</PriorityNumber>
<PriorityDate>2019-10-14</PriorityDate>
<PriorityPartialIndicator>false</PriorityPartialIndicator>
<PriorityStatusCode>Claimed</PriorityStatusCode>
</Priority>
</PriorityDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/083</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/155</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-17</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1078805</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>22397</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
