<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-30T08:57:51</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018222476</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018222476</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-08</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="3">Application withdrawn</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-30</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>THE LONDONER</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Предоставяне на казино и хазартни услуги; Предоставяне на казино и игрални съоръжения; Развлечение, а именно, музикални представления на живо, театрални продукции и комедийни продукции; Фитнес центрове, А именно, Предоставяне съоръжения за фитнес и упражнения; Развлекателни центрове и зали; Предоставяне на казино и хазартни услуги чрез уебсайт и глобална компютърна мрежа.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Poskytování služeb kasin a hraní o peníze; Poskytování kasinových a herních zařízení; Zábava, jmenovitě, živá hudební vystoupení, divadelní představení a komedie; Zdravotní kluby, Jmenovitě, Poskytování prostor na cvičení a fitness; Zábavní centra a zábavní arkády; Poskytování kasinových a herních služeb prostřednictvím webových stránek a globální počítačové sítě.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Udbydelse af kasino- og spillevirksomhed; Udbydelse af kasino- og spillefaciliteter; Underholdningsvirksomhed, nemlig levende musikalsk optræden, teaterproduktion og komedieproduktion; Helseklubber, Nemlig, Tilvejebringelse af fitness- og motionsudstyr; Forlystelsescentre og -arkader; Kasino- og spillevirksomhed udbudt via websteder og et globalt computernetværk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Casino- und Spielbetrieb; Casino- und Spieleinrichtungen; Unterhaltung, nämlich Live-Musikveranstaltungen, Theaterproduktionen und Comedyproduktionen; Gesundheitsklubs, Nämlich, Vermietung von Fitness- und Trainingseinrichtungen; Betrieb von Vergnügungszentren und Automatenhallen; Bereitstellung von Casino- und Glücksspieleinrichtungen über Websites und ein weltweites Computernetz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παροχή υπηρεσιών καζίνο και τυχερών παιχνιδιών· Παροχή εγκαταστάσεων καζίνο και τυχερών παιχνιδιών· Ψυχαγωγία, συγκεκριμένα, ζωντανές μουσικές παραστάσεις, θεατρικές παραγωγές και κωμικές παραγωγές· Λέσχες υγείας, Συγκεκριμένα, Παροχή εγκαταστάσεων γυμναστικής και προπόνησης· Κέντρα και αίθουσες ψυχαγωγίας· Παροχή υπηρεσιών χαρτοπαικτικών λεσχών (καζίνο) και τυχερών παιχνιδιών μέσω ιστοθέσης και παγκόσμιου δικτύου ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Casino and casino gaming services; providing casino and casino gaming facilities; entertainment, namely, live musical performances, theatrical productions and comedy productions; health clubs, namely, providing fitness and exercise facilities; amusement centers and arcades; providing casino and casino gaming services by means of web sites and a global computer network.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de juegos de azar y de casino; Facilitación de instalaciones de casinos y juegos de azar; Esparcimiento, en concreto, actuaciones musicales en directo, producciones teatrales y producciones de comedia; Clubes deportivos, En concreto, Facilitación de instalaciones de fitness y ejercicio; Centros recreativos y salas recreativas; Prestación de servicios de casino y juego a través de sitios web y de una red informática mundial.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kasiino- ja hasartmänguteenuste pakkumine; Kasiino- ja hasartmängurajatiste pakkumine; Meelelahutus, nimelt muusikalised elavettekanded, teatrietendused ja komöödia etteasted; Terviseklubid, Teisisõnu, Ruumide ja vahendite pakkumine kehaliseks vormisolekuks ja treenimiseks; Ajaviitekeskused ja lõbustushallid; Kasiino- ja mänguteenuste pakkumine veebisaitide ja ülemaailmsete arvutivõrkude kaudu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kasino- ja rahapelipalveluiden tarjoaminen; Kasino- ja uhkapelipalvelujen tarjoaminen; Ajanviete, nimittäin live-musiikkiesitykset, teatterituotannot ja komediatuotannot; Kuntosalit (kuntoilu), Nimittäin, Kuntoilu- ja voimistelutilojen tarjoaminen; Viihdekeskukset ja -hallit; Kasino- ja uhkapelipalvelujen tarjoaminen WWW-sivustojen ja maailmanlaajuisen tietokoneverkon välityksellä.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Fourniture de services de casinos et de jeux; Mise à disposition de salles de casino et de jeux; Divertissement, à savoir représentations musicales en direct, productions théâtrales et productions de comédies; Club de santé (mise en forme physique), À savoir, Mise à disposition de salles de sport; Salles de jeux électroniques et d'arcade; Fourniture de services de casinos et de jeux d'argent via des sites web et un réseau informatique mondial.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pružanje usluga kasina i igara na sreću; Pružanje prostora za kasina i igre na sreću; Zabava, i to glazbene izvedbe uživo, kazališne predstave i nastupi komičara; Zdravstveni klubovi, Naime, to jest, Pružanje objekata i opreme za fitnes i tjelovježbu; Zabavni centri i arkade; Pružanje usluga kasina i igara na sreću putem mrežnih stranica i globalne računalne mreže.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kaszinó- és játékszolgáltatások; Kaszinói és játéktermi létesítmények rendelkezésre bocsátása; Szórakoztatás, nevezetesen élő zenei előadások, színházi előadás és vígjátéki előadások; Egészségmegőrző klubok, Nevezetesen, Fitnesz- és edzőlétesítmények biztosítása; Szórakoztató központok és játéktermek; Kaszinói és játéktermi szolgáltatások nyújtása webhelyek és a globális számítógépes hálózat révén.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di casinò e giochi di denaro; Servizi di casinò e giochi d'azzardo; Divertimento, ovvero spettacoli musicali dal vivo, produzioni teatrali e produzioni comiche; Palestre (fitness club), Ovvero, Fornitura d'installazioni per la ginnastica e l'esercizio fisico; Centri di divertimento e sale giochi; Fornitura di servizi di casinò e di giochi di denaro mediante un sito Web e una rete informatica globale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kazino ir lošimų paslaugų teikimas; Lošimo namų ir azartinių žaidimų patalpų su įranga teikimas; Pramogos, būtent tiesioginiai muzikiniai pasirodymai, teatro spektakliai ir komedija; Sveikatingumo klubai, Būtent, Kūno rengybos ir mankštos patalpų su įranga teikimas; Atrakcionų parkai ir pramogų paviljono paslaugos; Kazino ir lošimo paslaugų teikimas per tinklavietę ir visuotinį kompiuterių tinklą.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kazino un azartspēļu nodrošināšana; Kazino un spēļu aprīkojuma un telpu nodrošināšana; Izklaide, proti, dzīvās mūzikas priekšnesumi, teātra uzvedumi un komēdiju uzvedumi; Veselības klubu pakalpojumi, Proti, Fitnesa un vingrošanas aprīkojuma nodrošināšana; Atrakciju centri un arkādes; Kazino un spēļu pakalpojumu sniegšana, izmantojot tīmekļa vietnes un pasaules datoru tīklu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Provvista ta' servizzi ta' każinò u ta' logħob; Il-provvista ta' faċilitajiet ta' każinos u ta' logħob ta' flus; Divertiment, jiġifieri, wirjiet mużikali diretti, produzzjonijiet teatrali u produzzjonijiet ta' kummiedji; Klabbs tas-saħħa, Jiġifieri, Provvista ta' faċilitajiet għas-saħħa tal-ġisem u għall-eżerċizzju; Ċentri u swali tad-divertiment; Provvista ta' servizzi ta' kasinos u ta' logħob ta' flus permezz ta' websajts u ta' netwerks tal-kompjuter globali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Casinodiensten en gokspelen; Het verschaffen van casino- en kansspelfaciliteiten; Ontspanning, te weten livemuziekoptredens, theaterproducties en komedieproducties; Gezondheidsclubs (conditietraining), Te weten, Beschikbaar stellen van faciliteiten voor fitness en lichaamsoefening; Amusementscentra en -hallen; Casino's en gokspelen door middel van een website en een wereldwijd computernetwerk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Świadczenie usług kasynowych i usług w zakresie gier; Udostępnianie obiektów kasynowych i urządzeń do gier; Rozrywka, mianowicie występy muzyczne na żywo, produkcje teatralne i podukcje komediowe; Fitness kluby, Mianowicie, Udostępnianie obiektów i sprzętu do ćwiczeń i fitnessu; Centra rozrywki i wesołe miasteczka; Świadczenie usług kasyn i gier hazardowych za pomocą witryn internetowych i globalnych sieci komputerowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Prestação de serviços de casino e de jogos a dinheiro; Fornecimento de instalações para casinos e jogos; Entretenimento, nomeadamente actuações musicais ao vivo, produções teatrais e produções de comédia; Clubes de saúde (manutenção da forma física), Nomeadamente, Fornecimento de instalações para exercício físico e de fitness; Centros de diversão e salões de jogos; Prestação de serviços de casino e de jogos a dinheiro através de sítios Web e de uma rede informática mundial.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Furnizare de servicii de cazino si jocuri; Furnizarea de spaţii pentru cazinouri şi jocuri; Divertisment, si anume, reprezentatii muzicale in direct, productii teatrale si de comedie; Cluburi de sănătate, Şi anume, Furnizarea de instalaţii pentru fitness şi exerciţii fizice; Centre şi săli de distracţii; Furnizare de servicii de cazinou si jocuri prin intermediul paginilor de internet si printr-o retea globala de calculatoare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Poskytovanie kasínových a hazardných herných služieb; Poskytovanie zariadení kasína a herných zariadení a priestorov; Zábava, menovite živé hudobné podujatia, divadelná výroba a komediálna výroba; Kluby zdravia, Menovite, Poskytovanie priestorov na fitnes a cvičenie; Zábavné strediská a arkády; Poskytovanie kasínových a herných služieb prostredníctvom internetových stránok a globálnej počítačovej siete.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Nudenje storitvev igralnic in iger na srečo; Zagotavljanje prostorov in opreme za kazinoje in igralništvo; Razvedrilo, in sicer glasbeni nastopi v živo, gledališke predstave in komedije; Zdravilišča, In sicer, Nudenje prostorov in opreme za telesno vadbo; Zabaviščni centri in igralni saloni; Nudenje storitev igralnic in igralništva po spletni strani in globalnem računalniškem omrežju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tillhandahållande av kasino- och speltjänster; Tillhandahållande av kasino- och hasardspelslokaler; Underhållning, nämligen, levande musikuppträdanden, teaterproduktioner och komediproduktioner; Hälsoklubbar, Nämligen, Tränings- och motionsanläggningar; Nöjescentrer och spelhallar; Tillhandahållande av kasino- och speltjänster medelst webbplatser och ett globalt datornät.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>43</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги на хотели и мотели; Ресторантьорски услуги; Услуги на хотели и мотели; Осигуряване на хотелска информация; Обслужване на бар; Кетъринг (приготвяне и доставка на храни и напитки); Предоставяне на помещения за конгреси, банкети, социални събития, събития за набиране на средства и специални мероприятия; Хотелски резервации за трети лица.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Hotelové služby; Restaurace; Hotelové služby; Poskytování informací o hotelích; Bary (Služby -); Zajištění stravování; Poskytování zařízení pro sjezdy, bankety, společenská setkání, získávání finančních prostředků a zvláštní akce; Rezervování hotelů pro třetí osoby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tjenester ydet af hoteller; Tjenester ydet af restauranter; Tjenester ydet af hoteller; Formidling af hotelinformation; Tjenester ydet af barer; Catering; Udbydelse af faciliteter til kongresser, banketter, sociale arrangementer, fundraising og særlige arrangementer; Gennemførelse af hotelreservationer for andre.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Dienstleistungen von Hotels; Verpflegung von Gästen in Restaurants; Dienstleistungen von Hotels; Bereitstellung von Hotelinformationen; Betrieb einer Bar; Catering; Bereitstellung von Einrichtungen für Kongresse, Bankette, gesellschaftliche Anlässe, Wohltätigkeits- und Sonderveranstaltungen; Hotelreservierungen für Dritte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ξενοδοχειακές υπηρεσίες· Υπηρεσίες εστιατορίου· Ξενοδοχειακές υπηρεσίες· Παροχή πληροφοριών για ξενοδοχεία· Μπαρ (Υπηρεσίες -)· Τροφοδοσία· Παροχή εγκαταστάσεων για συνέδρια, συνεστιάσεις, κοινωνικές εκδηλώσεις, εράνους και ειδικές εκδηλώσεις· Υπηρεσίες κρατήσεων σε ξενοδοχεία για λογαριασμό τρίτων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hotels; restaurants; hotel services; providing hotel information; bar services; catering services; providing general purpose facilities for conventions, banquets, social functions, fund raisers, and special events; making hotel reservations for others.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de hotelería; Servicios de restaurantes; Servicios de hotelería; Suministro de información de hoteles; Servicios de bar; Servicios de catering; Instalaciones para convenciones, banquetes, funciones sociales, colecta de fondos y acontecimientos especiales; Realización de reservas hoteleras para terceros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hotelliteenused; Restoraniteenused; Hotelliteenused; Hotelliteave; Baariteenused; Toitlustusteenindus; Vahendite pakkumine kokkusaamiste, bankettide, seltskondlike ürituste, korjandusürituste ja eriliste puhkude tarbeks; Hotellikohtade reserveerimine kolmandatele isikutele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hotellit; Ravintolapalvelut; Hotellit; Hotellitietojen tarjoaminen; Baaripalvelut; Pitopalvelu; Tilojen tarjoaminen kokouksia, juhla-aterioita, sosiaalisia tapahtumia, varainhankintaa ja erikoistapahtumia varten; Hotellivarausten teko muiden lukuun.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services hôteliers; Services de restauration (alimentation); Services hôteliers; Fourniture d'informations hôtelières; Services de bars; Services de traiteurs; Mise à disposition d'infrastructures pour conventions, banquets, événements sociaux, collectes de fonds et événements spéciaux; Réservations de chambres d'hôtel pour le compte de tiers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Hotelske usluge; Usluge restorana; Hotelske usluge; Pružanje informacija o hotelima; Usluge barova; Catering; Pružanje objekata za konvencije, bankete, društvena okupljanja, prikupljanje sredstava i posebna događanja; Rezerviranje hotelskog smještaja za druge.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szállodai szolgáltatások; Éttermi szolgáltatások; Szállodai szolgáltatások; Szállodákkal kapcsolatos információk biztosítása; Bár szolgáltatások; Vendéglátás; Létesítmények rendelkezésre bocsátása gyűlésekhez, bankettekhez, társasági összejövetelekhez, adománygyűjtésekhez és különleges rendezvényekhez; Szállodai foglalási szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi alberghieri; Servizi di ristoranti; Servizi alberghieri; Informazioni in materia di alberghi; Servizi di bar; Catering; Fornitura di strutture per convegni, banchetti, funzioni sociali, raccolta di fondi e manifestazioni speciali; Prenotazioni alberghiere per conto terzi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Viešbučių paslaugos; Restoranų paslaugos; Viešbučių paslaugos; Viešbučio informacijos teikimas; Barų paslaugos; Aprūpinimas maistu ir gėrimais; Sąlygų rengti suvažiavimus, kviestinius pietus, socialinius renginius, labdaros renginius ir specialius renginius sudarymas; Viešbučių rezervavimas kitiems.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Viesnīcu pakalpojumi; Restorānu pakalpojumi; Viesnīcu pakalpojumi; Ar viesnīcām saistītas informācijas sniegšana; Bāru pakalpojumi; Ēdienu sagatavošana un piegāde pēc pasūtījuma; Telpu nodrošināšana sanāksmēm, banketiem, sabiedriskām funkcijām, līdzekļu vākšanai un īpašiem pasākumiem; Viesnīcas rezervēšana trešajām personām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' lukanda; Servizzi ta' restorant; Servizzi ta' lukanda; Provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar lukandi; Servizzi ta' barijiet; Catering; Provvista ta' faċilitajiet għall-konvenzjonijiet, banketti, funzjonijiet soċjali, avvenimenti ta' ġbir ta' fondi u avvenimenti speċjali; Riservar f'lukandi għan nom ta' oħrajn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Hoteldiensten; Restauratie [het verstrekken van maaltijden]; Hoteldiensten; Verstrekking van informatie over hotels; Bardiensten; Catering; Verstrekking van faciliteiten voor congressen, banketten, sociale plechtigheden, fondsenwerving en speciale evenementen; Het reserveren van hotelkamers voor derden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi hotelowe; Usługi restauracyjne; Usługi hotelowe; Udzielanie informacji dotyczących hoteli; Usługi barowe; Obsługa gastronomiczna z własnym zapleczem, produktami i transportem; Udostępnianie obiektów na konferencje, na bankiety, na uroczystości prywatne, na kwesty i na szczególne wydarzenia; Rezerwacja hotelowa na rzecz osób trzecich.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de hotéis; Serviços de restaurantes; Serviços de hotéis; Fornecimento de informações sobre hotéis; Serviços de bar; Catering; Fornecimento de instalações para convenções, banquetes, festas sociais, angariação de fundos e eventos especiais; Realização de reservas de hotéis para terceiros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii hoteliere; Restaurante [servirea mesei]; Servicii hoteliere; Furnizare de informaţii în domeniul hotelier; Servicii ale barurilor; Catering; Asigurare de spatii pentru reuniuni, petreceri, intruniri sociale, colectare de fonduri si evenimente speciale; Rezervări de hotel pentru terţi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Hotelierske služby; Reštauračné (stravovacie) služby; Hotelierske služby; Poskytovanie hotelových informácií; Bary (služby); Catering; Poskytovanie zariadení pre zhromaždenia, bankety, spoločenské podujatia, dobročinné a špeciálne podujatia; Rezervovanie hotelov pre druhé osoby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Hotelirske storitve; Storitve restavracij; Hotelirske storitve; Nudenje informacij v zvezi s hoteli; Storitve barov; Catering; Nudenje prostorov za konvencije, bankete, družbene funkcije, zbiranje sredstev in posebne dogodke; Opravljanje hotelskih rezervacij za druge.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hotell; Restauranger; Hotell; Hotellinformation; Cocktailbartjänster; Catering; Upplåtande av lokaler för sammankomster, banketter, sociala evenemang, anskaffande av kapital, och specialtillställningar; Hotellreservationer för andras räkning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/102</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-02</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>267566</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>44725</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003128752</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-08-18</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Identity of marks and G&amp;S
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>016199481</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2016-12-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>016199481</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2017-04-24</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>THE LONDONER</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>016199481</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2016-12-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>016199481</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2017-04-24</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>THE LONDONER</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>602667</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>10018</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003129139</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-08-21</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Identity of marks and G&amp;S
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>003891091</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2004-06-07</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>003891091</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2005-10-13</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>THE LONDONER</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>003891091</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2004-06-07</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>003891091</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2005-10-13</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>THE LONDONER</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>007224165</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2008-09-10</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>007224165</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2009-05-12</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>THE LONDONER</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>007224165</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2008-09-10</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>007224165</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2009-05-12</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>THE LONDONER</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>196558</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>67447</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
