<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:38</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018222469</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018222469</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-08</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-08</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>PALL MALL SHIFT RED</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>34</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Цигари; Тютюн; Тютюн за собственоръчно свиване; Тютюн за лула; Тютюнови изделия; Заместители на тютюн (не за медицински цели); Пури; Пурети; Запалки за цигари; Запалки за пури; Кибрит; Принадлежности за използване с тютюн; Хартия за цигари; Кутии за пълнене на цигари; Филтри за цигари; Цигари (Джобни машинки за свиване на -); Ръчни машини за поставяне на тютюн в хартиени гилзи; Електронни цигари; Течни разтвори за използване в електронни цигари; Тютюневи продукти, предназначени да бъдат загрети; Пурети.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Cigarety; Tabák; Tabák k ručnímu balení; Dýmkový tabák; Tabákové výrobky; Náhražky tabáku (nikoli pro léčebné účely); Doutníky; Doutníčky (cigarillos); Zapalovače cigaret; Zapalovače na doutníky; Zápalky; Kuřácké potřeby; Cigaretový papír; Cigaretové dutinky; Cigaretové filtry; Kapesní baličky cigaret; Ruční plničky dutinek; Elektronické cigarety; Kapalné roztoky do elektronických cigaret; Tabákové výrobky pro účely zahřívání; Doutníčky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Cigaretter; Tobak; Rulletobak; Pibetobak; Tobaksprodukter; Tobakserstatninger [ikke til medicinske formål]; Cigarer; Cigarillos; Cigaretlightere; Cigartændere; Tændstikker; Artikler til brug med tobak; Cigaretpapir; Cigaretrør; Filtre til cigaretter; Lommeredskaber til rulning af cigaretter; Håndholdte maskiner til påfyldning af tobak i cigaretrør af papir; Elektroniske cigaretter; Flydende opløsninger til brug i e-cigaretter; Tobaksprodukter, som skal opvarmes; Små cigarer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Zigaretten; Tabak; Shag; Pfeifentabak; Tabakerzeugnisse; Tabakersatzstoffe, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Zigarren; Zigarillos; Zigarettenanzünder; Zigarrenanzünder; Streichhölzer; Raucherartikel; Zigarettenpapier; Zigarettenhülsen; Zigarettenfilter; Taschenapparate zum Drehen von Zigaretten; Handgeräte zum Einführen von Tabak in Zigarettenhülsen; Elektronische Zigaretten; Liquide für elektronische Zigaretten; Tabakerzeugnisse zum Erhitzen; Zigarillos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Τσιγάρα· Καπνός· Καπνός για στρίψιμο τσιγάρων· Καπνός για πίπα· Προϊόντα καπνού· Υποκατάστατα καπνού για μη ιατρικές χρήσεις· Καπνός, πούρα και τσιγάρα· Πουράκια· Αναπτήρες για τσιγάρα· Αναπτήρες πούρων· Σπίρτα· Είδη για χρήση με καπνό· Τσιγαρόχαρτο· Τσιγαρόχαρτο σε μορφή σωλήνα· Φίλτρα για τσιγάρα· Τσιγάρων (Συσκευές τσέπης για περιτύλιξη -)· Χειροκίνητες διατάξεις για την εισαγωγή καπνού σε κυλίνδρους χαρτιού· Ηλεκτρονικά τσιγάρα· Υγρά διαλύματα για χρήση σε ηλεκτρονικά τσιγάρα· Θερμαινόμενα προϊόντα καπνού· Πουράκια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Cigarettes; tobacco, raw or manufactured; roll your own tobacco; pipe tobacco; tobacco products; tobacco substitutes (not for medical purposes); cigars; cigarillos; cigarette lighters; cigar lighters; matches; smokers' articles; cigarette paper; cigarette tubes; cigarette filters; pocket apparatus for rolling cigarettes; hand held machines for injecting tobacco into paper tubes; electronic cigarettes; liquids for electronic cigarettes; tobacco products for the purpose of being heated; Small cigars.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cigarrillos; Tabaco; Tabaco de liar; Tabaco de pipa; Productos de tabaco; Sucedáneos del tabaco [que no sean para uso médico]; Puros; Puritos; Encendedores de cigarrillos; Encendedores de cigarros; Cerillas; Artículos de uso conjunto con el tabaco; Papel de fumar; Tubos para cigarrillos; Filtros para cigarrillos; Aparatos de bolsillo para liar cigarrillos; Máquinas manuales para la inyección de tabaco en tubos de papel para fumar; Cigarrillos electrónicos; Soluciones líquidas para cigarrillos electrónicos; Productos de tabaco para su calentamiento; Cigarros pequeños.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sigaretid; Tubakas; Lahtine tubakas; Piibutubakas; Tubakatooted; Tubaka aseained [v.a meditsiinilised]; Sigarid; Sigarillod, väikesigarid; Sigaretisüütlid; Sigarisüütajad; Tikud; Tooted tubakaga tarbimiseks; Sigaretipaber, suitsupaber; Sigaretihülsid; Sigaretifiltrid; Taskus kantavad sigaretikeerajad; Käeshoitavad seadmed tubaka sisestamiseks paberkestadesse; E-sigaretid; E-sigarettide vedelikud; Kuumutatavad tubakatooted; Väikesed sigarid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Savukkeet; Tupakka; Irtotupakka; Piipputupakka; Tupakkatuotteet; Tupakankorvikkeet ei-lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Sikarit; Pikkusikarit; Tupakansytyttimet; Sikarin sytyttimet; Tulitikut; Tupakointivälineet; Savukepaperi; Savukeholkit; Savukefiltterit; Savukkeenkäärimet [taskussa pidettävät]; Kädessä pidettävät koneet, joilla tupakkaa laitetaan paperiputkiin; Sähkösavukkeet; Sähkösavukkeissa käytettävät nestemäiset liuokset; Tupakkatuotteet lämmitettäviksi; Pikkusikarit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Cigarettes; Tabac; Tabac à rouler; Tabac à pipe; Produits du tabac; Succédanés du tabac à usage non médical; Cigares; Cigarillos; Briquets; Allume-cigares; Allumettes; Articles à utiliser avec le tabac; Papier à cigarettes; Tubes à cigarettes; Filtres pour cigarettes; Appareils de poche à rouler les cigarettes; Machines portables pour injecter le tabac dans des tubes en papier en vue de les fumer; Cigarettes électroniques; Solutions liquides pour cigarettes électroniques; Produits du tabac destinés à être chauffés; Cigarillos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Cigarete; Duhan; Duhan za motanje; Duhan za lule; Duhanski proizvodi; Zamjene za duhan [za nemedicinsku upotrebu]; Cigare; Cigariljosi [male cigare]; Upaljači za cigarete; Upaljači za cigare; Šibice; Artikli za uporabu s duhanom; Papirići za cigarete; Tube za cigarete; Usnici za cigarete; Cigarete (džepne naprave za savijanje cigareta); Ručni uređaji za punjenje filtar omotnica duhanom; Elektronske cigarete; Tekuće otopine za uporabu u elektronskim cigaretama; Duhanski proizvodi koji se griju; Male cigare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Cigaretták; Dohány; Sodorható dohány; Pipadohány; Dohányáru; Dohánypótlók [nem gyógyászati célra]; Szivarok; Szivarkák [cigarillo]; Öngyújtók, cigarettagyújtók; Szivargyújtók; Gyufák; Dohányzási cikkek; Cigarettapapír; Cigarettacsövek, cigarettatöltő csövek; Cigarettaszopókák; Zsebben hordható cigaretta sodró; Kézi készülékek a dohány papírcsövekbe töltéséhez; Elektromos cigaretták; Elektromos cigarettában használható folyékony oldatok; Hevítésre szánt dohánytermékek; Kis szivarok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Sigarette; Tabacco; Tabacco da sigarette fatte a mano; Tabacco da pipa; Prodotti a base di tabacco; Succedanei del tabacco (non per uso medico); Sigari; Cigarillos; Accendini; Accendisigari; Fiammiferi; Articoli per uso del tabacco; Carta da sigarette; Tubi per sigarette; Filtri per sigarette; Apparecchi tascabili per arrotolare le sigarette; Macchine portatili per l'iniezione di tabacco in involucri di carta; Sigarette elettroniche; Soluzioni liquide per sigarette elettroniche; Prodotti a base di tabacco da riscaldare; Sigaretti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Cigaretės; Tabakas; Sukamų cigarečių tabakas; Pypkių tabakas; Tabako gaminiai; Tabako pakaitalai ne medicinos reikmėms; Cigarai; Cigariukai [cigarilės]; Cigarečių žiebtuvėliai; Cigarų žiebtuvėliai; Degtukai; Rūkymo reikmenys; Cigaretinis popierius; Popieriniai cigarečių vamzdeliai; Cigarečių filtrai; Cigarečių sukimo kišeniniai įtaisai; Rankinės mašinėlės tabakui įstumti į popierines tūteles; Elektroninės cigaretės; Skysti tirpalai (elektroninėms cigaretėms); Kaitinamieji tabako gaminiai; Maži cigarai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Cigaretes; Tabaka; Tinamā tabaka; Pīpju tabaka; Tabakas izstrādājumi; Tabakas aizstājēji (nemedicīniskiem nolūkiem); Cigāri; Cigarillas; Cigarešu šķiltavas; Cigāru šķiltavas; Sērkociņi; Smēķēšanas piederumi; Cigarešu papīrs; Cigarešu ietvari; Cigarešu filtru čaulītes; Kabatas ierīces cigarešu uztīšanai; Rokas mašīnas tabakas ievadīšanai papīra caurulītēs; Elektroniskās cigaretes; Šķīdumi elektroniskajām cigaretēm; Tabakas izstrādājumi karsēšanas nolūkiem; Maza izmēra cigāri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Sigaretti; Tabakk; Tabakk tat-trembil bl-idejn; Tabakk tal-pipi; Prodotti tat-tabakk; Sostituti tat-tabakk mhux għal skopijiet mediċi; Sigarri; Sigarri żgħar; Lajters tas-sigaretti; Lajters tas-sigarri; Sulfarini; Oġġetti għall-użu mat-tabakk; Karta tas-sigaretti; Tubi tas-sigaretti (mingħajr tabakk fihom); Filtri tas-sigaretti; Sigaretti (Magni tal-but għall-brim tas- -); Magni li jinżammu fl-idejn għall-injettar ta' tabakk f'tubi tal-karti; Sigaretti elettroniċi; Soluzzjonijiet likwidi għall-użu fis-sigaretti elettroniċi; Prodotti tat-tabakk għall-użu biex jissaħħnu; Sigarri żgħar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Sigaretten; Tabak; Shag; Pijptabak; Tabaksproducten; Tabakssurrogaten (niet voor medisch gebruik); Sigaren; Cigarillo's; Aanstekers voor sigaretten; Aanstekers voor sigaren; Lucifers; Artikels voor gebruik met tabak; Sigarettenpapier; Sigarettenhulzen; Filters voor sigaretten; Sigarettenrollers [zakformaat]; Handbediende apparaten voor het vullen van papierhulzen met tabak; Elektronische sigaretten; Vloeibare oplossingen voor gebruik in elektronische sigaretten; Tabaksproducten om te verhitten; Sigaren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Papierosy; Tytoń; Tytoń do robienia papierosów; Tytoń do fajek; Wyroby tytoniowe; Substytuty tytoniu (nie do celów medycznych); Cygara; Cygaretki; Zapalniczki do papierosów; Zapalniczki do cygar; Zapałki; Artykuły do użytku z tytoniem; Bibułki papierosowe; Gilzy papierosowe; Filtry do papierosów; Papierosy (Kieszonkowe przyrządy do skręcania -); Ręczne urządzenia do wstrzykiwania tytoniu w papierowe rolki; Papierosy elektroniczne; Ciekłe roztwory do użytku w e-papierosach; Produkty tytoniowe przeznaczone do ogrzewania; Małe cygara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cigarros; Tabaco; Tabaco de enrolar; Tabaco de cachimbo; Produtos de tabaco; Sucedâneos de tabaco sem ser para uso medicinal; Charutos; Cigarrilhas; Isqueiros para cigarros; Isqueiros para charutos; Fósforos; Artigos para uso com tabaco; Papel para cigarros; Tubos de cigarros; Filtros para cigarros; Máquinas de bolso para enrolar cigarros; Máquinas manuais para injecção de tabaco em mortalhas em forma de tubo; Cigarros eletrónicos; Soluções líquidas para uso em cigarros eletrónicos; Produtos de tabaco destinados a serem aquecidos; Cigarrilhas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Țigarete; Tutun; Tutun de rulat; Tutun de pipă; Produse din tutun; Înlocuitori de tutun nu pentru uz medical; Țigări de foi; Cigarillos [tip de trabuc de dimensiuni reduse]; Brichete pentru țigarete; Brichete pentru trabucuri; Chibrituri; Articole pentru uz cu tutun; Foițe pentru țigarete; Tuburi de țigară; Capete de țigarete; Rularea țigaretelor (Dispozitive de buzunar pentru -); Masini manuale pentru injectarea tutunului in tuburile de hartie; Țigarete electronice; Soluții lichide pentru utilizare în țigări electronice; Produse din tutun pentru a fi încălzite; Țigări de foi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Cigarety; Tabak; Tabak na šúľanie cigariet; Fajkový tabak; Tabakové produkty; Tabakové náhradky s výnimkou náhradiek na lekárske účely; Cigary; Krátke cigary; Cigaretové zapaľovače; Zapaľovače cigár; Zápalky; Potreby pre fajčiarov; Cigaretový papier; Cigaretové tuby; Cigaretové filtre; Vreckové strojčeky na šúľanie cigariet; Ručné prístroje na vkladanie tabaku do papierových rúrok; Elektronické cigarety; Kvapalné nikotínové náplne do elektronických cigariet; Tabakové výrobky určené na ohrievanie; Cigary.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Cigarete; Tobak; Tobak za zvijanje cigaret; Tobak za pipo; Tobačni izdelki; Nadomestki tobaka (ne za zdravstvene namene); Cigare; Cigarilosi; Vžigalniki za cigarete; Vžigalniki za cigare; Vžigalice; Potrebščine za uporabo s tobakom; Cigaretni papir; Tulci za cigarete; Filtri za cigarete; Žepni strojček za zvijanje cigaret; Ročne naprave za vstavljanje tobaka v papirne tulce; Elektronske cigarete; Tekoče raztopine za uporabo v elektronskih cigaretah; Tobačni izdelki, ki so namenjeni za segrevanje; Majhne cigare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Cigaretter; Tobak; Rulltobak; Piptobak; Tobaksprodukter; Tobakssubstitut, inte för medicinska ändamål; Cigarrer; Cigariller; Cigarettändare; Cigarrtändare; Tändstickor; Artiklar för användning med tobak; Cigarettpapper; Cigaretthylsor; Cigarettfilter; Fickcigarrettrullare; Handhållna maskiner för införing av tobak i pappersrör; Elektroniska cigaretter; Flytande lösningar för användning i elektroniska cigaretter; Tobaksprodukter för uppvärmning; Små cigarrer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>229250</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>11647</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
