<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-14T07:55:52</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018222216</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018222216</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-08</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-10-11</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-08</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-14</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>HALALTOURS</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162189550</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/222/018222216/000162189550.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>03.07.19</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.01.03</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.01.24</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Пътеводители; Пътни карти; Карти; Списания за пътешествия; Пътеводители; Указатели на градове; Книги.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Průvodce (knihy); Silniční mapy; Mapy; Časopisy o cestování; Průvodce (knihy); Městské adresáře; Knihy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Guidebøger; Vejkort; Kort [geografiske]; Rejsemagasiner; Guidebøger; Byvejvisere; Bøger.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Reiseführer; Straßenkarten; Stadtpläne; Reisemagazine; Reisehandbücher; Städteverzeichnisse (Druckereierzeugnisse); Bücher.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ταξιδιωτικοί οδηγοί· Οδικοί χάρτες· Χάρτες· Ταξιδιωτικά περιοδικά· Ταξιδιωτικοί οδηγοί· Κατάλογοι πόλεων· Βιβλία.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Guide books; Road maps; Maps; Travel magazines; Guide books; City directories; Books.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Guías turísticas [publicaciones]; Mapas de carreteras; Mapas; Revistas de viajes; Guías turísticas [publicaciones]; Directorios de ciudad; Libros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Juhendiraamatud; Teedekaardid; Kaardid (geograafia); Reisiajakirjad; Juhendiraamatud; Linnateatmikud, -kataloogid; Raamatud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Opaskirjat; Tiekartat; Kartat; Matkailualan aikakauslehdet; Opaskirjat; Kaupunkihakemistot; Kirjat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Guides de voyage imprimés; Cartes routières; Cartes [géographie]; Revues de voyage; Guides de voyage imprimés; Répertoires de villes [annuaires]; Livres.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Turistički vodiči; Cestovne karte; Mape; Putni časopisi; Turistički vodiči; Telefonski imenici; Knjige.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Útikönyvek; Autóstérképek; Térképek; Utazási magazinok; Útikönyvek; Városi címtárak; Könyvek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Guide turistiche; Carte stradali; Cartine; Riviste di viaggi; Guide turistiche; Elenchi cittadini; Libri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Gidai (knygos); Kelių žemėlapiai; Žemėlapiai; Kelionių žurnalai; Gidai (knygos); Miestų katalogai; Knygos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ceļveži; Ceļu kartes; Kartes; Ceļojumu žurnāli; Ceļveži; Pilsētu katalogi; Grāmatas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Gwidi turistiċi [kotba]; Mapep tat-toroq; Mapep; Rivisti tal-ivvjaġġar; Gwidi turistiċi [kotba]; Direttorji tal-ibliet; Kotba.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Gidsen; Wegenkaarten; Plattegronden; Reistijdschriften; Gidsen; Stadsgidsen; Boeken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przewodniki; Mapy drogowe; Mapy; Magazyny podróżnicze; Przewodniki; Spisy miast; Książki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Guias (roteiros); Mapas de estrada; Mapas; Revistas de viagens; Guias (roteiros); Diretórios de cidades; Livros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ghiduri; Hărți rutiere; Hărți; Reviste de călătorii; Ghiduri; Cataloage de orașe; Cărți.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Sprievodcovia [knihy]; Cestné mapy; Mapy; Cestovateľské časopisy; Sprievodcovia [knihy]; Mestské zoznamy; Knihy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Vodiči; Cestni zemljevidi; Zemljevidi; Revije o potovanjih; Vodiči; Telefonski imeniki; Knjige.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Guideböcker; Vägkartor; Kartor; Resetidskrifter; Guideböcker; Företagskataloger; Böcker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Рекламиране и рекламни услуги; Стопанско управление; Търговска администрация; Административна дейност; Бизнес одит; Административно обработване на поръчки на клиенти; Рекламиране чрез пощенски поръчки; Консултантски услуги за търговско управление; Организиране на търгове; Рекламиране чрез афиши; Търговски оценки; Бизнес информации; Търговски справки; Изследвания с търговска цел; Консултации в областта на търговското ръководство и организация; Подпомагане при управлението на търговски дейности; Консултантски и съветнически услуги в областта на търговското управление; Административно управление на хотели; Бизнес мениджмънт на спортисти; Консултации, свързани с бизнес организация; Проучване с търговска цел; Търговско управление при лицензиране на стоки и услуги за трети лица; Агенции за търговска информация; Предоставяне на търговска информация и съвети за клиенти [център за потребителски съвети]; Помощ при управление на търговски или промишлени предприятия; Събиране на информация в компютърни бази данни; Събиране на статистически данни; Управление на компютърни файлове; Анализ на себестойността; Търсене в компютърни бази данни [за трети лица]; Представяне на стоки; Рекламни услуги по пощатата; Разпространение на реклами; Разпространение на мостри; Възпроизвеждане на документи; Съставяне на извлечения от сметки; Икономическо прогнозиране; Трудови борси; Агенции за внос и износ; Фактуриране; Услуги за художествено оформление за рекламни цели; Маркетингови услуги; Проучване на пазара; Преглед на печата; Онлайн реклама в компютърна мрежа; Изложения с търговска или рекламна цел; Организиране на търговски панаири с търговска или рекламна цел; Услуги за наемане на подизпълнители [търговско съдействие]; Консултантски услуги в областта на човешките ресурси; Набиране на кадри; Фотокопиране; Представяне на стоки и услуги в средства за масова информация за търговията на дребно; Услуги за сравняване на цени; Снабдяване за сметка на трети лица [закупуване на стоки или услуги за други предприятия]; Производство на рекламни филми; Бизнес консултантски услуги; Услуги в областта на връзките с обществеността; Рекламни текстове (Публикуване на -); Рекламни агенции; Изготвяне на рекламни рубрики; Отдаване под наем на рекламни съоръжения; Радиорекламиране; Отдаване под наем на рекламно пространство и време; Отдаване под наем на рекламно време във всички средства за комуникация; Насърчаване на продажбите [за трети лица]; Набиране на спонсори; Систематизиране на информация в компютърни бази данни; Телемаркетингови услуги; Приемане на телефонни съобщения [за отсъстващи абонати]; Телевизионни реклами; Машинописни услуги; Актуализиране на рекламни материали; Писане на рекламни текстове; Рекламни услуги, свързани с транспортната индустрия.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Propagace; Služby v oblasti obchodního managementu; Obchodní administrativa; Kancelářské práce; Provádění podnikových auditů; Administrativní zpracování objednávek; Zásilková reklama; Poradenské služby pro obchodní vedení; Vedení dražeb; Venkovní reklama; Oceňování podniků; Obchodní informace; Poptávky; Obchodní průzkum; Poradenství v oblasti řízení a organizace podniku; Pomoc při řízení obchodní činnosti; Vedení podniků (poradenství); Řízení obchodní činnosti hotelů; Řízení obchodní činnosti sportovců; Poradenství v oblasti organizace podniku; Obchodní průzkum; Obchodní správa licencí k výrobkům a službám jiných osob; Zprostředkování obchodních informací; Obchodní informace a rady pro spotřebitele [poradna pro spotřebitele]; Pomoc při řízení obchodních či průmyslových podniků; Sběr údajů do počítačových databází; Sestavování statistiky; Vedení počítačové evidence; Analýza nákladů a cen; Vyhledávání dat v počítačových souborech [pro třetí osoby]; Předvádění zboží; Cílené zasílání reklamních materiálů; Šíření reklam; Šíření vzorků; Kopírování dokumentů; Vyhotovování výpisů z účtu; Vyhotovování hospodářských prognóz; Zprostředkování zaměstnání; Kanceláře dovozní a vývozní; Fakturace; Grafická úprava pro reklamní účely; Marketing; Průzkum trhu; Výstřižková služba; Online inzerce v počítačové síti; Pořádání výstav pro obchodní či reklamní účely; Pořádání veletrhů pro obchodní či reklamní účely; Subdodavatelské služby [pomoc v obchodní činnosti]; Poradenství v oblasti řízení lidských zdrojů; Nábor zaměstnanců; Fotokopírování; Prezentace zboží a služeb v komunikačních médiích pro maloobchod; Srovnávání cen; Zásobovací služby pro jiné osoby [nákup zboží a služeb pro jiné podniky]; Výroba reklamních filmů; Obchodní konzultační služby; Styk s veřejností; Vydávání reklamních textů; Zprostředkování propagace; Příprava inzertních sloupků; Pronájem reklamního materiálu; Rozhlasová reklama; Pronájem reklamních ploch; Pronájem reklamního času v komunikačních médiích; Podpora prodeje jiných osob; Vyhledávání sponzorů; Systematizace údajů do počítačových databází; Telemarketing; Záznamenávání vzkazů pro nedostupné předplatitele; Televizní reklama; Psaní na stroji; Aktualizace reklamních materiálů; Psaní reklamních textů; Reklamní služby v oblasti cestovního ruchu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Reklamevirksomhed; Forretningsledelse; Forretningsadministration; Varetagelse af kontoropgaver; Auditering af virksomheder; Administrativ behandling af købsordrer; Annoncering pr. postordre; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsledelse; Auktionsvirksomhed; Udendørs avertering; Vurdering i forretningsanliggender; Forretningsinformation; Indhentning af forretningsoplysninger; Forretningsundersøgelser; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsledelse og organisation; Bistand ved forretningsledelse; Konsulenttjenester og rådgivning vedrørende forretningsledelse; Forretningsmæssig bistand ved ledelse af hoteller; Forretningsadministration for sportsfolk; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsorganisation; Forretningsresearch; Kommerciel administration ved licensering af andres varer og tjenesteydelser; Forretningsmæssig oplysningsagenturvirksomhed; Kommerciel information og rådgivning til forbrugere [forbrugerrådgivning]; Bistand ved forretningsvirksomhed og industriel virksomhed; Kompilering af informationer i computerdatabaser; Kompilering af statistikker; Administration af datastyrede arkiver; Omkostningsanalyser; Datasøgning for andre i computerregistre; Demonstration af varer; Avertering pr. post; Udsendelse af reklamer og annoncer; Distribution af vareprøver; Kopiering af dokumenter; Udarbejdelse af kontoopgørelser; Økonomiske prognoser; Arbejdsformidlingskontorvirksomhed; Import- og eksportagenturer; Fakturering; Layout til reklamemæssige formål; Marketing; Markedsforskning; Nyhedsudklipsbureau; Online-annoncering på et computernetværk; Organisering af udstillinger med kommercielle eller reklamemæssige formål; Organisering af varemesser med kommercielle eller reklamemæssige formål; Outsourcing [forretningsmæssig bistand]; Rådgivning vedrørende personaleledelse; Personalerekruttering; Fotokopiering; Præsentation af varer og tjenesteydelser i kommunikationsmedier for detailhandlen; Sammenligning af priser; Indkøbsbistand til andre ved køb af varer og tjenesteydelser; Produktion af reklamefilm; Forretningsmæssig rådgivningsvirksomhed; PR-virksomhed; Publikation af reklametekster; Reklamebureauvirksomhed; Udarbejdelse af reklamerubrikker; Udlejning af reklamemateriale; Radioreklamer; Udlejning af reklameplads; Udlejning af reklametid på kommunikationsmedier; Salgsfremmende foranstaltninger for andre; Søgning efter sponsorater; Sortering og redigering af informationer computerdatabaser; Telemarketing; Telefonsvareservice for abonnenter, som er midlertidigt fraværende; TV-reklamer; Maskinskrivning; Ajourføring af reklamemateriale; Skrivning af reklametekster; Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed i forbindelse med rejsebranchen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werbung; Geschäftsführung; Unternehmensverwaltung; Büroarbeiten; Unternehmensprüfungen; Verwaltungstechnische Bearbeitung von Bestellungen; Versandwerbung; Beratungsdienste in Fragen der Geschäftsführung; Auktions- und Versteigerungsdienste; Plakatanschlagwerbung; Wertermittlungen in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Geschäftsinformationen; Auskünfte in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Ermittlungen in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Beratung bei der Organisation und Führung von Unternehmen; Planungen [Hilfe] bei der Geschäftsführung; Geschäftsführungsberatung; Geschäftsführung von Hotels im Auftrag Dritter; Geschäftsführung für Sportler; Organisationsberatung in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Nachforschungen in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Kommerzielle Verwaltung der Lizenzierung von Waren und Dienstleistungen für Dritte; Erteilung von Auskünften in Handels- und Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Erteilung von Auskünften [Information] und Beratung für Verbraucher in Handels- und Geschäftsangelegenheiten [Verbraucherberatung]; Hilfe bei der Führung von gewerblichen oder Handelsbetrieben; Zusammenstellung von Daten in Computerdatenbanken; Erstellen von Statistiken; Dateienverwaltung mittels Computer; Aufstellung von Kosten-Preisanalysen; Nachforschung in Computerdateien [für Dritte]; Vorführung von Waren für Werbezwecke; Direktversandwerbung; Verbreitung von Werbung; Verteilung von Warenproben zu Werbezwecken; Vervielfältigung von Dokumenten; Erstellung von Rechnungsauszügen; Erstellung von Wirtschaftsprognosen; Personal-, Stellenvermittlung; Betrieb einer Im- und Exportagentur; Fakturierung; Layoutgestaltung für Werbezwecke; Marketing; Marktforschung; Sammeln und Zusammenstellen von themenbezogenen Presseartikeln; Online- Werbung in einem Computernetzwerk; Organisation von Ausstellungen für wirtschaftliche oder Werbezwecke; Veranstaltung von Messen zu gewerblichen oder zu Werbezwecken; Outsourcing-Dienste [Hilfe bei Geschäftsangelegenheiten]; Beratung in Fragen des Personalwesens; Personalanwerbung; Fotokopierarbeiten; Präsentation von Waren und Dienstleistungen in Kommunikations-Medien, für den Einzelhandel; Preisvergleichsdienste; Beschaffungsdienstleistungen für Dritte [Erwerb von Waren und Dienstleistungen für andere Unternehmen]; Produktion von Werbefilmen; Unternehmensberatungsdienste; Öffentlichkeitsarbeit; Herausgabe von Werbetexten; Dienstleistungen einer Werbeagentur; Werbung durch Werbeschriften; Vermietung von Werbematerial; Rundfunkwerbung; Vermietung von Werbeflächen; Vermietung von Werbezeit in Kommunikations-Medien; Verkaufsförderung [Sales promotion] [für Dritte]; Sponsorensuche; Systematisierung von Daten in Computerdatenbanken; Telemarketing; Telefonantwortdienst für abwesende Teilnehmer; Fernsehwerbung; Schreibmaschinenarbeiten; Aktualisierung von Werbematerial; Verfassen von Werbetexten; Werbung für die Reisebranche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαφήμιση· Διοίκηση επιχειρήσεων· Διαχείριση επιχειρήσεων· Εργασίες γραφείου· Λογιστικός έλεγχος επιχειρήσεων· Διοικητική επεξεργασία παραγγελιών αγοράς· Διαφήμιση με αλληλογραφία· Διοίκηση (Υπηρεσίες συμβουλών για την επιχειρησιακή -)· Υπηρεσίες δημοπρασιών· Αφισοκόλληση· Εκτιμήσεις επιχειρηματικές· Εμπορική πληροφόρηση· Επιχειρηματικές έρευνες· Επιχειρηματική πραγματογνωμοσύνη· Επιχειρήσεων (Συμβουλές για οργάνωση και διεύθυνση -)· Υποστήριξη στον τομέα της διαχείρισης επιχειρηματικών δραστηριοτήτων· Υπηρεσίες εμπειρογνώμονα και συμβουλευτική σε θέματα διαχείρισης επιχειρήσεων· Ξενοδοχείων διαχείρηση· Επαγγελματική διαχείριση αθλητών· Συμβουλευτική σε θέματα οργάνωσης επιχειρήσεων· Επιχειρηματική έρευνα· Εμπορική διοίκηση αδειών εκμετάλλευσης προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Πρακτορεία εμπορικών πληροφοριών· Παροχή εμπορικών πληροφοριών και παροχή συμβουλών σε καταναλωτές [καταστήματα παροχής συμβουλών σε καταναλωτές]· Παροχή βοηθείας στον τομέα της εμπορικής ή βιομηχανικής διαχείρισης· Συλλογή δεδομένων σε βάσεις δεδομένων· Σύνταξη στατιστικών· Διαχείρηση αρχείων πληροφορικής· Ανάλυση τιμής κόστους· Πληροφόρησης σε αρχεία πληροφορικής (αναζήτηση -) [για τρίτους]· Επίδειξη προϊόντων· Υπηρεσίες διαφημιστικού ταχυδρομείου· Διάδοση διαφημιστικών μηνυμάτων· Μετάδοση [διανομή] δειγμάτων· Αναπαραγωγή εγγράφων· Κατάρτιση λογιστικών καταστάσεων· Προβλέψεις οικονομικές· Πρακτορεία εύρεσης εργασίας· Πρακτορεία εισαγωγών-εξαγωγών· Εργασίες έκδοσης τιμολογίων· Υπηρεσίες διάταξης για διαφημιστικούς σκοπούς· Υπηρεσίες μάρκετινγκ· Έρευνα αγοράς· Υπηρεσίες συγκέντρωσης αποκομμάτων ειδήσεων· Διαφήμιση on line σε δίκτυο πληροφορικής· Εκθέσεις για εμπορικούς ή διαφημιστικούς σκοπούς· Οργάνωση εκθέσεων εμπορικών για σκοπούς εμπορικούς ή διαφημιστικούς· Υπηρεσίες υπεργολαβίας [παροχή βοηθείας σε επιχειρήσεις]· Συμβουλευτική για θέματα διοίκησης προσωπικού· Πρόσληψη προσωπικού· Υπηρεσίες παραγωγής φωτοαντιγράφων· Παρουσίαση προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών σε μέσα επικοινωνίας για το λιανικό εμπόριο· Υπηρεσίες σύγκρισης τιμών· Εφοδιασμού για τρίτους (υπηρεσίες -) [αγορά προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για άλλες επιχειρήσεις]· Παραγωγή διαφημιστικών ταινιών· Υπηρεσίες συμβουλευτικής επιχειρήσεων· Υπηρεσίες δημοσίων σχέσεων· Δημοσίευση διαφημιστικών κειμένων· Πρακτορεία διαφημιστικά· Μηνύματα διαφημιστικά· Διαφημιστικού υλικού μίσθωση· Διαφημιστικά ραδιοφωνικά μηνύματα· Διαφημιστικών χώρων μίσθωση· Μίσθωση διαφημιστικού χρόνου σε μέσα επικοινωνίας· Προώθηση πωλήσεων [για τρίτους]· Αναζήτηση χορηγίας· Συστηματοποίηση δεδομένων σε βάσεις δεδομένων· Υπηρεσίες τηλεμπορίας (τηλεμάρκετινγκ)· Υπηρεσίες αυτόματου τηλεφωνητή για μη διαθέσιμους συνδρομητές· Διαφημιστικά τηλεοπτικά μηνύματα· Υπηρεσίες δακτυλογράφησης· Ενημέρωση για υλικό διαφημιστικό· Συγγραφή διαφημιστικών κειμένων· Υπηρεσίες διαφήμισης σε σχέση με την ταξιδιωτική βιομηχανία.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Advertising; Business management; Business administration; Office functions; Business auditing; Administrative processing of purchase orders; Advertising by mail order; Advisory services for business management; Auctioneering services; Outdoor advertising; Business appraisals; Business inquiries; Business inquiries; Business investigations; Business management and organization consultancy; Business management assistance; Business management consultancy and advisory services; Business management of hotels; Business management of sports people; Business organization consultancy; Business research; Commercial administration of the licensing of the goods and services of others; Commercial information agency services; Commercial information and advice for consumers [consumer advice shop]; Commercial or industrial management assistance; Compilation of information into computer databases; Compilation of statistics; Computerized file management; Cost price analysis; Data search in computer files for others; Demonstration of goods; Direct mail advertising; Dissemination of advertisements; Distribution of samples; Document reproduction; Drawing up of statements of accounts; Economic forecasting; Employment agency services; Import-export agencies; Invoicing; Layout services for advertising purposes; Marketing; Marketing studies; News clipping services; Online advertising on a computer network; Organization of exhibitions for commercial or advertising purposes; Organization of trade fairs for commercial or advertising purposes; Outsourcing services [business assistance]; Personnel management consultancy; Personnel recruitment; Photocopying services; Presentation of goods and services on communications media, for retail purposes; Price comparison services; Procurement services for others [purchasing goods and services for other businesses]; Production of advertising films; Business consulting; Public relations services; Publication of publicity texts; Advertising agency services; Publicity columns preparation; Publicity material rental; Radio advertising; Rental of advertising space; Rental of advertising time on communication media; Sales promotion for others; Sponsorship search; Systemization of information into computer databases; Telemarketing services; Telephone answering for unavailable subscribers; Television advertising; Typing; Updating of advertising material; Writing of publicity texts; Advertising services relating to the travel industries.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicidad; Gestión de empresas; Administración de negocios; Trabajos de oficina; Auditoría empresarial; Tramitación administrativa de pedidos de compra; Publicidad por correspondencia; Asesoramiento sobre dirección de empresas; Prestación de servicios de subasta; Publicidad exterior; Valoración de negocios comerciales; Información de negocios; Indagaciones sobre negocios; Investigación comercial; Consultoría sobre organización y dirección de negocios; Asistencia en la dirección de negocios; Asesoramiento y consultoría en materia de dirección de empresas; Gerencia administrativa de hoteles; Servicios de representación de deportistas; Consultoría sobre organización de negocios; Búsquedas de negocios; Gestión comercial de licencias de productos y servicios de terceros; Servicios de agencias de información comercial; Información y asesoramiento comerciales al consumidor; Asistencia en la dirección de empresas comerciales o industriales; Compilación de información en bases de datos informáticas; Recopilación de estadísticas; Servicios de gestión informática de archivos; Análisis del precio de costo; Búsqueda de información en archivos informáticos para terceros; Demostración de productos; Distribución de material publicitario [folletos, prospectos, impresos, muestras]; Difusión de anuncios; Distribución de muestras; Reproducción de documentos; Elaboración de estados de cuenta; Previsiones económicas; Servicios de oficinas de empleo; Agencias de importación-exportación; Facturación; Servicios de composición de página con fines publicitarios; Marketing; Estudio de mercados; Servicios de comunicados de prensa; Publicidad en línea por una red informática; Organización de exposiciones con fines comerciales o publicitarios; Organización de ferias con fines comerciales o publicitarios; Servicios de externalización [asistencia comercial]; Consultoría sobre gestión de personal; Selección de personal; Servicios de fotocopia; Presentación de productos y servicios en medios de comunicación para el comercio minorista; Servicios de comparación de precios; Servicios de abastecimiento para terceros [compra de productos y servicios para otras empresas]; Producción de películas publicitarias; Consultoría comercial; Servicios de relaciones públicas; Publicación de textos publicitarios; Servicios de agencias de publicidad; Preparación de columnas publicitarias; Alquiler de material publicitario; Publicidad radiofónica; Alquiler de espacios publicitarios; Alquiler de tiempo publicitario en medios de comunicación; Promoción de ventas para terceros; Búsqueda de patrocinadores; Sistematización de información en bases de datos informáticas; Servicios de telemarketing; Servicios de contestador automático para abonados ausentes; Publicidad televisada; Servicios de mecanografía; Actualización de documentación publicitaria; Redacción de textos publicitarios; Servicios publicitarios relacionados con el sector turístico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reklaam; Ärijuhtimine; Ärijuhtimine; Kontoriteenused; Äri auditeerimine; Ostutellimuste töötlemine; Postimüügireklaam; Äritegevuse juhtimise nõustamine; Oksjonid, enampakkumised; Välireklaam; Äritegevuse hindamine; äriinformatsioon; Ärialased päringud, küsitlused; Ärialased uuringud; Äritegevuse juhtimise ja korraldamise konsultatsioonid; Ärijuhtimisabi; Ärijuhtimise alased konsultatsioonid ja nõustamine; Hotellide ärialane juhtimine; Sportlaste äritegevuse juhtimine; Äritegevuse korraldamise konsultatsioonid; Äriuuringud; Teiste omanike kaupade ja teenuste litsentsimise korraldamine äri eesmärgil; Kaubandusteabeagentuuride teenused; Äriteave ja klientide äriline nõustamine [klientide nõustamise keskus]; Kaubandus- või tööstusalane juhtimisabi; Info kogumine arvuti andmebaasidesse; Statistika koostamine; Arvutipõhine dokumendihaldus; Omahinnaanalüüsid; Andmeotsing arvutifailides kolmandatele isikutele; Kaupade demonstreerimine; Posti teel reklaami levitamine; Reklaammaterjalide levitamine; Näidiste (proovide) levitamine; Dokumentide paljundamine; Arvete seisu, bilansi koostamine; Majandusprognoosid; Tööhõivekontoriteenused; Impordi-ekspordikontorid, -agentuurid; Arvete esitamine; Reklaamide küljendamine teenusena; Turundus; Turu-uuringud; Pressiülevaateteenused; Arvutivõrgureklaam; Kaubandus- ja reklaamnäituste korraldamine; Messide korraldamine äri või reklaami eesmärgil; Allhanketeenused [ärialane abi]; Personalijuhtimisalased konsultatsioonid; Tööjõu värbamine; Fotokopeerimisteenused; Kaupade ja teenuste esitlemine meediakanalites jaekaubandusele; Hinnavõrdlusteenused; Hanketeenused teistele ettevõtetele [kaupade ja teenuste ostmine]; Reklaamfilmide produtseerimine; Ärialane nõustamine; Suhtekorraldusteenused; Reklaamtekstide publitseerimine, avaldamine; Reklaamiagentuuriteenused; Reklaamtekstide ettevalmistamine; Reklaammaterjali üürimine; Raadioreklaam; Reklaamipindade üürimine; Reklaamiaja rentimine massiteabevahendites; Müügikampaaniad, -reklaam teenusena; Sponsorite otsimine; Info süstematiseerimine arvuti andmebaasides; Telemarketingiteenused; Telefonivastamisteenused kättesaamatute abonentide puhul; Telereklaam; Kirjutusmasinal kirjutamine; Reklaammaterjalide ajakohastamine, moderniseerimine; Reklaamtekstide kirjutamine; Reisitööstusega seotud reklaamiteenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mainonta; Liikkeenjohto; Yrityshallinto; Toimistotehtävät; Yritysten tilintarkastus; Ostomääräysten hallinnollinen käsittely; Postimyyntimainonta; Liikkeenhoitoa koskevat neuvontapalvelut; Huutokauppapalvelut; Ulkomainonta; Liiketoiminnan arviointi; Yritystiedotus; Liikkeenhoitoa koskevat kyselyt; Tutkimus liittyen liikkeenhoitoon; Liikkeenhoitoon ja organisaatioon liittyvä konsultointi; Avustaminen liiketoiminnan johtamisessa; Liikkeenjohdon konsultointi- ja neuvontapalvelut; Hotellien johtaminen; Manageripalvelut urheilijoille; Liiketoiminnan järjestämiseen liittyvä konsultointi; Liikkeenhoitoa koskeva tutkimus; Kaupallinen hallinnointi koskien toisten tavaroiden ja palveluiden lisensointia; Tietotoimistot, kaupalliset; Kaupallinen tiedotus ja kuluttajaneuvonta; Kaupan tai teollisuuden hallinnollinen avustustoiminta; Tietokantatietojen koostaminen; Tilastotietojen kerääminen; Tietokonetiedostojen hallinta; Hankintahinta-arviointi; Tiedon etsintä tietokonetiedostoista [muille]; Tavaroiden esittely; Suorapostimainonta; Mainosten jakelu; Tavaranäytteiden jakelu; Dokumenttien kopiointi; Tilinpitoselvitys; Talousennusteiden tekeminen; Työnvälitys; Tuonti- ja vientitoiminta; Laskutus; Tekstin sommittelu mainostarkoituksiin; Markkinointipalvelut; Markkinatutkimus; Lehtileikepalvelut; Online-mainonta tietoverkoissa; Näyttelyt kaupallisiin tai mainontatarkoituksiin; Messujen järjestäminen kaupallisiin tai mainontatarkoituksiin; Ulkoistamispalvelut [yritystoiminnan avustamisena]; Henkilöstöhallintakonsultointi; Henkilöstörekrytointi; Valokopiointipalvelut; Tavaroiden ja palveluiden esitteleminen viestintävälineissä vähittäiskauppaa varten; Vertailupalvelut (hintojen); Hankintapalvelut muille [tavaroiden ja palveluiden osto muille yrityksille]; Tuotanto (mainosfilmien); Yrityskonsultointipalvelut; Suhdetoimintapalvelut; Mainoslehtisten julkaisu; Mainostoimistot; Mainostekstien laadinta; Mainosmateriaalin vuokraus; Radiomainokset; Mainostilan vuokraus; Mainosajan vuokraus tiedotusvälineissä; Myynninedistäminen [muille]; Sponsoroinnin etsintäpalvelut; Tietokantatietojen systematisointi; Puhelinmyyntipalvelut; Puhelinvastaajapalvelut saavuttamattomissa oleville tilaajille; Televisiomainokset; Konekirjoituspalvelut; Mainosmateriaalin päivitys; Mainostekstien kirjoittaminen; Matkailualaan liittyvät mainontapalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publicité; Services de gestion commerciale; Administration commerciale; Travaux de bureau; Audits d'entreprises [analyses commerciales]; Traitement administratif de commandes d'achats; Publicité par correspondance; Services de conseils pour la direction des affaires; Services de vente aux enchères; Publicité extérieure; Estimation en affaires commerciales; Informations d'affaire; Renseignements d'affaires; Investigations pour affaires; Conseils en organisation et direction des affaires; Aide à la direction des affaires; Services de conseillers et de conseils en gestion d'entreprises; Gérance administrative d'hôtels; Gestion d'affaires pour le compte de sportifs; Conseils en organisation des affaires; Recherches pour affaires; Administration commerciale de licences de produits et de services de tiers; Services d'agences d'informations commerciales; Informations et conseils commerciaux aux consommateurs; Aide à la direction d'entreprises commerciales ou industrielles; Compilation d'informations dans des bases de données informatiques; Établissement de statistiques; Services de gestion informatisée de fichiers; Analyse du prix de revient; Recherches d'informations dans des fichiers informatiques pour des tiers; Démonstration de produits; Distribution de matériel publicitaire [tracts, prospectus, imprimés, échantillons]; Diffusion d'annonces; Diffusion [distribution] d'échantillons; Reproduction de documents; Établissement de relevés de comptes; Prévisions économiques; Services de bureaux de placement; Agences d'import-export; Facturation; Mise en pages à buts publicitaires; Marketing; Étude de marché; Services de revues de presse; Publicité en ligne sur un réseau informatique; Organisation d'expositions à buts commerciaux ou de publicité; Organisation de foires à buts commerciaux ou de publicité; Services de sous-traitance [assistance commerciale]; Services de conseils en gestion de personnel; Recrutement de personnel; Services de photocopie; Présentation de produits et de services dans les médias de communication pour le commerce de détail; Services de comparaison de prix; Services d'approvisionnement pour des tiers [achat de produits et de services pour d'autres entreprises]; Production de films publicitaires; Services de conseillers d'affaires; Services de relations publiques; Publication de textes publicitaires; Services d'agences de publicité; Courrier publicitaire; Location de matériel publicitaire; Publicité radiophonique; Location d'espaces publicitaires; Location de temps publicitaire sur tout moyen de communication; Promotion des ventes pour des tiers; Recherche de parraineurs; Systématisation d'informations dans des bases de données informatiques; Services de télémarketing; Services de réponse téléphonique pour abonnés absents; Publicité télévisée; Services de dactylographie; Mise à jour de documentation publicitaire; Rédaction de textes publicitaires; Services publicitaires dans le domaine de l'industrie touristique.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Oglašavanje; Poslovno upravljanje; Upravljanje poduzećima; Uredski poslovi; Vođenje knjiga; Administrativna obrada narudžbi; Reklamiranje putem pošte; Usluge savjetovanja za upravljanje poduzećima; Usluge prodaja na dražbi; Plakatiranje [oglašavanje]; Procjene komercijalnih poslova; Poslovne informacije; Poslovi (obavještenja o poslovima); Istraživanja za poslove; Savjeti o organizaciji i vođenju poslova; Pomoć u vođenju poslova; Konzultantske i savjetodavne usluge za poslovno upravljanje; Poslovno upravljanje hotelima; Poslovno upravljanje za osobe iz svijeta sporta; Savjetovanje u svezi poslovne organizacije; Istraživanje za poslove; Komercijalno upravljanje u svezi licenci proizvoda i usluga trećih osoba; Agencije za komercijalne obavijesti; Potrošači [pružanje komercijalni savjeta i informacija potrošačima]; Pomoć u upravljanju industrijskim ili trgovačkim poduzećima; Računalne baze podataka (Sakupljanje informacija u -); Izrada statističkih podataka; Vođenje informatičkih kartoteka; Analiza proizvodne cijene; Inormatički podaci (pretraživanje podataka u informatičnoj kartoteci za treće); Demonstracija proizvoda; Raspačavanje reklamnog materijala [traktata, prospekata, tiskanica, uzoraka]; Distribucija reklamnih oglasa; Podjela [distribucija] uzoraka; Kopiranje dokumenata; Izrada izvoda računa; Predviđanje gospodarske situacije; Uredi za zapošljavanje; Agencije za uvoz-izvoz; Fakturiranje; Usluge prijeloma u reklamne svrhe; Marketing; Istraživanje tržišta; Tisak (praćenje tiska); Online oglašavanje na računalnim mrežama; Izložbe u komercijalne i reklamne svrhe; Organiziranje trgovačkih sajmova u komercijalne ili reklamne svrhe; Vanjske usluge [komercijalna pomoć]; Savjetovanje o osoblju; Selekcija osoblja; Usluge fotokopiranja; Prezentacija proizvoda i usluga putem komunikacijskih medija za maloprodaju; Usluge usporedbe cijena; Nabava za treće osobe [usluge kupnje proizvoda i usluga za druga poduzeća]; Proizvodnja reklama; Poslovno savjetovanje; Usluge odnosa s javnošću; Objavljivanje promidžbenih tekstova; Agencije za promidžbu; Reklamna pošta; Iznajmljivanje promidžbenog materijala; Radijsko oglašavanje i reklame; Iznajmljivanje reklamnih prostora; Iznajmljivanje vremena za reklamiranje na komunikacijskim medijima; Promicanje prodaje za treće osobe; Traženje sponzorstva; Sistematiziranje podataka za središnju kartoteku; Usluge telemarketinga; Usluge telefonskog odgovaranja za odsutne pretplatnike; Televizijsko reklamiranje; Daktilografske usluge; Ažuriranje reklamnog materijala; Pisanje marketinških tekstova; Usluge oglašavanja u svezi s turističkim industrijama.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hirdetési- és reklámszolgáltatások; Üzleti menedzsment; Üzleti adminisztráció; Irodai munkák; Üzleti könyvvizsgálat; Vásárlási megrendelések ügyintézése; Reklámlevél szolgáltatás; Üzletvezetési tanácsadási szolgáltatások; Árverési szolgáltatások; Szabadtéri reklámozás, hirdetés; Üzleti értékelések; Üzleti információk; Üzleti tájékoztatás, információnyújtás; Üzleti vizsgálatok, kutatások; Üzletszervezési és üzletvezetési tanácsadás; Segítségnyújtás üzleti tevékenységek menedzsmentjében; Üzletvezetési konzultációs és tanácsadó szolgáltatások; Szállodai üzletvezetés; Üzletvitel sportolók számára; Üzletszervezéssel kapcsolatos konzultáció; Kutatások ügyletekkel kapcsolatban; Áruk és szolgáltatások engedélyezésének kereskedelmi ügyintézése; Kereskedelmi információs ügynökségek; Kereskedelmi információ és tanácsadás fogyasztóknak [fogyasztói tanácsadás]; Segítségnyújtás kereskedelmi vagy iparvállalatok irányításában és működtetésében; Információk számítógépes adatbázisokba való gyűjtése; Statisztikák összeállítása; Számítógépes fájlkezelés, adatkezelés; Költségelemzés; Adatkutatás számítógép fájlokban mások számára; Árubemutatás; Reklámanyagok [röplapok, prospektusok, nyomtatványok, áruminták] terjesztése; Reklámterjesztés; Termékminták, áruminták terjesztése; Iratmásolás; Számlakivonatok összeállítása; Gazdasági előrejelzések; Állásközvetítő irodák; Import-export ügynökségek; Számlázás; Tördelési szolgáltatások hirdetési célokból; Marketing szolgáltatások; Piackutatás; Sajtófigyelés; On-line hirdetői tevékenység számítógépes hálózaton; Kereskedelmi- vagy reklámcélú kiállítások; Kereskedelmi- vagy reklámcélú vásárok szervezése; Outsourcing szolgáltatások [üzleti segítségnyújtás]; Konzultáció személyzeti kérdésekben; Munkaerő-toborzás; Fénymásolási szolgáltatások; Áruk és szolgáltatások bemutatása kommunikációs médiákban, a kiskereskedelem számára; Árösszehasonlító szolgáltatások; Beszerzői szolgáltatások [áruk illetve szolgáltatások beszerzése más cégeknek]; Reklámfilmek készítése; Üzleti konzultációs szolgáltatások; Közönségszolgálati szolgáltatások; Reklámszövegek publikálása; Reklámügynökségek, hirdetési ügynökségek; Hirdetési rovatok készítése; Reklámanyagok kölcsönzése; Rádiós reklámozás; Hirdetési felület kölcsönzése; Reklámidő kölcsönzése kommunikációs médiában; Értékesítési promóciós szolgáltatások; Szponzorok felkutatása; Információk számítógépes adatbázisokba való rendezése; Telemarketing szolgáltatások; Telefonos üzenetközvetítés [telefonon el nem érhető ügyfeleknek]; Televíziós reklámozás; Gépírási szolgáltatások; Reklámanyag frissítése; Reklámszövegek írása; Utazási ágazattal kapcsolatos hirdetési szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicità; Gestione aziendale; Amministrazione commerciale; Lavori di ufficio; Verifica di conti; Trattamento amministrativo di ordinazioni d'acquisti; Pubblicità per corrispondenza; Servizi di consulenza per la gestione degli affari; Servizi di vendita all'asta; Pubblicità esterna; Valutazioni in affari commerciali; Informazioni in materia d'affari; Ragguagli d'affari; Investigazioni per affari; Servizi di consulenza per l'organizzazione e la gestione degli affari; Assistenza nella gestione degli affari; Servizi di consulenza per l'organizzazione aziendale; Gestione amministrativa di alberghi per conto terzi; Gestione aziendale per conto degli sportivi; Servizi di consulenza per l'organizzazione degli affari; Ricerche per affari; Amministrazione commerciale di licenze di prodotti e di servizi di terzi; Servizi di agenzie di informazioni commerciali; Informazioni e consulenza commerciale ai consumatori; Assistenza nella gestione di imprese industriali o commerciali; Compilazione di informazioni in banche dati informatiche; Elaborazione di statistiche; Servizi di gestione di archivi informatici; Analisi del prezzo di costo; Ricerche d'informazioni su schedari informatici [per terzi]; Dimostrazione pratica di prodotti per scopi pubblicitari; Distribuzione di materiale pubblicitario [volantini, prospetti, stampati, campioni]; Diffusione di annunci pubblicitari; Distribuzione di campioni per scopi pubblicitari; Riproduzione di documenti; Stesura di estratti di conti; Previsioni economiche; Servizi di uffici di collocamento; Agenzie per l'importazione e l'esportazione; Fatturazione; Layout per scopi pubblicitari; Marketing; Ricerche di mercato; Servizi di rassegne stampa; Pubblicità online su rete informatica; Organizzazione di esposizioni per scopi commerciali o pubblicitari; Organizzazione di fiere per scopi commerciali o di pubblicità; Servizi di subappalto [assistenza commerciale]; Servizi di consulenza in materia di gestione del personale; Reclutamento di personale; Servizi di fotocopiatura; Presentazione di prodotti e servizi in mezzi di comunicazione per la vendita al dettaglio; Servizi di comparazione dei prezzi; Servizi di approvvigionamento per conto terzi [acquisto di prodotti e di servizi per altre imprese]; Produzione di spot pubblicitari; Servizi di consulenza aziendale; Servizi di pubbliche relazioni; Pubblicazione di testi pubblicitari; Servizi di agenzie di pubblicità; Pubblicità per posta; Noleggio di materiale pubblicitario; Pubblicità radiofonica; Locazione di spazi pubblicitari; Affitto di spazi pubblicitari su mezzi di comunicazione; Promozione delle vendite per i terzi; Ricerca di sponsor; Sistemazione di informazioni in banche dati informatiche; Servizi di telemarketing; Servizi di risposta telefonica per abbonati assenti; Pubblicità televisiva; Servizi di dattilografia; Aggiornamento di materiale pubblicitario; Redazione di testi pubblicitari; Servizi pubblicitari relativi all'industria turistica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Reklama; Verslo vadyba; Verslo tvarkyba; Įstaigų veikla; Verslo auditas; Prekių užsakymų administracinis tvarkymas; Reklamos pristatymas paštu; Verslo vadybos patarėjų paslaugos; Pardavimas aukcione; Viešasis reklamavimas; Verslo operacijų įvertinimas; Informacija (verslo -); Verslo patikrinimai; Verslo nagrinėjimas; Verslo vadybos ir organizavimo konsultacijos; Verslo vadybos pagalba; Konsultavimas ir patarimai verslo vadybos klausimais; Viešbučių verslo vadyba; Verslo vadyba (sportininkams); Verslo organizavimo konsultacijos; Verslo tyrimai; Trečiųjų asmenų prekių ir paslaugų licencijavimo komercinis administravimas; Komercinės informacijos agentūrų paslaugos; Komercinė informacija ir patarimai vartotojams [konsultacijų teikimas]; Komercijos ar pramonės vadybos pagalba; Informacijos rinkimas kompiuterinėse duomenų bazėse; Statistinių duomenų rinkimas; Kompiuterizuotas rinkmenų (bylų) tvarkymas; Savikainos analizė; Duomenų paieška kompiuterių rinkmenose [kitiems]; Prekių rodymas; Reklama paštu; Reklamų skleidimas; Pavyzdžių platinimas; Dokumentų dauginimas; Sąskaitų būklės apyskaitų sudarymas; Ekonominis prognozavimas; Samdos agentūrų paslaugos; Importo ir eksporto agentūros; Sąskaitų-faktūrų išrašymas; Maketavimo paslaugos reklamos tikslams; Rinkodara; Rinkos tyrimai; Naujienų apžvalgų paslaugos; Viešasis elektroninis reklamavimas kompiuterių tinkle; Parodų rengimas (komercijos ar reklamos reikmėms); Mugių rengimas (komercijos ar reklamos reikmėms); Paslaugų nuoma [verslo pagalba]; Personalo vadybos konsultacijos; Personalo komplektavimas; Fotokopijavimas; Prekių ir paslaugų pristatymas visuomenės informavimo priemonėse mažmeninės prekybos reikmėms; Kainų palyginimo paslaugos; Tiekimo paslaugos kitiems [prekių ir paslaugų pirkimas kitiems verslams]; Reklaminių filmų gamyba; Verslo konsultacijos; Viešųjų ryšių paslaugos; Reklaminių tekstų skelbimas; Reklamos agentūrų paslaugos; Reklaminių skilčių rengimas; Reklaminės medžiagos nuoma; Radijo reklama; Reklamos vietų nuoma; Reklamos laiko nuoma žiniasklaidoje; Prekių pardavimo skatinimas [kitiems]; Rėmėjų paieška; Informacijos sisteminimas kompiuterinėse duomenų bazėse; Telerinkodaros paslaugos; Telefoniniai atsakymai (kai abonentas nepasiekiamas); Televizijos reklama; Spausdinimas (mašinėle); Reklaminės medžiagos tobulinimas; Reklaminių tekstų rašymas; Reklamos paslaugos, susijusios su turizmu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reklāma; Uzņēmējdarbības vadības pakalpojumi; Uzņēmumu pārvaldīšana; Biroja darbi; Uzņēmējdarbības audita pakalpojumi; Pirkumu pasūtījumu administratīvā apstrāde; Reklāma ar pasta starpniecību; Padomu sniegšana darījumu vadīšanā; Izsoļu organizēšana; Afišu izvietošana; Uzņēmumu novērtēšana; Uzņēmējdarbības informācija; Uzņēmējdarbības uzziņu sniegšana; Pētījumi darījumu jomā; Konsultāciju sniegšana darījumu vadīšanā un organizēšanā; Atbalsta sniegšana uzņēmējdarbības vadībā; Konsultācijas un padomu sniegšana darījumu vadīšanas jomā; Viesnīcu darījumu vadīšana; Darījumu vadīšana sportistiem; Konsultāciju sniegšana par uzņēmējdarbības organizēšanu; Pētījumi darījumu jomā; Preču un pakalpojumu licencēšanas komerciālā vadība; Komercinformācijas aģentūru pakalpojumi; Komerciālas informācijas un padomu sniegšana patērētājiem par preču un pakalpojumu izvēli; Palīdzības sniegšana komerciālu vai rūpniecības uzņēmumu pārvaldībā; Informācijas apkopošana datoru datubāzēs; Statistikas apkopošana; Datorizēta failu pārvaldība; Pašizmaksas analīze; Datu meklēšana datoru datnēs (failos) trešajām personām; Preču demonstrēšanas pakalpojumi; Reklāmas pakalpojumu nodrošināšana ar pasta starpniecību; Reklāmas izplatīšana; Preču paraugu izplatīšana; Dokumentu pavairošana; Aktu par savstarpējo norēķinu salīdzināšanu sagatavošana; Ekonomiskā prognozēšana; Darbā iekārtošanas biroju pakalpojumi; Importa-eksporta aģentūru pakalpojumi; Faktūrrēķinu izrakstīšanas pakalpojumi; Reklāmas materiālu maketēšana; Mārketinga pakalpojumi; Mārketinga pētījumi; Ziņu apkopošanas pakalpojumi; Reklāma tiešsaistē ar datortīklu starpniecību; Izstāžu organizēšana komerciāliem vai reklāmas nolūkiem; Gadatirgu organizēšana komerciāliem vai reklāmas nolūkiem; Ārpakalpojumu nodrošināšana (palīdzība uzņēmējdarbībā); Konsultāciju sniegšana personālvadībā; Personāla atlase; Fotokopēšana (gaismas kopiju izgatavošana); Preču un pakalpojumu prezentēšana sakaru līdzekļos mazumtirdzniecības nolūkā; Cenu salīdzināšanas pakalpojumi; Uzņēmumu apgāde (preču un pakalpojumu sagāde trešo personu interesēs); Reklāmas filmu veidošana; Konsultāciju sniegšana darījumu jomā; Sabiedrisko attiecību pakalpojumi; Reklāmas tekstu publicēšana; Reklāmas aģentūru pakalpojumi; Reklāmas sleju sagatavošana; Reklāmas materiālu iznomāšana; Radioreklāma; Reklāmas laukumu iznomāšana; Reklāmas laika iznomāšana masu saziņas līdzekļos; Preču noieta veicināšana; Sponsoru meklēšana; Informācijas sistematizēšana datoru datubāzēs; Telemārketinga pakalpojumi; Autoatbildētāja pakalpojumu nodrošināšana prombūtnē esošiem abonentiem; Televīzijas reklāmu veidošana; Mašīnrakstīšanas pakalpojumi; Reklāmas materiālu aktualizēšana; Publicitātes veicināšanai paredzētu tekstu rakstīšana; Reklāmas pakalpojumi saistībā ar ceļojumu nozari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reklamar; Il-ġestjoni ta' negozju; Amministrazzjoni ta' negozju; Funzjonijiet ta' uffiċċju; Il-verifika tan-negozju; L-ipproċessar amministrattiv ta' ordnijiet tax-xiri; Reklamar permezz ta' ordni bil-posta; Servizzi ta' pariri dwar il-ġestjoni ta' negozju; Servizzi ta' irkantijiet; Reklamar fuq barra; Stimi ta' negozji; Informazzjoni dwar negozju; Inkjesti dwar negozju; Investigazzjonijiet dwar negozju; Konsulenza dwar il-ġestjoni u l-organizzazzjoni ta' negozju; Assistenza fil-ġestjoni ta' attivitajiet tan-negozju; Servizzi ta' pariri u konsulenza dwar ġestjoni tan-negozju; Il-ġestjoni tan-negozju ta' lukandi; Ġestjoni ta' negozju ta' personalitajiet sportivi; Konsulenza dwar l-organizzazzjoni ta' negozju; Riċerka dwar negozju; Servizzi ta' amministrazzjoni kummerċjali ta' ħaddieħor, għal-liċenzjar ta' oġġetti u servizzi; Aġenziji ta' informazzjoni kummerċjali; Konsumaturi (Tagħrif kummerċjali u pariri għal -) [ċentru ta' pariri lill-konsumatur]; L-assistenza fil-ġestjoni kummerċjali jew industrijali; Il-kumpilazzjoni ta' informazzjoni f'dejtabejżis tal-kompjuter; Il-kumpilazzjoni ta' statistika; Il-ġestjoni kompjuterizzata ta' fajls; Analiżi tal-prezz ta' produzzjoni; Tiftix ta' data ġo fajls fil-kompjuter (għal oħrajn); Dimostrazzjoni ta' prodotti; Reklamar dirett bil-posta; It-tixrid ta' materjal ta' reklamar; Distribuzzjoni ta' kampjuni; Riproduzzjoni ta' dokumenti; It-tħejjija ta' dikjarazzjonijiet ta' kontijiet; Tbassir ekonomiku; Aġenziji tal-impjieg; Aġenziji ta' l-importazzjoni/esportazzjoni; Fatturazzjoni; Servizzi ta' taqsim/arranġament skond pjan għal skopijiet ta' reklamar; Servizzi ta' kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Riċerka tas-suq; Servizzi ta' qtugħ ta' siltiet ta' aħbarijiet; Reklamar onlajn fuq netwerk tal-kompjuters; Esibizzjonijiet għal skopijiet kummerċjali jew ta' reklamar; L-organizzazzjoni ta' fieri tal-kummerċ għal skopijiet kummerċjali jew ta' reklamar; Servizzi ta' esternalizzazzjoni [assistenza fin-negozju]; Konsulenza dwar il-ġestjoni tal-personàl; Ir-reklutaġġ ta' personàl; Servizzi ta' fotokopjar; Preżentazzjoni ta' prodotti u servizzi fuq mezzi tal-komunikazzjoni għall-bejgħ bl-imnut; Servizzi ta' paragun tal-prezzijiet; Servizzi ta' akkwist għal oħrajn [xiri ta' prodotti u servizzi għal negozji oħra]; Il-produzzjoni ta' films tar-reklamar; Konsulenza dwar negozju; Servizzi tar-relazzjonijiet pubbliċi; Il-pubblikazzjoni ta' testi pubbliċitarji; Aġenziji tar-reklamar; Il-preparazzjoni ta' kolonni tal-pubbliċità; Il-kiri ta' materjal ta' reklamar; Reklamar fuq ir-radju; Il-kiri ta' spazju għar-reklamar; Kiri ta' ħin għar-reklamar fuq il-mezzi ta' komunikazzjoni; Il-promozzjoni tal-bejgħ għal oħrajn; Tiftix għal sponsorizzazzjoni; Is-sistematizzazzjoni ta' informazzjoni f'dejtabejżis tal-kompjuter; Servizzi ta' telepromozzjoni; Tweġib tat-telefon għal abbonati li ma jkunux disponibbli; Produzzjoni ta' reklami televiżivi; Servizzi ta' ttajpjar; L-aġġornament ta' materjal tar-reklamar; Il-kitba ta' testi pubbliċitarji; Servizzi ta' reklamar dwar l-industriji tal-ivvjaġġar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Publiciteit; Diensten op het gebied van bedrijfsvoering; Zakelijke administratie; Administratieve diensten; Zakelijke analyse van bedrijven [auditing]; Administratieve verwerking van bestelorders; Publiciteit per post; Advisering voor bedrijfsleiding; Veilingdiensten; Reclame door aanplakbiljetten; Evaluaties op zakelijk gebied; Zakelijke informatie; Inlichtingen over zaken; Onderzoek op zakelijk gebied; Bedrijfsorganisatorische en -bestuurlijke advisering; Hulp bij de leiding van zaken; Bedrijfsorganisatorische consultancy en advisering; Professionele hotelleiding; Zakelijk beheer voor sporters; Advisering over bedrijfsorganisatie; Zakelijk onderzoek; Zakelijke administratie van licenties op producten en diensten van derden; Diensten van agentschappen voor handelsinlichtingen; Handelsinformatie en -adviezen voor consumenten; Hulp bij de leiding van handels- en industriële ondernemingen; Gegevensverzameling in een centraal bestand; Opstellen van statistieken; Beheer van gegevensbestanden; Kostprijsanalyse; Opzoeken van informatie in computerbestanden [voor derden]; Demonstratie van producten; Verspreiding van reclamemateriaal [vlugschriften, prospectussen, drukwerken, monsters]; Verspreiding van reclame; Verspreiding van monsters; Reproductie van documenten; Opstellen van rekeningoverzichten; Economische prognoses; Diensten van arbeidsbureaus; Import- en exportagentschappen; Facturering; Lay-out verzorging voor publicitaire doeleinden; Marketing; Marktstudie; Knipseldiensten; Online reclame op een computernetwerk; Organisatie van tentoonstellingen voor commerciële of publicitaire doeleinden; Organisatie van beurzen voor commerciële of publicitaire doeleinden; Outsourcing [zakelijke assistentie]; Advisering met betrekking tot personeel; Personeelswerving; Fotokopieerdiensten; Presentatie van goederen en diensten in communicatiemedia voor de detailhandel; Prijsvergelijkingsdiensten; Aankoop voor andere bedrijven; Productie van reclamefilms; Zakelijke consultancy; Public relationsdiensten; Uitgave van reclameteksten; Diensten van reclamebureaus; Samenstellen van reclamedrukwerk; Verhuur van reclamemateriaal; Radioreclame; Verhuur van advertentieruimte; Verhuur van reclametijd op communicatiemedia; Verkooppromotie [voor derden]; Sponsorwerving; Systematisering in een centraal bestand van gegevens; Telemarketing; Telefoonbeantwoording voor afwezige abonnees; Reclame per televisie; Typewerkzaamheden; Bijhouden van reclamedocumentatie; Opstellen [schrijven] van reclameteksten; Reclame met betrekking tot het reiswezen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Reklama; Zarządzanie działalnością gospodarczą; Administrowanie działalnością gospodarczą; Prace biurowe; Audyt działalności gospodarczej; Zarządzanie w zakresie zamówień handlowych; Reklama korespondencyjna; Usługi doradcze w zarządzaniu działalnością gospodarczą; Usługi aukcyjne; Reklama zewnętrzna; Wyceny handlowe; Informacja gospodarcza; Badania dotyczące działalności gospodarczej; Badania biznesowe; Doradztwo w zakresie organizowania i prowadzenia działalności gospodarczej; Pomoc w zarządzaniu działalnością gospodarczą; Usługi doradcze i konsultingowe w zakresie zarządzania działalnością gospodarczą; Zarządzanie hotelami; Usługi menedżerskie dla sportowców; Doradztwo w zakresie organizacji działalności gospodarczej; Badania w zakresie biznesu; Zarządzanie handlowe w zakresie koncesjonowania dóbr i usług na rzecz osób trzecich; Agencje informacji handlowej; Handlowe informacje i porady udzielane konsumentom [punkty informacji konsumenckiej]; Pomoc przy zarządzaniu przedsiębiorstwami przemysłowymi lub handlowymi; Komputerowe bazy danych (Pozyskiwanie danych do -); Statystyczne zestawienia; Komputerowe zarządzanie plikami; Analizy kosztów; Wyszukiwanie informacji w plikach komputerowych dla osób trzecich; Pokazy towarów; Bezpośrednia reklama pocztowa; Rozpowszechnianie reklam; Kolportaż próbek; Powielanie dokumentów; Sporządzanie wyciągów z konta; Ekonomiczne prognozy; Biura pośrednictwa pracy; Agencje importowo-eksportowe; Fakturowanie; Usługi w zakresie opracowania graficznego do celów reklamowych; Usługi marketingowe; Badania rynkowe; Usługi przeglądu prasy; Reklama online za pośrednictwem sieci komputerowej; Wystawy w celach handlowych lub reklamowych; Organizowanie targów w celach handlowych lub reklamowych; Outsourcing [doradztwo biznesowe]; Doradztwo w zakresie zarządzania personelem; Rekrutacja personelu; Fotokopiowanie; Prezentacja towarów i usług w mediach komunikacyjnych, dla handlu detalicznego; Usługi w zakresie porównywania cen; Usługi w zakresie nabywania dla osób trzecich [zakupy produktów i usług dla innych przedsiębiorstw]; Produkcja filmów reklamowych; Doradztwo biznesowe; Usługi public relations; Publikowanie tekstów reklamowych; Agencje reklamowe; Przygotowywanie reklam prasowych; Wypożyczanie materiałów reklamowych; Reklamy radiowe; Wynajmowanie przestrzeni reklamowej; Wynajem czasu reklamowego we wszystkich środkach przekazu; Promocja sprzedaży dla osób trzecich; Poszukiwania w zakresie patronatu; Systematyzacja danych w komputerowych bazach danych; Telemarketing; Telefoniczne udzielanie informacji [dla nieobecnych abonentów]; Reklamy telewizyjne; Maszynopisanie; Uaktualnianie materiałów reklamowych; Tworzenie tekstów reklamowych; Usługi reklamowe w zakresie branży podróżniczej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicidade; Gestão de empresas; Administração de empresas; Trabalhos de escritório; Auditorias de empresas; Processamento administrativo de ordens de compra; Publicidade por correspondência; Serviços de assessores para a direção de negócios comerciais; Serviços de leilões; Serviços de publicidade de exterior; Avaliações em negócios comerciais; Informação de negócios; Inquéritos de negócios comerciais; Investigações em negócios comerciais; Consultadoria em organização e direção de negócios comerciais; Assistência na direção de negócios comerciais; Serviços de consultoria e assessoria para gestão de negócios comerciais; Gerência administrativa de hotéis; Gestão empresarial de desportistas; Consultoria em organização de negócios comerciais; Pesquisas comerciais; Administração comercial do licenciamento de produtos e serviços para terceiros [serviços de]; Serviços de agências de informações comerciais; Serviços de aconselhamento e informação comercial aos consumidores [loja do consumidor]; Assistência na direção de empresas comerciais ou industriais; Compilação de informação numa base de dados informática; Compilação de estatísticas; Gestão de ficheiros informáticos; Análise do preço de custo; Pesquisas de informações em ficheiros informáticos [para terceiros]; Demonstração de produtos; Distribuição de material publicitário [folhetos, prospetos, impressos, amostras]; Difusão de publicidade; Difusão [distribuição] de amostras; Reprodução de documentos; Elaboração de extratos de contas; Previsões económicas; Serviços de agências de emprego; Agências de importação-exportação; Faturação; Serviços de paginação [layout] para fins publicitários; Marketing; Estudo de mercados; Serviços de revistas de imprensa; Publicidade online numa rede informática; Organização de exposições com fins comerciais ou de publicidade; Organização de feiras para fins comerciais ou de publicidade; Serviços de outsourcing [assistência em negócios comerciais]; Consultadoria em gestão de pessoal; Recrutamento de pessoal; Reprodução por heliografia; Apresentação de produtos e serviços em meios de comunicação social para o sector do comércio retalhista; Serviços de comparação de preços; Serviços de fornecimento para terceiros [compra de produtos e serviços para outras empresas]; Produção de filmes publicitários; Consultoria empresarial; Serviços de relações públicas; Publicação de textos publicitários; Serviços de agências de publicidade; Preparação de colunas publicitárias; Aluguer de material publicitário; Publicidade radiofónica; Aluguer de espaços publicitários; Aluguer de tempo para publicidade nos meios de comunicação; Promoção de vendas [prestada a terceiros]; Angariação de patrocínios; Sistematização de informação numa base de dados informática; Serviços de telemarketing; Serviços de resposta telefónica [para assinantes ausentes]; Publicidade pela televisão; Serviços de datilografia; Atualização de documentação publicitária; Redação de textos publicitários; Serviços publicitários relacionados com os setores de viagens.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicitate; Administrare de afaceri; Administrarea afacerilor; Lucrări de birou; Contabilitate; Prelucrare administrativă de comenzi de marfă; Publicitate prin corespondență; Conducerea afacerilor (Servicii de consultanță pentru -); Vânzare prin licitație publică; Afișaj; Estimare în afaceri comerciale; Informaţii comerciale; Date referitoare la afaceri; Investigații pentru afaceri; Consultanță în managementul și organizarea afacerilor; Asistență în conducerea afacerilor; Servicii de consultanță și consiliere în managementul afacerilor; Administrarea hotelurilor; Managementul afacerilor sportivilor; Consultanță privind organizarea afacerii; Cercetări pentru afaceri; Administrarea comercială a licențelor produselor și a serviciilor pentru terți; Agenții de informații comerciale; Informații și asistență comerciale pentru consumatori; Asistență în management pentru întreprinderi comerciale sau industriale; Compilarea informațiilor în baze de date informatice; Compilații statistice; Gestionare de fișiere informatice; Analiza prețului de cost; Căutare de informaţii în fişiere informatice, pentru terţi; Prezentare de produse; Publicitate directă prin poștă; Difuzare de anunțuri; Distribuire de eșantioane; Reproducere de documente; Întocmire de extrase de cont; Previziuni economice; Agenții de plasare; Agenţii de import-export; Facturare; Servicii de layout în scopuri publicitare; Servicii de marketing; Studii de piață; Servicii de revista presei; Publicitate on-line într-o rețea informatizată; Organizare de expoziții în scopuri comerciale sau publicitare; Organizarea de târguri în scopuri comerciale și publicitare; Servicii de externalizare [asistență în afaceri]; Consultanță pentru probleme legate de personal; Recrutare de personal; Servicii de fotocopiere; Prezentare de produse şi servicii în medii de comunicare pentru comerţul cu amănuntul; Servicii de comparare a prețurilor; Servicii de aprovizionare pentru terți [achiziții de bunuri și servicii pentru alte întreprinderi]; Producție de clipuri publicitare; Consultanță în afaceri; Servicii de relații cu publicul; Publicare de texte publicitare; Agenții de publicitate; Cronică publicitară; Închiriere de material publicitar; Publicitate radiofonică; Închiriere de spații publicitare; Închiriere de timp publicitar în mijloacele de comunicare; Promovarea vânzărilor pentru terți; Căutare de sponsorizare; Sistematizarea informațiilor în fișiere electronice; Servicii de telemarketing; Servicii de preluare de mesaje vocale pentru abonați telefonici; Publicitate televizată; Servicii de dactilografiere; Reactualizarea materialelor publicitare; Redactare de texte publicitare; Servicii de publicitate privind industria turismului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reklama; Obchodný manažment; Obchodná administratíva; Kancelárske práce; Obchodné alebo podnikové audity (revízia účtov); Administratívne spracovanie obchodných objednávok; Zásielkové reklamné služby; Poradenské služby pri riadení obchodnej činnosti; Dražby; Vonkajšia reklama; Obchodné odhady; Obchodné informácie; Poskytovanie obchodných alebo podnikateľských informácií; Obchodný alebo podnikateľský prieskum; Poradenstvo pri organizovaní a riadení obchodnej činnosti; Pomoc pri riadení obchodnej činnosti; Konzultačné služby a poradenstvo v oblasti obchodného manažmentu; Administratívna správa hotelov; Obchodný manažment pre športovcov; Poradenstvo pri organizovaní obchodnej činnosti; Obchodný alebo podnikateľský výskum; Obchodná správa licencií výrobkov a služieb (pre tretie osoby); Komerčné informačné kancelárie; Obchodné informácie a rady spotrebiteľom pri výbere tovarov a služieb; Pomoc pri riadení obchodných alebo priemyselných podnikov; Zbieranie údajov do počítačových databáz; Zostavovanie štatistík; Správa počítačových súborov; Analýzy nákladov; Vyhľadávanie informácií v počítačových súboroch [pre zákazníkov]; Predvádzanie tovaru; Rozširovanie reklamných materiálov zákazníkom (letáky, prospekty, tlačoviny, vzorky); Rozširovanie reklamných oznamov; Rozširovanie vzoriek tovarov; Rozmnožovanie dokumentov; Zostavovanie výpisov z účtov; Hospodárske (ekonomické) predpovede; Sprostredkovateľne práce; Kancelárie zaoberajúce sa dovozom a vývozom; Fakturácie; Grafická úprava tlačovín na reklamné účely; Marketing; Marketingový prieskum; Prehľad tlače (výstrižkové služby); Online reklama na počítačovej komunikačnej sieti; Organizovanie obchodných alebo reklamných výstav; Organizovanie obchodných alebo reklamných veľtrhov; Subdodávateľské služby (obchodné služby); Personálne poradenstvo; Nábor zamestnancov; Fotokopírovacie služby; Prezentácia tovaru a služieb v komunikačných médiách, pre maloobchod; Služby porovnávania cien; Zásobovacie služby pre tretie osoby (nákup tovarov a služieb pre iné podniky); Tvorba reklamných filmov; Obchodné poradenstvo; Vzťahy s verejnosťou (public relations); Vydávanie reklamných textov; Reklamné agentúry; Príprava inzertných stĺpcov; Prenájom reklamných materiálov; Rozhlasová reklama; Prenájom reklamných plôch; Prenájom reklamného času v komunikačných médiách; Podpora predaja (pre tretie osoby); Vyhľadávanie sponzorov; Zoraďovanie údajov v počítačových databázach; Telemarketingové služby; Odkazovacie telefónne služby (pre neprítomných predplatiteľov); Televízna reklama; Písanie na stroji; Aktualizovanie reklamných materiálov; Písanie reklamných textov; Reklamné služby v oblasti cestovného ruchu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oglaševanje in oglaševalske storitve; Poslovno upravljanje; Poslovna administracija; Pisarniški posli; Poslovno revidiranje; Administrativna obdelava naročilnic; Reklamiranje po pošti; Svetovalne storitve s področja poslovnega vodenja; Storitve v zvezi s prodajami na dražbi; Plakatiranje; Poslovne cenitve; Poslovne informacije; Poslovne poizvedbe; Poslovne preiskave; Poslovodno in organizacijsko svetovanje; Pomoč pri upravljanju poslovnih dejavnosti; Storitve poslovodnega posvetovanja in svetovanja; Poslovno upravljanje hotelov; Poslovno upravljanje športnikov; Svetovanje v zvezi s poslovno organizacijo; Raziskave na področju poslovanja; Poslovna administracija licenciranja blaga in storitev drugih; Agencije za poslovne informacije; Komercialne informacije in svetovanje za potrošnike (poslovalnica za svetovanje potrošnikom); Pomoč pri industrijskem ali poslovnem vodenju; Sestavljanje informacij v računalniške podatkovne baze; Sestavljanje statistik; Vodenje podatkovnih baz; Stroškovno - cenovne analize; Iskanje podatkov v računalniških datotekah (za druge); Predstavitev izdelkov; Neposredno oglaševanje po pošti; Širjenje oglasov; Distribucija vzorcev; Reprodukcija dokumentov; Saldakonti; Ekonomske prognoze; Zaposlovalne agencije; Uvozno - izvozne agencije; Fakturiranje; Storitve urejanja v oglaševalske namene; Storitve trženja; Tržne raziskave; Raziskovanje in zbiranje podatkov iz medijev; Spletno oglaševanje preko računalniškega omrežja; Razstave v komercialne ali oglaševalske namene; Organizacija trgovskih sejmov za komercialne ali oglasne namene; Storitve zunanjih izvajalcev (poslovna pomoč); Svetovanje pri upravljanju s človeškimi viri; Zaposlovanje osebja; Storitve fotokopiranja; Predstavitev izdelkov in storitev v komunikacijskih medijih za maloprodajo; Storitve primerjave cen; Prokuratorske storitve [nabava blaga in storitev za druga podjetja]; Produkcija oglaševalskih filmov; Storitve poslovnega svetovanja; Storitve na področju odnosov z javnostmi; Objavljanje reklamnih besedil; Oglaševalske agencije; Priprava reklamnih rubrik; Oddajanje oglasnih materialov v najem; Reklamno oglaševanje po radiu; Oddajanje oglasnih površin v najem; Najem oglaševalskega prostora v komunikacijskih medijih; Pospeševanje prodaje (za druge); Iskanje sponzorstva; Sistematizacija informacij v računalniške baze podatkov; Storitve telemarketinga; Storitve telefonskih tajnic; Reklamno oglaševanje po televiziji; Strojepisje; Izpopolnjevanje reklamnega gradiva; Pisanje reklamnih tekstov; Oglaševalske storitve, povezane s potovalnimi dejavnostmi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Reklam; Företagsledning; Företagsadministration; Kontorstjänster; Företagsrevision; Administrativ behandling av inköpsordrar; Annonsering via postorder; Rådgivningstjänster för företagsledning; Auktionering; Utomhusreklam; Affärsvärderingar; Kommersiell information; Undersökningar avseende företags- eller affärsverksamhet; Företagsutredningar; Konsultationer avseende företagsledning och -organisation; Assistans vid förvaltning av affärsverksamheter; Konsulttjänster och rådgivning avseende företagsledning; Företagsledning av hotell; Tillvaratagande av idrottsmäns affärsintressen; Företagsorganisationskonsultationer; Företagsundersökningar; Kommersiell administration av licensiering av varor och tjänster för andra; Byråer för kommersiell information; Rådgivning för konsumenter (kommersiell information och -) [konsumentrådgivningsbutik]; Assistans vid affärs- eller industriledning; Sammanställning av information i databaser; Sammanställande av statistik; Datoriserad registerhantering; Marknadsprisanalyser; Datakörningar i datafiler (för andra); Varudemonstrationer; Direktreklam; Spridning av reklam; Utdelning av varuprover; Reproduktion av dokument; Räkenskapsredovisning; Ekonomisk prognostisering; Arbetsförmedlingar; Import-exportagenturer; Faktureringstjänster; Layout-tjänster för reklamändamål; Marketing; Marknadsföringsstudier; Nyhetsklippningstjänster; Annonsering online via datanätverk; Utställningar för kommersiella eller reklamrelaterade ändamål; Anordnande av mässor för kommersiella eller reklamändamål; Outsourcingtjänster [affärsassistans]; Konsultationer avseende personaladministration; Personalrekrytering; Fotokopieringstjänster; Presentation av varor och tjänster inom kommunikationsmedier för detaljhandel; Prisjämförelser; Inköp av varor och tjänster för annans räkning; Produktion av reklamfilmer; Företagskonsultation; Public relationstjänster; Publicering av reklamtexter; Reklambyråer; Utarbetande av reklamtexter; Uthyrning av annons- och reklammaterial; Radioreklamverksamhet; Uthyrning av annonsutrymmen; Uthyrning av annonseringstid på kommunikationsmedia; Sales promotiontjänster; Sökande av sponsring; Systematisering av information i databaser; Telemarketingtjänster; Telefonsvarartjänster; Tv-reklamverksamhet; Maskinskrivning; Uppdatering av annons- och reklammaterial; Skrivning av reklamtexter; Annons- och reklamverksamhet avseende resebranschen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>36</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за застраховки по време на пътуване; Издаване на пътнически чекове от пътнически агенции; Изплащане на пътнически чекове; Издаване на пътнически ваучери; Пътнически застраховки; Кредитни услуги, свързани с пътуването; Финансови услуги, свързани с пътувания; Спешни финансови услуги за пътници; Банкови услуги, свързани с пътнически чекове; Електронно прехвърляне на средства за пътнически агенции; Поръчителство за заплащане на медицински разходи за пътуващи; Издаване на карти за отстъпка за млади хора за всички цели; Консултантски и посреднически услуги, свързани със застраховки при пътуване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby v oblasti cestovního pojištění; Vydávání cestovních šeků cestovními kancelářemi; Vykupování cestovních šeků; Vydání cestovních poukazů; Cestovní pojištění; Úvěrové služby vztahující se k cestování; Finanční služby související s cestováním; Finanční služby pro cestovatele v případě nouze; Bankovní služby týkající se cestovních šeků; Elektronické převody finančních prostředků pro cestovní kanceláře; Záruky na platby léčebných cestovních výdajů; Vydávání slevových karet pro mladé lidi k mnoha účelům; Poradenské a zprostředkovací služby v oblasti cestovního pojištění.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Rejseforsikring; Rejsebureauers udstedelse af rejsechecks; Indløsning af rejsechecks; Udstedelse af rejseværdikuponer; Rejseforsikringsvirksomhed; Kreditvirksomhed i forbindelse med rejser; Finansiel virksomhed i forbindelse med rejser; Finansielle nødsituationsrelaterede tjenesteydelser for rejsende; Bankvirksomhed i forbindelse med rejsechecks; Elektroniske overførsler af penge for rejsebureauer; Garanti for betaling af medicinske udgifter afholdt af rejsende; Uddeling af rabatkort til unge til alle formål; Konsulentbistand og mæglervirksomhed i forbindelse med rejseforsikringer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Reiseversicherungdienstleistungen; Ausgabe von Reiseschecks durch Reiseagenturen; Einlösung von Reiseschecks; Ausgabe von Reisegutscheinen; vermitteln von Reiseversicherungen; Gewährung von Krediten für Reisen; Finanzdienstleistungen Bezug auf Reisen; Finanzdienstleistungen für Reisende in Notsituationen; Bankdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Reiseschecks; Durchführung des elektronischen Zahlungsverkehrs für Reisebüros; Garantieübernahme für die Bezahlung von Arztkosten für Reisende; Ausgabe von Rabattkarten für junge Menschen für alles Zwecke; Maklerberatung und Maklerdienstleistungen im Zusammenhang mit der Reiseversicherung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες ταξιδιωτικής ασφάλισης· Εκδοση ταξιδιωτικών επιταγών από ταξιδιωτικά πρακτορεία· Εξαγορά ταξιδιωτικών επιταγών· Έκδοση ταξιδιωτικών κουπονιών· Υπηρεσίες ασφαλειών ταξιδίων· Πιστωτικές υπηρεσίες σε σχέση με ταξίδια· Χρηματοοικονομικές υπηρεσίες σχετικά με τα ταξίδια· Οικονομικές υπηρεσίες άμεσης εξυπηρέτησης για ταξιδιώτες· Τραπεζικές υπηρεσίες σε σχέση με ταξιδιωτικές επιταγές· Ηλεκτρονική μεταφορά κεφαλαίων για ταξιδιωτικά γραφεία· Εγγυήσεις κάλυψης ιατρικών εξόδων για ταξιδιώτες· Έκδοση εκπτωτικών καρτών για νέους ανθρώπους για κάθε χρήση· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών και μεσιτείας σε σχέση με ταξιδιωτικές ασφάλειες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Travel insurance; Issuing traveler's checks by travel agencies; Redemption of travellers' cheques; Issuing of travel vouchers; Travel insurance; Credit services relating to travel; Financial services relating to travel; Emergency financial services for travellers; Banking services relating to travellers' cheques; Electronic funds transfer for travel agents; Guaranteeing payment of medical expenses for travellers; All-purpose discount cards for young people; Consultancy and brokerage services relating to travel insurance.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de seguros de viaje; Emisión de cheques de viaje por agencias de viaje; Canjeo de cheques de viaje; Emisión de vales de viaje; Servicios de seguros de viaje; Servicios de crédito relativos a los viajes; Servicios financieros relacionados con los viajes; Servicios financieros de emergencia para viajeros; Servicios bancarios relacionados con cheques de viaje; Transferencia electrónica de fondos para agentes de viajes; Servicios de garantías de pago por gastos médicos para viajeros; Emisión de tarjetas de descuentos para gente joven para fines de todo tipo; Servicios de consultoría y corretaje en relación con seguros de viajes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reisikindlustuse teenused; Reisibüroode reisitšekkide väljaandmine; Reisitšekkide lunastamine; Reisitšekkide väljalaskmine; Reisikindlustus; Reisimisalased krediiditeenused; Reisimise finantsteenused; Finantsteenused hädaolukorda sattunud reisijatele; Reisitšekkidega seotud pangandusteenused; Reisibüroode elektrooniliste rahaülekannete sooritamine; Reisijate ravikulude tasumise tagamine; Noortele sooduskaartide väljastamine kõikidel eesmärkidel; Reisikindlustuse nõustamis- ja vahendusteenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Matkavakuutuspalvelut; Matkatoimistojen hoitama matkashekkien myöntäminen; Matkasekkien lunastaminen; Matkakuponkien antaminen; Matkavakuutuspalvelut; Matkailuun liittyvät luottopalvelut; Matkailuun liittyvät rahoituspalvelut; Rahoituspalvelut matkustajille hätätapauksessa; Matkasekkeihin liittyvät pankkipalvelut; Elektroninen varainsiirto matkanjärjestäjille; Matkustajien lääkintäkulujen maksun takaaminen; Alennuskorttien myöntäminen nuorille kaikenlaisiin tarkoituksiin; Matkavakuutuksiin liittyvät konsultointi- ja välityspalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d'assurance en matière de voyages; Émission de chèques de voyage par des agences de voyages; Remboursement de chèques de voyage; Émission de bons de voyage; Services d'assurance-voyage; Services de crédits en matière de voyages; Services financiers en matière de voyages; Services financiers d'urgence pour voyageurs; Services bancaires liés aux chèques de voyage; Services de transferts électroniques de fonds pour agents de voyage; Garantie de paiement de frais médicaux pour voyageurs; Émission de cartes de réduction pour jeunes à toutes fins; Services de conseils et de courtage en matière d'assurance voyage.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge putnog osiguranja; Izdavanje putnih čekova od strane turističkih agencija; Unovčenje putničkih čekova; Izdavanje putnih vaučera; Putno osiguranje; Kreditne usluge u svezi s putovanjima; Financijske usluge u svezi s putovanjima; Hitne financijske usluge za putnike; Bankovne usluge u svezi s putnim čekovima; Elektronički prijenos sredstava za turističke vodiče; Jamčenje za plaćanje putnih zdravstvenih troškova; Izdavanje kartica za popust za mlade ljude, za sve potrebe; Konzultantske usluge i usluge posredovanja u vezi s putnim osiguranjem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Utazási biztosítási szolgáltatások; Utazási csekkek kibocsátása utazási irodákon keresztül; Utazási csekkek beváltása; Utazási utalványok kibocsátása; Utazás biztosítási szolgáltatások; Utazással kapcsolatos hitelszolgáltatások; Utazással kapcsolatos pénzügyi szolgáltatások; Pénzügyi szolgáltatások vészhelyzet esetére utasok számára; Utazási csekkekkel kapcsolatos banki szolgáltatások; Elektronikus pénzátutalások utazási irodák számára; Utazók orvosi kiadásai megtérítésének szavatolása; Kedvezményes kártyák kiadása fiatalok számára, minden célra; Utasbiztosítással kapcsolatos tanácsadási és ügynöki szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di assicurazione per viaggi; Emissione di traveler's checks ad opera di agenzie di viaggi; Rimborso di traveller's cheque; Emissione di buoni viaggio; Servizi assicurativi in materia di viaggio; Servizi di credito riguardanti i viaggi; Servizi finanziari riguardanti i viaggi; Servizi finanziari di emergenza per viaggiatori; Servizi bancari relativi a travellers' cheque; Trasferimento elettronico di fondi per agenti di viaggio; Pagamento a garanzia di spese mediche per viaggiatori; Emissione di carte sconto per giovani per tutti gli scopi; Servizi di consulenza e brokeraggio inerenti le assicurazioni sui viaggi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kelionių draudimo paslaugos; Kelionių agentūrų vykdomas kelionės čekių išdavimas; Kelionės čekių išpirkimas (apmokėjimas); Kelioninių čekių emisija; Kelionių draudimo paslaugos; Kredito paslaugos, susijusios su kelionėmis; Kelionių finansinės paslaugos; Skubios finansinės paslaugos keliautojams; Bankininkystės paslaugos, susijusios su kelionės čekiais; Elektroninis lėšų pervedimas, skirtas kelionių agentams; Gydymo išlaidų apmokėjimo garantavimas keliautojams; Nuolaidų kortelių išdavimas jauniems žmonėms visoms reikmėms; Konsultacijų ir tarpininkavimo paslaugos, susijusios su kelionių draudimu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ceļojumu aprošināšanas pakalpojumi; Ceļojuma čeku izsniegšana ceļojumu aģentūrās; Ceļojuma čeku izpirkšana; Ceļojuma vaučeru izsniegšana; Ceļojumu apdrošināšanas pakalpojumi; Kredītpakalpojumi ceļojumiem; Finanšu pakalpojumi saistībā ar ceļojumiem; Ārkārtas finansiālie pakalpojumi ceļotājiem; Banku pakalpojumi saistībā ar ceļojumu čekiem; Elektroniskie līdzekļu pārskaitījumi ceļojumu aģentūrām; Medicīnisko izdevu apmaksas nodrošināšana ceļotājiem; Atlaižu kartes izsniegšana jauniem cilvēkiem visiem nolūkiem; Konsultācijas un starpniecība saistībā ar ceļojuma apdrošināšanu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' assigurazzjoni tal-vjaġġi; Ħruġ ta' ċekkijiet tal-vjaġġaturi minn aġenziji tal-ivvjaġġar; Tisrif ta' ċekkijiet tal-vjaġġaturi (travellers' cheques); Il-ħruġ ta' vawċers tas-safar; Servizzi ta' assigurazzjoni relatati mal-ivvjaġġar; Servizzi ta' kreditu relatati mal-ivvjaġġar; Servizzi finanzjarji relatati mas-safar; Servizzi finanzjarji ta' emerġenza għall-vjaġġaturi; Servizzi bankarji relatati ma' ċekkijiet għas-safar (travellers' cheques); Trasferimenti ta' fond elettroniku għall-aġenti tal-ivvjaġġar; Garanzija ta' pagamenti ta' spejjeż mediċi għall-vjaġġaturi; Ħruġ ta' kards ta' skont għaż-żgħażagħ għall-għanijiet kollha; Servizzi ta' konsulenza u senserija relatati mal-assigurazzjoni tal-ivvjaġġar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diensten op het gebied van reisverzekeringen; Uitgifte van reischeques door reisagentschappen; Terugbetaling van reischeques; Reisvouchers (Uitgifte van -); Reisverzekeringen; Kredietdiensten met betrekking tot reizen; Financiële diensten met betrekking tot reizen; Financiële nooddiensten voor reizigers; Bankdiensten met betrekking tot reischeques; Overboeking (Elektronische -) van gelden voor reisagenten; Garantstelling voor betalingen van de medische kosten voor reizigers; Uitgifte van kortingskaarten voor jonge mensen voor alle doeleinden; Advisering en bemiddeling met betrekking tot reisverzekeringen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi ubezpieczenia podróżnego; Emisja czeków podróżnych przez biura podróży; Wykup czeków podróżnych; Emisja bonów podróżnych; Ubezpieczenia podróżne; Usługi kredytowe w zakresie podróży; Usługi finansowe związane z podróżami; Usługi finansowe dla podróżnych świadczone w nagłych wypadkach; Usługi bankowe związane z czekami podróżnymi; Elektroniczny transfer środków finansowych dla biur podróży; Gwarantowanie pokrycia kosztów leczenia na rzecz podróżnych; Wydawanie kart rabatowych dla młodych ludzi do wszystkich celów; Usługi doradztwa i pośrednictwa związane z ubezpieczeniami turystycznymi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de seguro de viagens; Emissão de cheques de viagem por agências de viagens; Redenção de cheques de viagem; Emissão de vales de viagem; Seguros de viagem; Serviços de crédito relacionados com viagens; Serviços financeiros relacionados com viagens; Serviços financeiros de emergência para viajantes; Serviços bancários relacionados com cheques de viagem; Transferência eletrónica de fundos para agentes de viagens; Garantias de pagamento de despesas médicas para viajantes; Emissão de cartões de desconto para jovens, para todos os fins; Serviços de consultoria e corretagem relacionados com seguros de viagem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de asigurări de călătorie; Emisiune de cecuri de călătorie de către agențiile de turism; Rambursarea cecurilor de călătorie; Emisiune de cecuri de călătorie; Asigurări de călătorie; Servicii de credit pentru călătorii; Servicii financiare privind călătoriile; Servicii financiare de urgență pentru călători; Servicii bancare privind cecurile de călătorie; Transfer electronic de fonduri pentru agenți de călătorii; Garantarea plății cheltuielilor medicale pentru călători; Emitere de carduri de reduceri pentru tinei în toate scopurile; Servicii de consultanță și curtaj în asigurări de călătorie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Služby cestovného poistenia; Vydávanie cestovných šekov cestovnými agentúrami; Vyplácanie cestovných šekov; Vydávanie cestovných šekov; Cestovné poistenie; Úverové služby pri cestovaní; Finančné služby súvisiace s cestovaním; Núdzové finančné služby pre cestovateľov; Bankové služby vzťahujúce sa na cestovné šeky; Elektronický prevod finančných prostriedkov pre cestovné agentúry; Ručenie platieb za lekárske výdavky pre cestovateľov; Výdaj zľavových kariet pre mladých ľudí pre všetky účely; Konzultačné a maklérske služby v oblasti cestovného poistenia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve potovalnega zavarovanja; Izdajanje potovalnih čekov s strani potovalnih agencij; Unovčenje potovalnih čekov; Izdajanje potovalnih bonov; Potovalno zavarovanje; Kreditne storitve v zvezi s potovanji; Finančne storitve v zvezi s potovanjem; Nujne finančne storitve za popotnike; Bančne storitve v zvezi s potovalnimi čeki; Elektronski prenos sredstev za potovalne agente; Garantiranje plačila zdravstvenih stroškov za potnike; Izdajanje kartic za popuste za mlade za vse namene; Svetovalne in posredniške storitve v zvezi s potovalnim zavarovanjem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Reseförsäkringstjänster; Utfärdande av resecheckar genom resebyråer; Inlösen av resecheckar; Utförande av resevouchers; Försäkringstjänster avseende resor; Kredittjänster i anslutning till resor; Finansiella tjänster avseende resor; Finansiella nödtjänster för resande; Banktjänster avseende resecheckar; Elektroniska överföringar av penningmedel för resebyråer; Garanterande av betalning av medicinska utgifter för resenärer; Utgivning av rabattkort för unga människor för alla ändamål; Rådgivnings- och förmedlingstjänster avseende reseförsäkring.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>39</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Транспорт; Организиране на екскурзии; Въздушен транспорт; Отдаване под наем на летателни апарати; Болничен транспорт; Транспортиране с бронирани автомобили; Организиране на морски пътувания; Организиране на пътувания; Транспортиране с шлепове; Отдаване под наем на плавателни съдове; Съхраняване на плавателни съдове; Воден транспорт; Резервация на места за пътуване; Бутилиране; Автобусен транспорт; Паркинги за автомобили; Отдаване под наем на автомобили; Автомобилен транспорт; Превозване на товари, стоки; Шофьорски услуги; Куриерски служби [съобщения или стоки]; Доставяне [доставка]; Придружаване на пътници; Фериботен транспорт; Отдаване под наем на гаражи; Отдаване под наем на коне; Автобусен чартър; Отдаване под наем на места за паркиране; Пътуване и превоз на пътници; Съхраняване на носители на данни или на електронно съхранени документи; Развлекателен транспорт с лодки; Пренасяне на багаж; Отдаване под наем на превозни средства с покрити багажници; Отдаване под наем на складове за стоки; Отдаване под наем на инвалидни колички; Разглеждане на забележителности [туризъм]; Таксиметрови услуги; Трамваен транспорт; Транспортно комисионерство; Транспортни резервации; Транспортна логистика; Пътнически резервации; Отдаване под наем и наемане на превозни средства; Туристически консултации; Уреждане на туристически обиколки; Екскурзоводни услуги; Куриерски услуги (Пътуване -); Уреждане на туристически обиколки; Услуги за покупки на пътувания; Услуги за придружаване на туристи; Информация за трафика; Организиране на пътувания; Услуги на круизни кораби; Организиране и провеждане на поклонения (пътувания); Услуги за резервация на билети за пътувания; Туристическа агенция предлагаща услуги за организиране на пътувания; Придружаване на пътници; Транспортиране на пътници и пътнически багаж; Продажба на билети за пътувания; Агенции за продажба на пътувания; Организиране на пътувания; Осигуряване на пътнически визи, паспорти и пътнически документи за пътувания в чужбина; Услуги за резервации за туристически обиколки; Организиране напътувания; Консултации в областта на пътуването, предоставяни чрез телефонни кол центрове и горещи линии; Предоставяне на упътвания за шофьори при пътуване; Отдаване под наем на машини за издаване на пътни билети; Консултиране при планиране на маршрути за пътуване; Предоставяне на информация за пътувания чрез глобални мрежи; Организиране на екскурзии; Координиране на пътувания за отделни лица и групи; Транспортни услуги за разглеждане на забележителности; Провеждане на туристически обиколки и екскурзии; Организация и организиране на пътувания; Предоставяне на превозни средства за обиколки и екскурзии; Организиране на екскурзии като част от пакетни ваканции; Провеждане на туристически обиколки; Планиране и организиране на обиколки за разглеждане на забележителности и еднодневни екскурзии; Предоставяне на информация на туристи във връзка с екскурзии и разглеждане на забележителности.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přeprava; Pořádání zájezdů; Letecká doprava; Pronájem letadel; Převoz sanitkou; Přeprava obrněnými vozy; Pořádání zábavních plaveb; Cesty (organizování); Přeprava nákladními říčními čluny; Pronájem plavidel; Uskladnění lodí; Lodní doprava; Rezervace místenek; Plnění lahví; Autobusová doprava; Parkování automobilů; Pronájem automobilů; Automobilová doprava; Doprava; Služby řidičů; Kurýrní služby [zprávy nebo zboží]; Doručování [dodávání]; Doprovázení cestujících; Lodní trajektová doprava; Pronájem garáží; Pronájem koní; Pronájem autobusů; Pronájem parkovacích míst; Služby v oblasti cestování a osobní doprava; Fyzické skladování elektronických dat nebo dokumentů; Vyjížďky výletní lodí; Nošení; Pronájem střešních nosičů na automobily; Pronájem skladů; Pronájem invalidních vozíků; Prohlídky [turistické]; Taxi doprava; Tramvajová doprava; Zprostředkování přepravy; Rezervace dopravy; Logistika v dopravě; Rezervace dopravy; Pronájem vozidel; Poradenská činnost v oblasti cestovního ruchu; Organizování zájezdů; Služby cestovních průvodců; Služby průvodců na cestách; Organizování zájezdů; Služby objednávání cestování; Služby turistického průvodce; Cestovní informace; Organizování cest; Služby okružních plaveb; Organizování a provádění poutních jízd a cest (cestování); Rezervace jízdenek; Služby cestovních kanceláří týkající se zprostředkování zájezdů; Doprovázení cestujících; Přeprava cestovních zavazadel; Služby v oblasti výdeje cestovních lístků; Agentury na objednávání cestování; Organizování cest; Zařizování cestovních víz, pasů a cestovních dokladů pro osoby cestující do zahraničí; Služby týkající se rezervace zájezdů a výletů; Zařizování a organizování zájezdů; Poradenství v oblasti cestování poskytované call centry a horkými linkami; Navigační služby pro řidiče při cestování; Pronájem automatů na výdej cestovních lístků; Poradenství pro plánování cestovních tras; Poskytování cestovních informací prostřednictvím globálních sítí; Pořádání zájezdů; Koordinování cestovních příprav pro jednotlivce a skupiny; Doprava při prohlídkách památek; Vedení prohlídek památek a jízd po památkách; Organizace a pořádání výletů; Poskytování vozidel pro zájezdy a exkurze; Pořádání exkurzí jako součásti organizovaných zájezdů; Vedení zájezdů; Plánování a zajišťování poznávacích výletů a jednodenních výletů; Poskytování informací turistům o exkurzích a poznávacích výletech.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Transport; Arrangering af transport til rejseudflugter; Lufttransport; Udlejning af luftfartøjer; Ambulancetransport; Transport i pansrede vogne; Arrangering af krydstogter; Organisering af ture; Pramtransport; Bådudlejning; Opbevaring af både; Bådtransport; Pladsreservation ved rejser; Tapning [påfyldning på flasker]; Bustransport; Parkeringspladser; Biludlejning; Biltransport; Kærrekørsel [trækvogn]; Chaufførvirksomhed; Kurérvirksomhed [meddelelser eller varer]; Udbringning; Ledsagelse af rejsende; Færgetransport; Garageudlejning; Hesteudlejning; Udlejning af busser; Udlejning af parkeringspladser; Rejser og transport af passagerer; Fysisk opbevaring af data eller dokumenter lagret på elektroniske medier; Transport med lystbåde; Dragervirksomhed; Udlejning af tagbagagebærere; Udlejning af pakhuse og lagerrum; Udlejning af kørestole; Arrangering af sightseeings; Taxikørsel; Sporvognskørsel; Transportmæglervirksomhed; Transportreservation; Transportlogistik; Rejsereservation; Udlejning af befordringsmidler til brug på land; Rejserådgivning; Turledelse; Rejseguidevirksomhed; Rejselederserviceydelser; Turledelse; Bestilling af rejser; Rejseledervirksomhed; Rejseinformation; Organisering af rejser; Arrangering af rejsekrydstogter (transport); Organisering og ledelse af pilgrimsrejser (rejser); Billetreservation til rejser; Rejsebureauvirksomhed i forbindelse med arrangering af rejser (transport); Ledsagelse af rejsende; Transport af rejsebagage; Billetsalg i forbindelse med rejser; Agenturvirksomhed til bookning af rejser; Organisering af rejser; Arrangering af rejsevisa og rejsedokumenter for personer, der rejser i udlandet; Reservation af ture; Arrangering og organisering af rundture; Konsulentbistand vedrørende rejser ydet via callcentre og hotlines; Stillen kørselsvejledning til rådighed til rejsebrug; Udlejning af maskiner til udstedelse af billetter til rejser; Rådgivning vedrørende planlægning af rejseruter; Udbydelse af rejseinformation via globale netværk; Arrangering af transport til rejseudflugter; Koordinering af rejsearrangementer for enkeltpersoner og grupper; Transporttjenester vedrørende sightseeingture; Ledelse af sightseeingture; Organisering og arrangering af udflugter; Tilvejebringelse af køretøjer til ture og rundrejser; Organisering af udflugter i forbindelse med pakkerejser; Ledelse af ture; Planlægning og organisering af sightseeingture og dagture; Formidling af turistinformation i forbindelse med udflugter og sightseeing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Transportwesen; Veranstaltung von Reisen; Lufttransporte; Luftfahrzeugvermietung; Krankentransporte; Transport in gepanzerten Fahrzeugen; Veranstaltung von Kreuzfahrten; Organisation von Fahrten; Transport mit Lastkähnen; Vermietung von Booten; Einlagerung von Booten; Transport mit Schiffen; Buchung von Reisen; Flaschenabfülldienste; Beförderung von Personen mit Bussen [Autobusse, Omnibusse]; Parkplatzdienste; Autovermietung; Kraftfahrzeugtransportdienste; Dienstleistungen eines Fuhrunternehmers [Güterbeförderung]; Chauffeurdienste; Kurierdienste [Nachrichten oder Waren]; Zustellung [Auslieferung]; Reisebegleitung; Transport mit Fährschiffen; Vermietung von Garagen; Vermietung von Pferden; Reisebusvermietung; Vermietung von Parkplätzen; Reisedienstleistungen und Transport von Reisenden; Physische Lagerung von elektronisch gespeicherten Daten und Dokumenten; Beförderung von Personen mit Vergnügungsdampfern; Gepäckträgerdienste; Vermietung von Gepäckträgern für Fahrzeuge; Vermietung von Lagern; Vermietung von Rollstühlen; Veranstaltung von Besichtigungen; Taxidienste; Personenbeförderung mit Straßenbahnen; Dienstleistungen eines Transportmaklers; Reservierungsdienste [Transportwesen]; Transportlogistik; Reservierungsdienste [Reisen]; Landfahrzeugvermietung; Reiseberatung; Reisedurchführung; Reiseführerdienste; Reiseleiterdienste; Reiseplanungsdienste; Reisebuchungsdienste; Reisebegleitdienste; Reiseinformationsdienste; Reiseorganisationsdienste; Kreuzfahrtdienste (Reisen); Organisation und Durchführung von Pilgerfahrten und -reisen (Reisen); Reiseticketreservierung; Reisebürodienste zur Organisation von Reisen; Begleitung von Reisenden; Transport von Reisegepäck; Ausstellung von Reisetickets; Dienstleistung von Reiseagenturen; Organisation von Reisearrangements; Organisation von Reisevisa und Reisedokumenten für Auslandsreisende; Reservierung für Touren (Reisen); Veranstaltung von Ausflugsfahrten; Beratung im Reisebereich abgewickelt über Callcenter und Hotlines; Bereitstellung von Routenwahlinformationen für Reisezwecke; Vermietung von Ausgabeautomaten für Reisetickets; Beratung bei der Planung von Reiserouten; Zurverfügungstellen von Reiseinformationen über weltweite Netzwerke; Organisation des Transports im Rahmen von Reisen; Organisation von Reiseveranstaltungen für Einzelpersonen und Gruppen; Beförderungsdienste für Besichtigungstouren; Leitung von Besichtigungstouren und -fahrten; Veranstaltung und Organisation von Ausflügen; zur Verfügung stellen von Fahrzeugen für Ausflüge und Exkursionen; Organisation von Ausflügen im Rahmen von Pauschalreisen; Durchführung von Touren; Planung und Organisation von Sightseeing-Touren und Tagesfahrten; Zurverfügungstellen von Informationen zu Exkursionen und Sightseeing-Touren für Touristen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μεταφορές· Διοργάνωση εκδρομών· Αερομεταφορές· Εκμίσθωση αεροσκαφών· Ασθενοφόρο (Μεταφορά με -)· Τεθωρακισμένα οχήματα μεταφοράς· Οργάνωση θαλάσσιων ταξιδιών αναψυχής (κρουαζιερών)· Οργάνωση περιηγήσεων· Μεταφορά με φορτηγίδες· Εκμίσθωση σκαφών· Παροπλισμός πλοίων· Υδροδότηση· Θέσεων ταξιδιωτικών (Κράτηση -)· Υπηρεσίες εμφιάλωσης· Μεταφορές με λεωφορείο· Υπηρεσίες στάθμευσης αυτοκινήτων· Ενοικίαση αυτοκινήτων· Υπηρεσίες μεταφοράς με αυτοκίνητο· Αμαξαγώγιο· Οδηγού προσωπικού (Υπηρεσίες -)· Υπηρεσίες ταχυμεταφοράς [μηνυμάτων ή εμπορευμάτων]· Διανομή [παράδοση]· Ταξιδιωτών συνοδεία· Πλοίο επιβατικό οχηματαγωγό (Μεταφορά με -)· Γκαράζ (Μίσθωση -)· Αλόγων (Μίσθωση -)· Ναύλωση λεωφορείων· Μίσθωση χώρων στάθμευσης· Οργάνωση ταξιδίων και μεταφορά επιβατών· Φυσική αποθήκευση ηλεκτρονικά αποθηκεύσιμων δεδομένων ή εγγράφων· Πλοίων αναψυχής (Υπηρεσίες -)· Μεταφορικές εργασίες· Μίσθωση εσχαρών οροφής για οχήματα· Μίσθωση αποθηκών· Μίσθωση αναπηρικών αμαξιδίων· Τουριστικές (Επισκέψεις -)· Υπηρεσίες ταξί· Τραμ (Υπηρεσίες -)· Μεσιτεία μεταφοράς· Κρατήσεις θέσεων για μεταφορά· Εφοδιαστική σε σχέση με μεταφορές· Κρατήσεις ταξιδιών· Μίσθωση και εκμίσθωση οχημάτων· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών επί θεμάτων ταξιδιών· Διαχείριση εκδρομών· Υπηρεσίες ταξιδιωτικής ξενάγησης· Υπηρεσίες ταχυμεταφοράς ταχυδρομείου· Διαχείριση εκδρομών· Υπηρεσίες κρατήσεων για ταξίδια· Υπηρεσίες τουριστικής συνοδείας· Παροχή πληροφοριών για ταξίδια· Οργάνωση ταξιδίων· Υπηρεσίες κρουαζιερόπλοιων· Οργάνωση και διεξαγωγή προσκυνηματικών εκδρομών και ταξιδίων (ταξίδια)· Υπηρεσίες κρατήσεων εισιτηρίων για ταξίδια· Υπηρεσίες ταξιδιωτικών πρακτορείων για οργάνωση ταξιδιών· Ταξιδιωτών συνοδεία· Μεταφορά των αποσκευών επιβατών· Υπηρεσίες έκδοσης εισιτηρίων για ταξίδια· Πρακτορεία ταξιδιωτικών κρατήσεων· Οργάνωση ταξιδίων· Διακανονισμός σε σχέση με ταξιδιωτικές βίζες, διαβατήρια και ταξιδιωτικά έγγραφα για ταξιδιώτες εξωτερικού· Υπηρεσίες κρατήσεων για περιηγήσεις· Διακανονισμός και οργάνωση εκδρομών· Παροχή συμβουλών, στον τομέα των ταξιδιών, μέσω τηλεφωνικών κέντρων και γραμμών βοήθειας· Παροχή κατευθύνσεων οδήγησης για ταξίδια· Εκμίσθωση μηχανών για έκδοση εισιτηρίων για ταξίδια· Παροχή συμβουλών για τον σχεδιασμό δρομολογίων ταξιδίου· Παροχή ταξιδιωτικών πληροφοριών μέσω παγκόσμιων δικτύων· Διοργάνωση εκδρομών· Συντονισμός οργάνωσης ταξιδιών για μεμονωμένα άτομα και ομάδες· Υπηρεσίες μεταφορών για τουριστικές περιηγήσεις σε αξιοθέατα· Διεύθυνση περιηγήσεων και επισκέψεων σε αξιοθέατα· Οργάνωση και διοργάνωση εκδρομών· Παροχή οχημάτων για περιηγήσεις και εκδρομές· Οργάνωση εκδρομών στο πλαίσιο πακέτων διακοπών· Διεξαγωγή περιηγήσεων· Προγραμματισμός και οργάνωση περιηγήσεων σε αξιοθέατα και ημερήσιων εκδρομών· Παροχή πληροφοριών σε τουρίστες για εκδρομές και περιηγήσεις σε αξιοθέατα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Transport; Arranging of transportation for travel tours; Air transport; Aircraft rental; Ambulance transport; Armoured-car transport; Arranging of cruises; Tour organising; Barge transport; Boat rental; Boat storage; Boat transport; Booking of seats for travel; Bottling services; Bus transport; Car parking; Car rental; Car transport; Carting; Chauffeur services; Courier services [messages or merchandise]; Delivery; Escorting of travellers; Ferry-boat transport; Garage rental; Horse rental; Motor coach rental; Parking place rental; Travel and passenger transportation; Physical storage of electronically stored data or documents; Pleasure boat transport; Porterage; Rental of vehicle roof racks; Rental of warehouses; Rental of wheelchairs; Sightseeing [tourism]; Taxi transport; Tram transport; Transport brokerage; Transport reservation; Transportation logistics; Travel reservation; Vehicle rental; Travel consultancy; Operating of tours; Travel guide services; Travel courier services; Operating of tours; Services for the booking of travel; Escorting of travellers; Travel information; Travel arrangement; Cruise ship services; Organising and operating pilgrimages and tours; Travel ticket reservation services; Travel agents services for arranging travel; Escorting of travellers; Transportation of travellers' baggage; Ticketing services for travel; Travel booking agencies; Travel arrangement; Arranging for travel visas and travel documents for persons travelling abroad; Tour reservation services; Arranging and organising of tours; Consultancy in the field of travel provided by telephone call centers and hotlines; Providing driving directions for travel purposes; Rental of machines which issue tickets for travel; Consultancy for travel planning of routes; Providing of travel information via global networks; Arranging of transportation for travel tours; Coordinating travel arrangements for individuals and for groups; Transport services for sightseeing tours; Conducting of sightseeing tours and travel; Organising and arranging tours; Providing vehicles for tours and excursions; Arranging of excursions as part of package holidays; Tour conducting; Planning and arranging of sightseeing tours and day trips; Providing information to tourists relating to excursions and sightseeing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de transporte; Organización de transporte para circuitos turísticos; Transporte aéreo; Alquiler de aeronaves; Transporte en ambulancia; Transporte en vehículos blindados; Organización de cruceros; Organización de giras; Transporte en chalana; Alquiler de barcos; Servicios de depósito de barcos; Transporte en barco; Reservas de plazas de viaje; Servicios de embotellado; Servicios de autobuses; Servicios de aparcamiento; Alquiler de coches; Transporte en automóvil; Acarreo; Servicios de chóferes; Servicios de mensajería [correo o mercancías]; Reparto [entregas]; Acompañamiento de viajeros; Transporte en transbordador; Alquiler de garajes; Alquiler de caballos; Alquiler de autocares; Alquiler de plazas de aparcamiento; Servicios de transporte de viajeros; Almacenamiento físico de datos o documentos archivados electrónicamente; Servicios de barcos de recreo; Servicios de portes; Alquiler de portaequipajes [bacas] para vehículos; Alquiler de almacenes [depósitos]; Alquiler de sillas de ruedas; Visitas turísticas; Transporte en taxi; Servicios de tranvías; Corretaje de transporte; Reservas de transporte; Servicios logísticos de transporte; Reservas de viajes; Alquiler de vehículos; Consultoría en viajes; Organización de tours; Servicios de guías de viaje; Servicios de guías de viajes; Organización de tours; Servicios de reservas para viajes; Servicios de acompañamiento turístico; Información de viajes; Organización de viajes; Servicios de viajes en cruceros; Organización y realización de peregrinajes y viajes de peregrinación (viajes); Servicios de reserva de billetes de viaje; Servicios de agentes de viajes para organizar viajes; Acompañamiento de viajeros; Transporte de equipaje de pasajeros; Servicios de emisión de billetes de viaje; Agencias de reservas de viajes; Organización de viajes; Preparación de visados de viajes, pasaportes y documentos de viaje para personas que viajan al extranjero; Servicios de reservas para visitas turísticas; Concertación y organización de visitas turísticas (excursiones); Servicios de consultoría en materia de viajes prestados mediante centros de atención telefónica y líneas directas de atención telefónica; Suministro de información sobre itinerarios de viaje; Alquiler de máquinas de emisión de billetes de viaje; Consultoría para la planificación de rutas de viajes; Suministro de información sobre viajes mediante redes mundiales; Organización de transporte para circuitos turísticos; Coordinación de planes de viajes para particulares y para grupos; Servicios de transporte para visitas turísticas; Organización de visitas y excursiones turísticas; Organización y servicios de organización de excursiones; Facilitación de vehículos para realizar giras turísticas y excursiones; Organización de excursiones como parte de paquetes de vacaciones; Servicios de guía de viajes organizados; Planificación y organización de visitas turísticas guiadas y excursiones de un día; Suministro de información a turistas sobre excursiones y visitas turísticas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Transport; Huvireiside transpordi korraldamine; Õhutransport; Lennukite rent; Kiirabitransport, sanitaartransport; Soomustransport; Merereiside korraldamine; Ringreiside korraldus; Praamitransport; Paadilaenutus; Paatide hoiustamine, ladustamine; Laevatransport, laevaveod; Kohtade ettetellimine, reserveerimine reisidele; Villimisteenused; Bussitransport, -veod; Autode parkimine; Autorent, autode rent; Autotransport, -veod; Voorivedu, küütimine; Autojuhiteenused; Kulleriteenused [sõnumite või kaupade edasitoimetamine]; Kaupade kohale-, kättetoimetamine; Reisijate saatmine, eskortteenused; Praamitransport, -veod, -vedu; Garaažide üürimine, rentimine; Hobuste rentimine; Busside rent; Parkimiskohtade üürimine; Reisiteenused ja reisijate transport; Elektrooniliselt talletatud andmete või dokumentide füüsiline säilitamine; Transport lõbusõidulaevadega; Pakikandmine; Sõidukite katusepakiraamide üürimine, laenutus; Ladude üürimine, rentimine; Ratastoolide üürimine, rentimine, laenutus; Vaatamisväärsustega tutvumine [turism]; Taksoteenused; Trammitransport; Transpordimaaklerlus, transpordivahendus, vedudevahendus, veovahendus; Transpordi, sõidukite ettetellimine, reserveerimine; Transpordilogistika; Reiside reserveerimine, ettetellimine; Sõidukite üürimine, laenutus, rentimine; Reisinõustamine; Reisioperaatoriteenused; Reisijuhi teenused; Reisisaatjateenused; Reisioperaatoriteenused; Reisibroneerimisteenused; Turismigiidi teenused; Reisiinfo; Reiside korraldamine; Kruiisilaevade teenused; Palverännakute ja reiside (väljasõitude) korraldamine ja läbiviimine; Reisipiletite reserveerimisteenused; Reisibüroode reiside korraldamise teenused; Reisijate saatmine, eskortteenused; Reisijate pagasi transport; Reisipiletiteenused; Reisibroneerimisbürood; Reiside korraldamine; Isikute reisiviisade, passide ja reisidokumentide korraldamine reisimiseks välismaal; Ringreisi reserveerimisteenused; Huvireisikorraldus; Reisikonsultatsioon telefonikõnekeskuste ja -abiliinide kaudu; Reisiotstarbeliste sõidujuhiste pakkumine; Sõidupileteid väljastavate müügiautomaatide rentimine; Nõustamine reisimarsruutide planeerimiseks; Reisiinfo pakkumine globaalsete võrkude kaudu; Huvireiside transpordi korraldamine; Reisikorralduse koordineerimine üksikisikutele ja rühmadele; Transporditeenused vaatamisväärsustega tutvumiseks; Huvireiside, vaatamisväärsustega tutvumiste korraldamine; Väljasõitude organiseerimine ja korraldamine; Ringreisi- ja ekskursioonisõidukite pakkumine; Ekskursioonide korraldamine paketireiside osana; Turismireiside korraldamine; Ekskursioonide ja päevareiside planeerimine ja korraldamine; Ekskursioonide ja ringreiside teave turistidele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kuljetus; Kuljetuksen järjestäminen kiertomatkoille; Ilmakuljetus; Ilmakulkuneuvojen vuokraus; Ambulanssikuljetus; Panssariautokuljetus; Risteilyjen järjestäminen; Retkien järjestäminen; Proomukuljetus; Veneiden vuokraus; Veneiden varastointi; Venekuljetus; Matkojen paikanvaraukset; Pullotuspalvelut; Bussikuljetus; Autojen pysäköinti; Autonvuokraus; Kuljetuspalvelut autolla; Kuljetus rattailla; Autonkuljettajapalvelut; Kuriiripalvelut [viestien tai tavaroiden toimitukseen]; Jakelu [toimitus]; Matkustajien saattopalvelut; Autolauttakuljetus; Autotallivuokraus; Hevosten vuokraus; Vaunujen (Rautatie -) vuokraus; Paikoitusalueiden vuokraus; Matkustuspalvelut ja matkustajien kuljetus; Elektronisesti tallennettujen tietojen ja asiakirjojen fyysinen varastointi; Huvijahtikuljetus; Kantajapalvelut; Ajoneuvojen kattotelineiden vuokraus; Varastojen vuokraus; Pyörätuolien vuokraus; Kiertoajelujen järjestäminen; Taksikuljetukset; Raitiotiekuljetus; Kuljetusvälitys; Kuljetusvaraus; Kuljetuslogistiikka; Matkojen varaaminen; Ajoneuvojen vuokraus; Matkailuneuvonta; Kiertomatkojen järjestäminen; Matkaopaspalvelut; Matkaoppaan palvelut; Kiertomatkojen järjestäminen; Matkanvarauspalvelut; Matkailijoiden saattopalvelut; Matkailuneuvonta; Matkojen järjestäminen; Laivaristeilypalvelut; Pyhiinvaellusten ja pyhiinvaellusmatkojen järjestäminen ja toteuttaminen (matkailu); Matkalippujen varauspalvelut; Matkatoimistopalvelut matkojen järjestämiseksi; Matkustajien saattopalvelut; Matkustajien matkatavaroiden kuljetus; Matkalippujen kirjoituspalvelut; Matkavaraustoimistot; Matkojen järjestäminen; Matkustusviisumien, passien ja matkustusasiakirjojen järjestäminen ulkomaille matkustaville henkilöille; Kiertomatkojen varauspalvelut; Matkojen järjestäminen ja toteuttaminen; Puhelinpalvelukeskusten ja puhelinpalvelulinjojen tarjoama konsultointi matkojen alalla; Ajo-ohjeiden tarjoaminen matkustustarkoituksiin; Matkalippuautomaattien vuokraus; Matkareittien suunnittelua koskeva konsultointi; Matkailutietojen tarjoaminen maailmanlaajuisten verkkojen välityksellä; Kuljetuksen järjestäminen kiertomatkoille; Yksityisten ihmisten ja ryhmien matkajärjestelyjen koordinointi; Kuljetuspalvelut kiertoajeluja varten; Kiertoajelujen ja tutustumiskäyntien vetäminen; Retkien organisointi ja järjestäminen; Ajoneuvojen tarjoaminen kiertomatkoja ja tutustumisretkiä varten; Tutustumisretkien järjestäminen pakettimatkojen osana; Kiertomatkojen ohjaaminen; Kiertoajelujen ja päivämatkojen suunnittelu ja järjestäminen; Tutustumisretkiin ja nähtävyyksien katseluun liittyvien tietojen tarjoaminen matkailijoille.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Transports; Organisation de transports dans le cadre de circuits touristiques; Transports aériens; Location d'aéronefs; Transport en ambulance; Transport en véhicules blindés; Organisation de croisières; Organisation de voyages; Transport en chaland; Location de bateaux; Entreposage de bateaux; Transport en bateau; Réservation de places de voyage; Mise en bouteilles; Services d'autobus; Services de parcs de stationnement; Location de voitures; Transport en automobile; Charroi; Services de chauffeurs; Messagerie [courrier ou marchandises]; Distribution [livraison]; Accompagnement de voyageurs; Transport en navire transbordeur; Location de garages; Location de chevaux; Location d'autocars; Location de places de stationnement; Voyages et transport de passagers; Entreposage de supports de données ou de documents stockés électroniquement; Services de bateaux de plaisance; Portage; Location de galeries pour véhicules; Location d'entrepôts; Location de fauteuils roulants; Visites touristiques; Transport en taxi; Services de trams; Courtage de transport; Réservations pour le transport; Services de logistique en matière de transport; Réservations pour les voyages; Location de véhicules; Services de conseils en voyages; Organisation d'excursions, de visites touristiques et de voyages; Services de guide de voyage; Services d'accompagnement de mineurs voyageant seuls; Organisation d'excursions, de visites touristiques et de voyages; Services de réservation de voyages; Services d'accompagnement touristique; Informations en matière de voyages; Organisation de voyages; Services de croisières; Organisation et réalisation d'itinéraires et de voyages de pèlerinage (voyages); Services de réservation de billets de voyage; Services d'agences de voyages pour l'organisation de voyages; Accompagnement de voyageurs; Transport de bagages de passagers; Services de billets de voyage; Agences de réservation de voyage; Organisation de voyages; Préparation de visas et de documents de voyage pour les personnes se rendant à l'étranger; Services de réservation d'excursions; Exploitation et organisation d'excursions; Services de conseils en matière de voyages fournis par des centres d'appels téléphoniques et des lignes d'assistance téléphonique; Informations en matière d'itinéraires routiers; Location de machines émettant des billets de voyage; Assistance en matière de planification d'itinéraires; Mise à disposition d'informations en matière de voyages via des réseaux mondiaux; Organisation de transports dans le cadre de circuits touristiques; Coordination de préparatifs de voyages individuels et de groupe; Services de transport pour visites touristiques; Conduite de circuits et d'itinéraires de visite; Organisation et gestion d'excursions; Mise à disposition de véhicules pour des visites et des excursions; Préparation d'excursions dans le cadre de voyages organisés; Encadrement d'excursions, de visites touristiques et de voyages; Planification et préparation de visites touristiques guidées et de sorties à la journée; Mise à disposition d'informations aux touristes en matière d'excursions et de visites touristiques guidées.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Prijevoz; Organiziranje ekskurzija; Prijevoz zrakom; Iznajmljivanje letjelica; Hitna pomoć (prijevoz kolima hitne pomoći); Prijevoz u blindiranim vozilima; Organiziranje krstarenja; Organiziranje izleta; Prijevoz teglenicama; Iznajmljivanje čamaca; Skladištenje čamaca; Prijevoz brodom; Rezerviranje mjesta za putovanje; Usluge punjenja boca; Prijevoz autobusom; Parkiranje vozila; Iznajmljivanje automobila; Usluge prijevoza automobilima; Prijevoz kolicima; Usluge vozača; Dostavljačke usluge [prijevoz pošte ili robe]; Predaja [dostava]; Pratnja putnika; Trajektni prijevoz; Iznajmljivanje garaže; Iznajmljivanje konja; Iznajmljivanje autobusa; Iznajmljivanje parkirališnih mjesta; Putovanje i prijevoz putnika; Fizičko skladištenje elektronički pohranjenih podataka i dokumenata; Razonoda na brodu (usluge brodova za razonodu); Nošenje [prtljage]; Iznajmljivanje prtljažnih nosača za automobile; Iznajmljivanje skladišta; Iznajmljivanje invalidskih kolica; Turističke posjete; Taksi-usluge; Tramvajske usluge; Posredovanje u prijevozu; Prijevoz (rezervacije za prijevoz); Logističke usluge u svezi s prijevozom; Putovanja (rezervacije za putovanja); Zakup [čarter] vozila; Konzultantske usluge koje se odnose na putovanja; Vođenje izleta; Usluge turističkog vođenja; Putničke dostavljačke usluge; Vođenje izleta; Usluge rezerviranja putovanja; Usluge pratnje putnika na putovanjima; Putne obavijesti; Organiziranje putovanja; Usluge krstarenja brodom; Organizacija i provođenje hodočašća i hodočasničkih putovanja (putovanja); Usluge rezervacije putnih karata; Usluge turističke agencije za organiziranje putovanja; Pratnja putnika; Prijevoz prtljage putnika; Usluge izdavanja karata za putovanje; Agencije za rezerviranje putovanja; Organiziranje putovanja; Pripremanje putnih viza i putnih dokumenata za osobe koje putuju u inozemstvo; Usluge rezervacije za izlete; Organizacija izletničkih putovanja; Konzultantske usluge u području putovanja koje se pružaju putem telefonskih pozivnih centara i linija za pomoć; Davanje prometnih uputa u svrhe putovanja; Iznajmljivanje strojeva za izdavanje putnih karata; Savjetovanje vezano uz planiranje rute putovanja; Pružanje informacija o putovanjima putem globalnih mreža; Organiziranje ekskurzija; Koordiniranje putnih aranžmana za pojedince i za grupe; Usluge prijevoza za turističke ture; Vođenje obilaznih tura i vožnji; Organizacija i priređivanje izleta; Pružanje vozila za ture i ekskurzije; Organizacija ekskurzija kao dio putnih aranžmana; Usluge turističkog vođenja; Planiranje i organizacija tura razgledavanja i dnevnih izleta; Pružanje informacija turistima o ekskurzijama i razgledavanju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szállítás; Kirándulások, túrák, társasutazások szervezése; Légi szállítás; Repülőgép kölcsönzés; Betegszállítás; Páncélautós szállítás; Hajóutak szervezése; Túrák szervezése; Szállítás uszállyal; Hajók, csónakok kölcsönzése; Vízi járművek tárolása; Vízi járművel történő szállítás; Helyfoglalás (utazás); Palackozási szolgáltatások; Autóbuszok működtetése; Parkolási szolgáltatások; Autókölcsönzés; Autószállítás; Fuvarozás szekérrel, talicskával; Sofőrszolgáltatás; Futárszolgálatok [üzenetek vagy áruk küldésére]; Szállítás [kézbesítés]; Utaskísérés; Komphajón történő szállítás; Garázsok bérlése; Lovak kölcsönzése; Autóbuszkölcsönzés; Parkolóhelyek bérbeadása; Utazás és utasok szállítása; Elektronikusan tárolt adatok és dokumentumok (fizikai) tárolása; Sétahajó szolgáltatások; Teherhordás [hordár szolgáltatások]; Gépkocsi tetőcsomagtartók kölcsönzése; Raktárak bérbeadása; Tolószékek kölcsönzése; Városnézés [turizmus]; Taxi szolgáltatások; Villamosközlekedés; Szállítási ügynökség; Helyfoglalás szállítással kapcsolatban; Szállítási logisztikai szolgáltatások; Helyfoglalás utazással kapcsolatban; Járművek kölcsönzése és bérbeadása; Utazási szaktanácsadás; Körutak, túrák lebonyolítása; Idegenvezetői szolgáltatások; Kiskorúak kísérése utazás során; Körutak, túrák lebonyolítása; Utazásfoglalási szolgáltatások; Turistakísérő szolgáltatások; Utazási információ; Utazásszervezés, kirándulásszervezés; Tengeri hajóút szolgáltatások; Zarándokutak és utazások (kirándulások) szervezése és lebonyolítása; Utazási jegyeladási szolgáltatások; Utazási irodai szolgáltatások utazás megszervezésére; Utaskísérés; Utasok csomagjainak szállítása; Jegyeladási szolgáltatások utazáshoz; Utazásfoglalási ügynökségek; Utazásszervezés, kirándulásszervezés; Turistavízumok, útlevelek és utazási okmányok beszerzése külföldre utazók számára; Foglalási szolgáltatások kirándulásokhoz, utazásokhoz; Utazások szervezése; Telefonos ügyfélszolgálatok és segélyvonalak révén történő szaktanácsadás az utazás területén; Autós útbaigazítás nyújtása utazáshoz; Utazásokhoz jegyeket kiadó gépek bérbeadása; Útvonal tervezési tanácsadás utazáshoz; Utazási információk biztosítása globális hálózatokon keresztül; Kirándulások, túrák, társasutazások szervezése; Utazás koordinálása egyének és csoportok számára; Szállítási szolgáltatások városnéző körutakhoz; Városnéző túrák és kirándulások vezetése; Kirándulások szervezése és megtartása; Járművek túrákhoz és kirándulásokhoz való biztosítása; Kirándulások szervezése üdülési csomagok részeként; Idegenvezetés; Városnéző körutak és egynapos kirándulások tervezése és szervezése; Kirándulásokkal és városnézéssel kapcsolatos tájékoztatás turisták számára.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Trasporto; Organizzazione di trasporti per giri turistici; Trasporti aeronautici; Noleggio di aerei; Trasporto in ambulanza; Trasporto di valori in veicoli blindati; Organizzazione di crociere; Organizzazione di tour; Trasporto in chiatta; Noleggio di battelli; Deposito di barche; Trasporto in battello; Prenotazione di posti di viaggio; Servizi di imbottigliamento; Servizi di autobus; Servizi di parcheggi; Noleggio di automobili; Trasporto in automobile; Trasporto con carretti; Servizi di autisti; Servizi di corriere [corrispondenza o merci]; Consegna [distribuzione]; Accompagnamento di viaggiatori; Trasporto in nave traghetto; Noleggio di rimesse; Noleggio di cavalli; Affitto di pullman; Noleggio di posti di parcheggio; Viaggi e traporto di passeggeri; Immagazzinamento di supporti dati o di documenti memorizzati sotto forma elettronica; Servizi di battelli da diporto; Facchinaggio; Noleggio di portabagagli per veicoli; Noleggio di magazzini; Noleggio di sedie a rotelle; Visite turistiche; Servizi di taxi; Servizi di tram; Mediazione nel trasporto; Prenotazioni per il trasporto; Organizzazione di trasporti; Prenotazioni per i viaggi; Noleggio di veicoli; Consulenze inerenti i viaggi; Organizzazione di tour; Servizi di guide turistiche; Servizi di guida per viaggi; Organizzazione di tour; Servizi per la prenotazione di un viaggio; Servizi d'accompagnamento turistico; Informazioni sui viaggi; Organizzazione di viaggi; Servizi di navi da crociera; Organizzazione e realizzazione di pellegrinaggi e viaggi di pellegrinaggio (viaggi); Servizi di prenotazione di biglietti per viaggi; Servizi di agenti di viaggio per l'organizzazione di viaggi; Accompagnamento di viaggiatori; Trasporto di passeggeri e dei relativi bagagli; Servizi di emissione di biglietti per viaggi; Agenzie di prenotazione di viaggi; Organizzazione di viaggi; Organizzazione di visti di viaggio, passaporti e documenti di viaggio per persone che viaggiano all'estero; Prenotazione di viaggi; Organizzazione di viaggi; Consulenze in materia di viaggi fornite da call center e sportelli telefonici; Fornitura di indicazioni stradali per i viaggi; Noleggio di macchine di emissione di biglietti per viaggi; Consulenza relativa alla pianificazione di percorsi di viaggio; Messa a disposizione di informazioni di viaggio tramite reti globali; Organizzazione di trasporti per giri turistici; Coordinamento dell'organizzazione di viaggi per singoli e gruppi; Servizi di trasporto per visite turistiche; Conduzione di visite e gite guidate; Allestimento e organizzazione di gite; Fornitura di veicoli per tour ed escursioni; Organizzazione di escursioni nell'ambito di pacchetti vacanza; Conduzione di viaggi turistici; Pianificazione e organizzazione di visite turistiche e gite in giornata; Fornitura di informazioni a turisti inerenti escursioni e visite turistiche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vežimas; Transporto parūpinimas turistinėms kelionėms; Oro transportas; Orlaivių nuoma; Sanitarinis transportas; Šarvuotųjų automobilių transportas; Jūrų kelionių rengimas; Turų organizavimas; Gabenimas baržomis; Valčių nuoma; Valčių sandėliavimas; Laivų transportas; Vietų užsakymas [kelionėms]; Išpilstymo į butelius paslaugos; Autobusų transportas; Automobilių statymas; Automobilių nuoma; Automobilių transportas; Vežimas kinkomuoju transportu; Samdomų vairuotojų paslaugos; Kurjerių paslaugos [pranešimai ar prekės]; Įteikimas (pristatymas); Turistų lydėjimas; Keltų transportas; Garažų nuoma; Arklių nuoma; Turistinių autobusų nuoma; Automobilių stovėjimo vietų nuoma; Kelionės ir keleivių vežimas; Fizinis elektroninių duomenų ar dokumentų saugojimas; Iškylos valtimis; Krovinių nešiojimas; Transporto priemonių stogo bagažinių nuoma; Sandėlių nuoma; Ligonių vežiojimo kėdžių nuoma; Ekskursijos [turistinės]; Taksi transportas; Tramvajų transportas; Transporto tarpininkavimas; Vežiojimų užsakymas; Transporto logistika; Kelionių užsakymai; Transporto priemonių nuoma; Konsultacijos kelionių klausimais; Kelionių (ekskursijų) rengimas; Kelionių gido paslaugos; Kelionių gidų paslaugos; Kelionių (ekskursijų) rengimas; Kelionių užsakymo paslaugos; Turistų lydėjimo paslaugos; Kelionių informacija; Kelionių organizavimas; Kruizinių laivų paslaugos; Piligrimų išvykų ir kelionių (kelionių) organizavimas ir vedimas; Kelionių bilietų išankstinis užsakymas; Kelionių agentų paslaugos, susijusios su kelionių rengimu; Turistų lydėjimas; Keleivių bagažo vežimas; Kelionių bilietų paslaugos; Kelionių užsakymo agentūros; Kelionių organizavimas; Kelionės vizų ir kelionės dokumentų rengimas keliaujantiems į užsienį; Turų užsakymo paslaugos; Kelionių rengimas; Telefono skambučių centrų ir karštųjų linijų teikiamos kelionių konsultacijos; Vairavimo maršrutų teikimas kelionėms; Kelionės bilietus išduodančių automatų nuoma; Kelionių maršrutų planavimo konsultacijos; Informacijos apie keliones teikimas pasauliniais tinklais; Transporto parūpinimas turistinėms kelionėms; Individualių ir grupių kelionių rengimo koordinavimas; Pažintinių ekskursijų transporto paslaugos; Apžvalginių išvykų ir kelionių vedimas; Išvykų organizavimas ir rengimas; Transporto priemonių parūpinimas kelionėms ir ekskursijoms; Ekskursijų kaip poilsinių kelionių paketų dalies rengimas; Turų vedimas; Apžvalginių ir vienos dienos kelionių planavimas ir rengimas; Su ekskursijomis ir apžvalginėmis kelionėmis susijusios informacijos teikimas turistams.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Transporta pakalpojumi; Transporta pakalpojumu nodrošināšana ekskursantiem; Gaisa pārvadājumi; Lidaparātu iznomāšana; Ātrās palīdzības transporta pakalpojumi; Bruņu transporta pakalpojumi; Jūras braucienu organizēšana; Tūrisma braucienu organizēšana; Liellaivu pārvadājumi; Kuģu iznomāšana; Laivu uzglabāšana; Pārvadājumi ar ūdenstransportu; Vietu rezervēšana ceļojumiem; Iepildīšana pudelēs; Autobusu pārvadājumi; Autostāvvietu pakalpojumi; Automašīnu iznomāšana; Autopārvadājumi; Pajūgu transporta pakalpojumi; Šoferu pakalpojumi; Ziņojumu vai preču piegāde ar kurjeru; Piegāde [preču piegāde]; Ceļotāju pavadīšanas pakalpojumi; Prāmju un laivu transporta pakalpojumi; Garāžu iznomāšana; Zirgu iznomāšana; Tālsatiksmes autobusu iznomāšana; Autostāvvietu iznomāšana; Ceļotāju un pasažieru pārvadāšana; Elektroniski uzkrātu datu vai dokumentu fiziskā uzglabāšana; Pārvadājumi ar izpriecu kuģiem; Mantu pārnešanas pakalpojumi; Transportlīdzekļu nojumju noma; Noliktavu iznomāšana; Ratiņkrēslu iznomāšana; Ievērojamu vietu apskates organizēšana (tūrisma pakalpojumi); Taksometru pakalpojumi; Tramvaju pakalpojumi; Starpniecība pārvadājumu jomā; Transportlīdzekļu rezervēšana; Transporta loģistikas pakalpojumi; Ceļojumu rezervēšana; Transportlīdzekļu iznomāšana; Ceļojumu konsultācijas; Tūrisma braucienu nodrošināšana; Ceļojumu vadītāju pakalpojumi; Ceļotāju pavadoņu pakalpojumi; Tūrisma braucienu nodrošināšana; Ceļojumu rezervēšanas pakalpojumi; Tūristu pavadoņu pakalpojumi; Informācijas sniegšana ceļojumu jomā; Ceļojumu organizēšana; Izpriecu ceļojumu kuģu pakalpojumi; Svētceļojumu organizēšana un realizēšana (ceļojumu sagatavošana); Ceļojumu biļešu rezervēšana; Ceļojumu aģentūru pakalpojumi ceļojumu sagatavošanā; Ceļotāju pavadīšanas pakalpojumi; Pasažieru bagāžas pārvadāšana; Ceļojumu biļešu nodrošināšanas pakalpojumi; Ceļojumu rezervēšanas aģentūras; Ceļojumu organizēšana; Ceļojumu vīzu, pasu un ceļojumu dokumentu kārtošana cilvēkiem, kas ceļo uz ārzemēm; Tūrisma braucienu rezervēšanas pakalpojumi; Ceļojumu sagatavošana; Konsultācijas par ceļošanu, kas nodrošinātas ar telefona zvanu centru un izziņu līniju starpniecību; Braukšanas norādījumu sniegšana autoceļotājiem; Ceļojuma biļešu izsniegšanas iekārtu noma; Konsultācijas par ceļojuma maršrutu plānošanu; Piekļuves nodrošināšana ceļojumu informācijas globālajā tīklā; Transporta pakalpojumu nodrošināšana ekskursantiem; Ceļojumu organizēšanas koordinēšana indivīdiem un grupām; Transporta pakalpojumi ievērojamu vietu apskatei; Ievērojamu apskates vietu braucienu apskates braucienu vadīšana; Ekskursiju organizēšana un rīkošana; Transportlīdzekļu nodrošināšana braucieniem un ekskursijām; Ekskursiju rīkošana kā komplekso tūrisma braucienu daļa; Ceļojumu vadīšana; Ievērojamu vietu apskatīšanas un vienas dienas braucienu plānošana un rīkošana; Informācijas sniegšana tūristiem saistībā ar ekskursijām un ievērojamu vietu apskatīšanu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Trasport; L-organizzazzjoni ta' eskursjonijiet; Trasport bl-ajru; Kiri ta' ajruplani; Trasport bl-ambulanza; Trasport b'karozza armata bl-armi; L-arranġament ta' kruċieri; Organizzazzjoni ta' turs; It-trasportazzjoni ta' barkun; Kiri ta' dgħajjes; Il-ħżin ta' dgħajjes; Trasport bid-dgħajjes; Prenotazzjoni ta' siġġijiet għall-ivvjaġġar; Servizzi ta' bbottiljar; Trasport bil-karozza tal-linja; L-ipparkjar ta' karrozzi; Servizzi ta' għoti ta' karozzi fuq kiri; Servizzi ta' trasport bil-karozza; Il-ġarr permezz ta' karrettun; Servizzi ta' xufier; Servizzi ta' kurrier [messaġġi jew merkanzija]; Konsenja [konsenja]; L-iskortar tal-vjaġġaturi; Trasport bil-laneċ; Il-kiri ta' garaxxijiet; Kiri ta' żwiemel; Kiri ta' kowċis; Kiri ta' postijiet għall-parkeġġ; Trasportazzjoni minn post għall-ieħor tal-passiġġieri; Il-ħażna fiżika ta' data maħżuna elettronikament jew ta' dokumenti; Trasport bid-dgħajjes tad-divertiment; Il-ġarr tal-bagalji tal-passiġġieri; Kiri ta' xtillieri ta' fuq is-saqaf tal-vetturi; Kiri ta' mħażen; Il-kiri ta' siġġijiet bir-roti; Żjarat ta' postijiet ta' interess [turiżmu]; Trasport bit-taksi; Trasport bit-tramm; Senserija tat-trasport; Riservazzjoni ta' trasport; Loġistika tat-trasportazzjoni; Reservazzjoni ta' l-ivvjaġġar; Il-kiri ta' vetturi; Konsulenza dwar l-ivvjaġġar; Tmexxija ta' turs; Servizzi ta' gwida [tal-ivvjaġġar]; Servizzi ta' kurjer tal-ivvjaġġar; Tmexxija ta' turs; Servizzi ta' prenotazzjoni tal-ivvjaġġar; Servizzi ta' akkumpanjament turistiku; Tagħrif dwar l-ivvjaġġar; Arranġamenti għall-ivvjaġġar; Servizzi ta' vapur tal-kruċieri; Organizzazzjoni u twettiq ta' pellegrinaġġi u vjaġġi ta' pellegrini (vjaġġi); Servizzi ta' riservazzjoni tal-biljetti tal-ivvjaġġar; Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-vjaġġi għall-arranġament tal-ivvjaġġar; L-iskortar tal-vjaġġaturi; Trasportazzjoni ta' bagalji tal-passiġġieri; Servizzi ta' biljetti għall-ivvjaġġar; Aġenziji tal-prenotazzjoni tal-ivvjaġġar; Arranġamenti għall-ivvjaġġar; L-arranġament ta' viżas għall-ivvjaġġar, passaporti u dokumenti tal-ivvjaġġar għall-persuni li se jivvjaġġaw barra mill-pajjiż; Servizzi ta' prenotazzjoni għall-ġiti; Arranġamenti u l-organizzar ta' tours; Konsulenza fil-qasam tal-ivvjaġġar ipprovduta minn ċentri tat-telefonati u hotlines; Forniment ta' direzzjonijiet għas-sewqan għall-finijiet ta' vvjaġġar; Kiri ta' magni li joħorġu biljetti tal-ivvjaġġar; Konsulenza dwar l-ippjanar ta' rotot tal-ivvjaġġar; Provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar vjaġġi permezz ta' netwerks globali; L-organizzazzjoni ta' eskursjonijiet; Koordinazzjoni ta' arranġamenti għall-ivvjaġġar għal individwi u għal gruppi; Servizzi ta' trasport għal ġiti ta' turisti; Tmexxija ta' ġiti u vjaġġi turistiċi; Organizzazzjoni u arranġamenti ta' ħarġiet; Provvista ta' vetturi għal ġiti u eskursjonijiet; Organizzazzjoni ta' eskursjonijiet bħala parti minn pakketti ta' btajjel; Tmexxija ta' ġiti; Ippjanar u organizzazzjoni ta' żjarat turistiċi u ġiti ta' ġurnata; Provvista ta' informazzjoni lit-turisti dwar eskursjonijiet u ġiti turistiċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Transport; Organisatie van georganiseerde reizen; Transport door de lucht; Verhuur van luchtvaartuigen; Ambulancevervoer; Transport per gepantserd voertuig; Organisatie van cruises; Organisatie van reizen; Vervoer per aak; Verhuur van boten; Opslag van boten; Vervoer per boot; Plaatsreservering voor reizen; Bottelen; Autobusdiensten; Diensten van parkeerterreinen; Verhuur van automobielen; Transport per automobiel; Vervoer per kar; Chauffeursdiensten; Koeriersdiensten [post of goederen]; Bezorging [levering]; Begeleiding van reizigers; Veerpontdiensten; Verhuur van garages; Verhuur van paarden; Verhuur van touringcars; Verhuur van parkeerplaatsen; Reizigersvervoer; Fysieke opslag van elektronisch bewaarde gegevens of documenten; Plezierbootdiensten; Kruiersdiensten; Verhuur van imperialen; Verhuur van opslagruimten; Verhuur van rolstoelen; Toeristische rondleidingen; Vervoer per taxi; Tramdiensten; Transportmakelaardij; Transportreservering; Logistieke diensten op het gebied van transport; Reisreservering; Verhuur van voertuigen; Advisering op het gebied van reizen; Organisatie van reizen; Diensten op het gebied van reisbegeleiding; Reisgidsen; Organisatie van reizen; Diensten op het gebied van het boeken van reizen; Begeleiding van toeristen; Reisinformatie; Organisatie van reizen; Diensten op het gebied van cruiseschepen; Het organiseren en houden van pelgrimstochten en -reizen (reizen); Reservering van reistickets; Reisagentschappen voor het organiseren van reizen; Begeleiding van reizigers; Transport van passagiers en hun bagage; Ticketverkoop voor reizen; Agentschappen voor het boeken van reizen; Organisatie van reizen; Regelen van reisvisa en reisdocumenten voor personen die naar het buitenland reizen; Reserveringen van excursies; Organisatie van excursies; Advisering op het gebied van reizen door callcenters en meldpunten; Verschaffen van route-informatie voor reisdoeleinden; Verhuur van machines die plaatsbewijzen uitgeven voor reizen; Raadgeving met betrekking tot het plannen van reisroutes; Terbeschikkingstelling van reisinformatie via wereldwijde netwerken; Organisatie van georganiseerde reizen; Het coördineren van reisarrangementen voor individuele personen en groepen; Transportdiensten voor toeristische rondleidingen; Het verzorgen van toeristische trips en reizen; Het organiseren en houden van excursies; Verschaffen van voertuigen voor rondleidingen en excursies; Organisatie van excursies in het kader van pakketreizen; Het begeleiden van rondreizen; Planning en organisatie van excursies en dagtochten; Informatieverstrekking aan toeristen met betrekking tot excursies en begeleide tours.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Transport; Usługi w zakresie organizowania transportu dla wycieczek; Powietrzny (Transport -); Wynajem statków powietrznych; Transport karetkami ratunkowymi; Transport samochodami opancerzonymi; Organizowanie rejsów; Organizowanie wycieczek; Transport barkami; Wynajem łodzi; Przechowywanie łodzi; Transport łodziami; Rezerwacja miejsc na podróż; Usługi butelkowania; Transport autobusowy; Parkowanie samochodów; Wynajem samochodów; Usługi transportu samochodami silnikowymi; Przewożenie; Usługi kierowców; Usługi kurierskie [wiadomości lub towary]; Dostawa [dostarczanie towarów]; Eskortowanie podróżnych; Transport promowy; Wynajmowanie garaży; Wynajmowanie koni; Wynajem autokarów; Wynajmowanie miejsc parkingowych; Transport pasażerski; Magazynowanie elektronicznych nośników danych lub dokumentów; Transport łodziami spacerowymi; Przenoszenie, przewóz bagaży; Wypożyczanie samochodowych bagażników dachowych; Wynajmowanie magazynów; Wypożyczanie wózków inwalidzkich; Zwiedzanie turystyczne; Usługi taksówek; Transport tramwajowy; Maklerstwo transportowe; Rezerwacja transportu; Logistyka transportu; Rezerwacja miejsc na podróż; Pojazdy (Wypożyczanie -); Doradztwo w zakresie podróży; Prowadzenie wycieczek; Usługi przewodników turystycznych; Usługi w zakresie pilotów wycieczek; Prowadzenie wycieczek; Usługi w zakresie rezerwowania podróży; Usługi pilotażu turystycznego; Udzielanie informacji dotyczących podróży; Organizowanie podróży; Usługi w zakresie rejsów statkami wycieczkowymi; Organizacja i realizacja pielgrzymek i wyjazdów (podróże); Usługi rezerwacji biletów na podróż; Usługi agencji podróży polegające na organizowaniu podróży; Eskortowanie podróżnych; Transport bagażu podróżnego; Usługi w zakresie biletów na podróż; Agencje rezerwacji podróży; Organizowanie podróży; Organizacja wiz podróżnych, paszportów i dokumentów na podróż dla osób wyjeżdżających za granicę; Usługi w zakresie rezerwacji wycieczek; Organizowanie wycieczek; Doradztwo w dziedzinie podróży świadczone przez centra obsługi telefonicznej i infolinie; Udzielanie wskazówek o trasie dojazdu do celów podróży; Wynajem maszyn wydających bilety na podróż; Doradztwo w zakresie planowania trasy podróży; Dostarczanie informacji o podróżach za pośrednictwem ogólnoświatowych sieci; Usługi w zakresie organizowania transportu dla wycieczek; Koordynowanie planów podróży dla osób prywatnych i grup; Usługi transportu na wycieczki ze zwiedzaniem; Zarządzanie trasami zwiedzania i wycieczek; Organizacja i organizowanie wycieczek; Udostępnianie pojazdów na wycieczki i wyprawy; Organizowanie wypraw w ramach wakacji zorganizowanych; Oprowadzanie wycieczek; Planowanie i organizowanie wycieczek ze zwiedzaniem i wycieczek jednodniowych; Udzielanie informacji turystom związanych z wyprawami i zwiedzaniem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Transporte; Organização de transporte para passeios turísticos; Transporte por via aérea; Aluguer de aeronaves; Transporte em ambulância; Transporte por veículos blindados; Organização de cruzeiros; Organização de viagens recreativas de grupo; Transporte em lancha [barcaça]; Aluguer de barcos; Depósito de barcos; Transporte por barco; Reserva de lugares para viagens; Serviços de engarrafamento de bebidas; Serviços de autocarros; Serviços de estacionamento de automóveis; Aluguer de automóveis; Transporte em automóveis; Transporte em charretes; Serviços de motoristas; Serviços de correio [mensagens ou mercadorias]; Expedição [entrega]; Acompanhamento de passageiros [viajantes]; Transporte em navio transbordador; Aluguer de garagens; Aluguer de cavalos; Aluguer de autocarros; Aluguer de lugares de estacionamento; Viagens e transporte de passageiros; Armazenamento físico de dados ou documentos guardados em suporte eletrónico; Serviços de barcos de recreio; Serviços de portes; Aluguer de tejadilhos para veículos; Aluguer de entrepostos; Aluguer de cadeiras de rodas; Visitas turísticas; Transporte por táxi; Serviços de carros elétricos; Corretagem de transporte; Reservas para transporte; Logística de transporte; Reservas para viagens; Aluguer de veículos; Consultadoria em viagens; Organização de visitas turísticas; Serviços de guias para viagens; Serviços de acompanhantes em viagens; Organização de visitas turísticas; Serviços para reservas de viagens; Serviços de acompanhamento turístico; Informações de viagens; Organização de viagens; Serviços de viagens em navios; Organização e realização de peregrinações e viagens; Serviços de reserva de bilhetes para viagens; Serviços de agência de viagens para a organização de viagens; Acompanhamento de passageiros [viajantes]; Transporte de bagagens de passageiros; Serviços de emissão de bilhetes para viagens; Agências de reservas de viagens; Organização de viagens; Obtenção de vistos, passaportes e documentos para viajar para pessoas que viajam ao estrangeiro; Serviços de reserva de visitas turísticas; Realização e organização de excursões; Consultadoria em matéria de viagens proporcionada através de centros de chamadas e linhas de assistência telefónica; Fornecimento de orientações para itinerários de viagem; Aluguer de máquinas de emissão de bilhetes para viagens; Consultadoria para planeamento de itinerários de viagens; Prestação de informações de viagem através de redes mundiais; Organização de transporte para passeios turísticos; Coordenação da organização de viagens para indivíduos e grupos; Serviços de transporte para visitas turísticas; Realização de visitas e viagens a locais de interesse turístico; Organização e realização de excursões; Disponibilização de veículos para visitas turísticas e excursões; Organização de excursões como parte do pacote de férias; Realização de excursões; Planeamento e organização de visitas turísticas e excursões; Disponibilização de informação a turistas sobre excursões e visitas turísticas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Transport; Organizare de excursii; Transport aeronautic; Închirierea de aeronave; Transport cu ambulanța; Transportul cu mașina blindată; Organizarea de croaziere; Organizarea tururilor; Lepuri (Transport cu -); Închirieri de bărci; Depozitarea ambarcațiunilor; Transport cu vaporul; Rezervare de locuri pentru călătorii [transporturi]; Servicii de îmbuteliere; Servicii de transport cu autobuzul; Parcare (Servicii de -); Închiriere de mașini; Servicii de transport cu automobile; Cărăușie; Șoferi (Servicii de -); Servicii de curierat [mesaje sau mărfuri]; Furnizare [livrare]; Însoțirea de călători; Transport cu feribotul; Închiriere de garaje; Închiriere de cai; Închiriere de autobuze; Închirierea de locuri de parcare; Transportul pasagerilor; Suporturi fizice de stocare a datelor sau a documentelor electronice; Transport pe vase de agrement; Hamalâc; Închirierea de portbagaje de capotă pentru vehicule; Închirierea de depozite; Închirierea de fotolii rulante; Vizitarea obiectivelor turistice; Servicii de taxi; Transport cu tramvaiul; Curtaj de transport; Transport (Rezervări pentru -); Logistică de transport; Călătorii (Rezervări pentru -); Locație de vehicule; Consultanță în legătură cu călătoriile; Organizare de tururi; Servicii de ghid turistic; Servicii de ghizi pentru călătorii; Organizare de tururi; Servicii de rezervare pentru călătorii; Servicii de însoţire turistică; Informații de călătorie; Organizarea de călătorii; Servicii de croaziere; Organizare și susținere de excursii și călătorii în pelerinaj; Rezervare de bilete de călătorie; Servicii de agenție de turism pentru organizarea călătoriilor; Însoțirea de călători; Transport de bagaje ale pasagerilor; Servicii de emitere de bilete pentru călătorii; Agenții de rezervare a călătoriilor; Organizarea de călătorii; Rezolvarea formalităților pentru vize, pașapoarte și documente de călătorie pentru persoanele care călătoresc în străinătate; Servicii de rezervări de circuite turistice; Intermediere si organizare de circuite; Consultanță în domeniul călătoriilor, oferită de call center-uri și de hotline-uri; Furnizare de indicații rutiere pentru scopuri turistice; Închiriere de aparate care emit bilete de călătorie; Consultanță pentru planificarea de itinerarii; Furnizare de informații turistice prin rețele mondiale; Organizare de excursii; Coordonarea organizării de călătorii individuale și de grup; Servicii de transport pentru excursii turistice; Coordonare de tururi și excursii de vizitare a obiectivelor turistice; Organizare şi realizare de excursii; Furnizare de vehicule pentru tururi și excursii; Organizare de excursii incluse în pachetele de vacanță; Coordonare de tururi turistice; Planificare și organizare de tururi de oraș și de excursii de o zi; Furnizare de informații pentru turiști despre excursii și tururi de oraș.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Dopravné služby; Organizovanie turistickej dopravy; Letecká doprava; Prenájom leteckých dopravných prostriedkov; Prevoz sanitkou; Doprava pancierovými vozidlami; Organizovanie turistických plavieb; Organizovanie turistickej dopravy; Doprava nákladnými vlečnými člnmi; Prenajímanie plavidiel (člnov, lodí); Úschova lodí a člnov; Lodná doprava; Rezervácie miesteniek na cestovanie; Plnenie fliaš; Autobusová doprava; Parkovanie automobilov (služby); Prenájom automobilov; Automobilová doprava; Dovoz, doprava; Služby vodičov; Doručovacie služby (správy alebo tovar); Doručovanie [doručovanie tovaru]; Sprevádzanie turistov; Lodná trajektová doprava; Prenájom garáží; Prenájom koní; Prenájom autokarov; Prenájom miest na parkovanie; Cestovanie a osobná doprava; Skladovanie elektronicky uložených údajov a dokumentov; Výletné lode (služby); Nosenie batožín; Požičiavanie nosičov na automobily; Prenájom skladísk; Prenájom pojazdných kresiel; Turistické prehliadky; Taxislužba; Električková doprava; Sprostredkovanie dopravy; Rezervácie dopravy; Logistické služby v doprave; Rezervácie zájazdov; Prenájom vozidiel; Cestovné konzultácie; Organizovanie turistickej dopravy; Služby cestovných sprievodcov; Cestovné kuriérske služby; Organizovanie turistickej dopravy; Služby objednávania cestovania; Služby spojené so sprevádzaním turistov; Poskytovanie cestovných informácií; Zabezpečovanie cestovania; Služby okružnej cesty loďou; Organizácia a realizácia pútí a pútnických zájazdov (zájazdy); Rezervovanie cestovných lístkov; Služby cestovnej kancelárie v oblasti zabezpečovania cestovania; Sprevádzanie turistov; Preprava batožiny cestujúcich; Predaj cestovných lístkov; Služby agentúry pre objednávanie cestovania; Zabezpečovanie cestovania; Zabezpečovanie cestovných víz, pasov a cestovných dokladov pre osoby cestujúce do zahraničia; Rezervovanie zájazdov; Dojednanie/organizácia cesty; Konzultácie v oblasti cestovania, poskytované prostredníctvom telefonických call centier a asistenčných liniek; Poskytovanie informácií o cestovnej trase; Prenájom strojov na vydávanie cestovných lístkov; Konzultácie v oblasti plánovania cestovných trás; Poskytovanie informácií o zájazdoch prostredníctvom celosvetových sietí; Organizovanie turistickej dopravy; Koordinovanie cestovných plánov pre jednotlivcov a skupiny; Turistické prehliadky (doprava); Vedenie prehliadok a zájazdov; Organizácia a usporadúvanie výletov; Poskytovanie vozidiel pre zájazdy a exkurzie; Organizovanie exkurzií ako súčasť dovolenkových balíkov; Vedenie zájazdov; Plánovanie a organizovanie vyhliadkových zájazdov a celodenných výletov; Poskytovanie informácií pre turistov v oblasti exkurzií a vyhliadkových výletov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Transport; Organizacija ekskurzij; Zračni transport; Izposoja letal; Prevoz z reševalnim vozilom; Prevoz z blindiranimi vozili; Prirejanje križarjenj; Organizacija izletov; Prevoz s tovornim čolnom; Najem čolnov; Skladiščenje čolnov; Ladijski transport; Rezervacije sedežev za potovanja; Polnjenje steklenic; Avtobusni transport; Parkiranje avtomobilov; Izposoja avtomobilov; Storitve prevoza z avtomobilom; Prevozništvo; Šoferske storitve; Kurirske storitve (sporočila ali trgovsko blago); Dobava [dostava]; Spremljanje potnikov; Trajektni transport; Najem garaž; Izposoja konjev; Najem avtobusa; Najem parkirnih prostorov; Potovanja in prevoz potnikov; Shranjevanje (fizično) elektronsko shranjenih podatkov ali dokumentov; Transport z izletniškimi ladjami; Nošenje prtljage; Izposoja strešnih prtljažnikov (za vozila); Oddajanje skladišč v najem; Najem invalidskih vozičkov; Ogledovanje turističnih znamenitosti; Taksi storitve; Tramvajski transport; Posredništvo transportnih storitev; Transportne rezervacije; Transportna logistika; Potovalne rezervacije; Najem in izposoja vozil; Svetovanje o potovanjih; Organiziranje potovanj; Storitve turističnih vodičev; Storitve turističnega vodiča; Organiziranje potovanj; Storitve rezerviranja potovanj; Storitve turističnega spremljanja; Informacije o potovanjih; Organizacija potovanj; Storitve ladijskih križarjenj; Organizacija in izvajanje romanj in potovanj (potovanja); Storitve rezervacije vozovnic za potovanja; Storitve potovalnih posrednikov pri organizaciji potovanj; Spremljanje potnikov; Prevoz potniške prtljage; Storitve izdaje vozovnic za potovanja; Agencije za rezervacijo potovanj; Organizacija potovanj; Urejanje potovalnih vizumov, potnih listov in potovalnih dokumentov za osebe, ki potujejo v tujino; Storitve rezervacij izletov; Prirejanje izletov; Svetovanje na področju potovanj, nudeno preko telefonskih klicnih centrov in vročih linij; Nudenja navodil o smeri vožnje za namene potovanja; Najem avtomatov za izdajanje vozovnic za potovanje; Svetovanje v zvezi z načrtovanjem potovalnih poti; Nudenje informacij o potovanjih prek svetovnih omrežij; Organizacija ekskurzij; Koordiniranje potovalnih aranžmajev za posameznike in skupine; Storitve prevoza potovanja z ogledom turističnih znamenitosti; Vodenje ogledov in izletov; Organizacija in prirejanje izletov; Nudenje vozil za izlete in ekskurzije; Organizacija ekskurzij kot del počitniških paketov; Izvajanje potovanj; Načrtovanje in organizacija ogledov turističnih znamenitosti in enodnevnih izletov; Nudenje informacij turistom v zvezi z ekskurzijami in ogledi turističnih znamenitosti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Transporter; Anordnande av transporter vid resor; Lufttransporter; Uthyrning av luftfarkoster; Ambulanstransporter; Bepansrade biltransporter; Anordnande av kryssningar; Anordnande av rundturer; Pråmtransporter; Båtuthyrning; Upplåtande av förvaringsplatser för båtar; Båttransporter; Biljettbokningar avseende resor; Buteljeringstjänster; Busstransporter; Parkering av bilar; Biluthyrning; Biltransportservice; Kärrtransporter; Chaufförstjänster; Kurirtjänster [meddelanden eller varor]; Leverans [leverans]; Resesällskap; Färjetransporter; Garageuthyrning; Uthyrning av hästar; Uthyrning av bussar; Uthyrning av parkeringsplatser; Rese- och passagerartransporter; Fysisk lagring av elektroniskt lagrad data eller dokument; Transport med fritidsbåtar; Forsling av bagage; Uthyrning av takräcken för fordon; Uthyrning av lagerlokaler; Uthyrning av rullstolar; Sightseeing; Taxitjänster; Spårvagnstransporter; Transportmäkleri; Bokning av transporter; Transportlogistik; Bokning av resor; Uthyrning av fordon; Rådgivningstjänster avseende resor; Organisering av rundresor; Reseguidetjänster; Reseledartjänster; Organisering av rundresor; Tjänster för bokning av resor; Resebyråtjänster; Reseinformation; Researrangemang; Kryssningsfartygstjänster; Organisation och genomförande av pilgrimsfärder och -resor (resor); Biljettbokningstjänster för resor; Resebyråtjänster för anordnande av resor; Resesällskap; Transport av passagerarbagage; Biljettjänster för resor; Resebokningsbyrå; Researrangemang; Arrangerande av resevisum, pass och resedokument för personer som reser utomlands; Reservationstjänster avseende resor; Anordnande och organisation av rundturer; Konsultation inom området resor som anordnas via callcenter och direkttelefon; Upplåtande av vägbeskrivningar för resor; Uthyrning av automater för utfärdande av resebiljetter; Konsulttjänster avseende planering av färdvägar; Tillhandahållande av reseinformation via globala nätverk; Anordnande av transporter vid resor; Samordning av researrangemang för individer och grupper; Transporttjänster avseende sightseeingturer; Ledning av rundturer och -färder; Organisation och anordnande av utflykter; Tillhandahållande av fordon för rundturer och utflykter; Anordnande av utflykter som en del av paketresor; Ledning av rundturer; Planering och anordnande av sightseeingturer och dagsutflykter; Tillhandahållande av turistinformation om utflykter och sightseeing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Образователни курсове, свързани с туристическата индустрия; Публикуване на онлайн пътеводители, пътни карти, градски справочници и листинги за ползване от пътници, без възможност за изтегляне; Организиране и провеждане на образователни курсове във връзка с пътническата индустрия; Организиране на обиколки с обучителна цел; Публикуване на съвети за пътуване; Услуги за публикуване на пътеводители.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vzdělávací kurzy v oblasti průmyslu cestovního ruchu; Publikování on-line průvodců, map, městských adresářů a seznamů pro použití cestovateli, bez možnosti stažení; Příprava a organizace vzdělávacích kurzů v oblasti cestovního ruchu; Organizování zájezdů pro školicí účely; Publikování cestovních tipů; Služby vydávání cestovních průvodců.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Uddannelseskurser med relation til rejsebranchen; Udgivelse af online-vejledningsbøger, kort, byvejvisere og oversigter til brug for rejsende, kan ikke downloades; Arrangering og afholdelse af uddannelseskurser vedrørende rejsebranchen; Organisering af ture med undervisningsmæssige formål; Udgivelse af rejsetips; Udgivelse af guidebøger.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Ausbildung in Bezug auf die Reisebranche; Veröffentlichung von nicht herunterladbaren Online-Reiseführern, -Landkarten, -Städteverzeichnissen und -Broschüren für Reisende; Veranstaltung und Durchführung von Bildungskursen bezogen auf die Reiseindustrie; Organisation von Touren zu Schulungszwecken; Publikation von Reisetipps; Veröffentlichung von Reiseführern.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εκπαιδευτικά μαθήματα σε σχέση με τον κλάδο των ταξιδίων· Δημοσίευση στο διαδίκτυο οδηγών, ταξιδιωτικών χαρτών, ευρετηρίων πόλης, καθώς και καταχωρίσεων για χρήση από ταξιδιώτες, χωρίς δυνατότητα τηλεφόρτωσης· Διοργάνωση και διεξαγωγή εκπαιδευτικών προγραμμάτων για τον ταξιδιωτικό κλάδο· Οργάνωση περιηγήσεων για εκπαιδευτικούς σκοπούς· Δημοσίευση ταξιδιωτικών συμβουλών· Υπηρεσίες για την έκδοση ταξιδιωτικών οδηγών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Educational courses relating to the travel industry; Publication of online guide books, travel maps, city directories and listings for use by travellers, not downloadable; Arranging and conducting of education courses relating to the travel industry; Organisation of tours for training purposes; Publication of travel tips; Services for the publication of travel guides.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cursos educativos relacionados con la industria de los viajes; Publicación en línea de guías, mapas de viaje, callejeros y guías de ocio de ciudades para viajeros, no descargables; Organización y realización de cursos educativos relacionados con el sector de los viajes; Organización de giras [excursiones] con fines educativos; Publicación de consejos para viajes; Servicios para la publicación de guías turísticas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reisitööstusega seotud hariduslikud kursused; Reisijatele allalaadimatute reisijuhtide, reisikaartide, linnajuhtide ja kataloogide publitseerimine veebis; Reisitööstusega seotud õppekursuste korraldamine ja läbiviimine; Koolitusekskursioonide korraldamine; Reisinõuannete avaldamine; Reisijuhtide kirjastamise teenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Matkailualaan liittyvät koulutuskurssit; Muiden kuin ladattavien online-opaskirjojen, -matkakarttojen, -katuhakemistojen ja -luetteloiden julkaiseminen matkailijoiden käyttöön; Matkailualan opetuskurssien järjestäminen ja pitäminen; Tutustumiskäyntien organisointi koulutustarkoituksiin; Matkavinkkien julkaiseminen; Matkaoppaiden julkaisemispalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Cours d'enseignement concernant l'industrie touristique; Publication en ligne de guides, de cartes touristiques, de listes et de répertoires de villes pour voyageurs, non téléchargeables; Organisation et conduite de cours éducatifs en rapport avec l’industrie des voyages; Organisation d’excursions à des fins de formation; Publication de conseils en matière de voyages; Services de publication de guides de voyage.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Obrazovni tečajevi u svezi s industrijom putovanja; Izdavanje internetskih vodiča, putnih karata, imenika gradova za putnike, bez mogućnosti preuzimanja; Organizacija i provođenje obrazovnih tečajeva o industriji putovanja; Organizacija obilazaka za potrebe osposobljavanja; Publikacija putnih savjeta; Usluge izdavanja putnih vodiča.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Utazási ágazattal kapcsolatos tanfolyamok; Online, nem letölthető útikönyvek, térképek, városkalauzok és utazók által használt listák megjelentetése; Utazási ágazattal kapcsolatos tanfolyamok szervezése és lebonyolítása; Képzési célú túrák szervezése; Utazási tippek közzététele; Útikalauzok kiadásához kapcsolódó szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Corsi d'istruzione relativi all'industria dei viaggi; Pubblicazione online di guide, mappe di viaggio, elenchi e liste cittadine non scaricabili per viaggiatori; Organizzazione e conduzione di corsi d'istruzione relativi all'industria dei viaggi; Organizzazione di escursioni a scopo di formazione; Pubblicazione di consigli di viaggio; Servizi di pubblicazione di guide sui viaggi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Švietimo kursai, susiję su turizmo pramone; Neatsisiunčiamų vadovėlių, kelionių vadovų, miestų planų ir sąrašų, skirtų keliautojams, leidyba internetu; Mokymo kursų apie kelionių sektorių rengimas ir vedimas; Ekskursijų organizavimas mokymo reikmėms; Kelionių patarimų publikavimas; Kelionių vadovų (knygų) leidyba.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Izglītojoši kursi saistībā ar ceļošanu; Ceļotājiem paredzētu tiešsaistes ceļvežu, karšu, pilsētu izziņu grāmatu un sarakstu publicēšana, nav lejupielādējami; Ar tūrisma nozari saistītu izglītības kursu rīkošana un vadīšana; Ekskursiju organizēšana apmācības nolūkos; Ceļojumu padomu publicēšana; Tūrisma ceļvežu izdošanas pakalpojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Korsijiet edukattivi relatati mal-industrija tal-ivvjaġġar; Pubblikazzjoni ta' kotba tal-gwida, mapep għall-ivvjaġġar, direttorji u listi ta' bliet onlajn għall-użu minn vjaġġaturi, li ma jistgħux jitniżżlu; Organizzazzjoni u tmexxija ta’ korsijiet edukattivi relatati mal-industrija tal-ivvjaġġar; L-organizzazzjoni ta' ġiti għal skopijiet ta' taħriġ; Pubblikazzjoni ta' pariri dwar vjaġġi; Servizzi għall-pubblikazzjoni ta' gwidi turistiċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Educatieve cursussen met betrekking tot het reiswezen; Publicatie van online gidsen, reiskaarten, stadsgidsen en lijsten voor gebruik door reizigers, niet downloadbaar; Het organiseren en geven van onderwijscursussen met betrekking tot het reiswezen; Organisatie van rondleidingen voor opleidingsdoeleinden; Publicatie van reistips; Uitgeven van reisgidsen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kursy edukacyjne w dziedzinie branży turystycznej; Publikowanie przewodników, map turystycznych, spisów i wykazów miast online i nie do pobrania, do użytku przez podróżnych; Organizacja i przeprowadzanie kursów edukacyjnych związanych z sektorem turystycznym; Organizowanie wycieczek do celów szkoleniowych; Publikacja wskazówek dla podróżnych; Wydawanie przewodników turystycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cursos de educação relacionados com a indústria de viagens; Publicação de livros guia online, mapas, diretórios e listagens para uso por viajantes, não passíveis de download; Organização e realização de cursos de ensino relacionados com a indústria de viagens; Organização de excursões para fins de formação; Publicação de dicas de viagem; Serviços para a publicação de guias de viagem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cursuri de pregătire în industria turismului; Publicare de ghiduri, hărți de călătorie, registre cu orașe și liste online, pentru uzul călătorilor, nedescărcabile; Organizare și coordonare de cursuri educative în domeniul industriei turismului; Organizare de tururi în scopuri instructive; Publicare de recomandări de călătorie; Servicii pentru publicarea de ghiduri de călătorie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vzdelávacie kurzy v oblasti cestovného ruchu; Vydávanie on-line príručiek, cestovných máp, mestských telefónnych zoznamov pre cestovateľov, bez možnosti prevzatia; Organizovanie a vedenie vzdelávacích kurzov v oblasti cestovného ruchu; Organizovanie zájazdov na školiace účely; Publikovanie tipov na cestovanie; Služby týkajúce sa vydávania cestovných príručiek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Izobraževalni tečaji v zvezi s potovalno industrijo; Nudenje nenaložljivih spletnih vodičev, potovalnih zemljevidov, mestnih imenikov in seznamov za popotnike; Organizacija in izvajanje izobraževalnih tečajev v zvezi s potovalno industrijo; Organizacija potovanj za namene usposabljanja; Objavljanje potovalnih nasvetov; Storitve za objavljanje potovalnih vodičev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Utbildningskurser med inriktning på reseindustrin; Publicering av online-guideböcker, vägkartor, stadskataloger och förteckningar för resenärer, inte nedladdningsbara; Organisation och genomförande av utbildningskurser avseende resebranschen; Organisering av turer för träningsändamål; Publicering av restips; Tjänster för publicering av reseguider.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>43</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ресторантьорство; Временно настаняване; Бюра за настаняване [хотели, пансиони]; Обслужване на бар; Услуги за грижа за животни и домове за животни; Резервации за пансиони; Пансиони; Ресторанти на самообслужване; Услуги на столова; Детски ясли; Кетъринг (приготвяне и доставка на храни и напитки); Ваканционни лагери [настаняване]; Резервации за хотели; Хотели; Мотели; Осигуряване на условия за къмпинг; Отдаване под наем на столове, маси, покривки за маса и стъклени съдове; Отдаване под наем на готварски уреди; Отдаване под наем на автомати (диспенсери) за питейна вода; Отдаване под наем на апаратура за осветление, различна от тази за театрални декори или телевизионни студия; Отдаване под наем на зали за срещи; Предоставяне на временен подслон; Отдаване под наем на палатки; Отдаване под наем на преносими постройки; Ресторантьорски услуги; Домове за възрастни хора; Ресторанти на самообслужване; Закусвални; Резервации за временен подслон; Туристически домове, хижи; Резервиране на стаи за пътници; Уреждане на хотелски стаи за туристи; Резервация на квартири за пътници; Услуги на туристическа агенция за запазване на места в ресторанти; Предоставяне на места за временна почивка на пътници.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby zajišťující stravování a nápoje; Dočasné ubytování; Služby ubytovací kanceláře [hotely, penziony]; Bary; Služby zaměřené na péči o zvířata a útulky pro zvířata; Rezervace ubytování v penzionech; Penziony; Samoobslužné jídelny; Jídelny; Dětské jesle; Catering (poskytování jídla a nápojů); Prázdninové tábory (Ubytovací služby -); Rezervace ubytování v hotelech; Hotelové služby; Motely (Služby -); Provozování kempů; Pronájem židlí, stolů, ubrusů, skleněného nádobí; Pronájem kuchyňských přístrojů; Pronájem zásobníků na pitnou vodu; Pronájem osvětlovacích přístrojů, jiných než pro divadelní nebo televizní účely; Pronájem jednacích místností; Pronájem přechodného ubytování; Pronájem stanů; Pronájem přenosných staveb; Restaurace; Domovy pro seniory; Samoobslužné restaurace; Bufety; Rezervace přechodného ubytování; Turistické noclehárny; Rezervace pokojů pro turisty; Rezervace hotelových pokojů pro turisty; Rezervace ubytování pro turisty; Služby cestovních kanceláří pro rezervování restaurací; Poskytování dočasných odpočívadel pro cestující.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tilvejebringelse af mad og drikke; Midlertidig indkvartering; Bureauer til anvisning af midlertidigt logi; Tjenester ydet af barer; Pleje af dyr og dyreinternater; Restaurantvirksomhed; Tjenester ydet af pensionater; Cafeterievirksomhed; Kantinevirksomhed; Pasning af småbørn i børnehaver; Catering; Indlogering i ferielejre; Hotelreservation; Hoteller; Moteller; Stillen campingpladsfaciliteter til rådighed; Udlejning af stole, borde, duge, glasvarer; Udlejning af madlavningsapparater; Udlejning af drikkevandsdispensere; Udlejning af lysapparater, andre end til teatre og TV-studier; Udlejning af mødelokaler; Udlejning af midlertidig indkvartering; Teltudlejning; Udlejning af transportable bygninger; Tjenester ydet af restauranter; Tjenester ydet af alderdomshjem; Selvbetjeningsrestaurantvirksomhed; Tjenester ydet af snackbarer; Reservation af midlertidig indkvartering; Feriehjem; Reservation af værelser for rejsende; Reservation af hotelværelser for rejsende; Reservation af indkvartering til rejsende; Rejsebureauservice i form af reservation på restauranter; Tilrådighedsstillelse af midlertidige hvileområder for passagerer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Dienstleistungen zur Verpflegung; Beherbergung von Gästen; Zimmervermittlung [Hotels, Pensionen]; Betrieb einer Bar; Dienstleistungen von Tierpflege- und Tierheimen; Zimmerreservierung in Pensionen; Dienstleistungen von Pensionen; Verpflegung von Gästen in Cafeterias; Verpflegung von Gästen in Kantinen; Dienstleistungen einer Kinderkrippe; Catering; Betrieb von Feriencamps [Beherbergung]; Zimmerreservierung in Hotels; Betrieb von Hotels; Betrieb von Motels; Betrieb eines Campingplatzes; Vermietung von Stühlen, Tischen, Tischwäsche, Gläsern; Vermietung von Kochgeräten; Vermietung von Trinkwasserspendern; Vermietung von Beleuchtungsgeräten, ausgenommen für Bühnenausstattung oder Fernsehstudios; Vermietung von Versammlungsräumen; Vermietung von Gästezimmern; Vermietung von Zelten; Vermietung von transportablen Bauten; Verpflegung von Gästen in Restaurants; Dienstleistungen von Alten- und Seniorenheimen; Verpflegung von Gästen in Selbstbedienungsrestaurants; Verpflegung von Gästen in Schnellimbissrestaurants [Snackbars]; Zimmerreservierung; Vermietung von Ferienhäusern; Reservierung von Zimmern für Reisende; Buchung von Hotelzimmern für Reisende; Buchung von Unterkünften für Reisende; Reservierung von Restaurants durch Reisebüros; Bereitstellung von Ruhebereichen für Reisende zu vorübergehenden Nutzung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες παροχής διατροφής και ποτών· Προσωρινή κατάλυση· Πρακτορεία παροχής στέγης [ξενοδοχεία, πανσιόν]· Μπαρ (Υπηρεσίες -)· Υπηρεσίες χώρων φροντίδας και καταφυγίων ζώων· Υπηρεσίες ξενοδοχειακών κρατήσεων, κρατήσεων προσωρινών καταλυμάτων, κρατήσεων σε ξενώνες· Χώροι προσωρινής διαμονής (πανσιόν)· Εστιατόρια αυτοεξυπηρέτησης· Κυλικεία· Βρεφονηπιακοί σταθμοί· Τροφοδοσία· Κατασκηνώσεων διακοπών (υπηρεσίες -) [φιλοξενία]· Ξενοδοχείων (Κράτηση -)· Ξενοδοχειακές υπηρεσίες· Μοτέλ (Υπηρεσίες -)· Εκμετάλλευση εγκαταστάσεων για κατασκήνωση· Μίσθωση καρεκλων, τραπεζιών,τραπεζομάντηλων και γυαλικών· Εκμίσθωση μαγειρικών συσκευών· Εκμίσθωση διανομέων πόσιμου νερού· Ενοικίαση συσκεύων φωτισμού εκτός θεατρικών και τηλεοπτικών στούντιο· Μίσθωση αιθουσών συνεδριάσεων· Μίσθωση εποχιακής στέγασης· Μίσθωση σκηνών· Μίσθωση κατασκευών λυόμενων· Υπηρεσίες εστιατορίου· Ευγηρίας οίκοι· Εστιατόρια αυτοεξυπηρέτησης· Εστιατόρια ταχείας και διαρκούς εξυπηρέτησης [σνακ-μπαρ]· Κράτηση εποχιακής στέγασης· Κατοικίες τουριστικές· Κρατήσεις δωματίων για ταξιδιώτες· Κρατήσεις δωματίων ξενοδοχείων για ταξιδιώτες· Κρατήσεις καταλυμάτων για ταξιδιώτες· Υπηρεσίες ταξιδιωτικού πρακτορείου για κρατήσεις σε εστιατόρια· Παροχή προσωρινών χώρων ανάπαυσης για επιβάτες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Services for providing food and drink; Providing temporary accommodation; Accommodation bureau services [hotels, boarding houses]; Bar services; Boarding for animals; Boarding house bookings; Boarding house services; Cafeteria services; Canteen services; Day-nursery [crèche] services; Food and drink catering; Holiday camp services [lodging]; Hotel reservations; Hotels; Motels; Providing campground facilities; Rental of chairs, tables, table linen, glassware; Rental of cooking apparatus; Rental of drinking water dispensers; Rental of lighting apparatus other than for theatrical sets or television studios; Rental of meeting rooms; Rental of temporary accommodation; Rental of tents; Rental of transportable buildings; Restaurant services; Retirement home services; Self-service restaurant services; Snack-bar services; Temporary accommodation reservations; Tourist homes; Reservation of rooms for travellers; Booking of hotel rooms for travellers; Booking of accommodation for travellers; Travel agency services for booking restaurants; Providing temporary rest areas for passengers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de restauración (alimentación); Puesta a disposición de alojamientos temporales; Servicios de agencias de alojamiento [hoteles, pensiones]; Servicios de bar; Servicios de asilos y residencias para animales; Reserva de pensiones; Servicios de pensiones; Servicios de cafeterías; Servicios de comedores; Servicios de guarderías infantiles; Servicios de catering; Campamentos de vacaciones (servicios de -) [hospedaje]; Reserva de hoteles; Hotelería (Servicios de -); Motel (Servicios de -); Explotación de campings; Alquiler de sillas, mesas, mantelería y cristalería; Alquiler de aparatos de cocción; Alquiler de dispensadores de agua potable; Alquiler de aparatos de iluminación que no sean para decorados de teatro ni para estudios de televisión; Alquiler de salas de reunión; Alquiler de alojamiento temporal; Alquiler de tiendas de campaña; Alquiler de construcciones transportables; Servicios de restaurantes; Servicios de residencias para la tercera edad; Servicios de restaurantes de autoservicio; Servicios de bares de comida rápida; Reserva de alojamiento temporal; Casas de vacaciones; Reserva de habitaciones para viajeros; Reservas de habitaciones de hotel para viajeros; Servicios de reservas de alojamiento para viajeros; Servicios de reserva de restaurantes prestados por agencias de viajes; Facilitación de zonas de descanso temporal para pasajeros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Toitlustusteenused; Tähtajaline majutamine; Majutusbürooteenused [hotellid, pansionaadid]; Baariteenused; Loomahoolduskeskuste ja loomade varjupaikade teenused; Pansionaadikohtade, kostikohtade reserveerimine, ettetellimine; Pansionaaditeenused; Selvekohvikuteenused, kafeteeriateenused; Kantiiniteenused; Lastepäevakoduteenused, päevaste lastesõimede teenused; Toitlustusteenindus; Puhkelaagriteenused [majutus]; Hotellikohtade reserveerimine, ettetellimine; Hotellid; Motellid; Laagriplatsiteenused; Toolide, laudade, laudlinade, klaasnõude üürimine, rentimine, laenutus; Toiduvalmistusseadmete rent; Joogiveeautomaatide rent; Valgustusaparaatide rent, v.a teatrites ja televisioonis kasutatavate; Koosolekuruumide tähtajaline üürimine, rentimine; Ajutise elamispinna üürimine; Telkide üürimine, rentimine, laenutus; Teisaldatavate ehitiste üürimine, rentimine, laenutus; Restoraniteenused; Vanadekoduteenused; Selverestoraniteenused; Kiirtoidukohvikuteenused, püstijalabaariteenused; Ajutise elamispinna ettetellimine, reserveerimine; Matkakodud, turismibaasid; Majutuse broneerimine reisijatele; Hotellitubade broneerimine reisijatele; Majutuskohtade broneerimine reisijaile; Reisibürooteenused restoranide broneerimiseks; Reisijatele ajutiste puhkealade pakkumine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ravitseminen ja juomien anniskelu; Tilapäismajoitus; Majoitusliikkeet [hotellit, täysihoitolat]; Baaripalvelut; Eläintenhoito- ja eläinkotien palvelut; Täysihoitolavaraukset; Täysihoitolat; Kafeteriapalvelut; Kanttiinit; Päiväkodit lapsille; Pitopalvelu; Majoituspalvelut leirintäalueiden yhteydessä; Hotellihuoneiden varauspalvelut; Hotellit; Motellit; Leirintätilojen tarjoaminen; Tuolien, pöytien, pöytäliinojen ja lasitavaroiden vuokraus; Keittolaitteiden vuokraus; Vuokraus (Juomavesiautomaattien -); Valaistuslaitteiden vuokraus muuhun kuin teatterilavasteisiin tai televisiostudioihin; Kokoustilojen vuokraus; Tilapäisten majoitustilojen vuokraus; Telttojen vuokraus; Siirrettävien rakennusten vuokraus; Ravintolapalvelut; Vanhainkodit; Itsepalveluravintolat; Pikaruokalat; Tilapäismajoitusvaraukset; Matkustajakodit; Huoneiden varaaminen matkailijoille; Hotellihuoneiden varaus matkailijoille; Majoituksen varaaminen matkailijoille; Matkatoimistopalvelut ravintolavarausten tekemiseen; Väliaikaisten lepotilojen tarjoaminen matkustajille.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de restauration (alimentation); Mise à disposition d'hébergements temporaires; Services d'agences de logement [hôtels, pensions]; Services de bars; Services de soins pour animaux et refuges pour animaux; Réservation de pensions; Services de pensions; Services de cafétérias; Services de cantines; Services de crèches d'enfants; Services de traiteurs; Services de camps de vacances [hébergement]; Réservation d'hôtels; Services hôteliers; Services de motels; Mise à disposition de terrains de camping; Location de chaises, tables, linge de table et verrerie; Location d'appareils de cuisson; Location de fontaines [distributeurs] à eau potable; Location d’appareils d’éclairage autres que pour les décors de théâtre ou des studios de télévision; Location de salles de réunions; Location de logements temporaires; Location de tentes; Location de constructions transportables; Services de restaurants; Services de maisons de retraite pour personnes âgées; Services de restaurants en libre-service; Services de snack-bars; Réservation de logements temporaires; Maisons de vacances; Réservation de chambres pour voyageurs; Réservation de chambres d'hôtel pour voyageurs; Services de réservations de logement pour voyageurs; Services d'agences de voyage pour la réservation de restaurants; Fourniture de zones de repos temporaire pour les passagers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge pružanja hrane i pića [okrepa]; Privremeni smještaj; Agencije za smještaj [hotelski, pansionski]; Usluge barova; Usluge njege životinja i prihvatilišta za životinje; Rezerviranje pansiona; Pansioni; Restorani sa samoposluživanjem; Kantine; Jaslice [dječji vrtići]; Catering; Ljetovanje [usluge kampova za ljetovanje]; Rezerviranje hotela; Hotelske usluge; Moteli (usluge motela); Kampovi (iskorištavanje terena za kampiranje); Iznajmljivanje stolaca, stolova, stolnog rublja i staklenog posuđa; Iznajmljivanje aparata za kuhanje; Iznajmljivanje uređaja za pitku vodu; Iznajmljivanje rasvjetnih uređaja, osim za kazališnu dekoraciju i televizijske studije; Iznajmljivanje prostorija za sastanke; Iznajmljivanje privremenih smještaja; Iznajmljivanje šatora; Iznajmljivanje prenosivih građevinskih objekata; Usluge restorana; Usluge staračkog doma; Restorani sa samoposluživanjem; Bifei; Usluge rezervacije smještaja; Ljetovališta; Rezervacija soba za putnike; Rezerviranje hotelskih soba za putnike; Rezerviranje smještaja za putnike; Usluge putničkih agencija za rezervaciju mjesta u restoranima; Pružanje privremenih odmorišta za putnike.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vendéglátás (élelmezés); Ideiglenes szállásbiztosítás; Szállásügynökségek [szállodák, panziók]; Bár szolgáltatások; Állatápoló és állatgondozó otthonok szolgáltatásai; Foglalás panziókban; Panziók; Önkiszolgáló éttermek; Kantinok, büfék, étkezdék; Bölcsődék, óvodák; Vendéglátás; Üdülőtáborok szolgáltatásai [szállásadás]; Szállodai szobafoglalás, szállásfoglalás; Szállodai szolgáltatások; Motelek; Kempingezési lehetőség biztosítása; Székek, asztalok, asztalterítők, üvegáruk kölcsönzése; Főzőeszközök bérbeadása; Ivóvízadagoló automaták bérbeadása; Világítóberendezések bérbeadása, nem színházi vagy televízióstúdiós használatra; Terembérlés találkozókhoz [tárgyalótermek]; Átmeneti szállások kiadása; Sátrak kölcsönzése; Hordozható épületek, építmények bérbeadása; Éttermi szolgáltatások; Nyugdíjasotthonok, időskorúak otthona; Önkiszolgáló éttermek; Gyorséttermek, snack bárok; Szállásfoglalás; Turistaházak; Szobafoglalás utazóknak; Szállodai szobák lefoglalása utazók számára; Szállásfoglalás utazók számára; Utazási irodai szolgáltatások éttermi asztalfoglalásokkal kapcsolatban; Átmeneti pihenőhelyek biztosítása utasok részére.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di ristorazione (alimentazione); Alloggi temporanei; Servizi di agenzie per alloggi [hotels, pensioni]; Servizi di bar; Servizi legati alla cura di animali e a rifugi per animali; Prenotazione di pensioni; Servizi di pensioni; Servizi di caffetterie; Servizi di mense; Servizi di asili nidi; Servizi di catering; Servizi di campi di vacanze [alloggio]; Prenotazione d'alberghi; Servizi alberghieri; Servizi di motel; Gestione di aree per campeggio; Noleggio di sedie, tavoli, biancheria da tavolo, bicchieri; Noleggio di apparecchi per cucinare; Noleggio di distributori di acqua potabile; Noleggio di apparecchi di illuminazione non per set teatrali né per studi televisivi; Noleggio di sale per riunione; Locazione di alloggi temporanei; Noleggio di tende; Noleggio di costruzioni trasportabili; Servizi di ristoranti; Servizi di case di riposo per persone anziane; Servizi di ristoranti self-service; Servizi di snack-bars; Prenotazione di abitazioni temporanee; Case per vacanze; Prenotazione di camere per viaggiatori; Prenotazione di camere d'albergo per viaggiatori; Prenotazione di alloggi per viaggiatori; Servizi di agenzia di viaggio per la prenotazione di ristoranti; Fornitura di aree di riposo temporaneo per passeggeri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Maisto ir gėrimų parūpinimo paslaugos; Laikinas apgyvendinimas; Apgyvendinimo biurų paslaugos [viešbučiai, pensionai]; Barų paslaugos; Gyvūnų priežiūros ir gyvūnų prieglaudų paslaugos; Pensionų rezervavimas; Pensionų paslaugos; Kavos barų paslaugos; Valgyklų paslaugos; Lopšelių paslaugos; Aprūpinimas maistu ir gėrimais; Trumpo poilsio stovyklų paslaugos [nuomojamos patalpos]; Viešbučių rezervavimas; Viešbučiai; Moteliai; Poilsio stovyklaviečių paslaugos; Kėdžių, stalų, staltiesių, stiklo dirbinių nuoma; Maisto gaminimo [virimo, kepimo] aparatų nuoma; Geriamojo vandens dalytuvų nuoma; Apšvietimo priemonių nuoma (ne teatrui ar televizijos studijoms); Susitikimo patalpų nuoma; Trumpa patalpų nuoma; Palapinių nuoma; Kilnojamųjų statinių nuoma; Restoranų paslaugos; Senelių namų paslaugos; Savitarnos restoranų paslaugos; Užkandinių paslaugos; Laikino būsto parūpinimas; Turizmo bazės; Kambarių keliautojams rezervavimas; Viešbučių kambarių rezervavimas keliautojams; Būsto keliautojams užsakymas; Kelionių agentūrų teikiamos restoranų rezervavimo paslaugos; Laikinų poilsio vietų parūpinimas keleiviams.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apgāde ar uzturu; Viesu izmitināšanas nodrošināšana; Viesu izmitināšanas biroju pakalpojumi (viesnīcās, pansijās); Bāru pakalpojumi; Dzīvnieku kopšanas un dzīvnieku namu pakalpojumi; Pansiju rezervēšana; Pansiju pakalpojumi; Kafetēriju pakalpojumi; Ēdnīcu pakalpojumi; Dienas mazbērnu novietņu pakalpojumi; Ēdināšanas pakalpojumi; Brīvdienu nometņu pakalpojumi [izmitināšana]; Viesnīcu rezervēšana; Viesnīcu pakalpojumi; Moteļu pakalpojumi; Kempingu pakalpojumu nodrošināšana; Krēslu, galdu, galda drānu un stikla trauku iznomāšana; Virtuves iekārtu iznomāšana; Dzeramā ūdens iekārtu iznomāšana; Apgaismošanas iekārtu noma, izņemot teātra skatuves vai televīzijas studiju vajadzībām; Sanāksmju telpu iznomāšana; Īslaicīgās uzturēšanās mītņu izīrēšana; Telšu iznomāšana; Pārvietojamu ēku iznomāšana; Restorānu pakalpojumi; Veco ļaužu pansionātu pakalpojumi; Pašapkalpošanās restorānu pakalpojumi; Uzkodu bāru pakalpojumi; Īslaicīgās uzturēšanās mītņu rezervēšana; Tūristu mītņu pakalpojumi; Istabu rezervēšana ceļotājiem; Viesnīcu numuru rezervēšana ceļotājiem; Apmešanās vietu rezervēšana ceļotājiem; Ceļojumu aģentūru pakalpojumi restorānu rezervēšanai; Pagaidu atpūtas zonu nodrošināšana pasažieriem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi għall-provvista ta' ikel u xorb; Akkomodazzjoni temporanja; Servizzi ta' provvista ta' akkomodazzjoni (f'lukandi, alloġġi eċċ); Servizzi ta' barijiet; Servizzi tal-kura tal-annimali u xelters tal-annimali; L-ibbukkjar ta' alloġġi; Alloġġi; Ristoranti fejn wieħed jinqeda waħdu; Kantini; Ospizji tat-tfal; Catering; Servizzi ta' kamp għall-vakanzi (alloġġ); Riservazzjonijiet f'lukanda; Lukandi; Motels; Il-provvista ta' faċilitajiet għall-ikkampjar; Kiri ta' siġġijiet, imwejjed, tvalji tal-imwejjed u oġġetti tal-ħġieġ; Il-kiri ta' apparat tat-tisjir; Il-kiri ta' magni tal-ilma li wieħed jista' jixrob minnhom; Kiri ta' apparat ta' mixgħela minbarra dak għal settijiet tat-teatru jew studjos tat-televiżjoni; Il-kiri ta' kmamar għal-laqgħat; Il-kiri ta' akkomodazzjoni temporanja; Kiri ta' tined; Kiri ta' bini li jista' jittieħed minn post għal ieħor; Servizzi ta' restorant; Djar tal-irtirar; Ristoranti fejn wieħed jinqeda waħdu; Barijiet li jagħmlu ikel ħafif u ta' malajr; Servizzi ta' riservazzjoni ta' kmamar; Djar għat-turisti; Riservazzjoni ta' kmamar għal min jivvjaġġa; Il-prenotazzjoni ta' kmamar ta' lukandi għal vjaġġaturi; Servizzi ta' prenotazzjoni ta' akkomodazzjoni għall-vjaġġaturi; Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-ivvjaġġar biex tagħmel riservazzjonijiet f'ristoranti; Il-forniment ta' żoni ta' serħan temporanju għall-passiġġieri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Restauratie (het verstrekken van voedsel en dranken); Tijdelijke huisvesting; Bureaus voor het verstrekken van logies [hotels, pensions]; Bardiensten; Diensten van dierenpensions; Pensionreservering; Diensten van pensions; Diensten van cafetaria's; Diensten van kantines; Diensten van crèches; Catering; Vakantiekampen [logies]; Hotelreservering; Hoteldiensten; Moteldiensten; Ter beschikking stellen van kampeerterreinen; Verhuur van stoelen, tafels, tafellinnen en glaswerk; Verhuur van kookapparatuur; Verhuur van waterdispensers; Verhuur van verlichtingsapparatuur, anders dan voor tv-studio's en toneeldecors; Verhuur van vergaderzalen; Verhuur van tijdelijke huisvesting; Verhuur van tenten; Verhuur van verplaatsbare constructies; Restauratie [het verstrekken van maaltijden]; Diensten van bejaardentehuizen; Diensten van zelfbedieningsrestaurants; Diensten van snackbars; Reservering van tijdelijke accommodaties; Vakantiehuizen [logies]; Reservering van kamers voor reizigers; Hotelkamers voor reizigers (Het boeken van -); Accomodatie voor reizigers (Het boeken van -); Diensten van reisagenten voor het maken van reserveringen voor restaurants; Verschaffing van tijdelijke rustzones voor passagiers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi zaopatrzenia w żywność i napoje; Tymczasowe zakwaterowanie; Biura zakwaterowania [hotele, pensjonaty]; Usługi barowe; Usługi obejmujące pielęgnację zwierząt i pensjonaty dla zwierząt; Rezerwacja miejsc w pensjonatach; Pensjonaty; Restauracje samoobsługowe; Stołówki; Żłobki dla dzieci; Obsługa gastronomiczna z własnym zapleczem, produktami i transportem; Wakacje (organizowanie obozów -) [zakwaterowanie]; Rezerwacje miejsc w hotelach; Hotele; Motele; Zapewnianie obiektów i wyposażenia kempingowego; Wypożyczanie krzeseł, stołów, bielizny stołowej i szklanych naczyń; Wypożyczanie urządzeń do gotowania; Wypożyczanie dozowników wody pitnej; Wypożyczanie urządzeń oświetleniowych innych niż do dekoracji teatralnych lub studiów filmowych; Wynajmowanie sal na zebrania; Wynajmowanie zakwaterowania na pobyt czasowy; Wypożyczanie namiotów; Wynajem budynków przenośnych; Usługi restauracyjne; Domy opieki dla osób w podeszłym wieku; Restauracje samoobsługowe; Bary szybkiej obsługi [snack-bary]; Usługi rezerwacji pokojów; Domy turystyczne; Rezerwowanie pokojów dla podróżnych; Rezerwacja pokojów hotelowych dla podróżnych; Rezerwacja zakwaterowania na rzecz podróżnych; Usługi biur podróży w zakresie rezerwowania restauracji; Zapewnianie miejsc do tymczasowego odpoczynku dla pasażerów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de restauração (alimentação); Alojamento temporário; Serviços de agências de alojamento temporário [hotéis, pensões]; Serviços de bar; Serviços de centros de acolhimento de animais e abrigos de animais; Reserva de pensões; Serviços de pensões; Serviços de cafeterias; Serviços de cantinas [refeitórios]; Serviços de creches; Serviços de catering; Serviços de campos de férias [hospedagem/albergaria]; Reserva de hotéis; Hotéis; Motels; Serviços de campismo; Aluguer de cadeiras, mesas, toalhas de mesa, copos; Aluguer de aparelhos de cozinha; Aluguer de dispensadores de água potável; Aluguer de aparelhos de iluminação, não sendo para palcos ou estúdios de televisão; Aluguer de salas de reunião; Aluguer de alojamento temporário; Aluguer de tendas; Aluguer de construções transportáveis; Serviços de restaurantes; Serviços de casas de retiro para a terceira idade; Serviços de restaurantes self-service; Serviços de snack-bares; Reservas de alojamento temporário; Casas de turismo; Reserva de quartos para viajantes; Reservas de quartos de hotel para viajantes; Reserva de alojamento para viajantes; Serviços de agências de viagens para a marcação de reservas em restaurantes; Fornecimento de zonas de repouso temporárias para passageiros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de alimentaţie publică; Cazare temporară; Agenții de cazare [hoteluri, pensiuni]; Servicii ale barurilor; Servicii de îngrijire şi cazare a animalelor; Rezervări de pensiuni; Pensiuni; Restaurante cu autoservire; Cantine; Creșe de copii; Catering; Vacanţă (Servicii oferite de tabere de -); Rezervări de hoteluri; Servicii hoteliere; Moteluri (Servicii oferite de -); Punerea la dispoziție a terenurilor de camping; Închiriere de scaune, mese, veselă și lenjerie de masă; Închiriere aparate de gătit; Închirierea dozatoarelor de apă potabilă; Închirierea dispozitivelor de iluminat, altele decât pentru scene de teatru sau studiouri de televiziune; Închiriere de săli de reuniune; Închirieri de spații de cazare temporară; Închiriere de corturi; Închiriere de construcții transportabile; Restaurante [servirea mesei]; Cămine de bătrâni; Restaurante cu autoservire; Snack-baruri; Rezervări de spații de cazare temporară; Case de vacanţă; Rezervări de camere pentru călători; Rezervare de camere de hotel pentru călători; Rezervare de locuri de cazare pentru călători; Servicii de agenție de voiaj pentru rezervarea de locuri la restaurante; Furnizare de spații de odihnă temporare pentru pasageri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reštauračné služby (strava); Prechodné ubytovanie; Ubytovacie kancelárie (hotely, penzióny); Bary (služby); Služby ošetrovania zvierat a hotelov pre zvieratá; Rezervácie ubytovania v penziónoch; Penzióny; Samoobslužné jedálne; Závodné jedálne; Detské jasle; Catering; Prázdninové tábory [ubytovacie služby]; Rezervácie ubytovania v hoteloch; Hotelierske služby; Motelové (Služby -); Poskytovanie pozemkov pre kempingy; Požičiavanie stoličiek, stolov, obrusov a nápojového skla; Požičiavanie prístrojov na prípravu jedál; Prenájom automatov na pitnú vodu; Prenájom osvetľovacích prístrojov (nie na osvetľovanie divadelnej scény alebo televíznych štúdií); Prenájom prednáškových sál; Prenájom prechodného ubytovania; Požičiavanie turistických stanov; Prenájom prenosných stavieb; Reštauračné (stravovacie) služby; Domovy dôchodcov; Samoobslužné reštaurácie; Rýchle občerstvenie (snackbary); Rezervácie prechodného ubytovania; Turistické ubytovne; Rezervovanie ubytovania pre cestovateľov; Rezervovanie hotelových izieb pre cestovateľov; Rezervovanie ubytovania pre cestovateľov; Služby cestovných kancelárií pre rezervovanie reštaurácii; Poskytovanie dočasných odpočívadiel pre cestujúcich.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Nudenje hrane in pijače; Začasna nastanitev; Nastanitvene agencije [za hotele, penzione]; Storitve barov; Storitve za nego živali in zavetišč za živali; Rezervacije penzionov; Penzioni; Samopostrežne restavracije; Menze; Otroške jasli; Catering; Storitve počitniških kampov; Hotelske rezervacije; Hoteli; Moteli; Nudenje prostora in opreme za taborjenje; Najem stolov, miz, namiznih prtov, steklenih posod; Najem aparatov za kuhanje; Najem avtomatov s pitno vodo; Izposoja naprav za osvetljevanje, razen za gledališke scene ali televizijske studie; Najem sejnih sob; Najem začasnih nastanitev; Najem šotorov; Najem prenosnih zgradb; Storitve restavracij; Domovi upokojencev; Samopostrežne restavracije; Bifeji; Storitve rezervacije sob; Turistični domovi; Rezervacija sob za popotnike; Rezervacije hotelskih sob za popotnike; Rezervacija nastanitve za popotnike; Storitve potovalnih agencij za rezervacije restavracij; Zagotavljanje začasnih prostorov za počitek za potnike.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Utskänkning av mat och dryck; Upplåtande av tillfälligt boende; Hotellbokningsagenturer; Cocktailbartjänster; Tjänster som tillhandahålls av djurvårds- och djurhem; Pensionatsbokningar; Pensionatrörelser; Cafeteriatjänster; Kantiner; Daghem; Catering av mat och dryck; Semesteranläggningar [logi]; Hotellbokning; Hotell; Motell; Upplåtande av campingplatser; Uthyrning av stolar, bord, bordslinne och glasvaror; Uthyrning av matlagningsutrustningar; Uthyrning av dricksvattenautomater; Uthyrning av belysningar, ej för teateruppsättningar eller tv-studior; Uthyrning av möteslokaler; Uthyrning av tillfälliga bostäder; Uthyrning av tält; Uthyrning av flyttbara byggnader; Restauranger; Seniorboende; Självserveringsrestauranger; Snackbarer; Rumsreservationstjänster; Semesterbostäder; Bokning av rum åt resenärer; Bokning av hotellrum för resenärer; Bokning av logi för resenärer; Resebyråtjänster för bokning av restauranger; Tillhandahållande av tillfälliga viloområden för resenärer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/124</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-03</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/196</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-14</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>10710</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
