<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-10T08:16:17</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018222899</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018222899</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-08</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-08</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-08</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-10</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ESB INTERNATIONAL</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162186438</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/222/018222899/000162186438.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.02</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.05</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.06</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.18</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.98</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.02</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.05</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.19</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>29.01.04</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Управление на търговски сделки; Търговска администрация; Управление на бизнес проекти; Снабдяване за сметка на трети лица [закупуване на стоки или услуги за други предприятия]; Услуги за анализи и проучване на пазара.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pomoc při řízení obchodní činnosti; Obchodní administrativa; Management obchodních projektů; Zásobovací služby pro jiné osoby [nákup zboží a služeb pro jiné podniky]; Průzkum a analýzy trhu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Forretningsledelse; Forretningsadministration; Administration af erhvervsprojekter; Indkøbsbistand til andre ved køb af varer og tjenesteydelser; Markedsanalyse og -undersøgelse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Geschäftsführung; Unternehmensverwaltung; Kaufmännisches Projektmanagement; Beschaffungsdienstleistungen für Dritte [Erwerb von Waren und Dienstleistungen für andere Unternehmen]; Marktanalysen und -forschung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διοίκηση επιχειρήσεων· Διαχείριση επιχειρήσεων· Διαχείριση επιχειρηματικών έργων· Εφοδιασμού για τρίτους (υπηρεσίες -) [αγορά προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για άλλες επιχειρήσεις]· Ανάλυση και έρευνα αγοράς.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Business management; business administration; business project management services; procurement services; market analysis and research services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Gestión de negocios comerciales; Administración comercial; Gestión de proyectos empresariales; Servicios de abastecimiento para terceros [compra de productos y servicios para otras empresas]; Investigación y análisis de mercados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ärijuhtimine; Ärikorraldus; Äriprojektide juhtimine; Hanketeenused teistele ettevõtetele [kaupade ja teenuste ostmine]; Turu-uuringud ja -analüüsid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Liikkeenjohto; Yrityshallinto; Liiketoimintaprojektien hallinta; Hankintapalvelut muille [tavaroiden ja palveluiden osto muille yrityksille]; Markkinatutkimus ja -analyysit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Gestion des affaires commerciales; Administration commerciale; Gestion de projets commerciaux; Services d'approvisionnement pour des tiers [achat de produits et de services pour d'autres entreprises]; Analyses et études de marché.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Vođenje komercijalnih poslova; Komercijalna administracija; Upravljanje poslovnim projektima; Nabava za treće osobe [usluge kupnje proizvoda i usluga za druga poduzeća]; Analize i istraživanje tržišta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kereskedelmi ügyletek; Kereskedelmi adminisztráció; Üzleti projektmenedzsment; Beszerzői szolgáltatások [áruk illetve szolgáltatások beszerzése más cégeknek]; Piackutatás és analízis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Gestione di affari commerciali; Amministrazione commerciale; Gestione di progetti aziendali; Servizi di approvvigionamento per conto terzi [aquisto di prodotti e di servizi per altre imprese]; Analisi e ricerche di mercato.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Verslo vadyba; Verslo tvarkyba; Verslo projektų vadyba; Tiekimo paslaugos kitiems [prekių ir paslaugų pirkimas kitiems verslams]; Rinkos analizė ir tyrimai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Darījumu vadīšana; Uzņēmumu pārvaldīšana; Uzņēmējdarbības projektu pārvaldība; Uzņēmumu apgāde [preču un pakalpojumu sagāde trešo personu interesēs]; Tirgus izpēte un analīze.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Il-ġestjoni ta' negozju; L-amministrazzjoni ta' negozju; Il-ġestjoni ta' proġetti tan-negozju; Servizzi ta' akkwist għal oħrajn [xiri ta' prodotti u servizzi għal negozji oħra]; Analiżi u riċerka tas-suq.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Beheer van commerciële zaken; Zakelijke administratie; Zakelijk projectmanagement; Aankoop voor andere bedrijven; Marktanalyse en -onderzoek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Zarządzanie w działalności gospodarczej; Administrowanie działalności gospodarczej; Zarządzanie projektami z zakresu działalności gospodarczej; Usługi w zakresie nabywania dla osób trzecich [zakupy produktów i usług dla innych przedsiębiorstw]; Badania i analizy rynkowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Gestão de negócios comerciais; Administração comercial; Gestão de projetos empresariais; Serviços de fornecimento para terceiros [compra de produtos e serviços para outras empresas]; Análises e investigações de mercado.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Gestiunea afacerilor comerciale; Administraţie comercială; Managementul proiectelor de afaceri; Servicii de aprovizionare pentru terţi [achiziţii de bunuri şi servicii pentru alte întreprinderi]; Analiză şi cercetare de piaţă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Obchodný manažment, obchodná správa; Obchodná administratíva; Riadenie obchodných projektov; Zásobovacie služby pre tretie osoby (nákup tovarov a služieb pre iné podniky); Analýza a prieskum trhu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Vodenje komercialnih poslov; Poslovna administracija; Upravljanje poslovnih projektov; Prokuratorske storitve [nabava blaga in storitev za druga podjetja]; Tržne analize in raziskave.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Företagsledning; Företagsadministration; Affärsmässig projektledning; Inköp av varor och tjänster för annans räkning; Marknadsanalyser och -undersökningar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>36</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Финансови сделки; Финансови оценки; Услуги за финансиране и предоставяне на средства; Услуги за финансово планиране; Управление на активи; Услуги, свързани с недвижими имоти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby finanční; Finanční oceňování; Financování a poskytování finančních prostředků; Služby finančního plánování; Správa aktiv; Služby nemovitostní (realitní služby).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Finansiel virksomhed; Finansiel vurdering; Tjenesteydelser i forbindelse med finansiering; Finansiel planlægningsvirksomhed; Forvaltning af aktiver; Virksomhed i forbindelse med fast ejendom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Finanzwesen; Finanzielle Bewertung; Finanzierungen; Finanzplanung; Anlagenverwaltung; Immobiliendienstleistungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Οικονομικές υπηρεσίες· Χρηματοοικονομική αξιολόγηση· Υπηρεσίες χρηματοδότησης· Οικονομικός σχεδιασμός· Διαχείριση στοιχείων ενεργητικού· Κτηματομεσιτικές υπηρεσίες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Financial services; financial evaluation; financing and funding services; financial planning; asset management services; real estate services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios financieros; Estimaciones financieras; Servicios de financiación y recursos financieros; Servicios de planificación financiera; Gestión de activos; Servicios inmobiliarios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Finantsteenused; Finantsilised hinnangud; Finantseerimis- ja rahastamisteenused; Finantsplaneerimine; Varahaldus; Kinnisvarateenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Rahoituspalvelut; Rahataloudellinen arviointi; Rahasto- ja rahoituspalvelut; Rahoitussuunnittelu; Varainhoito; Kiinteistöpalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services financiers; Évaluation financière; Services de financement; Services de planification financière; Gestion d'actifs; Services de biens immobiliers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Financijske usluge; Financijsko vrednovanje; Usluge financiranja; Usluge financijskog planiranja; Upravljanje aktivom; Usluge agencija za nekretnine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Pénzügyi szolgáltatások; Pénzügyi értékelés; Finanszírozási szolgáltatások; Pénzügyi tervezés; Vagyonkezelési szolgáltatások; Ingatlannal kapcsolatos szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Affari finanziari; Stime finanziarie; Servizi di finanziamento e di prestito; Servizi di pianificazione finanziaria; Servizi di gestione patrimoniale; Servizi immobiliari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Finansinės paslaugos; Finansinis vertinimas; Finansavimo paslaugos; Finansinio planavimo paslaugos; Turto valdymas; Nekilnojamojo turto paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Finanšu pakalpojumi; Finanšu novērtēšana; Finansēšanas un kreditēšanas pakalpojumi; Finanšu plānošana; Aktīvu pārvaldes pakalpojumi; Pakalpojumi nekustamā īpašuma jomā.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi f'finanzi; Stima finanzjarja; Servizzi ta' finanzjar u finanzjament; Servizzi ta' ppjanar finanzjarju; Il-ġestjoni ta' assi; Servizzi ta' beni immobbli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Financiële diensten; Financiële evaluatie; Financieringsdiensten; Financiële planning; Vermogensbeheer; Diensten op het gebied van onroerend goed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi finansowe; Ewaluacja finansowa; Usługi finansowania; Usługi w zakresie planowania finansowego; Zarządzanie aktywami; Usługi w zakresie nieruchomości.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços financeiros; Avaliação relacionada com finanças; Serviços de financiamento e fundos; Serviços de planeamento financeiro; Gestão de ativos; Serviços imobiliários.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii financiare; Evaluare financiară; Servicii de finanţare; Planificare financiară; Gestionare a activelor; Servicii imobiliare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Služby v oblasti finančníctva; Finančné oceňovanie; Financovanie a poskytovanie finančných prostriedkov; Finančné plánovanie; Manažment aktív; Realitné služby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Finančne storitve; Finančno vrednotenje; Storitve financiranja in investiranja; Storitve finančnega načrtovanja; Upravljanje premoženja; Storitve poslovanja z nepremičninami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Finansiella tjänster; Finansiell värdering; Finansieringstjänster; Finansiella planeringstjänster; Förvaltning av tillgångar; Tjänster avseende fast egendom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>37</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Строителство; Услуги по строителство на сгради в областта на гражданското строителство, електрическия сектор и енергетиката; Услуги за управление проекти за строителство; Контрол, надзор и управление (ръководене) на строителни дейности; Поддръжка и ремонт на сгради; Монтажни услуги; Уплътняване на сгради; Проектно управление на сградостроителни обекти и модернизиране на инсталации, сградна апаратура, оборудване и устройства, предназначени за повишаване на енергийната ефективност и енергоспестяването; Консултантски, информационни и съветнически услуги, свързани с всички горепосочени услуги.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Stavebnictví; Stavební služby v oboru stavebnictví, elektřiny a energie; Stavební projektové řízení; Dohled, dozor a řízení (vedení) stavebních prací; Údržba a opravy budov; Instalační služby; Izolace budov; Projektové řízení stavebních prací a modernizace zařízení, stavebních přístrojů, zařízení a spotřebičů za účelem zvýšení energetické účinnosti a úspory energie; Informační, poradenské a konzultační služby týkající se všech výše uvedených služeb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Byggevirksomhed; Bygge- og konstruktionsvirksomhed inden for civilingeniørvirksomhed, elektricitet og energi; Ledelse af byggeprojekter; Overvågning, tilsyn og ledelse vedrørende bygningskonstruktion; Vedligeholdelse og reparation af bygninger; Installationsvirksomhed; Isolering af bygninger; Projektledelse inden for bygningsarbejder og opgradering af installationer, bygningsapparater, udstyr og tilbehør, som er beregnet til at øge energieffektivitet og energibesparelse; Konsulentbistand, information og rådgivning vedrørende ovennævnte tjenesteydelser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bauwesen; Bauarbeiten im Bereich Tiefbau, Elektrizität und Energie; Bauprojektmanagement; Bauüberwachung, Aufsicht und Oberaufsicht von Bauarbeiten (Leitung); Gebäudeinstandhaltung und -reparatur; Installationsarbeiten; Isolierung von Gebäuden; Projektmanagement von Bauvorhaben und der Aufrüstung von Anlagen, Baugeräten, Ausrüstungen und Geräten für die Steigerung der Energieeffizienz und Energieeinsparung; Information und Beratung in Bezug auf alle vorstehend genannten Leistungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Οικοδομικές εργασίες· Υπηρεσίες κατασκευής κτιρίων στον τομέα των έργων πολιτικών μηχανικών, του ηλεκτρισμού και της ενέργειας· Υπηρεσίες διαχείρισης κατασκευαστικών έργων· Εποπτεία, επίβλεψη και διοικητική διαχείριση (ηγεσία) κατασκευαστικών εργασιών· Συντήρηση και επισκευή κτιρίων· Υπηρεσίες εγκατάστασης· Μόνωση κτιρίων· Διαχείριση έργων σε σχέση με οικοδομικές εργασίες και αναβάθμιση εγκαταστάσεων, συσκευών, εξοπλισμού και διατάξεων κτιρίων σχεδιασμένων για αύξηση ενεργειακής απόδοσης και εξοικονόμηση ενέργειας· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών και πληροφόρησης σε σχέση με όλες τις προαναφερθείσες υπηρεσίες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Building construction; Building construction services in the field of civil engineering, electricity, and energy; Building project management services; Supervision, inspection and management relating to building work; Building maintenance and repair; Building installation services; insulation of buildings; project management of building works and the upgrading of installations, building apparatus, equipment and appliances designed to increase energy efficiency and energy conservation; consultancy, information and advisory services relating to all of the aforementioned services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de construcción; Servicios de construcción en materia de ingeniería civil, electricidad y energía; Servicios de gestión de proyectos para la construcción; Supervisión, vigilancia y gestión (dirección) de trabajos de construcción; Mantenimiento y reparación de edificios; Servicios de instalación; Aislamiento de edificios; Gestión de proyectos de obras de construcción y la mejora de instalaciones, aparatos de construcción y equipos diseñados para aumentar la eficiencia energética y la conservación de la energía; Servicios de consultoría, información y asesoramiento relacionados con todos los servicios mencionados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ehitustegevus; Ehitusteenused järgmise alal: tsiviilehitus, elektri ja energia tootmine; Ehitusprojektide juhtimise teenused; Ehitustööde ülevaatus, järelevalve ja juhtimine; Ehitiste hooldus ja remont; Paigaldustööd; Ehitiste soojustamine; Ehitustööde projektijuhtimine ja ehitusseadmete, -aparatuuri, -varustuse ning -paigaldiste täiustamine energiatõhususe ja energia säästmise suurendamiseks; Info- ja nõustamisteenused ning konsultatsioonid eelmainitud teenuste kohta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Rakentaminen; Rakennusten rakentamispalvelut tie- ja vesirakentamisen, sähkön ja energian alalla; Rakennusprojektien hallintapalvelut; Rakennustyön valvonta, tarkkailu ja johtaminen; Rakennusten huolto ja korjaus; Asennuspalvelut; Rakennusten eristäminen; Rakennustöihin liittyvä projektinjohtaminen sekä energiatehokkuuden ja energiansäästön lisäämiseen suunniteltujen laitteistojen, rakennuslaitteiden, -välineiden ja -kojeiden tasonnosto; Kaikkiin edellä mainittuihin palveluihin liittyvät konsultointi-, tiedotus- ja neuvontapalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Construction; Services de construction de bâtiments dans le domaine de l'ingénierie civile, de l'électricité et de l'énergie; Services de gestion de projets de construction; Supervision, contrôle et direction (gestion) de travaux de construction; Entretien et réparation d'immeubles; Services d'installation; Isolation de bâtiments; Gestion de projets de travaux de construction et mise à niveau d'installations, appareils de bâtiments, équipements et dispositifs conçus pour augmenter le rendement énergétique et la conservation de l'énergie; Services de conseil, d'information et d'assistance concernant tous les services précités.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Građevina; Usluga izgradnje u području građevinarstva, električne energije i energetike; Usluge upravljanja građevinskim projektima; Nadzor, nadgledanje i nadzor (vođenje) nad građevinskim radovima; Održavanje i popravak zgrada; Usluge postavljanja; Izolacija zgrada; Upravljanje projektima u građevinskim radovima i nadogradnji instalacija, građevinskih uređaja, opreme i uređaja namijenjenih povećanju energetske učinkovitosti i očuvanja energije; Informativne, savjetodavne i konzultantske usluge povezane s navedenim uslugama.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Építkezés; Építési szolgáltatások az építőmérnöki munka, villamosság és energia területén; Építési projektvezetési szolgáltatások; Ellenőrzés, felügyelet és igazgatás ellátása építési tevékenységek során; Épület karbantartás és javítás; Felszerelési szolgáltatások; Épületek szigetelése; Építési munkák projektmenedzsmentje, valamint létesítmények, építőipari berendezések, felszerelések és készülékek korszerűsítése az energiahatékonyság és az energiatakarékosság növelése céljából; Összes fent említett szolgáltatással kapcsolatos tájékoztató és tanácsadó szolgálat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Costruzione; Servizi di consulenza in materia edile nel settore dell'ingegneria civile, dell'elettricità e dell'energia; Gestione di progetti d'edilizia; Supervisione, controllo e direzione di lavori di costruzione; Manutenzione e riparazione di edifici; Servizi d'installazione; Isolamento di edifici; Gestione di progetti riguardanti opere edili e miglioramento d'impianti, apparecchi edili, apparecchiature ed accessori studiati per migliorare l'efficienza energetica e la conservazione d'energia; Servizi informativi e di consulenza relativi ai suddetti servizi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Statyba; Pastatų statybos paslaugos civilinės inžinerijos, elektros ir energetikos srityse; Statybų projektų administravimas; Statybos darbų priežiūra ir kontrolė (vadovavimas); Pastatų priežiūra ir remontas; Instaliavimo [įdiegimo] paslaugos; Pastatų izoliavimo darbai; Pastatų projektų valdymo ir įrengimų, statybinių aparatų, įrangos ir prietaisų, skirtų energijos vartojimo efektyvumui didinti ir energijos taupymui, tobulinimas; Informacinės, patariamosios ir konsultacinės paslaugos, susijusios su aukščiau nurodytosiomis paslaugomis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Būvniecība; Ēku celtniecības pakalpojumi inženierbūvniecības, elektrības un enerģijas jomā; Būvprojektu pārvaldīšana; Celtniecības pārraudzība, uzraudzība un vadīšana (vadība); Ēku apkope un remonts; Labiekārtošanas (iekārtu uzstādīšanas) darbi; Ēku izolācija; Būvdarbu projektu vadīšana, kā arī tādu instalāciju, celtniecības iekārtu, aprīkojuma un ierīču uzlabošana, kas ir paredzētas energoefektivitātes uzlabošanai un enerģijas saglabāšanai; Informācijas, padomdevēju un konsultāciju pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar visiem iepriekšminētajiem pakalpojumiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' kostruzzjoni; Servizzi ta' kostruzzjoni tal-bini fil-qasam tal-inġinerija ċivili, l-elettriku u l-enerġija; Servizzi ta' ġestjoni ta' proġetti ta' bini; Superviżjoni, sorveljanza u ġestjoni (sorveljanza) ta' xogħol tal-bini; Manutenzjoni u tiswija ta' bini; Servizzi ta' installazzjoni; Iżolazzjoni ta' bini; Ġestjoni ta' proġett ta' xogħol tal-bini u l-aġġornament ta' installazzjonijiet, apparat tal-bini, apparat u tagħmir intiżi biex ikabbru l-effiċjenza fl-enerġija u l-konservazzjoni tal-enerġija; Servizzi ta' informazzjoni, pariri u konsulenza dwar is-servizzi kollha hawn fuq imsemmija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Bouw; Bouwkundige advisering op het gebied van civiele techniek, elektrotechniek en energie; Beheer van bouwprojecten; supervisie, toezicht en directievoering (leiding) over bouwkundige werkzaamheden; Onderhoud en reparatie van gebouwen; Installatiewerkzaamheden; Isolatie van gebouwen; Projectbeheer met betrekking tot bouwwerkzaamheden en de renovatie van installaties, apparaten, uitrusting en toestellen voor gebouwen, ontworpen voor het verbeteren van de energiezuinigheid en voor energiebesparing; Consultancy, informatie en advisering met betrekking tot elk van de voornoemde diensten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi budowlane; Usługi budowlane w dziedzinie inżynierii wodno-lądowej, elektryczności i energii; Usługi zarządzania projektami budowlanymi; Nadzorowanie, kontrola i prowadzenie prac budowlanych (kierowanie pracami budowlanymi); Konserwacja i naprawa budynków; Usługi instalacyjne; Izolowanie budynków; Zarządzanie projektem robót budowlanych i modernizacji instalacji, urządzeń, sprzętu i urządzeń budowlanych mających na celu zwiększenie efektywności energetycznej i oszczędności energii; Usługi informacyjne, doradcze i konsultacyjne w zakresie wszystkich, uprzednio wymienionych usług.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Construção; Serviços de construção nos domínios da engenharia civil, eletricidade e energia; Serviços de gestão de projectos de construção; Supervisão, vigilância e direção de trabalhos de construção; Manutenção e reparação de edifícios; Serviços de instalação; Isolamento de edifícios; Gestão de projetos de obras de construção e atualização de instalações, aparelhos, equipamento e dispositivos de construção concebidos para melhorar a eficiência energética e a conservação de energia; Serviços de consultadoria, de informações e de assessoria relacionados com todos os serviços atrás referidos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Construcţii; Servicii de construcții de clădiri în domeniul tehnicii civile, electricității și energiei; Servicii de management proiect de constructii; Supervizare, supraveghere şi dirigenţie (conducere) a lucrărilor de construcţii; Reparaţii şi întreţinere de clădiri; Servicii de instalatii; Lucrări de izolaţii la clădiri; Gestionare de proiect referitor la lucrări de construcție și modernizarea instalațiilor, aparatelor, din clădiri, echipamentelor și instalațiilor destinate creșterii eficienței energetice și conservării energiei; Servicii de consultanta, informare si consiliere in domeniul tuturor serviciilor mentionate anterior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Stavebníctvo; Stavebné služby v oblasti inžinierskych stavieb, elektriny a energie; Služby v oblasti stavebného projektového manažmentu; Dohľad, dozor a riadenie (vedenie) v súvislosti so stavebnými prácami; Údržba a opravy budov; Inštalačné/zriaďovacie služby; Zatepľovanie stavieb; Riadenie projektov v oblasti stavebných prác a zlepšovania systémov, zariadení, vybavenia a spotrebičov na zvyšovanie šetrenia energie a premeny energie; Informačné, poradenské a konzultačné služby týkajúce sa všetkých uvedených služieb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Gradbeništvo; Storitve gradnje zgradb na področju gradbeništva, električne energije in energije; Storitve upravljanja gradbenih projektov; Supervizorstvo, nadzor in kontrola (vodenje) gradbenih dejavnosti; Vzdrževanje in popravilo zgradb; Inštalacije; Izolacija stavb; Vodenje projektov gradbenih del in nadgradnje napeljav, gradbenih aparatov, opreme in naprav, oblikovanih za povečanje energetske učinkovitosti in varčevanja z energijo; Informacijske in svetovalne storitve v zvezi z omenjenimi storitvami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Uppförande/anläggande av byggnationer; Byggkonstruktionstjänster inom området för väg- och vattenbyggnation, elektricitet och energi; Ledningstjänster avseende byggnadsprojekt; Övervakning, tillsyn och drift (ledning) av bygg- och anläggningsarbeten; Underhåll och reparation av byggnader; Installationstjänster; Byggnadsisolering; Projektledning avseende byggnadsarbeten och uppgradering av installationer, byggapparater, utrustning och apparater konstruerade för att öka energieffektivitet och energisparande; Konsultation, information och rådgivning rörande samtliga nämnda tjänster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>39</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Захранване с и дистрибуция на енергия, горива, изкопаеми горива, електричество, електрическа енергия, газ, природен газ и газообразни горива; Услуги за дистрибуция, предоставяне и транспортиране на възобновяема енергия; Публични комунални услуги във вид на разпространение на електричество и газ; Консултации, информация и консултантски услуги свързани с доставка и дистрибуция на газ, електричество и други видове енергия.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Dodávka a distribuce energie, paliv, fosilních paliv, elektřiny, elektrické energie, plynu, zemního plynu a plynných paliv; Distribuce a rozvod obnovitelné energie; Komunální služby ve formě distribuce elektřiny a plynu; Poradenské, informační a konzultační služby vztahující se k dodávce a distribuci plynu, elektřiny a ostatních forem energie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Levering og distribution af energi, brændstoffer, fossilt brændsel, elektricitet, elektrisk energi, gas, naturgas og luftformige brændstoffer; Distribution og forsyning af vedvarende energi; Offentlige forsyningsværk til distribution af elektricitet og gas; Rådgivning, information og konsulentbistand vedrørende forsyning og distribution af gas, elektricitet og andre former for energi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Versorgung mit und Verteilung von Energie, Brennstoffen, fossilen Brennstoffen, Elektrizität, elektrischer Energie, Gas, Erdgas und gasförmigen Brennstoffen; Verteilung von und Versorgung mit erneuerbarer Energie; Öffentliche Versorgungsleistungen in Form der Verteilung von Elektrizität und Gas; Beratung und Information in Bezug auf die Versorgung mit und die Verteilung von Gas, Strom und anderen Energieformen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εφοδιασμός και διανομή ενέργειας, καυσίμων, ορυκτών καυσίμων, ηλεκτρισμού, ηλεκτρικής ενέργειας, αερίου, φυσικού αερίου και αέριων καυσίμων· Διανομή και παροχή ανανεώσιμης ενέργειας· Υπηρεσίες κοινής ωφελείας με τη μορφή διανομής ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος και αερίου· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών και πληροφοριών σε σχέση με την παροχή και τη διανομή αερίου, ηλεκτρισμού και λοιπών μορφών ενέργειας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Supply and distribution of energy, fuels, fossil fuels, electricity, electrical energy, gas, natural gas and gaseous fuels; supply and distribution of renewable energy; public utility services in the nature of electricity and gas distribution; advisory, information and consultancy services relating to the supply and distribution of electricity, gas and other forms of energy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Suministro y distribución de energía, combustibles, combustibles fósiles, electricidad, energía eléctrica, gas, gas natural y combustibles gaseosos; Distribución y suministro de energías renovables; Servicios públicos del tipo de distribución de electricidad y gas; Servicios de asesoramiento, información y consultas relacionados con la distribución y el suministro de gas, electricidad y otras formas de energía.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Energia, kütuste, fossiilkütuste, elektrienergia, gaasi, maagaasi ja gaaskütuste tarnimine ja jaotus; Taastuvenergiajaotus ja -varustus; Kommunaalteenused elektri- ja gaasivarustusteenustena; Nõustamis-, info- ja konsulteerimisteenused seoses gaasi, elektri ning muude energiavormide tarnimise ja jaotamisega.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Energian, polttoaineiden, fossiilisten polttoaineiden, sähkön, sähköenergian, kaasun, maakaasun ja kaasumaisten polttoaineiden toimitus ja jakelu; Uusiutuvan energian toimitus ja jakelu; Yleishyödylliset palvelut sähkön ja kaasun jakelun muodossa; Neuvonta-, tiedotus- ja konsultointipalvelut, jotka liittyvät kaasun, sähkön ja muiden energiamuotojen toimitukseen ja jakeluun.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Fourniture et distribution d'énergie, combustibles, combustibles fossiles, électricité, énergie électrique, gaz, gaz naturel et combustibles gazeux; Distribution et fourniture d'énergie renouvelable; Services publics sous forme de distribution d'électricité et de gaz; Services de conseils, d'informations et d'assistance liés à l'alimentation et à la distribution de gaz, d'électricité et d'autres formes d'énergie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Nabava i distribucija energije, goriva, fosilnih goriva, električne energije, plina, prirodnog plina i plinovitih goriva; Distribucija i opskrba obnovljivom energijom; Komunalne usluge u obliku distribucije električne energije i plina; Savjetodavne, informativne i konzultantske usluge povezane s opskrbom i distribucijom plina, električne energije i drugih oblika energije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Energia, tüzelőanyagok, fosszilis tüzelőanyagok, elektromosság, elektromos energia, gáz, földgáz és gázállapotú tüzelőanyagok szolgáltatása és terjesztése; Megújuló energia elosztása és biztosítása; Közüzemi szolgáltatások villamos energia- és gázelosztás formájában; Gáz, elektromos áram és az energia egyéb formáinak szolgáltatásával és elosztásával kapcsolatos tanácsadás, tájékoztatás és konzultáció.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Fornitura e distribuzione di energia, combustibili, combustibili fossili, elettricità, energia elettrica, gas, gas naturale e combustibili gassosi; Distribuzione ed erogazione d'energia rinnovabile; Servizi di pubblica utilità sotto forma di distribuzione d'elettricità e gas; Servizi di consulenza ed informazione in materia di fornitura e distribuzione di gas, elettricità ed altre forme d'energia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Energijos, degalų, iškastinio kuro, elektros, elektros energijos, dujų, gamtinių dujų ir dujinio kuro tiekimas ir paskirstymas; Atsinaujinančiosios energijos paskirstymas ir tiekimas; Elektros ir dujų paskirstymo komunalinės paslaugos; Patariamosios, informacinės ir konsultacinės paslaugos, susijusios su dujų, elektros ir kitų formų energijos tiekimu ir platinimu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Enerģijas, degvielas, fosilās degvielas, elektrības, elektriskās enerģijas, gāzes, dabasgāzes un gāzveida degvielas nodrošināšana un izplatīšana; Atjaunojamās enerģijas sadale un piegāde; Publiskās lietošanas pakalpojumi elektrības un gāzes izplatīšanas jomā; Ieteikumu, informācijas un konsultāciju pakalpojumi saistībā ar gāzes, elektrības un citu enerģijas veidu padevi un izplatīšanu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Forniment u tqassim ta' enerġija, karburanti, karburanti tal-fossili, elettriċità, enerġija elettrika, gass, gass naturali u karburanti tal-gass; Distribuzzjoni u provvista ta' enerġija li tiġġedded; Servizzi ta' utilità pubblika f'għamla ta' distribuzzjoni tal-elettriku u l-gass; Servizzi ta' għoti ta' pariri, informazzjoni u konsulenza dwar il-provvista u distribuzzjoni ta' gass, elettriku u forom oħra ta' enerġija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Levering en distributie van energie, brandstoffen, fossiele brandstoffen, elektriciteit, elektrische energie, gas, aardgas en gasvormige brandstoffen; Distributie en levering van duurzame energie; Openbare nutsdiensten in de vorm van elektriciteits- en gasvoorziening; Advies, informatie en raadgeving met betrekking tot de aanvoer en distributie van gas, elektriciteit en andere vormen van energie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dostarczanie i dystrybucja energii, paliwa, paliwa kopalnego, elektryczności, energii elektrycznej, benzyny, gazu ziemnego i paliwa gazowego; Dystrybucja i dostarczanie energii odnawialnej; Usługi komunalne w charakterze dystrybucji energii elektrycznej oraz gazu; Doradztwo, usługi informacyjne i doradcze odnoszące się do dostaw i dystrybucji gazu, energii elektrycznej i innych form energii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Abastecimento e distribuição de energia, combustíveis, combustíveis fósseis, electricidade, energia eléctrica, gás, gás natural e combustíveis gasosos; Distribuição e fornecimento de energia renovável; Serviços de utilidade pública sob a forma de distribuição de eletricidade e gás; Serviços de assessoria, informações e consultadoria relacionados com o fornecimento e a distribuição de gás, eletricidade e outras formas de energia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Furnizare şi distribuţie de energie, combustibili, combustibili fosili, electricitate, energie electrică, gaz, gaze naturale şi combustibili gazoşi; Distribuire şi alimentare cu energie regenerabilă; Servicii de utilități publice sub forma distribuției de electricitate și gaze; Servicii de consiliere, informare şi consultanţă legate de alimentarea şi distribuirea de gaz, electricitate şi alte forme de energie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Dodávka a distribúcia energie, palív, fosílnych palív, elektriny, elektrickej energie, plynu, zemného plynu a plynných palív; Distribúcia a dodávka obnoviteľnej energie; Komunálne služby v podobe distribúcie elektriny a zemného plynu; Poradenské, informačné a konzultačné služby v oblasti dodávky a distribúcie plynu, elektriny a iných foriem energie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oskrba in distribucija energije, goriv, fosilnih goriv, elektrike, električne energije, plina, zemeljskega plina in plinastih goriv; Distribucija in dobava obnovljive energije; Komunalne storitve v obliki distribucije električne energije in plina; Svetovalne, informacijske storitve in posvetovalne storitve v zvezi z dobavo in distribucijo plina, električne energije in drugih oblik energije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Leverans och distribution av energi, bränslen, fossila bränslen, elektricitet, elektrisk energi, gas, naturgas och gasformiga bränslen; Distribution och tillförsel av förnybar energi; Allmännyttiga tjänster i form av distribution av elektricitet och gas; Rådgivnings-, informations- och konsulttjänster inom området för tillförsel och distribution av gas, elektricitet och andra energiformer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>40</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Генерация и производство на енергия, горива, изкопаеми горива, електричество, електрическа енергия, газ, природен газ и обработка на материали с газови горива; Производство на регенеративна енергия; Информационни съветнически и консултантски услуги, свързани с всички гореспосочени услуги.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Výroba energie, paliv, fosilních paliv, elektřiny, elektrické energie, plynu, zemního plynu a plynných paliv, úprava materiálů; Produkce a výroba obnovitelné energie; Informační, poradenské a konzultační služby vztahující se k výše uvedeným službám.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Generering og produktion af energi, brændstoffer, fossilt brændsel, elektricitet, elektrisk energi, gas, naturgas og luftformige brændstoffer, behandling af materialer; Regenerativ energiproduktion; Information, rådgivning og bistand i forbindelse med alle ovennævnte tjenesteydelser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Erzeugung und Produktion von Energie, Brennstoffen, fossilen Brennstoffen, Elektrizität, elektrischer Energie, Gas, Erdgas und gasförmigen Brennstoffen, Materialbearbeitung; Regenerative Energieerzeugung; Information und Beratung in Bezug auf alle vorstehend genannten Leistungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παραγωγή ενέργειας, καυσίμων, ορυκτών καυσίμων, ηλεκτρισμού, ηλεκτρικής ενέργειας, αερίου, φυσικού αερίου και αέριων καυσίμων, επεξεργασία υλικών· Παραγωγή ανανεώσιμης ενέργειας· Υπηρεσίες παροχής πληροφοριών και συμβουλών σε σχέση με το σύνολο των προαναφερόμενων υπηρεσιών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Generation and production of energy, fuels, fossil fuels, electricity, electrical energy, gas, natural gas and gaseous fuels treatment of materials; Generation and production of renewable energy; information, advisory and consultancy services relating to all of the aforementioned services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Generación y producción de energía, combustibles, combustibles fósiles, electricidad, energía eléctrica, gas, gas natural y combustibles gaseosos, tratamiento de materiales; Producción de energía regenerativa; Servicios de información y asesoramiento relacionados con todos los servicios mencionados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Järgmiste ressursside tootmisteenused: energia, kütused, fossiilkütused, elektrienergia, gaas, maagaas, küttegaas ja materjalitöötlus; Taastuvenergia tootmine; Info- ja nõustamisteenused ning konsultatsioonid eelmainitud teenuste kohta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Energian, polttoaineiden, fossiilisten polttoaineiden, sähkön, sähköenergian, kaasun, maakaasun ja kaasumaisten polttoaineiden kehitys ja tuotanto, materiaalien käsittely; Uusiutuvan energian tuotanto; Kaikkiin edellä mainittuihin palveluihin liittyvät neuvonta-, tiedotus- ja konsultointipalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Génération et production d'énergie, de combustibles, de combustibles fossiles, d'électricité, d'énergie électrique, de gaz, de gaz naturel et de combustibles gazeux, traitement de matériaux; production d'énergie renouvelable; Services d'information et de conseils dans tous les domaines précités.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Proizvodnja energije, goriva, fosilnih goriva, električne struje, električne energije, plina, prirodnog plina i plinovitih goriva, obrada materijala; Energija (proizvodnja energije); Informacijske i savjetodavne usluge te usluge savjetovanja povezane sa svim prethodno navedenim uslugama.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Energia, üzemanyagok, fosszilis tüzelőanyagok, elektromosság, villamos energia, gáz, földgáz és gáznemű üzemanyagok előállítása és termelése, anyagok kezelése; Megújuló energia termelése és előállítása; Összes fent említett szolgáltatással kapcsolatos tájékoztató és tanácsadó szolgálat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Generazione e produzione d'energia, combustibili, combustibili fossili, elettricità, energia elettrica, gas, gas naturale e combustibili gassosi, trattamento di materiali; Produzione d'energia da fonti rinnovabili; Informazioni e consulenza relative ai suddetti servizi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Energijos, kuro, iškastinio kuro, elektros, elektros energijos, dujų, gamtinių dujų ir dujinio kuro gamyba ir gamyba; Atsinaujinančios energijos gamyba; Informacinės, patariamosios ir konsultacinės paslaugos, susijusios su aukščiau nurodytosiomis paslaugomis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Enerģijas, kurināmā, fosilā kurināmā, elektrības, elektriskās enerģijas, gāzes, dabasgāzes un gāzveida kurināmā ražošana un izstrāde; Atjaunojamās enerģijas ražošana un ģenerēšana; Informācijas, padomdevēju un konsultāciju pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar visiem iepriekšminētajiem pakalpojumiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Il-ġenerazzjoni u l-produzzjoni tal-enerġija, karburanti, karburanti tal-fossili, elettriċità, enerġija elettrika, gass, gass naturali u karburanti tal-gass, trattament ta' materjali; Produzzjoni ta' enerġija li tiġġedded; Servizzi ta' informazzjoni, pariri u konsulenza dwar is-servizzi kollha hawn fuq imsemmija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Het opwekken en produceren van energie, brandstoffen, fossiele brandstoffen, elektriciteit, elektrische energie, gas, aardgas en gasvormige brandstoffen, materiaalbehandeling; Productie en opwekking van duurzame energie; Informatie, advisering en consultancy met betrekking tot de voornoemde diensten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Wytwarzanie i produkcja energii, paliwa, paliw kopalnych, energii elektrycznej, energii elektrycznej, gazu, gazu ziemnego i paliwa gazowego, obróbka materiałów; Wytwarzanie energii odnawialnych; Usługi informacyjne, doradcze i konsultacyjne w zakresie wszystkich, uprzednio wymienionych usług.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Geração e produção de energia, combustíveis, combustíveis fósseis, eletricidade, energia elétrica, gás, gás natural e combustíveis gasosos, tratamento de materiais; Produção de energias renováveis; Serviços de informações, assessoria e consultadoria relacionados com todos os serviços atrás referidos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Generare și producție de energie, combustibili, combustibili fosili, electricitate, energie electrică, gaz, gaze naturale și combustibili gazoși, tratamentul materialelor; Generare de energie regenerabilă; Servicii de informare, consiliere si consultanta referitoare la toate serviciile mentionate mai sus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Výroba energie, palív, fosílnych palív, elektriny, elektrickej energie, plynu, zemného plynu a plynných palív, úprava materiálov; Výroba obnoviteľnej energie; Informačné, poradenské a konzultačné služby týkajúce sa všetkých uvedených služieb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Proizvodnja energije, goriv, fosilnih goriv, elektrike, električne energije, plina, zemeljskega plina in plinastih goriv, obdelava materialov; Proizvodnja obnovljive energije; Informacijske, svetovalne in posvetovalne storitve v zvezi z vsemi omenjenimi storitvami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Generering och produktion av energi, bränslen, fossila bränslen, elektricitet, elektrisk energi, gas, naturgas och gasformiga bränslen, materialhantering; Regenerativ energiproduktion; Informations-, rådgivnings- och konsulttjänster avseende alla nämnda tjänster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/101</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/173</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>12503</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>10633</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
