<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:44</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018222483</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018222483</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-08</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-08</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>VIMMU</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Научни и технологични услуги; Предоставяне на изследователски услуги; Биологични, клинични и медицински проучвания; Консултации във връзка с фармацевтични изследвания и разработки; Медицински лабораторни услуги; Тестване на фармацевтични продукти; Сертифициране, качествен контрол; Тестване, анализ и оценка на стоки и услуги на други с цел сертифициране.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vědecké a technologické služby; Služby v oblasti zajišťování výzkumu; Biologický výzkum, klinický výzkum a lékařský výzkum; Poradenství týkající se farmaceutického výzkumu a vývoje; Lékařské laboratorní služby (výzkum); Testování léčiv; Certifikace (kontrola kvality); Testování, analyzování a hodnocení zboží a služeb druhých pro účely certifikace.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Videnskabelige og teknologiske tjenesteydelser; Tilvejebringelse af forskningstjenester; Biologisk forskning, klinisk forskning og medicinsk forskning; Konsulentbistand vedrørende lægemiddelforskning og -udvikling; Medicinsk laboratorievirksomhed; Testning af farmaceutiske præparater; Certificering (kvalitetskontrol); Afprøvning, analyse og vurdering af andres varer og tjenesteydelser med henblik på certificering.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wissenschaftliche und technologische Dienstleistungen; Forschungsdienstleistungen; Biologische Forschung, klinische Forschung und medizinische Forschung; Beratung hinsichtlich pharmazeutischer Forschung und Entwicklung; Dienstleistungen eines medizinischen Labors; Durchführen von technischen Test bezüglich Arzneimitteln; Zertifizierung [Qualitätskontrolle]; Prüfung, Analyse und Bewertung von Waren und Dienstleistungen Dritter für Zertifizierungszwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Επιστημονικές και τεχνολογικές υπηρεσίες· Παροχή υπηρεσιών έρευνας· Βιολογική έρευνα, κλινική έρευνα και ιατρική έρευνα· Παροχή συμβουλών για τη φαρμακευτική έρευνα και ανάπτυξη· Ιατρικά εργαστήρια· Δοκιμή φαρμακευτικών προϊόντων· Πιστοποίηση (έλεγχος ποιότητας)· Δοκιμή, ανάλυση και αξιολόγηση των αγαθών και υπηρεσιών άλλων για σκοπούς πιστοποίησης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Science and technology services; Provision of research services; Biological research, clinical research and medical research; Consultancy relating to pharmaceutical research and development; Medical laboratory services; Testing of pharmaceuticals; Certification [quality control]; Testing, analysis and evaluation of the goods and services of others for the purpose of certification.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios científicos y tecnológicos; Prestación de servicios de investigación; Investigación biológica, investigación clínica e investigación médica; Consultoría relacionada con la investigación y el desarrollo farmacéuticos; Servicios de un laboratorio médico; Ensayos clínicos de productos farmacéuticos; Certificación [control de calidad]; Pruebas, análisis y evaluación de productos y servicios de terceros para certificación.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Teadus- ja tehnoloogiateenused; Uurimine, teadustöö; Bioloogilised, kliinilised ja meditsiinilised uuringud; Ravimiuuringute ja -arendusega seotud konsultatsioonid; Meditsiinilabori teenused; Ravimite katsetamine; Sertifitseerimine [kvaliteedikontroll]; Kolmandate isikute kaupade ja teenuste katsetamine, analüüsimine ja hindamine sertifitseerimiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tieteelliset ja teknologiset palvelut; Tutkimuspalvelujen tarjoaminen; Biologiset, kliiniset ja lääketieteelliset tutkimukset; Lääketutkimukseen ja -kehitykseen liittyvä neuvonta; Lääketieteelliset laboratoriopalvelut; Farmaseuttisten tuotteiden testaus; Sertifioinnit [laadunvalvonta]; Muiden tarjoamien tavaroiden ja palvelujen testaus, analysointi ja arviointi sertifiointitarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services scientifiques et technologiques; Mise à disposition de services de recherches scientifiques; Recherches biologiques, cliniques et médicales; Consultation en matière de recherche et développement pharmaceutiques; Services de laboratoires médicaux (recherche médicale); Réalisation de tests sur des produits pharmaceutiques; Contrôle de qualité en vue de la certification; Test, analyse et évaluation des produits et services de tiers à des fins de certification.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge znanosti i tehnologije; Pružanje istraživačkih usluga; Biološko istraživanje, kliničko istraživanje i medicinsko istraživanje; Savjetovanje o farmaceutskom istraživanju i razvoju; Usluge medicinskog laboratorija; Ispitivanje farmaceutskih proizvoda; Certifikacija [kontrola kvalitete]; Testiranje, analiza i ocjena robe i usluga za druge u svrhu certifikacije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tudományos és technológiai szolgáltatások; Kutatási szolgáltatások biztosítása; Biológiai kutatás, klinikai kutatás és egészségügyi kutatás; Gyógyszerészeti kutatással és fejlesztéssel kapcsolatos konzultáció; Orvosi laboratóriumi szolgáltatások; Gyógyszerek tesztelése; Tanúsítás [minőségellenőrzés]; Mások áruinak és szolgáltatásainak tesztelése, elemzése és értékelése tanúsítási célokra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di scienza e tecnologia; Fornitura di servizi di ricerca; Ricerca biologica, ricerca clinica e ricerca medica; Consulenza in materia di ricerca e sviluppo nel settore farmaceutico; Servizi di laboratori medici; Test di prodotti farmaceutici; Certificazione [controllo qualità]; Testing, analisi e valutazione di prodotti e servizi di terzi a scopo di certificazione.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Mokslo ir technologijų paslaugos; Tyrimų paslaugos; Biologiniai tyrimai, klinikiniai tyrimai ir medicininiai tyrimai; Farmacinių tyrimų ir vystymo konsultacijos; Medicinos laboratorijų paslaugos; Farmacijos produktų bandymas; Sertifikavimas [kokybės kontrolė]; Prekių ir paslaugų kitiems bandymas, analizė ir vertinimas sertifikatų išdavimo tikslais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Zinātniskie un tehnoloģiskie pakalpojumi; Izpētes pakalpojumu nodrošināšana; Bioloģiskie pētījumi, klīniskie pētījumi un medicīniskie pētījumi; Ar farmācijas pētniecību un izstrādi saistītas konsultācijas; Medicīnisko laboratoriju pakalpojumi; Farmaceitisko līdzekļu testēšana; Sertificēšana [kvalitātes kontrole]; Trešo personu preču un pakalpojumu pārbaude, analizēšana un novērtēšana sertifikācijas nolūkam.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi xjentifiċi u teknoloġiċi; Il-provvista ta' servizzi ta' riċerka; Riċerka bijoloġika, riċerka klinika u riċerka medika; Konsulenza relatata ma’ riċerka u żvilupp farmaċewtiku; Servizzi ta' laboratorju mediku; Ittestjar ta' sustanzi farmaċewtiċi; Servizzi ta' ċertifikazzjoni, kontroll tal-kwalità; L-ittestjar, l-analiżi u l-valutazzjoni ta' oġġetti u servizzi għall-oħrajn għal skopijiet ta' ċertifikazzjoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Wetenschappelijke en technologische diensten; Dienstverlening voor wetenschappelijk onderzoek; Biologisch onderzoek, klinisch onderzoek en medisch onderzoek; Advisering met betrekking tot onderzoek en ontwikkeling op farmaceutisch gebied; Diensten van medische laboratoria; Testen van farmaceutische producten; Certificaties, kwaliteitscontroles; Testen, analyseren en evalueren van goederen en diensten van anderen voor certificeringdoeleinden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi naukowe i technologiczne; Świadczenie usług badawczych; Badania biologiczne, badania kliniczne i badania medyczne; Doradztwo związane z badaniami farmaceutycznymi i opracowywaniem produktów farmaceutycznych; Laboratoria medyczne; Testowanie środków farmaceutycznych; Certyfikacja [kontrola jakości]; Testowanie, analiza i wycena towarów i usług osób trzecich do celów certyfikacji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de ciência e tecnologia; Fornecimento de serviços de investigação; Investigação biológica, investigação clínica e investigação médica; Consultoria em matéria de investigação e desenvolvimento farmacêutico; Serviços de laboratórios médicos; Ensaio de produtos farmacêuticos; Certificação [controle de qualidade]; Teste, análise e avaliação dos produtos e serviços de outros para certificação.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii în domeniul științei și tehnologiei; Prestare de servicii de cercetare; Cercetare biologică, cercetare clinică și cercetare medicală; Consultanță privind cercetarea și dezvoltarea farmaceutică; Laboratoare medicale; Testarea produselor farmaceutice; Certificare [controlul calității]; Testare, analiză și evaluare de produse și servicii ale altor persoane, în scopul certificării.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vedecké a technologické služby; Poskytovanie výskumných služieb; Biologický výskum, klinický výskum a medicínsky výskum; Poradenstvo týkajúce sa farmaceutického výskumu a vývoja; Služby lekárskych laboratórií; Testovanie liečiv; Certifikácie (kontroly kvality); Testovanie, analýza a hodnotenie výrobkov a služieb klientov za účelom certifikácie pre tretie osoby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Znanstvene in tehnološke storitve; Nudenje raziskovalnih storitev; Biološke raziskave, klinične raziskave in medicinske raziskave; Svetovanje v zvezi s farmacevtskimi raziskavami in razvojem; Storitve medicinskih laboratorijev; Testiranje farmacevtskih izdelkov; Certificiranje [nadzor kakovosti]; Testiranje, analiza in ocenjevanje blaga in storitev drugih za namene certificiranja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Vetenskapliga och tekniska tjänster; Upplåtande av forskningstjänster; Biologisk forskning, klinisk forskning och medicinsk forskning; Konsultationer avseende läkemedelsforskning och -utveckling; Medicinska laboratorietjänster; Läkemedelstester; Certifieringstjänster [kvalitetskontroller]; Provning, analys och utvärdering av andras varor och tjänster för certifieringsändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>44</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Грижи за хигиената и красотата; Сауна услуги; Солариумни услуги; Услуги във фризьорски салони и салони за красота; Медицински услуги; Медицински грижи; Грижи от медицинска сестра в домашни условия; Фармацевтични консултации; Приготвяне на рецепти от фармацевти; Услуги за медицински анализи, за диагностични и лечебни цели, предоставени от медицински лаборатории; Медицински скрининг.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Hygienická a kosmetická péče; Sauny; Solária; Služby kadeřnictví a salónu krásy; Zdravotní péče; Služby lékařské péče; Ošetřovatelská péče (domácí návštěvy); Farmaceutické poradenství; Příprava receptů lékárníky; Lékařské analýzy pro diagnostické a léčebné účely poskytované lékařskými laboratořemi; Lékařská vyšetření.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sundheds- og skønhedspleje; Saunavirksomhed; Solarievirksomhed; Tjenesteydelser i forbindelse med frisør- og skønhedssaloner; Medicinske tjenesteydelser; Lægelige plejetjenester; Hjemmesygepleje; Farmaceutisk rådgivningsvirksomhed; Behandling af recepter udført af farmaceuter; Medicinsk analyse til brug for diagnosticering og behandling udbudt af medicinske laboratorier; Medicinsk screening.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gesundheits- und Schönheitspflege; Saunadienstleistungen; Dienstleistungen von Solarien; Dienstleistungen eines Friseur- und Schönheitssalons; Medizinische Dienstleistungen; Ärztliche Versorgung; Häusliche Kranken- und Altenpflege; Pharmazeutische Beratung; Zubereitung von Rezepturen in Apotheken; Medizinische Analysedienstleistungen zu Diagnose- und Behandlungszwecken durch medizinische Labore; Durchführung medizinischer Tests.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υγιεινή και ομορφιά· Υπηρεσίες ατμόλουτρων φινλανδικού τύπου· Υπηρεσίες χώρων ηλιοθεραπείας με λάμπες υπεριωδών (solarium)· Υπηρεσίες κομμωτηρίων και κέντρων αισθητικής· Ιατρικές υπηρεσίες· Υπηρεσίες ιατρικής περίθαλψης· Νοσηλευτική φροντίδα παρεχόμενη στο σπίτι· Φαρμακευτική συμβουλευτική· Προετοιμασία συνταγών από φαρμακοποιούς· Υπηρεσίες ιατρικών αναλύσεων για διαγνωστικούς και θεραπευτικούς σκοπούς παρεχόμενες από ιατρικά εργαστήρια· Ιατρικές εξετάσεις.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hygienic and beauty care; Sauna services; Solarium services; Services of a hair and beauty salon; Medical services; Medical care; Home-visit nursing care; Pharmaceutical advice; Preparation of prescriptions by pharmacists; Medical analysis services for diagnostic and treatment purposes provided by medical laboratories; Medical screening.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cuidados de higiene y belleza; Servicios de sauna; Servicios de solárium; Servicios de un salón de peluquería y de belleza; Servicios médicos; Atención médica; Asistencia de enfermería a domicilio; Asesoramiento farmacéutico; Preparación de recetas médicas por farmacéuticos; Servicios de análisis médicos para diagnóstico y tratamiento prestados por laboratorios médicos; Screening (cribado) médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hügieeni- ja iluhooldusteenused; Saunateenused; Solaariumiteenused; Juuksuri- ja ilusalongiteenused; Meditsiiniteenused; Arstiabi; Koduhooldusteenused; Farmaatsiakonsultatsioonid; Retseptiravimite valmistamine apteekrite poolt; Meditsiinilaborite diagnostika ja ravi meditsiinianalüüsiteenused; Meditsiinilised sõeluuringud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Terveyden- ja kauneudenhoitopalvelut; Saunapalvelut; Solariumpalvelut; Kampaamo- ja kauneushoitolapalvelut; Lääkinnälliset palvelut; Lääketieteelliset hoitopalvelut; Kotisairaanhoito; Farmaseuttinen neuvonta; Reseptitilausten valmistaminen apteekeissa; Lääketieteellisten laboratorioiden tarjoamat lääketieteelliset analysointipalvelut diagnostisiin ja hoidollisiin tarkoituksiin; Lääketieteellinen seulonta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Soins hygiéniques et de beauté; Services de saunas; Services de solariums; Services d'un salon de coiffure et de beauté; Services médicaux; Soins médicaux; Soins infirmiers à domicile; Conseil pharmaceutique; Préparation d'ordonnances par des pharmaciens; Services d'analyses médicales fournis par des laboratoires médicaux à des fins diagnostiques et thérapeutiques; Dépistage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Higijenska i kozmetička njega; Usluge sauna; Usluge solarija; Usluge frizerskog i kozmetičkog salona; Medicinske usluge; Usluge medicinske njege; Pružanje zdravstvene njege u kući; Usluge farmaceutskog savjetovanja; Usluge farmaceuta za pripremu recepata; Usluge medicinske analize za potrebe dijagnoze i liječenja koje pružaju medicinski laboratoriji; Liječnički skrining.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Higiéniai és szépségápolási szolgáltatások; Szauna szolgáltatások; Szolárium szolgáltatások; Szépségszalon és fodrászati szolgáltatások; Orvosi szolgáltatások; Egészségügyi ellátás; Látogató ápolói szolgáltatások; Gyógyszerészeti konzultáció; Gyógyszerek elkészítéshez kapcsolódó gyógyszertári szolgáltatások; Orvosi laboratóriumok által nyújtott orvosi elemzési szolgáltatások diagnosztikai és kezelési célokra; Orvosi szűrővizsgálatok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Igiene e bellezza; Servizi di sauna; Servizi di solarium; Saloni di parrucchiere e di bellezza; Servizi medici; Cure mediche; Assistenza infermieristica domiciliare; Consulenza farmaceutica; Preparazione di ricette da parte di farmacisti; Servizi di analisi mediche a fini di diagnosi e trattamento resi da laboratori medici; Analisi mediche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Higieninė ir grožio priežiūra; Saunų paslaugos; Soliariumų paslaugos; Kirpyklos ir grožio salono paslaugos; Medicinos paslaugos; Medicininė priežiūra; Atvykstančių į namus slaugytojų paslaugos; Farmacinės konsultacijos; Receptų išrašymo farmacininkų paslaugos; Medicininių tyrimų laboratorijų paslaugos diagnozavimo ir gydymo reikmėms; Sveikatos tikrinimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Higiēniskās aprūpes un skaistumkopšanas pakalpojumi; Saunu pakalpojumi; Solāriju pakalpojumi; Frizētavu un skaistumkopšanas salonu pakalpojumi; Medicīniskie pakalpojumi; Medicīniskās aprūpes pakalpojumi; Slimnieku aprūpe mājās; Konsultācijas farmācijas jomā; Farmaceitu pakalpojumi recepšu zāļu izgatavošanā; Medicīnisko analīžu pakalpojumi diagnostikai un ārstēšanai, ko nodrošina medicīniskās laboratorijas; Medicīniskais skrīnings.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kura għall-iġjene u għas-saħħa; Servizzi ta' sawna; Servizzi ta' solarju; Servizzi ta' salon għax-xagħar u s-sbuħija; Servizzi mediċi; Servizzi ta' kura medika; Kura minn infermiera fid-dar; Parir farmaċewtiku; Preparazzjoni ta' preskrizjonijiet minn farmaċisti; Servizzi ta' analiżi medika għal skopijiet ta' dijanjożi u trattament ipprovduti minn laboratorji mediċi; Iskrinjar mediku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Hygiëne en schoonheidsverzorging van mensen; Diensten van sauna's; Diensten van solaria; Diensten op het gebied van kap- en schoonheidssalons; Medische diensten; Medische zorg; Thuisverzorging; Advisering op farmaceutisch gebied; Het klaarmaken van recepten door apothekers; Medische analysediensten met betrekking tot diagnose en behandeling door medische laboratoria; Medisch testen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Higiena i pielęgnacja urody; Usługi saun; Usługi solariów; Usługi salonów fryzjersko-kosmetycznych; Usługi medyczne; Usługi opieki medycznej; Domowa opieka pielęgniarska; Porady w zakresie farmakologii; Sporządzanie leków recepturowych przez farmaceutów; Usługi analiz medycznych do celów diagnostycznych i leczniczych świadczone przez laboratoria medyczne; Badania przesiewowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cuidados de higiene e de beleza; Serviços de sauna; Serviços de solário; Serviços prestados por salões de cabeleireiro e por institutos de beleza; Serviços médicos; Cuidados médicos; Visitas e cuidados de enfermagem ao domicílio; Assessoria farmacêutica; Preparação de receitas médicas por farmacêuticos; Serviços de análises clínicas relacionados com o diagnóstico e tratamento prestados por laboratórios médicos; Análises médicas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Îngrijiri de igienă și frumusețe; Servicii de saună; Solar (Servicii de -); Servicii furnizate de saloane de coafură și înfrumusețare; Servicii medicale; Servicii de îngrijiri medicale; Asistență medicală la domiciliu; Consiliere farmaceutică; Prepararea de rețete de către farmaciști; Servicii de analize medicale în scop de diagnostic și tratament furnizate de laboratoare medicale; Depistare medicală [screening].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Hygienická a kozmetická starostlivosť; Sauny (služby); Soláriá (služby); Služby kaderníctva a salónu krásy; Lekárske služby; Služby lekárskej starostlivosti; Ošetrovateľská starostlivosť (návštevy v domácnosti); Farmaceutické poradenstvo; Lekárnické služby (príprava predpísaných liekov); Lekárske rozbory na diagnostické a liečebné účely poskytované lekárskymi laboratóriami; Lekárske vyšetrenia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Higienska in lepotna nega; Storitve savn; Storitve solarijev; Storitve frizerskih in lepotnih salonov; Zdravstvene storitve; Storitve zdravstvene nege; Zdravstvena nega na domu; Farmacevtsko svetovanje; Storitve farmacevtov za pripravo receptov; Storitve medicinskih analiz za namene diagnosticiranja in zdravljenja, nudene s strani medicinskih laboratorijev; Medicinski skrining.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hygien- och skönhetsvård; Bastutjänster; Solarietjänster; Tjänster tillhandahållna av friser- och skönhetssalonger; Medicinska tjänster; Medicinska vårdtjänster; Hemsjukvård; Farmaceutiska rådgivningstjänster; Farmaceutiska tjänster för att expediera recept; Medicinska analystjänster för diagnostiska- och behandlingsändamål tillhandahållna av medicinska laboratorier; Medicinsk screening.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>36370</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
