<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-28T08:53:48</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018222919</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018222919</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-08</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-08</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Gresonr</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Китайски традиционни лечебни билки; Антибактериални почистващи средства за лице; Санитарно облекло; Анестетици; Антисептични почистващи средства за уста; Препарати за пречистване на въздуха; Дезодоранти за автомобили; Бебешки пелени; Кaпсули за лекарства; Албуминни хранителни добавки; Колир (разтвор за очи); Противовъзпалителни средства; Антимикробни средства за измиване на уста; Антибактериален сапун; Препарати за пречистване на въздуха; Мляко на прах [за бебета]; Антибиотични таблетки; Храна за бебета; Антибактериални препарати за миене на ръце; Противомикробни средства за миене на ръце.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Tradiční čínské léčivé byliny; Antibakteriální čisticí přípravky na obličej; Menstruační hygienické potřeby; Anestetika; Antiseptické ústní vody; Přípravky na čištění vzduchu; Deodoranty do automobilů; Dětské pleny; Tobolky na léky; Proteinové potravinové doplňky; Oční kapky; Protizánětlivé přípravky; Antimikrobiální ústní vody; Antibakteriální mýdla; Přípravky na dezinfikování vzduchu; Sušené kojenecké mléko; Antibiotické tablety; Potraviny pro kojence a batolata; Antibakteriální prostředky na mytí rukou; Antimikrobiální přípravky na mytí rukou.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Traditionelle kinesiske medicinske urter; Antibakterielle rensemidler til ansigtet; Hygiejniske bind; Bedøvelsesmidler; Antiseptiske mundskyllemidler; Luftrensepræparater; Luftopfriskere til biler; Babybleer; Kapsler til medicin; Albumin til brug som kosttilskud; Collyrium [øjenskyllepræparater]; Antiinflammatoriske midler; Antimikrobielle mundskyllemidler; Antibakteriel sæbe; Præparater til luftsterilisering; Mælkepulver til spædbørn; Antibiotiske tabletter; Mad til spædbørn; Antibakterielle håndvaskemidler; Antimikrobielle håndvaskemidler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Traditionelle chinesische Heilkräuter; Antibakterielle Gesichtsreinigungsmittel; Verbände für Gesundheitszwecke; Anästhetika; Antiseptische Mundwässer; Luftreinigungsmittel; Deodorants für Autos; Babywindeln; Kapseln für medizinische Zwecke; Nahrungsergänzungsmittel aus Albumin; Kollyrium; Entzündungshemmende Mittel; Antimikrobielle Mundwässer; Antibakterielle Seifen; Präparate zur Desinfektion der Luft; Milchpulver für Babys; Antibiotika in Tablettenform; Babynahrungsmittel; Antibakterielle Handwaschmittel; Antimikrobielle Handwaschmittel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παραδοσιακά κινέζικα φαρμακευτικά βότανα· Αντιβακτηριακό προϊόν καθαρισμού προσώπου· Ενδύματα υγιεινής· Αναισθητικά· Αντισηπτικά στοματικά διαλύματα· Αέρα (Προϊόντα διήθησης -)· Αποσμητικά αυτοκινήτου· Βρεφικές πάνες· Κάψουλες φαρμάκων· Αλβουμινούχα συμπληρώματα διατροφής· Παρασκευάσματα πλυσίματος ματιών· Αντιφλεγμονώδη· Αντιμικροβιακά διαλύματα στοματικών πλύσεων· Αντιβακτηριακά σαπούνια· Παρασκευάσματα απολύμανσης αέρα· Γάλα σε σκόνη για βρέφη· Αντιβιοτικά δισκία· Βρεφικές/Παιδικές τροφές· Αντιβακτηριακά προϊόντα για το πλύσιμο των χεριών· Αντιμικροβιακά προϊόντα για το πλύσιμο των χεριών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Chinese traditional medicinal herbs; Antibacterial facial cleanser; Bandages (Hygienic -); Anaesthetic preparations; Antiseptic mouthwashes for rinsing; Air purifying preparations; Car deodorants; Babies' diapers; Capsules for medicines; Albumin dietary supplements; Collyrium; Anti-inflammatories; Antibacterial mouthwashes; Anti-bacterial soap; Air sanitizing preparations; Milk powder for babies; Antibiotic tablets; Babies' food; Antibacterial handwashes; Anti-microbial handwash.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Hierbas medicinales tradicionales chinas; Limpiadores faciales antibacterianos; Productos para la menstruación; Anestésicos; Enjuagues bucales antisépticos; Productos para purificar el aire; Ambientadores [desodorantes] para coches; Pañales para bebés; Cápsulas para medicamentos; Complementos alimenticios a base de albúmina; Colirio; Antiinflamatorios; Enjuagues bucales antimicrobianos; Jabones antibacterianos; Preparaciones para desinfectar el aire ambiental; Leche en polvo para bebés; Antibióticos en comprimidos; Alimentos para bebés; Productos antibacterianos para lavar las manos; Productos antimicrobianos para lavarse las manos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Traditsioonilised hiina ravimtaimed; Antibakteriaalsed näopuhastusvahendid; Hügieenipesu; Anesteetikumid, tuimastid; Antiseptilised suuloputusveed; Õhupuhastusained; Autodeodorandid; Imikute mähkmed; Ravimkapslid; Albumiin toidulisandina; Silmaloputusvesi; Põletikuvastased ained; Antimikroobsed suuveed; Antibakteriaalne seep; Õhudesinfektsioonipreparaadid; Piimapulber imikutele; Antibiootilised tabletid; Imikutoit; Antibakteriaalsed kätepesuained; Mikroobidevastased kätepesuvahendid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Perinteiset kiinalaiset yrttilääkkeet; Antibakteeriset kasvojenpuhdistusaineet; Terveyssiteet; Anestesia-aineet; Antiseptiset suuvedet; Ilmanpuhdistusvalmisteet; Deodorantit autoihin; Vauvanvaipat; Kapselit (Lääke -); Valkuainen (albumiini) lisäravinteena; Lääkeaineita sisältävät silmävedet; Tulehduslääkkeet; Antimikrobiset suuvedet; Antibakteerinen saippua; Ilmanpuhdistusvalmisteet; Vauvojen maitojauheesta valmistettu maitojuoma; Antibioottitabletit; Vauvanruoat; Antibakteeriset käsienpesuliuokset; Mikrobeja tuhoava käsienpesuaine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Herbes médicinales traditionnelles chinoises; Nettoyant antibactérien pour le visage; Protections hygiéniques; Anesthésiques; Bains de bouche antiseptiques; Produits pour la purification de l'air; Désodorisants pour voitures; Couches pour bébés; Capsules pour médicaments; Compléments alimentaires d'albumine; Collyre; Anti-inflammatoires; Bains de bouche antimicrobiens; Savons antibactériens; Préparations pour l’assainissement de l’air; Lait en poudre pour bébés; Antibiotiques sous forme de comprimés; Aliments pour bébés; Produits antibactériens pour le lavage des mains; Produits antimicrobiens pour le lavage des mains.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Tradicionalne kineske ljekovite trave; Antibakterijsko sredstvo za čišćenje lica; Higijenska odjeća; Anestetici; Antiseptičke vodice za usta; Zrak (proizvodi za pročišćavanje zraka); Osvježivači prostora za automobile; Pelene za bebe; Kapsule za lijekove; Albumin kao dodatak prehrani; Kolir [lijek za očnu spojnicu]; Protuupalni lijekovi; Antimikrobne vodice za usta; Antibakterijski sapun; Preparati za dezinfekciju zraka; Mlijeko u prahu za bebe; Antibiotske tablete; Hrana za bebe; Antibakterijska sredstva za pranje ruku; Antimikrobno sredstvo za pranje ruku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hagyományos kínai gyógynövények; Antibakteriális arctisztítók; Menstruáció során használt termékek; Érzéstelenítők, anesztetikumok; Antiszeptikus szájvizek; Légtisztító készítmények; Autós szagtalanítók; Nadrágpelenkák babáknak; Kapszulák gyógyszerekhez; Albumin étrendkiegészítők; Szemvizek; Gyulladásgátló termékek; Antimikrobiális szájvizek, szájöblítők; Antibakteriális szappan; Légfertőtlenítő készítmények; Tejpor csecsemőknek; Antibiotikus tabletták; Bébiételek; Antibakteriális kézmosók; Antimikrobás kézmosók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Erbe della medicina tradizionale cinese; Detergenti antibatterici per il viso; Indumenti igienici; Anestetici; Collutori antisettici; Prodotti per la purificazione dell'aria; Deodoranti per automobile; Pannolini per bebé usa e getta; Capsule per medicamenti; Complementi alimentari di albumina; Collirio; Antinfiammatori; Collutori antimicrobici; Saponi antibatterici; Preparati disinfettanti per l'aria; Latte in polvere per neonati; Compresse antibiotiche; Alimenti per bambini (neonati); Prodotti antibatterici per lavare le mani; Prodotti antimicrobici per il lavaggio delle mani.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kiniškos tradicinės vaistažolės; Antibakteriniai veido valikliai; Higieninė apranga; Nejautros preparatai [anestetikai]; Antiseptiniai burnos skalavimo skysčiai; Oro valymo preparatai; Automobilių dezodorantai; Kūdikių vystyklai; Kapsulės (vaistams); Albumino maisto papildai; Akių lašai; Priešuždegiminiai vaistai; Antimikrobiniai burnos skalavimo skysčiai; Antibakterinis muilas; Oro sanitarijos preparatai; Pieno milteliai kūdikiams; Antibiotikų tabletės; Kūdikių maistas; Antibakteriniai rankų plovimo skysčiai; Antimikrobinis rankų ploviklis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ķīniešu tradicionālās ārstniecības augi; Antibakteriāli sejas tīrīšanas līdzekļi; Higiēniskie izstrādājumi menstruācijām; Anestēzijas līdzekļi; Antiseptiski mutes skalošanas līdzekļi; Gaisa attīrīšanas līdzekļi; Dezodoranti automobiļiem; Autiņi bērniem; Kapsulas medikamentiem; Albumīna uztura bagātinātāji; Acu losjoni; Pretiekaisuma līdzekļi; Antibakteriāli mutes skalošanas līdzekļi; Antibakteriālās ziepes; Gaisa dezinfekcijas līdzekļi; Piena maisījums zīdaiņiem un maziem bērniem; Antibiotiku tabletes; Maisījumi zīdaiņiem; Antibakteriālie roku mazgāšanas līdzekļi; Pretmikrobu roku mazgāšanas līdzekļi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ħxejjex mediċinali tradizzjonali Ċiniżi; Aġenti antibatterjali għat-tindif tal-wiċċ; Lbies sanitarju; Anestetiċi; Likwidu antisettiku għat-tlaħliħ tal-ħalq; Preparazzjonijiet li jippurifikaw l-arja; Deodoranti għal karozzi; Ħrieqi tat-trabi [srievet]; Kapsuli għal mediċini; Supplimenti tad-dieta bl-albumina; Ilma għall-ħasil tal-għajnejn; Anti-infjammatorji; Likwidi antimikrobiċi għall-ħasil tal-ħalq; Sapun antibatteriku; Preparazzjonijiet tas-sanitizzazzjoni tal-arja; Trab tal-ħalib għat-trabi; Pilloli antibijotiċi; Ikel għat-trabi; Ħasil tal-idejn antibatteriku; Prodotti antimikrobiċi għall-ħasil tal-idejn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Traditionele Chinese geneeskrachtige kruiden; Antibacteriële gezichtsreinigingsmiddelen; Kleding voor hygiënische doeleinden; Anesthetica; Antiseptische mondspoelingen; Luchtzuiveringsmiddelen; Luchtverfrissers voor auto's; Luiers voor baby's; Capsules voor geneesmiddelen; Voedingssupplementen op basis van albumine; Oogwater; Ontstekingsremmende middelen; Antimicrobiële mondspoelmiddelen; Antibacteriële zeep; Luchtzuiveringspreparaten; Melkpoeder voor baby's; Antibiotische tabletten; Babyvoeding; Antibacteriële handzeep; Antimicrobiële handwasmiddelen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Tradycyjne chińskie zioła lecznicze; Antybakteryjne środki do mycia twarzy; Odzież sanitarna; Anestetyki [środki znieczulające]; Antyseptyczny płyn do płukania ust; Środki do oczyszczania powietrza; Dezodoranty do samochodów; Pieluszki dla niemowląt; Kapsułki na lekarstwa; Białkowe suplementy diety; Płyny do przemywania oczu; Środki przeciwzapalne; Przeciwdrobnoustrojowe płyny do płukania jamy ustnej; Mydła antybakteryjne; Preparaty do dezynfekcji powietrza; Mleko w proszku dla niemowląt; Antybiotyki w tabletkach; Żywność dla niemowląt; Antybakteryjne środki do mycia rąk; Środki przeciwdrobnoustrojowe do mycia rąk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Ervas medicinais tradicionais chinesas; Produtos de limpeza antibacterianos; Proteções higiénicas; Anestésicos; Colutórios antissépticos; Preparações para a purificação do ar; Desodorizantes para automóveis; Fraldas para bebés; Cápsulas para medicamentos; Suplementos alimentares de albumina; Colírio; Anti-inflamatórios; Colutórios antimicrobianos; Sabão antibacteriano; Produtos para higienização do ar; Leite em pó para bebés; Pastilhas antibióticas; Alimentos para bebés; Preparações antibacterianas de lavagem de mãos; Preparações antimicrobianas para lavar as mãos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ierburi medicinale tradiționale chinezești; Produs antibacterian pentru curățarea feței; Îmbrăcăminte sanitară; Anestezice; Ape de gură antiseptice; Aer (produse pentru purificarea -ului); Deodorante pentru automobile; Scutece chiloței pentru bebeluși; Capsule pentru medicamente; Suplimente alimentare pe bază de albumină; Picături pentru ochi; Produse antiinflamatoare; Preparate antimicrobiene pentru clătirea gurii; Săpun antibacterian; Preparate pentru igienizarea aerului; Lapte praf pentru copii mici; Comprimate antibiotice; Alimente pentru bebeluși; Soluții antibacteriene pentru spălarea mâinilor; Produse antibacteriene de spălat pe mâini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Tradičné čínske liečivé rastliny; Antibakteriálne čistiace pleťové prípravky; Dámske menštruačné hygienické potreby; Anestetiká; Antiseptické ústne vody; Prípravky na čistenie vzduchu; Osviežovače vzduchu do áut; Detské plienky; Liekové kapsuly; Bielkovinové výživové doplnky; Roztoky na vyplachovanie očí; Protizápalové prípravky a produkty; Antimikrobiálne prípravky na umývanie ústnej dutiny; Antibakteriálne mydlá; Prípravky na dezinfekciu vzduchu; Sušené mlieko pre dojčatá; Antibiotické tablety; Potraviny pre dojčatá; Antibakteriálne tekuté mydlá; Antimikrobiálne prípravky na umývanie rúk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Tradicionalna kitajska zdravilna zelišča; Antibakterijska sredstva za čiščenje obraza; Higienska oblačila; Anestetiki; Antiseptična ustna voda; Pripravki za čiščenje zraka; Dezodoranti za avtomobile; Plenice za dojenčke; Kapsule za zdravila; Beljakovine kot prehranski dodatki; Sredstva za izpiranje oči; Protivnetna sredstva; Antimikrobne ustne vode; Antibakterijska mila; Pripravki za razkuževanje zraka; Mleko v prahu za dojenčke; Antibiotične tablete; Hrana za dojenčke; Antibakterijska čistila za roke; Protimikrobna sredstva za umivanje rok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Traditionella kinesiska medicinalörter; Bakteriedödande ansiktsrengöringsmedel; Sanitära beklädnader; Narkosmedel; Antiseptiska munvatten; Luftreningspreparat; Luftfräschare för bilar; Babyblöjor; Kapslar för mediciner; Kosttillskott av alubmin; Kollyrium (ögondroppar); Inflammationshämmande medel; Antimikrobiella munvatten; Bakteriedödande tvål; Preparat för luftsterilisering; Mjölkpulver för spädbarn; Antibiotikatabletter; Mat för bebisar; Antibakteriella handtvättmedel; Antimikrobiell handtvätt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Зарядни устройства; Маски против замърсяване за респираторна защита; Смартфони; Лаптопи; Външни батерии; Бебефони; Звукозаписни апарати; Периферни устройства, пригодени за използване с компютри; Звукозаписи; Очила; 3D очила; Електрически батерии с възможност за презареждане; Калъфи за смартфони; Навигационни инструменти; Кислородни маски; Галванични елементи; Шлемове за виртуална реалност; Костюми за гмуркане; Слушалки; Микрофони; Защитни козирки; Говорители; Слушалки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nabíječky baterií; Masky proti znečištění na ochranu dýchacího ústrojí; Chytré telefony (smartphony); Počítače; Napájecí bloky; Chůvičky; Přístroje pro záznam zvuku; Periferní zařízení počítačů; Audio nahrávky; Brýle; 3D brýle; Nabíjecí elektrické akumulátory; Pouzdra na chytré telefony (smartphony); Navigační přístroje; Dýchací masky; Elektrické baterie; Náhlavní soupravy pro virtuální realitu; Potápěčské obleky; Sluchátka; Mikrofony; Ochranné štíty; Reproduktory; Sluchátka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Opladere til batterier; Forureningsbegrænsende masker som åndedrætsværn; Smartphones; Computere; Power banks; Babyalarmer; Lydoptageapparater; Perifere enheder til computere; Indspilninger af lyd; Briller; 3D briller; Genopladelige elektriske batterier; Etuier til smartphones; Navigationsinstrumenter; Respirationsmasker; Batterier, elektriske; Virtual reality-headsets; Dykkerdragter; Hovedtelefoner; Mikrofoner; Beskyttelsesvisirer; Højttalere; Hovedtelefoner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Ladegeräte für Batterien; Umweltschutzmasken für den Atemschutz; Smartphones; Laptops [Computer]; Powerbanks; Babyüberwachungsgeräte; Tonaufzeichnungsgeräte; An Computer angepasste Peripheriegeräte; Tonaufnahmen; Brillen; 3D-Brillen; Wiederaufladbare elektrische Batterien; Schalen für Smartphones; Navigationsinstrumente; Atemmasken; Elektrische Batterien; Virtual-Reality-Headsets; Taucheranzüge; Kopfhörer; Mikrofone; Augenschutzschirme; Lautsprecher; Kopfhörer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Φορτιστές μπαταριών· Αντιρρυπαντικές μάσκες για αναπνευστική προστασία· Έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Ηλεκτρονικοί υπολογιστές· Τροφοδοτικά ισχύος· Μέσα παρακολούθησης βρεφών· Εγγραφή ήχου (Όργανα για τη -)· Περιφερειακός εξοπλισμός προσαρμοσμένος για χρήση σε ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Ηχητικές εγγραφές· Διόπτρες· Γυαλιά 3D· Επαναφορτιζόμενοι ηλεκτρικοί συσσωρευτές· Θήκες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Ναυσιπλοία (όργανα -ας)· Μάσκες για την υποβοήθηση της αναπνοής· Ηλεκτρικές μπαταρίες· Ακουστικά κεφαλής εικονικής πραγματικότητας· Φόρμες κατάδυσης· Κάσκες ακουστικών· Μικρόφωνα· Προστατευτικές προσωπίδες· Ηχεία· Ακουστικά κεφαλής με μικρόφωνο.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Battery chargers; Anti-pollution masks for respiratory protection; Smartphones; Computers; Power banks; Baby monitors; Sound recording apparatus; Computer peripheral devices; Sound recordings; Spectacles; 3d spectacles; Rechargeable electric batteries; Cases for smartphones; Navigational instruments; Breathing masks; Batteries, electric; Virtual reality headsets; Diving suits; Headphones; Microphones; Protective visors; Loudspeakers; Headsets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cargadores de pilas y baterías; Máscaras anticontaminación para la protección respiratoria; Teléfonos inteligentes [smartphones]; Ordenadores; Bancos de energía; Dispositivos de audio y vídeo para la vigilancia de bebés; Aparatos de grabación de sonido; Dispositivos periféricos utilizados con ordenadores; Grabaciones de audio; Gafas [óptica]; Gafas 3D; Baterías eléctricas recargables; Estuches para teléfonos inteligentes; Instrumentos de navegación; Mascarillas de respiración; Pilas eléctricas; Cascos de realidad virtual; Trajes de buceo; Auriculares; Micrófonos; Viseras protectoras; Altavoces; Cascos con micrófono.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Akulaadurid, patareilaadurid; Saastevastased maskid hingamisteede kaitseks; Nutitelefonid; Arvutid, raalid; Energiapangad; Beebimonitorid; Helisalvestusaparaadid, helisalvestusseadmed; Arvutite välisseadmed; Helisalvestised; Prillid [optika]; 3D-prillid; Laaditavad elektriakud; Nutitelefonide ümbrised; Navigatsiooniriistad; Hingamismaskid; Elektripatareid; Virtuaalreaalsuse peakomplektid; Skafandrid, tuukriülikonnad; Kõrvaklapid; Mikrofonid; Kaitsevisiirid; Kõlarid, valjuhääldid; Mikrofoniga kõrvaklapid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Latauslaitteet sähköparistoille; Kasvonaamarit hengityselinten suojaamiseen saasteilta; Älypuhelimet; Sylimikrot; Virtapankit; Vauvamonitorit; Äänityslaitteet; Tietokoneiden oheislaitteet; Audiotallenteet; Silmälasit; 3D-silmälasit; Ladattavat sähköakut; Älypuhelinten kuoret; Navigointikojeet; Hengitysnaamarit; Sähköparistot; Kuulokemikrofoniyhdistelmät virtuaalitodellisuutta varten; Sukelluspuvut; Kuulokkeet; Mikrofonit; Suojalipat; Kaiuttimet; Kuulokkeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Chargeurs de piles et batteries; Masques anti-pollution pour la protection respiratoire; Ordiphones [smartphones]; Ordinateurs; Batteries externes; Dispositifs audio et vidéo pour la surveillance de bébés; Appareils pour l'enregistrement du son; Périphériques adaptés pour utilisation avec des ordinateurs; Enregistrements audio; Lunettes [optique]; Lunettes 3D; Piles électriques rechargeables; Étuis pour smartphones; Instruments pour la navigation; Masques respiratoires; Piles électriques; Casques de réalité virtuelle; Combinaisons de plongée; Casques à écouteurs; Microphones; Visières protectrices; Haut-parleurs; Casques d'écoute.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Akumulatori (punjači električnih akumulatora); Maske za zaštitu respiratornog sustava od zagađenja; Pametni telefoni; Računala; Vanjski punjači baterija; Monitori za bebe; Uređaji za snimanje zvuka; Periferni uređaji prilagođeni za uporabu s računalima; Audio snimke; Naočale; 3D naočale; Punjive električne baterije; Etuiji za pametne telefone; Navigacijski instrumenti; Maske za disanje; Električne baterije; Slušalice za generiranje virtualne stvarnosti; Skafanderi za ronnjenje; Slušalice; Mikrofoni; Zaštitni viziri; Zvučnici; Slušalice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Akkumulátor- és elemtöltők; Szennyeződés elleni légzésvédő maszkok, álarcok; Okostelefonok; Számítógépek; Tápbankok; Bébiőrök; Hangrögzítő, hangfelvevő készülékek; Számítógéphez kialakított perifériák; Audio felvételek; Szemüvegek; Háromdimenziós szemüvegek; Újratölthető elektromos akkumulátorok; Tokok okostelefonhoz; Navigációs eszközök; Légzőmaszkok; Elektromos elemek, akkumulátorok; Virtuális valóság headsetek; Búvárruhák; Fejhallgatók; Mikrofonok; Védő szemellenzők; Hangszórók, hangosbemondók, megafonok; Fejhallgatók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Caricabatterie; Maschere anti-inquinamento per protezione respiratoria; Smartphone; Elaboratori elettronici; Batterie esterne; Dispositivi audio e video per la sorveglianza dei neonati; Apparecchi per la registrazione del suono; Periferiche concepite per essere utilizzate con i computer; Registrazioni audio; Occhiali [ottica]; Occhiali per 3D; Batterie elettriche ricaricabili; Custodie per smartphones; Strumenti per la navigazione; Maschere per la respirazione; Batterie elettriche; Caschi per realtà virtuale; Scafandri; Cuffie per la musica; Microfoni; Visiere protettive; Altoparlanti; Cuffie per la musica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Baterijų įkrovimo įtaisai; Apsauginės kvėpavimo kaukės nuo užterštumo; Išmanieji telefonai; Kompiuteriai; Išorinės baterijos; Prietaisai kūdikiams stebėti; Garso įrašymo aparatai; Kompiuterių išoriniai įrenginiai; Garso įrašai; Akiniai; 3D akiniai; Įkraunamos elektrinės baterijos; Išmaniųjų telefonų dėklai; Navigacijos prietaisai; Kvėpavimo kaukės; Elektrinės baterijos; Virtualiosios realybės ausinės; Narų kostiumai; Radijo ausinės; Mikrofonai; Apsauginiai skydeliai; Garsiakalbiai; Ausinės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Akumulatoru uzlādes ierīces; Pretpiesārņojuma maskas elpošanas aizsardzībai; Viedtālruņi; Datori; Ārējās baterijas; Elektroniskas ierīces zīdaiņu uzraudzībai; Skaņu ieraksta ierīces; Datoru perifērijas ierīces; Audioieraksti; Brilles; Brilles attēlu uztverei trīsdimensiju (3D) formātā; Elektriskas uzlādējamās baterijas; Viedtālruņu maciņi; Navigācijas instrumenti; Elpošanas maskas; Elektrisko akumulatoru baterijas; Virtuālās realitātes galvas ierīču komplekti; Nirēju un ūdenslīdēju kostīmi; Austiņas; Mikrofoni; Aizsardzības sejsegi; Skaļruņi; Radioaustiņas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Karikaturi għal batteriji elettriċi; Maskri kontra t-tniġġis għall-protezzjoni respiratorja; Smartfowns; Kompjuters; Stazzjonijiet tal-enerġija; Moniters tat-trabi; Tagħmir għar-reġistrazzjoni tal-ħoss; Periferali addattati għall-użu mal-kompjuters; Reġistrazzjonijiet tal-awdjo; Nuċċalijiet; Nuċċalijiet 3D; Batteriji elettriċi li jistgħu jkunu ċċarġjati; Kaxxi għall-ismartphones; Strumenti għan-navigazzjoni; Maskri respiratorji; Batteriji tal-elettriku; Ħedsets tar-realtà virtwali; Ħwejjeġ tal-għaddasa; Kuffji; Mikrofoni; Viżieri protettivi; Lawdspikers; Kuffji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Batterij-laders; Maskers tegen luchtvervuiling voor ademhalingsbescherming; Smartphones; Computers; Voedingsbanken (stroom); Babyfoons; Geluidsopname-apparaten; Computerrandapparatuur; Audio-opnamen; Brillen [optiek]; 3D-brillen; Oplaadbare elektrische batterijen; Etuis voor smartphones; Navigatie-instrumenten; Zuurstofmaskers; Elektrische batterijen; Virtual reality headsets; Duikpakken; Hoofdtelefoons; Microfoons; Beschermende vizieren; Luidsprekers; Hoofdtelefoons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Ładowarki do baterii; Maski ochronne przed zanieczyszczeniem do ochrony układu oddechowego; Smartfony; Komputery; Banki energii; Urządzenia do monitorowania niemowląt; Urządzenia do rejestrowania dźwięku; Sprzęt peryferyjny do komputerów; Nagrania audio; Okulary; Okulary 3D; Ładowalne baterie elektryczne; Etui na smartfony; Przyrządy nawigacyjne; Maski do oddychania; Baterie elektryczne; Zestawy na głowę do rzeczywistości wirtualnej; Skafandry dla nurków; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Mikrofony; Osłony ochronne na twarz; Głośniki; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Carregadores de baterias; Máscaras antipoluição para proteção respiratória; Smartphones; Computadores; Baterias externas; Dispositivos para vigilância de bebés; Aparelhos para a gravação de som; Periféricos adaptados para uso com computadores; Gravações de áudio; Óculos [ótica]; Óculos 3D; Baterias elétricas recarregáveis; Capas para smartphones; Instrumentos de navegação; Máscaras de respiração; Baterias elétricas; Headsets de realidade virtual; Fatos de mergulhador; Auriculares; Microfones; Viseiras protetoras; Altifalantes; Auriculares.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Alimentatoare pentru acumulatoare; Măști antipoluare pentru protecție respiratorie; Telefoane inteligente; Computere; Baterii externe; Dispozitive de monitorizare a bebelușilor; Înregistrarea sunetelor (Aparate pentru -); Periferice adaptate pentru a fi folosite la calculatoare; Înregistrări audio; Ochelari; Ochelari 3D; Baterii electrice reîncărcabile; Carcase pentru telefoane inteligente; Instrumente de navigație; Măști pentru respirație; Baterii galvanice; Căști pentru realitate virtuală; Costume de scafandru; Căști audio; Microfoane; Viziere de protecție; Difuzoare; Căști.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nabíjačky batérií; Dýchacie masky na ochranu pred znečistením; Smartfóny; Počítače; Externé akumulátory; Audiovizuálne prístroje na monitorovanie bábätiek; Zvukové nahrávacie zariadenia; Periférne zariadenia počítačov; Audionahrávky; Okuliare; 3D okuliare; Dobíjateľné elektrické batérie; Puzdrá na smartfóny; Navigačné nástroje; Dýchacie masky; Elektrické batérie (články); Súpravy okuliarov a slúchadiel na virtuálnu realitu; Potápačské kombinézy; Slúchadlá; Mikrofóny; Ochranné štíty; Reproduktory, amplióny; Slúchadlá s mikrofónom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Električni polnilniki za baterije; Maske proti onesnaženju za zaščito dihal; Pametni telefoni; Računalniki; Hranilnice električne energije; Otroške varuške; Aparati za snemanje zvoka; Zunanje enote, prilagojene za uporabo z računalniki; Avdio posnetki; Očala; 3D očala; Električne baterije za ponovno polnjenje; Etuiji za pametne telefone; Navigacijski instrumenti; Dihalne maske; Električne baterije; Slušalke z mikrofonom za navidezno resničnost; Potapljaške obleke; Slušalke; Mikrofoni; Zaščitni vizirji; Zvočniki; Slušalke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Batteriladdare; Föroreningsmasker för andningsskydd; Smartphones; Datorer; Laddningsstationer (powerbanks); Övervakningsapparater för spädbarn; Ljudupptagningsapparater; Kringutrustning anpassade för användning med datorer; Ljudinspelningar; Glasögon; 3D-glasögon; Uppladdningsbara elektriska batterier; Skal för smartphones; Navigationsinstrument; Andningsmasker; Batterier, elektriska; Hörlurar med mikrofon för virtual reality bruk; Dykardräkter; On-ear hörlurar; Mikrofoner; Skyddsvisir; Högtalare; Headsets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Защитни маски за уста за медицинска употреба; Дигитални термометри за медицински цели; Ръкавици за еднократна употреба за хирургични цели; Апарати за използване при ортодонтия; Апарати за масаж; Електронни апарати за медицински цели; Стоматологично оборудване; Маски за лице за медицинска употреба за антибактериална защита; Маски за лице за медицинска употреба; Електронни термометри за медицинска употреба; Термометри, поставяни в ухото; Кондоми за хигиенни цели; Санитарни маски за предпазване от прах за медицински цели; Надуваеми подложки за медицински цели; Бастуни за медицински цели; Термометри за медицински цели; Електрически апарати за естетически масаж; Електрически масажори; Масажори за крака; Секс играчки; Бебешки шишета; Санитарни маски за медицински цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Ochranné ústní masky pro lékařské použití; Digitální teploměry k lékařským účelům; Jednorázové rukavice pro chirurgické účely; Ortodontické přístroje; Masážní přístroje; Elektronické přístroje pro lékařské účely; Zařízení pro zubní lékařství; Roušky k použití v chirurgii jako antibakteriální ochrana; Roušky k lékařskému použití; Elektronické teploměry pro lékařské použití; Ušní teploměry; Kondomy pro hygienické účely; Hygienické masky na ochranu před prachem pro lékařské účely; Nafukovací podušky pro lékařské účely; Vycházkové hole pro lékařské účely; Teploměry pro lékařské účely; Elektrické přístroje ke kosmetické masáži; Elektrické masážní přístroje; Zařízení na masáž chodidel; Erotické hračky; Dětské láhve; Hygienické masky pro lékařské účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beskyttende mundbind til medicinske formål; Digitale termometre til medicinske formål; Engangshandsker til kirurgiske formål; Tandreguleringsindretninger; Massageapparater; Elektroniske apparater til medicinske formål; Tandlægeapparater og -instrumenter; Ansigtsmasker til kirurgiske formål til beskyttelse mod bakterier; Ansigtsmasker til medicinske formål; Elektroniske termometre til medicinsk brug; Øretermometre; Kondomer til hygiejniske formål; Sanitære masker til beskyttelse mod støv til medicinske formål; Lufthynder til medicinsk brug; Spadserestokke til medicinske formål; Termometre til medicinsk brug; Elektriske apparater til æstetisk massage; Elektriske massageapparater; Fodmassageapparater; Sexlegetøj; Sutteflasker; Beskyttelsesmasker til medicinske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Mundschutzmasken für medizinische Zwecke; Digitale Thermometer für medizinische Zwecke; Einweghandschuhe für chirurgische Zwecke; Zahnregulierungen; Massagegeräte; Elektronische Apparate für medizinische Zwecke; Zahnärztliche Apparate und Instrumente; Gesichtsmasken für chirurgische Zwecke zum Schutz vor Bakterien; Gesichtsmasken für medizinische Zwecke; Elektronische Thermometer für medizinische Zwecke; Ohrthermometer; Kondome für gesundheitliche Zwecke; Hygienemasken zum Schutz vor Staub für medizinische Zwecke; Luftkissen für medizinische Zwecke; Gehstöcke für medizinische Zwecke; Thermometer für medizinische Zwecke; Elektrische Massagegeräte für die Schönheitspflege; Elektrisch betriebene Massagegeräte; Geräte für die Fußmassage; Sexspielzeug; Saugflaschen; Hygienemasken für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Προστατευτικές μάσκες στόματος για ιατρική χρήση· Ψηφιακά θερμόμετρα για ιατρική χρήση· Γάντια μιας χρήσης για χειρουργική χρήση· Συσκευές για χρήση σε ορθοδοντική· Συσκευές μασαζ· Ηλεκτρονικές συσκευές για ιατρική χρήση· Οδοντιατρικός εξοπλισμός· Μάσκες χειρουργείου για αντιβακτηριδιακή προστασία· Μάσκες προσώπου για ιατρική χρήση· Ηλεκτρονικά θερμόμετρα για ιατρική χρήση· Θερμόμετρα αυτιού· Προφυλακτικά για προστασία της υγιεινής· Μάσκες υγιεινής για παρεμπόδιση της σκόνης για ιατρική χρήση· Αέρα (Μαξιλάρια -) για ιατρική χρήση· Μπαστούνια περιπάτου για ιατρική χρήση· Θερμόμετρα ιατρικά· Ηλεκτρικές συσκευές αισθητικής μάλαξης (αισθητικού μασάζ)· Ηλεκτροκίνητες συσκευές για μαλάξεις (μασάζ)· Συσκευές μαλάξεων (μασάζ) για τα πόδια· Σεξουαλικά παιχνίδια· Υποδοχείς για θήλαστρα· Μάσκες υγιεινής για ιατρική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Protective mouth masks for medical use; Digital thermometers for medical purposes; Disposable gloves for surgical use; Apparatus for use in orthodontics; Instruments for massage; Electronic apparatus for medical purposes; Apparatus for dental purposes; Face masks for surgical use for anti bacterial protection; Face masks for medical use; Electronic thermometers for medical use; Ear thermometers; Condoms for hygienic purposes; Sanitary masks for dust prevention for medical purposes; Air cushions for medical purposes; Canes for medical purposes; Temperature meters for medical use; Electric esthetic massage apparatus; Electrically operated massagers; Appliances for massaging feet; Sex toys; Babies' bottles; Sanitary masks for medical use.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Mascarillas bucales de protección para uso médico; Termómetros digitales para uso médico; Guantes desechables para uso quirúrgico; Aparatos de ortodoncia; Aparatos de masaje; Aparatos electrónicos para uso médico; Aparatos e instrumentos odontológicos; Máscaras faciales para protección antibacteriana de uso quirúrgico; Máscaras faciales para uso médico; Termómetros electrónicos para uso médico; Termómetros auriculares; Preservativos con una finalidad higiénica; Mascarillas sanitarias para prevenir el polvo con fines médicos; Cojines de aire para uso médico; Bastones para uso médico; Termómetros para uso médico; Aparatos eléctricos para masaje estético; Masajeadores eléctricos; Aparatos de masaje para los pies; Juguetes sexuales; Biberones; Mascarillas sanitarias para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meditsiinilised suukaitsemaskid; Digitaalsed termomeetrid (meditsiinilised); Ühekordsed kindad kirurgias kasutuseks; Ortodontilised seadmed; Massaažiaparaadid; Meditsiinilised elektroonikaseadmed; Hambaraviseadmed ja -riistad; Kirurgias kasutatavad bakteritevastased kaitsvad näomaskid; Meditsiinilised näomaskid; Elektroonilised termomeetrid meditsiiniotstarbeks; Kõrvatermomeetrid; Hügieeniotstarbelised kondoomid; Tolmumaskid meditsiinis kasutamiseks; Meditsiinilised õhkpadjad; Jalutuskepid meditsiiniliseks otstarbeks; Meditsiinilised termomeetrid; Elektrilised kosmeetilise massaaži aparaadid; Elektrilised massaažiseadmed; Jalamasseerijad; Sekslelud; Lutipudelid; Meditsiinilised hügieenimaskid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Suojaavat suunaamarit lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Digitaaliset lämpömittarit lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Kertakäyttökäsineet kirurgisiin tarkoituksiin; Välineet käytettäväksi hampaanoikomisessa; Hierontalaitteet; Elektroniset laitteet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Hammaslääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Kasvosuojukset kirurgiseen käyttöön suojaksi bakteereilta; Kasvonaamarit lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Elektroniset lämpömittarit lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Korvakuumemittarit; Kondomit terveydenhoitotarkoituksiin; Hygieniamaskit pölyltä suojautumiseen lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Ilmatyynyt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Kävelykepit lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Kuumemittarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Sähköiset hierontalaitteet kauneudenhoitoon; Sähkötoimiset hierontalaitteet; Jalkojen hierontalaitteet; Seksilelut; Tuttipullot; Saniteettinaamarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Masques de protection buccale à usage médical; Thermomètres numériques à usage médical; Gants jetables à usage chirurgical; Appareils d'orthodontie; Appareils de massage; Appareils électroniques à usage médical; Appareils et instruments dentaires; Masques de protection antibactériens à usage chirurgical; Masques pour le visage à usage médical; Thermomètres électroniques à usage médical; Thermomètres auriculaires; Préservatifs à usage hygiénique; Masques hygiéniques antipoussières à usage médical; Coussins à air à usage médical; Cannes à usage médical; Thermomètres à usage médical; Appareils électriques pour massages esthétiques; Appareils de massage électriques; Masseurs pour les pieds; Jouets sexuels; Biberons; Masques hygiéniques à usage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Zaštitne maske za usta za medicinsku uporabu; Digitalni termometri za medicinske svrhe; Jednokratne rukavice za kirurške svrhe; Uređaji za uporabu u ortodonciji; Uređaji za masažu; Elektronski uređaji za medicinske svrhe; Stomatološka oprema; Maske za lice za kiruršku uporabu za antibakterijsku zaštitu; Maske za lice za medicinsku uporabu; Elektronički termometri za medicinsku uporabu; Toplomjeri za uši; Kondomi za higijenske svrhe; Sanitarne maske za sprečavanje udisanja prašine za medicinske potrebe; Zračni jastuci za medicinske potrebe; Štapovi za hodanje za medicinske potrebe; Toplomjeri za medicinske potrebe; Električni uređaji za estetsku masažu; Električni masažeri; Masažeri za stopala; Seksualne igračke; Spremnici dječjih bočica; Sanitarne maske za medicinske svrhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szájvédő maszkok orvosi használatra; Digitális hőmérők orvosi használatra; Eldobható kesztyűk sebészeti célra; Fogszabályozáshoz használt eszközök, berendezések; Masszázsberendezések; Elektronikus készülékek orvosi használatra; Fogászati berendezések; Arcmaszkok sebészeti használatra baktériumok elleni védelemhez; Arcmaszkok gyógyászati használatra; Elektronikus hőmérők gyógyászati használatra; Fülhőmérők; Óvszerek higiéniás célokra; Egészségügyi maszkok por elleni védelemre, orvosi célokra; Levegővel töltött párnák gyógyászati célokra; Járóbotok gyógyászati célokra; Hőmérők gyógyászati célokra; Elektromos esztétikai masszázskészülékek; Elektromos masszázsberendezések; Lábmasszírozók; Szexuális játékszerek; Cumisüvegtartók; Gyógyászati célú egészségügyi maszkok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Maschere di protezione per la bocca per uso medico; Termometri digitali per uso medico; Guanti monouso per uso chirurgico; Apparecchi per l' ortodonzia; Apparecchi per il massaggio; Apparecchiature elettroniche per uso medico; Apparecchi e strumenti dentari; Maschere per il viso per protezione antibatterica; Maschere per il viso per uso medico; Termometri elettronici per uso medico; Termometri auricolari; Preservativi per uso igienico; Maschere igieniche per la protezione dalla polvere per uso medico; Cuscini ad aria per uso medico; Bastoni da passeggio per scopi medici; Termometri per uso medico; Apparecchi elettrici per il massaggio estetico; Massaggiatori elettrici; Massaggiatori per i piedi; Giocattoli del sesso [sex toys]; Poppatoi; Maschere igieniche per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Apsauginės burnos kaukės medicinos reikmėms; Skaitmeniniai termometrai medicinos reikmėms; Vienkartinės pirštinės chirurgijos reikmėms; Ortodontijos aparatai; Masažavimo aparatai; Elektroniniai aparatai medicinos reikmėms; Odontologijos aparatūra ir instrumentai; Chirurginės antibakterinės veido kaukės; Veido kaukės medicinos reikmėms; Elektroniniai termometrai medicinos reikmėms; Ausų termometrai; Prezervatyvai higienos reikmėms; Higieninės nuo dulkių apsaugančios kaukės (medicinos reikmėms); Pripučiamos pagalvėlės (medicinos reikmėms); Lazdos (kriukiai) (medicinos reikmėms); Medicininiai termometrai; Elektriniai estetinio masažo prietaisai; Elektriniai masažuokliai; Pėdų masažuokliai; Sekso žaislai; Žindymo buteliukai; Sanitarinės kaukės medicinos reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mutes aizsargmaskas, kas paredzētas lietošanai medicīnā; Digitālie termometri medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Vienreizlietojami cimdi ķirurģijas nolūkiem; Ortodontiskās ierīces; Masāžas aparāti; Elektroniskas iekārtas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Zobārstniecības ierīces un instrumenti; Antibakteriālas sejas maskas ķirurģiskām vajadzībām; Sejas maskas medicīniskām vajadzībām; Elektroniski termometri medicīniskām vajadzībām; Auss termometri; Prezervatīvi higiēniskiem nolūkiem; Sanitārās maskas aizsardzībai pret putekļiem medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Piepūšamie spilveni medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Pastaigu spieķi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Medicīniskie termometri; Elektriskie estētiskās masāžas aparāti; Elektriski darbināmas masāžas ierīces; Pēdu masāžas ierīces; Seksa rotaļlietas; Barošanas pudelītes; Sanitārās maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Maskri protettivi tal-ħalq għall-użu mediku; Termometri diġitali għal skopijiet mediċi; Ingwanti għal skopijiet kirurġiċi li jintremew wara l-użu; Apparat għall-użu fl-ortodonzja; Apparat għall-massaġġi; Apparat elettroniku għal skopijiet mediċi; Tagħmir dentali; Maskri tal-wiċċ għal użu kirurġiku għall-protezzjoni kontra l-batterji; Maskri tal-wiċċ għall-użu mediku; Termometri elettroniċi għal użu mediku; Termometri tal-widnejn; Kondoms għal skopijiet iġjeniċi; Maskri sanitarji għall-prevenzjoni mit-trab għal skopijiet mediċi; Kuxxini tal-arja għal skopijiet mediċi; Bsaten tal-mixi għal skopijiet mediċi; Termometri għal skopijiet mediċi; Apparat elettriku għall-massaġġi estetiċi; Massaġġaturi li jaħdmu bl-elettriku; Massaġġaturi tas-saqajn; Ġugarelli tas-sess; Reċipjenti bħala fliexken għat-tmigħ tat-trabi; Maskri sanitarji għal skopijiet mediċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Mondmaskers (Beschermende -) voor medisch gebruik; Digitale thermometers voor medische doeleinden; Wegwerphandschoenen voor chirurgische doeleinden; Orthodontie-apparaten; Massageapparaten; Elektronische apparatuur voor medische doeleinden; Tandheelkundige apparaten en instrumenten; Maskers voor chirurgisch gebruik ter bescherming tegen bacteriën; Gezichtsmaskers voor medisch gebruik; Elektronische thermometers voor medisch gebruik; Oorthermometers; Condooms voor hygiënische doeleinden; Hygiënische maskers voor stofpreventie voor medische doeleinden; Luchtkussens voor medisch gebruik; Wandelstokken voor medische doeleinden; Thermometers voor medisch gebruik; Elektrische schoonheidsmassageapparaten; Massagetoestellen (Elektrisch aangedreven -); Massagetoestellen voor de voeten; Seksspeeltjes; Zuigflessen; Hygiënische maskers voor medische doeleinden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Maski ochronne na usta do użytku medycznego; Termometry cyfrowe do celów medycznych; Jednorazowe rękawiczki do celów chirurgicznych; Urządzenia do użytku w ortodoncji; Urządzenia do masażu; Elektroniczne urządzenia do celów medycznych; Przyrządy i przybory dentystyczne; Maski na twarz do użytku w chirurgii dla ochrony przeciwbakteryjnej; Maski na twarz do użytku medycznego; Termometry elektroniczne do użytku medycznego; Termometry do ucha; Prezerwatywy do celów higienicznych; Maski sanitarne stosowane w celu ochrony przed kurzem do celów medycznych; Dmuchane poduszki do celów medycznych; Laski do celów medycznych; Termometry do celów medycznych; Elektryczne masażery kosmetyczne; Elektryczne przyrządy do masażu; Urządzenia do masażu stóp; Zabawki erotyczne; Pojemniki na butelki do karmienia; Maski higieniczne do celów medycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máscaras de proteção para a boca para uso médico; Termómetros digitais para uso médico; Luvas descartáveis para uso cirúrgico; Aparelhos de ortodontia; Aparelhos de massagem; Aparelhos eletrónicos para uso médico; Aparelhos e instrumentos dentários; Máscaras cirúrgicas para o rosto para proteção antibacteriana; Máscaras faciais para uso médico; Termómetros eletrónicos para uso médico; Termómetros auriculares; Preservativos para fins higiénicos; Máscaras higiénicas para prevenção de pó para uso médico; Almofadas de ar para uso médico; Bastões de caminhada de uso clínico; Termómetros para uso médico; Aparelhos elétricos de massagem estética; Massajadores acionados eletricamente; Massajadores para os pés; Brinquedos sexuais; Biberons [biberões]; Máscaras higiénicas para uso medicinal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Măști de protecție pentru gură de uz medical; Termometre digitale de uz medical; Mănuși de unică folosință de uz chirurgical; Aparate pentru utilizare în ortodonție; Aparate de masaj; Aparatură electronică pentru uz medical; Echipament stomatologic; Măști chirurgicale pentru protecție antibacteriană; Măști medicale; Termometre electronice de uz medical; Termometre auriculare; Prezervative de uz igienic; Măști sanitare pentru prevenirea prafului, de uz medical; Perne cu aer pentru uz medical; Bastoane de mers, de uz medical; Termometre de uz medical; Aparate electrice pentru masaje estetice; Aparate de masaj acționate electric; Aparate de masaj pentru picioare; Jucării erotice; Recipiente pentru biberoane; Măști sanitare de uz medical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ochranné masky na ústa na lekárske použitie; Digitálne teplomery na lekárske účely; Jednorazové rukavice na chirurgické účely; Prístroje na ortodontológiu; Masážne prístroje; Elektronické prístroje na lekárske účely; Zubárske prístroje a nástroje; Chirurgické masky na tvár na antibakteriálnu ochranu; Masky na tvár na lekárske účely; Elektronické teplomery na lekárske účely; Ušné teplomery; Kondómy na hygienické účely; Sanitárne masky na ochranu pred prachom na lekárske účely; Nafukovacie podušky na lekárske použitie; Vychádzkové palice na lekárske účely; Lekárske teplomery; Elektrické prístroje na estetickú masáž; Elektrické masážne prístroje; Zariadenia na masáž chodidiel; Erotické pomôcky; Detské fľaše; Sanitárne masky na lekárske účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zaščitne maske za usta za medicinsko uporabo; Digitalni termometri za medicinske namene; Rokavice za kirurške namene, za enkratno uporabo; Aparati, ki se uporabljajo v ortodontiji; Masažne naprave; Elektronski aparati za medicinske namene; Zobozdravstveni aparati in instrumenti; Obrazne maske za kirurško uporabo za zaščito pred bakterijami; Obrazne maske za medicinsko uporabo; Elektronski termometri za medicinsko uporabo; Ušesni termometri; Kondomi za higienske namene; Higienske maske za zaščito pred prahom za medicinske namene; Zračne blazine za medicinske namene; Sprehajalne palice za medicinske namene; Termometri za medicinske namene; Električni masažni aparati za estetske učinke; Električni masažni aparati; Naprave za masažo stopal; Spolni pripomočki; Posodice za stekleničke za hranjenje; Higienske maske za medicinsko uporabo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Skyddande munmasker för medicinskt bruk; Digitala termometrar för medicinska ändamål; Engångshandskar för kirurgiskt bruk; Apparater för användning i ortodonti; Massageapparater; Elektroniska apparater för medicinska ändamål; Dentala apparater och instrument; Bakterieskyddande ansiktsmasker för kirurgiskt bruk; Ansiktsmasker för medicinskt bruk; Elektroniska termometrar för medicinskt bruk; Örontermometrar; Kondomer för hygieniska ändamål; Sanitära ansiktsmasker för skydd mot damm, för medicinska ändamål; Luftdynor för medicinska ändamål; Promenadkäppar för medicinska ändamål; Termometrar för medicinska ändamål; Elektriska massageapparater för skönhetsvård; Elektriskt drivna massageapparater; Fotmassageapparater; Sexleksaker; Nappflaskor; Ansiktsskydd för medicinskt bruk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/186</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>C.1.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/206</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>C.1.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>66236</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018557168</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Proprietor - Total transfers</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>66236</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-29</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018694755</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Proprietor - Total transfers</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>66236</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-28</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
