<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-18T14:29:17</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226536</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226536</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-13</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>hu</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-18</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>SafeClean Household cleansing products</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162319131</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226536/000162319131.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>01.01.05</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>01.01.09</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>01.15.23</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.12</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.98</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Козметични тоалетни препарати; Препарати за грижа за тоалета на животни; Етерични масла и ароматни екстракти; Почистващи и ароматизиращи препарати; Препарати за изглаждане или полиране.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Toaletní přípravky; Kosmetické přípravky pro péči o zvířata; Vonné oleje a aromatické výtažky; Čistící prostředky a vonné přípravky; Brousicí přípravky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Toiletartikler; Plejemidler til dyr; Æteriske olier og aromatiske udtræk; Rengørings- og duftpræparater; Slibemidler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Körperpflegemittel; Tierpflegemittel; Ätherische Öle und aromatische Extrakte; Reinigungs- und Duftpräparate; Schleifmittel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καλλυντικά παρασκευάσματα· Παρασκευάσματα για την περιποίηση ζώων· Αιθέρια έλαια και αρωματικά εκχυλίσματα· Καθαριστικά και αρωματικά παρασκευάσματα· Προϊόντα για απόξεση/λείανση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Toiletries; Animal grooming preparations; Essential oils and aromatic extracts; Cleaning and fragrancing preparations; Abrasives.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Preparaciones de tocador; Productos para el cuidado y limpieza de animales; Aceites esenciales y extractos aromáticos; Preparaciones para limpiar y aromatizar; Abrasivos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tualettpreparaadid; Tooted loomade karvastiku hoolduseks; Eeterlikud õlid ja aroomiekstraktid; Puhastus- ja lõhnastusained; Abrasiivid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kosmeettiset ja peseytymisvalmisteet; Siistimisvalmisteet eläimille; Eteeriset öljyt ja aromaattiset uutteet; Puhdistus- ja raikastusvalmisteet; Hankausvalmisteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Préparations de toilette; Préparations pour le toilettage d'animaux; Huiles essentielles et extraits aromatiques; Préparations nettoyantes et parfumantes; Abrasifs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Toaletni pripravci; Pripravci za njegu životinja; Esencijalna ulja i aromatični ekstrakti; Pripravci za čišćenje i osvježivanje prostora; Strugači.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Testápolási cikkek; Állatápolási készítmények; Olajesszenciák és aromakivonatok; Tisztító és illatosító készítmények; Dörzsölő szerek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Preparati per la toilette; Prodotti per la toilette degli animali; Olii essenziali ed estratti aromatici; Preparati per pulire e profumare; Abrasivi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Tualetiniai preparatai; Gyvūnų higieninės ir grožio priežiūros preparatai; Eteriniai aliejai ir aromatiniai ekstraktai; Valymo ir kvėpinimo preparatai; Švitrai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Personiskās tualetes līdzekļi; Kopšanas līdzekļi dzīvniekiem; Ēteriskās eļļas un aromātiskie ekstrakti; Tīrīšanas un aromatizēšanas līdzekļi; Abrazīvie līdzekļi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Preparazzjonijiet tat-twaletta; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif ta' l-annimali; Żjut essenzjali u estratti aromatiċi; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif u għal riħa tfuħ; Preparazzjonijiet għal brix bi frizzjoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Preparaten voor de toiletverzorging; Producten voor cosmetische dierenverzorging; Essentiële oliën en aromatische extracten; Reinigingsproducten en geurproducten; Schuurmiddelen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Preparaty toaletowe; Preparaty do pielęgnacji zwierząt; Olejki esencjonalne i ekstrakty aromatyczne; Preparaty do czyszczenia i odświeżania; Środki ścierne i polerskie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Artigos de higiene pessoal; Produtos para tratamento (limpeza, etc.) de animais; Óleos essenciais e extratos aromáticos; Produtos para limpar e perfumar; Abrasivos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Produse de toaletă; Preparate pentru îngrijirea animalelor; Uleiuri esenţiale şi extracte aromatice; Preparate pentru curăţare şi odorizante; Abrazivi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Toaletné prípravky; Toaletné prípravky pre zvieratá; Éterické oleje a aromatické výťažky; Čistiace a vonné prípravky; Brúsivá.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Toaletna sredstva; Pripravki za nego živali; Eterična olja in aromatični ekstrakti; Preparati za čiščenje in odišavljanje; Abrazivi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Toalettartiklar; Preparat för pälsvård; Eteriska oljor och aromatiska extrakt; Rengöringsmedel och välluktande preparat; Slipmedel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Хранителни добавки и диетични препарати; Стоматологични препарати и изделия и лечебни средства за почистване на зъби; Санитарни препарати и изделия; Препарати и изделия за контрол на вредителите; Фармацевтични препарати и натурални средства за лечение; Медицински превръзки, превързочни материали покрития и апликатори; Ветеринарни препарати; Ветеринарни препарати и вещества; Медицински добавки за храни за животни; Лекарствени препарати за грижа за здравето; Фармацевтични препарати за ветеринарна употреба; Фармацевтични препарати за животни; Животински сосове [препарати]; Санитарни препарати за ветеринарни цели; Препарати от микроелементи за хуманна употреба; Комплекти за първа помощ за домашна употреба; Масажни гелове за медицински цели; Секвенции на нуклеинова киселина за медицински и ветеринарни цели; Микроелементи (Препарати, съдържащи -) за хуманни и ветеринарни цели; Лосиони за ветеринарни цели; Продукти с пантенол за медицинска употреба; Репеленти за кучета; Препарати за употреба при натуропатия; Хранителни добавки за ветеринарна употреба; Лосиони за кучета; Химически препарати за медицински цели; Химически препарати за ветеринарни цели; Витаминни и минерални препарати.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Potravní doplňky a dietetické přípravky; Zubní přípravky a výrobky a léčebné zubní pasty; Hygienické přípravky a výrobky; Přípravky proti rostlinným a živočišným škůdcům; Farmaceutické přípravky a přírodní léčiva; Obvazy, obvazový materiál a aplikátory léčebných přípravků; Veterinární přípravky; Veterinární přípravky a látky; Léčivé přísady do krmiva pro zvířata; Léčivé přípravky pro zdravotní péči; Farmaceutické výrobky pro veterinární účely; Farmaceutické přípravky pro zvířata; Koupelové přípravky k ošetření zvířat; Hygienické přípravky pro veterinářské účely; Přípravky se stopovými prvky pro lidskou spotřebu; Lékárničky pro domácí použití; Masážní gely pro léčebné účely; Sekvence nukleové kyseliny pro lékařské a veterinární účely; Přípravky se stopovými prvky pro humánní a veterinární použití; Lotiony pro veterinární účely; Přípravky obsahující panthenol pro lékařské účely; Repelenty pro psy; Přípravky k použití v naturopatii; Doplňky krmiva pro veterinární účely; Toaletní vody pro psy; Chemické přípravky pro léčebné účely; Chemické přípravky pro veterinární účely; Vitaminové a minerální prípravky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kosttilskud og diætetiske præparater; Tandpræparater og -artikler samt medicinske tandpastaer; Hygiejniske præparater og artikler; Præparater og artikler til skadedyrsbekæmpelse; Farmaceutiske præparater og naturlægemidler; Medicinske plaster, forbindsstoffer og applikatorer; Veterinære præparater; Veterinærmedicinske præparater og substanser; Medicinske tilsætningsstoffer til dyrefoder; Medicinske sundhedsplejepræparater; Farmaceutiske præparater til veterinærmedicinske formål; Farmaceutiske præparater til dyr; Rensemidler til dyr (skadedyrsudrydende); Hygiejnepræparater til veterinære formål; Præparater indeholdende sporstoffer til mennesker; Førstehjælpskasser til husholdningsbrug; Massagegel til medicinske formål; Nukleinsyresekvenser til medicinske og veterinære formål; Præparater i form af sporelementer til human og veterinær brug; Lotions til veterinær brug; Panthenolpræparater til medicinsk brug; Hundefordrivende midler; Præparater til anvendelse inden for naturopati; Tilskudsfoder til veterinære formål; Hundelotions; Kemiske præparater til medicinske formål; Kemiske præparater til veterinære formål; Vitamin- og mineralpræparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Diätetische Präparate und Nahrungsergänzungsmittel; Zahnmedizinische Präparate und Erzeugnisse sowie medizinische Zahnputzmittel; Hygienepräparate und -artikel; Schädlingsbekämpfungspräparate und -artikel; Arzneimittel und natürliche Heilmittel; Verbandmaterial, Abdeckmaterialien und Applikatoren [medizinisch]; Veterinärmedizinische Präparate; Veterinärmedizinische Präparate und Substanzen; Medizinische Futter-Zusatzstoffe; Medizinische Gesundheitspräparate; Pharmazeutische Präparate für veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Pharmazeutische Präparate für Tiere; Tierdesinfektionspräparate; Veterinärmedizinische Hygienepräparate; Präparate aus Spurenelementen für die menschliche Ernährung; Erste-Hilfe-Sets für die Verwendung im Haushalt; Massagegele für medizinische Zwecke; Nukleinsäuresequenzen für medizinische und veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Präparate von Spurenelementen für Human- und Tierkonsum; Lotionen für veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Panthenolpräparate für medizinische Zwecke; Hundeabstoßende Mittel; Medizinische Präparate zur Verwendung in der Naturheilkunde; Futterzusätze für veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Hundelotionen für veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Chemische Präparate für medizinische Zwecke; Chemische Präparate für veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Vitamin- und Mineralstoffpräparate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συμπληρώματα διατροφής και διαιτητικά παρασκευάσματα· Οδοντιατρικά παρασκευάσματα και είδη, και φαρμακευτικά οδοντοσκευάσματα· Παρασκευάσματα υγειονομικά και είδη αυτών· Παρασκευάσματα καταπολέμισης παρασίτων και ειδη αυτών· Φαρμακευτικά προϊόντα και φυσικές θεραπείες· Ιατρικές γάζες, καλύμματα και εξαρτήματα εφαρμογής· Κτηνιατρικά (Προϊόντα -)· Κτηνιατρικά παρασκευάσματα και ουσίες· Πρόσθετα (φαρμακευτικά) για ζωοτροφές· Φαρμακευτικά παρασκευάσματα για ιατρική περίθαλψη· Φαρμακευτικά παρασκευάσματα για κτηνιατρική χρήση· Φαρμακευτικά παρασκευάσματα για ζώα· Ζωικής διαλύματα [παρασκευάσματα]· Προϊόντα υγιεινής για κτηνιατρική χρήση· Παρασκευάσματα με ιχνοστοιχεία για χρήση από τον άνθρωπο· Κουτιά πρώτων βοηθειών για οικιακή χρήση· Ζελέ για μαλάξεις (μασάζ) για ιατρική χρήση· Αλληλουχίες νουκλεϊκών οξέων για ιατρική και κτηνιατρική χρήση· Ιχνοστοιχεία (παρασκευάσματα -ων) καταναλώσιμα από ανθρώπους και ζώα· Λοσιόν κτηνιατρικής χρήσης· Παρασκευάσματα πανθενόλης για ιατρική χρήση· Απωθητικά προιόντα σκύλων· Παρασκευάσματα για χρήση στη θεραπεία με φυσικές μεθόδους· Συμπληρώματα ζωοτροφών για κτηνιατρική χρήση· Σκύλους (Λοσιόν για -)· Χημικά (Παρασκευάσματα -) για την ιατρική· Χημικά (Παρασκευάσματα -) για χρήση κτηνιατρική· Παρασκευάσματα βιταμινούχα και ιχνοστοιχείων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Dietary supplements and dietetic preparations; Dental preparations and articles, and medicated dentifrices; Sanitary preparations and articles; Pest control preparations and articles; Pharmaceuticals and natural remedies; Medical dressings, coverings and applicators; Veterinary preparations; Veterinary preparations and substances; Medicated additives for animal foods; Medicinal healthcare preparations; Pharmaceutical preparations for veterinary use; Pharmaceutical preparations for animals; Animal dips [preparations]; Sanitary preparations for veterinary use; Trace element preparations for human use; First aid kits for domestic use; Massage gels for medical purposes; Nucleic acid sequences for medical and veterinary purposes; Preparations of trace elements for human and animal use; Lotions for veterinary purposes; Panthenol preparations for medical use; Repellents for dogs; Preparations for use in naturopathy; Feed supplements for veterinary use; Dog lotions for veterinary purposes; Chemical preparations for medical purposes; Chemical preparations for veterinary purposes; Vitamin and mineral preparations.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Suplementos y preparaciones dietéticas; Preparaciones y artículos dentales, así como dentífricos medicinales; Preparaciones sanitarias y productos de las mismas; Productos y preparaciones para el control de plagas; Remedios naturales y farmacéuticos; Apósitos, vendas y aplicadores médicos; Preparaciones veterinarias; Productos y sustancias veterinarias; Aditivos medicinales para alimentos de animales; Preparaciones medicinales para el cuidado de la salud; Preparados farmacéuticos para uso veterinario; Productos farmacéuticos para animales; Baños de inmersión antiparasitarios para animales [preparaciones]; Preparaciones sanitarias para uso veterinario; Preparados de oligoelementos para el consumo humano; Botiquines de primeros auxilios para uso doméstico; Geles de masaje para uso médico; Secuencias de ácidos nucleicos para uso médico y veterinario; Preparaciones de oligoelementos para el consumo humano y animal; Lociones para uso veterinario; Preparados de pantenol para uso médico; Repelentes para perros; Preparados para su uso en naturopatía; Complementos para piensos para uso veterinario; Lociones para perros; Preparaciones químicas para uso médico; Preparaciones químicas para uso veterinario; Preparaciones de vitaminas y minerales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Toidulisandid ja farmatseutilised dieetained; Hambaravipreparaadid ja -tooted ning ravitoimega hambapuhastusained; Hügieenipreparaadid ja -tooted; Kahjuritõrjepreparaadid ja -tooted; Farmatseutilised ja looduslikud ravimid; Meditsiinilised sidemed, katted ja aplikaatorid; Veterinaariapreparaadid, loomaravimid; Veterinaariapreparaadid ja -ained; Ravitoimelised lisandid loomatoitudele; Meditsiinilised tervisepreparaadid; Farmatseutilised preparaadid veterinaarias kasutamiseks; Farmaatsiatooted loomadele; Parasiiditõrjevedelikud loomadele; Veterinaarsed sanitaarpreparaadid; Mikroelemendipreparaadid inimtarbimiseks; Esmaabikomplektid koduseks kasutuseks; Ravitoimega massaažigeelid; Nukleiinhappejadad meditsiiniliseks ja veterinaarseks otstarbeks; Mikroelemendipreparaadid inimestele ja loomadele; Veterinaarsed loputusvedelikud; Meditsiinilised pantenoolpreparaadid; Koerte repellendid (putukatõrjeained); Naturopaatias kasutatavad preparaadid; Veterinaarsed söödalisandid; Koerte kehahooldusvahendid [losjoonid]; Meditsiinilised keemiapreparaadid; Veterinaarsed keemiapreparaadid; Vitamiin- ja mineraalpreparaadid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lisäravinteet ja dieettivalmisteet; Hammaslääkinnälliset valmisteet ja tuotteet sekä lääkeaineita sisältävät hampaidenpuhdistusaineet; Saniteettivalmisteet ja -tarvikkeet; Tuholaistorjuntavalmisteet ja -tuotteet; Lääkkeet ja luonnonlääkkeet; Lääkinnälliset sidontatarvikkeet, suojat ja asettimet; Eläinlääkinnälliset valmisteet; Eläinlääkinnälliset valmisteet ja aineet; Lääkeaineita sisältävät eläinten ruokien lisäaineet; Lääkinnälliset terveydenhoitovalmisteet; Farmaseuttiset valmisteet eläinlääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Farmaseuttiset valmisteet eläimiä varten; Eläinten pesuliuokset [farmaseuttiset valmisteet]; Hygieniatuotteet eläinlääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Hivenainevalmisteet ihmisille; Ensiapupakkaukset kotitalouskäyttöön; Hierontageelit lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Nukleiinihappoketjut lääketieteellisiin ja eläinlääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Hivenainevalmisteet ihmisille ja eläimille; Liuokset eläinlääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Pantenolivalmisteet lääkintäkäyttöön; Koirien syöpäläiskarkotteet; Valmisteet käytettäväksi luontaishoidossa; Eläinrehujen ravintolisät eläinlääkintätarkoituksiin; Koirien huuhtelunesteet [lääkinnälliset]; Kemialliset valmisteet lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Kemialliset valmisteet eläinlääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Vitamiini- ja kivennäisvalmisteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Compléments alimentaires et préparations diététiques; Préparations et articles dentaires, et dentifrices médicinaux; Préparation et articles d'hygiène; Préparations et articles pour la lutte contre les animaux nuisibles; Produits pharmaceutiques et remèdes naturels; Pansements, protections et applicateurs médicaux; Produits vétérinaires; Préparations et substances vétérinaires; Additifs destinés à la nutrition animale à usage vétérinaire; Préparations médicinales pour soins de santé; Préparations pharmaceutiques à usage vétérinaire; Préparations pharmaceutiques pour animaux; Bains parasiticides pour animaux [préparations]; Préparations hygiéniques à usage vétérinaire; Préparations à base d'oligo-éléments à usage humain; Trousses de premiers secours à usage ménager; Gels de massage à usage médical; Séquences d'acides nucléiques à usage médical et vétérinaire; Préparations d'oligo-éléments pour la consommation humaine et animale; Lotions à usage vétérinaire; Produits à base de panthénol à usage médical; Répulsifs pour chiens; Préparations médicales destinées à la naturopathie; Compléments pour l'alimentation du bétail à usage vétérinaire; Lotions pour chiens; Préparations chimiques à usage médical; Préparations chimiques à usage vétérinaire; Produits vitaminés et minéraux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Dodaci prehrani i dijetetski pripravci; Zubarski pripravci, proizvodi i medicinske paste za zube; Sanitarni pripravci i proizvodi; Pripravci i proizvodi za uklanjanje štetočina; Farmaceutski proizvodi i prirodna ljekovita sredstva; Medicinski povoji, pokrovi i aplikatori; Veterinarski proizvodi; Veterinarski pripravci i tvari; Ljekoviti aditivi za hranu za životinje; Ljekoviti pripravci za njegu zdravlja; Farmaceutski pripravci za veterinarsku uporabu; Farmaceutski pripravci za životinje; Pripravci za dezinfekciju životinja; Sanitarni pripravci za veterinarske potrebe; Pripravci oligoelemenata za ljudsku uporabu; Pribor za prvu pomoć za primjenu u kućanstvu; Masažni gelovi za medicinske svrhe; Sekvence nukleinske kiseline za primjenu u medicini i veterinarstvu; Preparati oligoelemenata za ljudsku i životinjsku prehranu; Losioni za veterinarske potrebe; Preparati na bazi pantenola za medicinsku uporabu; Psi (sredstva za odbijanje pasa) [repulzivi]; Pripravci za uporabu u naturopatiji; Dodaci hrani za veterinarske potrebe; Losioni za pse; Kemijski preparati za medicinske potrebe; Kemijski preparati za veterinarske potrebe; Vitaminski i mineralni pripravci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Táplálékkiegészítők és diétás készítmények; Fogászati készítmények és árucikkek, gyógyhatású fogkrémek; Egészségügyi készítmények és cikkek; Kártevőirtó készítmények és cikkek; Gyógyszerek és természetes gyógykészítmények; Gyógyászati kötszerek és applikátorok; Állatgyógyászati készítmények; Állatgyógyászati készítmények és anyagok; Gyógyászati állateledel-adalékok; Gyógyszeres egészségmegőrző készítmények; Gyógyszerészeti készítmények állatgyógyászati használatra; Gyógyszerészeti készítmények állatok számára; Állatok fertőtlenítésére szolgáló fürdőkészítmények; Egészségügyi készítmények állatorvosi célokra; Emberi fogyasztásra szánt nyomelem készítmények; Elsősegély-készletek háztartási használatra; Masszázsgélek gyógyászati használatra; Nukleinsav-szekvenciák gyógyászati és állatgyógyászati célokra; Nyomelem készítmények emberi és állati fogyasztásra; Oldatok, folyadékok állatgyógyászati használatra; Panthenol készítmények gyógyászati használatra; Rovarriasztó szerek kutyáknak; Természetgyógyászati készítmények; Táplálék-kiegészítők állatgyógyászati célokra; Testápoló folyadékok kutyáknak; Vegyi készítmények orvosi, gyógyászati célokra; Vegyi készítmények állatorvosi célokra; Vitamin- és ásványianyag-készítmények.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Integratori alimentari e preparati dietetici; Preparati e articoli odontoiatrici, e dentifrici medicati; Preparati e prodotti per l'igiene; Preparati ed articoli antiparassitari; Medicamenti farmaceutici e naturali; Bende mediche, fasciature ed applicatori; Prodotti veterinari; Preparati e sostanze veterinarie; Additivi medicati per alimenti per animali; Preparazioni medicamentose per la salute; Prodotti farmaceutici per uso veterinario; Preparati farmaceutici per animali; Bagni disinfettanti per animali [preparati]; Prodotti igienici per uso veterinario; Preparati di oligoelementi per uso umano; Cassetta di pronto soccorso per uso domestico; Gel per massaggi ad uso medico; Sequenze di acidi nucleici per uso medico e veterinario; Preparati di oligo-elementi per il consumo umano e animale; Lozioni per uso veterinario; Preparati a base di pantenolo per uso medico; Repulsivi per cani; Preparati per uso in naturopatia; Integratori alimentari per uso veterinario; Lozioni per cani; Preparati chimici per uso medico; Preparati chimici per uso veterinario; Preparati a base di vitamine e di minerali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Maisto papildai ir dietiniai produktai; Dantų priežiūros preparatai ir priemonės, medicininės dantų valymo priemonės; Higienos preparatai ir gaminiai; Kenkėjų naikinimo preparatai ir priemonės; Farmaciniai ir natūralūs vaistiniai preparatai; Medicininė tvarsliava, uždangalai ir kompresai; Veterinariniai preparatai; Veterinariniai preparatai ir medžiagos; Gydomieji gyvūnų pašaro priedai; Medicininiai sveikatos priežiūros preparatai; Farmaciniai preparatai veterinarijos reikmėms; Farmaciniai preparatai gyvūnams; Gyvūnų dezinfektantai [preparatai]; Higienos preparatai veterinarijos reikmėms; Mikroelementų preparatai (žmonėms); Buitiniai pirmosios pagalbos reikmenų rinkiniai; Masažo geliai medicinos reikmėms; Nukleorūgščių sekos medicinos ir veterinarijos reikmėms; Mikroelementų preparatai (žmonėms ir gyvuliams); Losjonai (veterinarijos reikmėms); Pantenolio preparatai medicinos reikmėms; Šunų repelentai; Preparatai natūropatijos reikmėms; Pašaro papildai veterinarijos reikmėms; Šunų losjonai; Cheminiai preparatai (medicinos reikmėms); Cheminiai preparatai (veterinarijos reikmėms); Vitamininiai ir mineraliniai preparatai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Uztura bagātinātāji un diētiskie preparāti; Zobārstniecības preparāti un izstrādājumi, ārstnieciskas zobu pastas un pulveri; Higiēnas līdzekļi un izstrādājumi; Preparāti un izstrādājumi kaitēkļu iznīcināšanai un aizsardzībai pret kaitēkļiem; Farmaceitiskie un dabiskie ārstniecības līdzekļi; Medicīniskie pārsēji, pārklāji un aplikatori; Veterinārie preparāti; Veterinārie preparāti un vielas; Medikamentus saturošas piedevas dzīvnieku barībai; Medicīniski veselības aprūpes preparāti; Farmaceitiskie preparāti veterināriem nolūkiem; Farmaceitiskie preparāti dzīvniekiem; Mazgāšanas līdzekļi dzīvnieku apstrādāšanai pret patogēniem organismiem un parazītiem; Higiēnas preparāti veterinārijas nolūkiem; Mikroelementu preparāti cilvēkam; Pirmās palīdzības piederumu komplekti mājsaimniecībai; Masāžas želejas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Nukleīnskābju sekvences medicīniskām un veterinārām vajadzībām; Mikroelementu preparāti cilvēkam un dzīvniekiem; Losjoni veterināriem nolūkiem; Pantenola preparāti izmantošanai medicīnā; Suņu atbaidīšanai paredzēti līdzekļi (repelenti); Naturopātijā izmantojami preparāti; Barības piedevas veterinārijas vajadzībām; Suņu losjoni; Ķīmiskie preparāti medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Ķīmiskie preparāti veterināriem nolūkiem; Vitamīnu un minerālvielu preparāti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Supplimenti tad-dieta u preparazzjonijiet dijetetiċi; Preparazzjonijiet u oġġetti għas-snien, u dentifriċi medikati; Prodotti u preparazzjonijiet sanitarji; Preparazzjonijiet u oġġetti għall-kontrol tal-pesti; Farmaċewtiċi u rimedji naturali; Infaxxar, oġġetti li kgħattu w applikaturi mediċi; Preparazzjonijiet veterinarji; Preparazzjonijiet u sustanzi veterinarji; Sustanzi medikati miżjuda mal-għalf tal-bhejjem; Preparazzjonijiet mediċinali għall-kura tas-saħħa; Preparazzjonijiet farmaċewtiċi għall-użu veterinarju; Preparazzjonijiet farmaċewtiċi għall-annimali; Ilma diżinfettant għall-ħasil tal-bhejjem [Preparazzjonijiet għall- -]; Preparazzjonijiet sanitarji għal skopijiet veterinarji; Preparazzjonijiet tal-oligoelementi għall-użu uman; Kitts tal-ewwel għajnuna għall-użu domestiku; Ġellijiet tal-massaġġi, għal skopijiet mediċinali; Sekwenzi tal-aċidu nuklejku għal skopijiet mediċi u veterinarji; Preparazzjonijiet ta' elementi bżonjużi fi kwantitajiet żgħar ħafna għal użu ma' bnedmin jew annimali; Lozjonijiet għal skopijiet veterinarji; Preparazzjonijiet tal-pantenol għall-użu mediku; Ripellenti għal klieb; Preparazzjonijiet għall-użu fin-naturopatija; Supplimenti tal-għalf għal skopijiet veterinarji; Lozjonijiet tal-klieb; Preparazzjonijiet kimiċi għal skopijiet mediċi; Preparazzjonijiet kimiċi għal skopijiet veterinarji; Preparazzjonijiet tal-vitamini u tal-minerali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diëtische supplementen en diëtische preparaten; Tandheelkundige preparaten en producten, en medicinale tandpasta; Hygiënische preparaten en artikelen; Preparaten en producten voor het bestrijden van ongedierte; Farmaceutische en natuurlijke geneesmiddelen; Verbandartikelen, pleisters en medische applicators; Veterinaire producten; Diergeneeskundige produkten en substanties; Medicinale additieven voor voedingsmiddelen voor dieren; Medicinale gezondheidsverzorgende preparaten; Farmaceutische producten voor diergeneeskundig gebruik; Farmaceutische preparaten voor dieren; Desinfectiebaden voor dieren [preparaten]; Hygiënische preparaten voor diergeneeskundige doeleinden; Preparaten van oligo-elementen voor menselijke consumptie; EHBO-dozen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Massagegels voor medisch gebruik; Nucleïnezuursequenties voor medische en diergeneeskundige doeleinden; Preparaten van oligo-elementen voor menselijke en dierlijke consumptie; Lotions voor veterinair gebruik; Panthenolpreparaten voor medisch gebruik; Afstotende middelen voor honden; Naturopathie (Preparaten voor gebruik bij -); Voersupplementen voor diergeneeskundige doeleinden; Hondenlotions; Chemische preparaten voor medisch gebruik; Chemische preparaten voor veterinair gebruik; Vitamine- en mineraalpreparaten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Suplementy diety i preparaty dietetyczne; Preparaty i artykuły dentystyczne oraz lecznicze środki do czyszczenia zębów; Preparaty i artykuły higieniczne; Preparaty i artykuły do tępienia szkodników; Farmaceutyki i naturalne środki lecznicze; Opatrunki medyczne, materiały opatrunkowe i aplikatory; Preparaty weterynaryjne; Preparaty i substancje weterynaryjne; Dodatki lecznicze do pożywienia zwierząt; Preparaty lecznicze do pielęgnacji zdrowia; Preparaty farmaceutyczne do użytku weterynaryjnego; Preparaty farmaceutyczne dla zwierząt; Kąpiele w płynie odkażającym dla zwierząt [preparaty]; Preparaty sanitarne do celów weterynaryjnych; Preparaty z pierwiastkami śladowymi dla ludzi; Apteczki pierwszej pomocy do użytku domowego; Żele do masażu do celów medycznych; Sekwencje kwasów nukleinowych do celów medycznych i weterynaryjnych; Preparaty z pierwiastkami śladowymi dla ludzi i zwierząt; Płyny do celów weterynaryjnych; Preparaty zawierające pantenol do użytku medycznego; Środki odstraszające insekty dla psów; Preparaty do stosowania w naturopatii; Suplementy do karm do celów weterynaryjnych; Płyny dla psów; Preparaty chemiczne do celów medycznych; Preparaty chemiczne do celów weterynaryjnych; Preparaty witaminowe i mineralne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Suplementos e preparações dietéticos; Preparações e artigos dentários, e dentífricos medicinais; Preparações e artigos de higiene; Preparações e artigos pesticidas; Produtos farmacêuticos e remédios naturais; Curativos, ligaduras e aplicadores médicos; Preparações veterinárias; Preparações e substâncias veterinárias; Aditivos medicinais para alimentação animal; Preparações medicinais de cuidados de saúde; Preparados farmacêuticos para uso veterinário; Produtos farmacêuticos para animais; Imersões para animais [preparações]; Preparações higiénicas para uso veterinário; Preparações de oligoelementos para consumo humano; Estojos de primeiros socorros para uso doméstico; Geles de massagem para uso medicinal; Sequências de ácido nucleico para uso médico e veterinário; Produtos de oligoelementos para consumo humano e animal; Loções para uso veterinário; Preparações de pantenol para uso médico; Repelentes para cães; Preparações destinadas à naturopatia; Suplementos alimentares para uso veterinário; Loções para cães; Produtos químicos para uso medicinal; Produtos químicos para uso veterinário; Preparações vitamínicas e minerais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Suplimente alimentare si preparate dietetice; Preparate şi articole dentare şi produse medicinale pentru îngrijirea dinţilor; Preparate şi articole sanitare; Produse şi articole pentru distrugerea dăunătorilor; Remedii naturale şi farmaceutice; Pansamente, bandaje şi plasturi medicali; Veterinare (Produse -); Preparate şi substanţe veterinare; Aditivi medicinali pentru hrana animalelor; Preparate medicinale pentru îngrijirea sănătăţii; Preparate farmaceutice de uz veterinar; Preparate farmaceutice pentru animale; Băi cu preparate pentru deparazitare pentru animale; Preparate igienice de uz veterinar; Preparate cu oligoelemente pentru consumul uman; Truse de prim ajutor de uz casnic; Geluri de masaj de uz medical; Secvenţe de acizi nucleici de uz medical şi veterinare; Oligoelemente (Preparate cu -) pentru consum uman şi animal; Loţiuni de uz veterinar; Preparate pe bază de panthenol, de uz medical; Produse repulsive pentru câini; Preparate utilizate în naturopatie; Suplimente pentru furaje de uz veterinar; Câini (Loţiuni pentru -); Chimice (preparate - de uz medical); Chimice (preparate - de uz veterinar); Preparate cu minerale şi vitamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Výživové doplnky a dietetické prípravky; Dentálne prípravky a potreby, liečivé prípravky na čistenie zubov; Hygienické prípravky a výrobky; Prípravky a pomôcky na reguláciu škodcov; Farmaceutické a prírodné liečivá; Zdravotnícke obväzové materiály, obklady a aplikátory; Zverolekárske prípravky; Veterinárne prípravky a substancie; Liečivé prísady do krmiva pre zvieratá; Liečivé prípravky pre starostlivosť o zdravie; Farmaceutické prípravky pre veterinárne účely; Farmaceutické prípravky pre zvieratá; Kúpeľové roztoky na ošetrenie kože zvierat; Hygienické prípravky na veterinárne použitie; Prípravky zo stopových prvkov na ľudskú spotrebu; Lekárničky do domácnosti; Masážne gély na lekárske účely; Sekvencie nukleových kyselín na lekárske a zverolekárske účely; Potravinové alebo krmivové prípravky so stopovými prvkami; Roztoky na veterinárne použitie; Prípravky s obsahom pantenolu na lekárske použitie; Repelenty pre psov; Prípravky na použitie pri prírodnej liečbe; Doplnky do krmiva na zverolekárske účely; Toaletné vody pre psov; Chemické prípravky na lekárske použitie; Chemické prípravky na zverolekárske použitie; Vitamíny a minerálne prípravky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Prehranska dopolnila in dietetske snovi; Zobni pripravki in izdelki ter zobne paste z zdravilnimi učinkovinami; Sanitarni pripravki in izdelki; Izdelki in preparati za uničevanje škodljivcev; Farmacevtski proizvodi in naravna zdravila; Obvezilni material, obliži in aplikatorji za oskrbo ran; Veterinarski pripravki; Veterinarski pripravki in snovi; Dodatki z zdravilnimi učinkovinami za živalska krmila; Medicinski pripravki za zdravstveno nego; Farmacevtski pripravki za veterinarsko uporabo; Farmacevtski pripravki za živali; Pripravki za kopanje živali; Sanitarni pripravki za veterinarsko uporabo; Pripravki z oligoelementi za človeško uporabo; Kompleti za prvo pomoč za gospodinjsko uporabo; Masažni geli za medicinske namene; Zaporedja nukleinskih kislin za medicinske in veterinarske namene; Preparati iz elementov v sledovih za človeško in živalsko uporabo; Losjoni za veterinarske namene; Pripravki na osnovi pantenola za medicinsko uporabo; Sredstva za odganjanje psov; Pripravki, ki se uporabljajo v naturopatiji; Prehranska dopolnila za veterinarsko uporabo; Losjoni za pse; Kemični pripravki za medicinske namene; Kemični pripravki za veterinarske namene; Vitaminski in mineralni pripravki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Dietiska tillskott och preparat; Dentala preparat och artiklar samt medicinska tandpulver, -krämer och -pastor; Sanitära preparat och -artiklar; Preparat och artiklar för skadedjursbekämpning; Läkemedel och naturläkemedel; Medicinska förband, -höljen och -skydd; Veterinärpreparat; Veterinära preparat och substanser; Medicinska tillsatser till djurfoder; Medicinska hälsovårdspreparat; Farmaceutiska preparat för veterinärt bruk; Farmaceutiska preparat för djur; Tvättpreparat för djur; Sanitära preparat för veterinärt bruk; Spårämnespreparat för människor; Förbandslådor för hushållsbruk; Massagegel för medicinska ändamål; Nukleinsyrasekvenser för medicinska och veterinära ändamål; Spårämnespreparat för människor och djur; Lotioner för veterinära ändamål; Pantenolpreparat för medicinskt bruk; Insektsavvisande medel för hundar; Alternativmedicinska preparat; Fodertillskott för veterinärt bruk; Hundtvättmedel (medicinska); Kemiska preparat för medicinska ändamål; Kemiska preparat för veterinära ändamål; Vitamin- och mineralpreparat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/083</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/155</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-17</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>828622</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
