<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-20T08:29:30</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226738</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226738</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-19</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-20</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>PRÈ LONDON</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Козметични средства; Парфюмерия; Етерични масла; Препарати за грижа за кожата; Препарати за коса и за третиране на окосмяването; Сапуни; Препарати за вана и душ; Слънцезащитни препарати [козметични средства]; Немедицински тоалетни принадлежности.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kosmetické přípravky; Parfémy; Éterické oleje; Přípravky pro péči o pleť; Přípravky pro péči o vlasy a přípravky na holení; Mýdla; Sprchové a koupelové přípravky; Ochranné opalovací přípravky; Neléčebné toaletní potřeby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kosmetik; Parfumer; Æteriske olier; Hudplejepræparater; Præparater til hår og behandling af hår; Sæber; Præparater til bad og brusebad; Solplejepræparater [kosmetik]; Ikke-medicinske toiletartikler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kosmetika; Parfüms; Ätherische Öle; Hautpflegemittel; Haarpräparate und Haarkuren; Seifen; Bade- und Duschpräparate; Sonnenschutzpräparate [Kosmetika]; Toilettemittel, nicht für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καλλυντικά· Αρωματισμού (Προϊόντα -)· Αιθέρια (Έλαια -)· Παρασκευάσματα για την περιποίηση του δέρματος· Παρασκευάσματα για την περιποίηση και τη θεραπεία των μαλλιών· Σαπούνια· Παρασκευάσματα για το μπάνιο και το ντους· Προϊόντα περιποίησης για την έκθεση στον ήλιο· Μη φαρμακευτικά είδη ατομικής περιποίησης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Cosmetics; perfumes; essential oils; skin care preparations; hair care preparations; soaps; bath and shower preparations; sun care preparations; non-medicated toilet preparations.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cosméticos; Perfumes; Aceites esenciales; Preparaciones para el cuidado de la piel; Preparaciones y tratamientos para el cabello; Jabones; Preparaciones para el baño y la ducha; Preparaciones de protección solar [cosméticos]; Productos de tocador no medicinales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kosmeetikavahendid; Parfüümid, lõhnaõlid; Eeterlikud õlid; Nahahooldusvahendid; Juuksehooldus- ja -töötlusvahendid; Seebid; Vanni- ja dušipreparaadid; Päikesekaitsepreparaadid [kosmeetikatooted]; Ravitoimeta tualett-tarbed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kosmetiikka; Parfyymit; Eteeriset öljyt; Ihonhoitovalmisteet; Hiusten hoito- ja käsittelyvalmisteet; Saippuat; Kylpy- ja suihkutuotteet; Auringonottoon tarkoitetut hoitovalmisteet [kosmeettiset tuotteet]; Lääkeaineita sisältämättömät hygieniatuotteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Cosmétiques; Parfums; Huiles essentielles; Préparations pour le soin de la peau; Préparations et traitements capillaires; Savons; Préparations de douche et bain; Préparations de protection solaire; Produits de toilette non médicinaux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kozmetički proizvodi; Mirisi; Esencijalna ulja; Pripravci za njegu kože; Pripravci i tretmani za kosu; Sapuni; Pripravci za kupanje i tuširanje; Pripravci za njegu kod sunčanja [kozmetika]; Neljekoviti toaletni proizvodi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kozmetikai szerek; Illatszer készítmények; Esszenciális olajok; Bőrápoló készítmények; Hajápoló készítmények; Szappanok; Fürdő- és tusolókészítmények; Készítmények napozáshoz [kozmetikumok]; Nem gyógyhatású piperecikkek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cosmetici; Profumo; Oli essenziali; Prodotti per la cura della pelle; Preparati e trattamenti per i capelli; Saponi; Preparazioni per bagno e doccia; Prodotti solari [cosmetici]; Prodotti non medicinali per la toilette.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kosmetika; Parfumerijos gaminiai; Eteriniai aliejai; Odos priežiūros preparatai; Plaukų priežiūros preparatai; Muilas; Vonios ir dušo preparatai; Preparatai nuo saulės [kosmetiniai]; Negydomieji tualeto reikmenys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kosmētiskie līdzekļi; Smaržas; Ēteriskās eļļas; Ādas kopšanas līdzekļi; Līdzekļi matiem un matu kopšanas līdzekļi; Ziepes; Vannas un dušas līdzekļi; Sauļošanās līdzekļi [kosmētiska]; Medikamentus nesaturoši tualetes piederumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kożmetiċi; Prodotti ta' fwejjaħ; Żjut meħudin minn pjanti; Preparazzjonijiet għall-ġilda; Preparazzjonijiet u trattamenti għax-xagħar; Sapun; Preparazzjonijiet tal-banju u tad-doċċa; Preparazzjonijiet għall-kura mix-xemx [kosmetiċi]; Preparazzjonijiet tat-twaletta mhux medikati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Cosmetica; Parfums; Etherische oliën; Huidverzorgingsproducten; Haarverzorgingsproducten en haarbehandelingsproducten; Zepen; Bad- en douchepreparaten; Zonverzorgingspreparaten [cosmetica]; Niet-medicinale producten voor de toiletverzorging.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kosmetyki; Produkty perfumeryjne; Olejki eteryczne; Preparaty do pielęgnacji skóry; Preparaty do włosów; Mydła; Preparaty do kąpieli i pod prysznic; Preparaty do ochrony przeciwsłonecznej [kosmetyczne]; Nielecznicze produkty toaletowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cosméticos; Perfumes; Óleos essenciais; Produtos para os cuidados da pele; Produtos e tratamentos para o cabelo; Sabões; Preparações para banho e duche; Produtos para proteção solar [cosméticos]; Produtos de toilette não medicinais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cosmetice; Parfumerie (Produse de -); Uleiuri eterice; Preparate pentru îngrijirea pielii; Preparate şi tratamente pentru păr; Săpunuri; Preparate pentru baie şi duş; Preparate pentru îngrijirea pielii în timpul expunerii la soare [cosmetice]; Produse de toaletă nemedicinale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kozmetické prípravky; Voňavkárske výrobky; Esenciálne (éterické) oleje; Pleťová kozmetika; Vlasová kozmetika a prípravky na ošetrenie vlasov; Mydlá; Prípravky na kúpanie a sprchovanie; Ochranné opaľovacie prípravky [kozmetické prípravky]; Toaletné prípravky bez liečivých prísad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kozmetični izdelki; Parfumerijski izdelki; Eterična olja; Sredstva za nego kože; Sredstva za nego in obdelavo las; Mila; Pripravki za kopanje in tuširanje; Pripravki za nego med sončenjem [kozmetična sredstva]; Toaletni pripomočki brez zdravilnih učinkovin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kosmetika; Parfymerivaror; Flyktiga oljor; Hudvårdspreparat; Preparat för behandling och vård av hår; Tvål; Bad- och duschpreparat; Solvårdspreparat; Icke-medicinska toalettartiklar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Оптични стоки; Слънчеви очила; Калъфи, Въжета и вериги за очила; Рамки и лещи за очила и слънчеви очила; Калъфи, капаци и чанти за телефони, компютри и електронни устройства; Части и принадлежности за горепосочените стоки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Výrobky oční optiky; Sluneční brýle; Pouzdra, skříňky, Šňůrky a řetízky k brýlím; Obruby a čočky pro brýle a sluneční brýle; Pouzdra, kryty a přenosné tašky na telefony, počítače a elektronická zařízení; Části a příslušenství výše uvedených výrobků.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Optikervarer; Solbriller; Mapper, Snore og kæder til briller; Brille- og solbrillestel og -glas; Hylstre, overtræk og transporttasker til telefoner, computere og elektroniske apparater; Dele og komponenter til førnævnte produkter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Brillen und Kontaktlinsen; Sonnenbrillen; Etuis, Kordeln und Ketten für Brillen; Gestelle und Gläser für Brillen und Sonnenbrillen; Etuis, Hüllen und Tragetaschen für Telefone, Computer und elektronische Geräte; Teile der und Zubehör für die vorgenannten Waren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Οπτικά είδη· Γυαλιά ηλίου· Θήκες, Κορδόνια και αλυσίδες για γυαλιά οράσεως· Σκελετοί και φακοί για γυαλιά οράσεως και γυαλιά ηλίου· Θήκες, καλύμματα και τσάντες μεταφοράς για τηλέφωνα, ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές και ηλεκτρονικές διατάξεις· Μέρη και εξαρτήματα για τα προαναφερθέντα είδη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Eyewear; sunglasses; cases, cords and chains for eyewear; spectacle and sunglasses frames and lenses; cases, covers and carry bags for telephones, computers and electronic devices; parts and fittings for the aforesaid goods.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Artículos de óptica para la vista; Gafas de sol; Estuches, Cordones y cadenas para artículos ópticos; Monturas y lentes de gafas y gafas de sol; Estuches, fundas y bolsas de transporte para teléfonos, ordenadores y dispositivos electrónicos; Piezas y accesorios para todos los productos citados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Optikakaubad; Päikeseprillid; Toosid, Prillipaelad ja -ketid; Prillide ja päikeseprillide raamid ning klaasid; Telefonide, arvutite ja elektroonikaseadmete ümbrised, katted ja kandekotid; Eelnimetatud kaupade osad ja tarvikud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Optikon tuotteet; Aurinkolasit; Kotelot, Silmälasinarut ja -ketjut; Silmälasien ja aurinkolasien kehykset ja linssit; Puhelinten, tietokoneiden ja elektroniikkalaitteiden kotelot, suojukset ja kantolaukut; Näiden tuotteiden osat ja komponentit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Articles de lunetterie; Lunettes de soleil; Étuis, Cordons et chaînettes pour lunettes; Montures et verres de lunettes et de lunettes solaires; Étuis, housses et sacs de transport pour téléphones, ordinateurs et dispositifs électroniques; Parties et composants de ces produits.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Optički proizvodi; Sunčane naočale; Kutije, Uzice i lanci za naočale; Okviri za dioptrijske i sunčane naočale te leće; Kutije, prekrivači i torbe za telefone, računala i elektroničke uređaje; Dijelovi i oprema za prethodno navedene proizvode.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Optikai cikkek; Napszemüvegek; Tokok, tartók, Zsinórok és láncok szemüvegekhez; Keretek és lencsék szemüvegekhez és napszemüvegekhez; Telefonok, számítógépek és elektronikus eszközök tokjai, fedelei és hordtáskái; A fent említett áruk alkatrészei és szerelvényei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Occhiali; Occhiali da sole; Astucci, Cordoncini e catenelle per articoli ottici; Montature e lenti per occhiali e occhiali da sole; Custodie, astucci e borse per trasporto di telefoni, computer e dispositivi elettronici; Parti e accessori per i prodotti summenzionati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Optikos prekės; Saulės akiniai; Dėžės, Akinių virvelės ir grandinėlės; Rėmeliai ir lęšiai akiniams bei akiniams nuo saulės; Telefonų, kompiuterių ir elektroninių prietaisų dėklai, dangteliai ir krepšiai; Anksčiau nurodytų prekių dalys ir priedai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Optikas preces; Saulesbrilles; Ietvari, Briļļu auklas un ķēdītes; Briļļu un saulesbriļļu rāmji un lēcas; Telefonu, datoru un elektronisko ierīču ietvari, pārvalki un somas; Iepriekš minēto preču daļas un piederumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Prodotti tat-tobba li jieħdu ħsieb il-kura tal-għajnejn; Nuċċalijiet tax-xemx; Kaxex, Kordi u ktajjen għan-nuċċalijiet; Frejmijiet u lentijiet għan-nuċċalijiet tal-vista u għan-nuċċalijiet tax-xemx; Kaxxetti, kavers u basktijiet tal-ġarr għat-telefowns, kompjuters u tagħmir elettroniku; Partijiet u fittings għall-oġġetti msemmija qabel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Eyewear; Zonnebrillen; Etuis, Koordjes en kettinkjes voor brillen; Monturen en lenzen voor brillen en zonnebrillen; Etuis, hoezen en draagtassen voor telefoons, computers en elektronische apparaten; Onderdelen en accessoires voor de voornoemde producten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Artykuły optyczne; Okulary przeciwsłoneczne; Futerały, Sznurki i łańcuszki do okularów; Oprawki i soczewki do okularów i okularów przeciwsłonecznych; Futerały, etui i torebki do przenoszenia telefonów, komputerów i urządzeń elektronicznych; Części i akcesoria do wyżej wymienionych towarów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Artigos de ótica; Óculos de sol; Estojos, Cordões e correntes para artigos de ótica; Armações e lentes para óculos e óculos de sol; Estojos, capas e malas de transporte para telefones, computadores e dispositivos eletrónicos; Peças e componentes para os artigos atrás referidos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Produse de optică; Ochelari de soare; Carcase, huse, Şnururi şi lănţişoare pentru ochelari; Rame si lentile pentru ochelari si ochelari de soare; Cutii, huse și genți de transport pentru telefoane, calculatoare și dispozitive electronice; Piese şi accesorii pentru produsele menţionate anterior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Výrobky očnej optiky; Slnečné okuliare; Puzdrá, Šnúrky a retiazky pre okuliare; Rámy a šošovky pre okuliare a slnečné okuliare; Puzdrá, kryty a vrecká na telefóny, počítače a elektronické prístroje; Časti a súčasti pre všetky vyššie uvedené výrobky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Proizvodi za optiko; Sončna očala; Etuiji, Vrvice in verižice za očala; Okviri in leče za korekcijska očala in sončna očala; Torbice, etuiji in nosilne torbe za telefone, računalnike in elektronske aparate; Deli in komponente za omenjeno blago.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Optikervaror; Solglasögon; Fodral, Snoddar och glasögonkedjor; Bågar och linser till pincenéer, glasögon och solglasögon; Höljen, fodral och bärväskor för telefoner, datorer, och elektroniska anordningar; Delar och komponenter till nämnda varor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>14</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Бижутерия; Калъфи за бижута и бижутерия,; Дребни бижутерийни украшения; Копчета за ръкавели; Декоративни игли; Игли за вратовръзки; Брошки [бижутерия]; Значки; Медальони с капачета; Медали, ордени; Халки за ключове; Аксесоари за мобилни телефони; Часовници и хронометрични уреди; Часовници, Часовници, Каишки за ръчни часовници, Каишки за ръчни часовници, Гривни за часовници; Презентационни кутии за ръчни и стенни часовници; Части и принадлежности за всички горепосочени стоки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Šperky; Kazety na klenoty a šperky; Přívěsky [šperky]; Manžetové knoflíčky; Dekorativní brože; Špendlíky do kravat; Brože [šperky]; Odznaky; Medailony; Medaile; Kroužky na klíče; Příslušenství mobilních telefonů; Hodinářské potřeby a chronometrické přístroje; Hodinky, Hodinky, Řemínky na náramkové hodinky, Řemínky na náramkové hodinky, Hodinkové náramky; Pouzdra na náramkové hodinky a hodiny; Části a vybavení veškerého výše uvedeného zboží.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Juvelerarbejder; Etuier til juvelerarbejder, smykker og juveler; Smykkevedhæng; Manchetknapper; Dekorative emblemer; Slipsnåle; Brocher [smykker]; Emblemer; Medaljoner; Medaljer; Nøgleringe; Tilbehør til mobiltelefoner; Ure og kronometriske instrumenter; Ure [armbåndsure], Ure, Remme til armbåndsure, Remme til armbåndsure, Urlænker; Etuier til armbåndsure og ure; Dele og tilbehør til alle førnævnte varer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Juwelierwaren, Schmuckwaren; Etuis für Schmuckwaren und Juwelen; Schmuckanhänger; Manschettenknöpfe; Dekorative Anstecknadeln; Krawattennadeln; Broschen [Schmuck]; Abzeichen; Medaillons; Medaillen; Schlüsselringe; Zubehör für Mobiltelefone; Uhren und Zeitmessinstrumente; Taschen-/Armbanduhren, Uhren, Bänder für Armbanduhren, Bänder für Armbanduhren, Uhrarmbänder [Schmuckwaren]; Etuis für Armbanduhren und Uhren; Teile und Zusatzteile für alle vorstehend genannten Waren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κοσμήματα· Θήκες για κοσμήματα· Κρεμαστά κοσμήματα· Μανικετόκουμπα· Διακοσμητικές καρφίτσες· Καρφίτσες για γραβάτες· Καρφίτσες [κοσμήματα]· Διακριτικά σήματα· Μενταγιόν· Μετάλλια· Μπρελόκ· Εξαρτήματα κινητών τηλεφώνων· Είδη ωρολογοποιίας και άλλα χρονομετρικά όργανα· Ωρολόγια, Ρολόγια τοίχου ή επιτραπέζια, Λουράκια για ωρολόγια χειρός, Λουράκια για ωρολόγια χειρός, Μπρασελέ για ρολόγια χειρός· Θήκες για ρολόγια τοίχου ή επιτραπέζια και για ρολόγια χειρός· Μέρη και εξαρτήματα για όλα τα προαναφερθέντα είδη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Jewellery; cases for jewellery and jewels; charms; cufflinks; decorative pins; tie pins; brooches; badges; medallions; medals; keyrings; mobile phone accessories; horological and chronometric instruments; watches, clocks, watch bands, watch straps, watch bracelets; cases for watches and clocks; parts and fittings for all the aforesaid goods.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Artículos de joyería; Estuches para artículos de joyería y joyas; Dijes [joyería]; Gemelos; Alfileres decorativos; Alfileres de corbata; Broches [joyería]; Insignias; Medallones; Medallas; Anillas para llaveros; Accesorios utilizados para teléfonos móviles; Artículos de relojería e instrumentos cronométricos; Relojes de uso personal, Relojes de pared, Correa para reloj de pulsera, Correa para reloj de pulsera, Pulseras de relojes; Estuches para relojes de pulsera y para relojes; Piezas y accesorios para todos los productos citados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Juveeltooted; Juveeli- ja ehtekarbid; Ripatsid [juveeltooted]; Mansetinööbid; Ehisnõelad; Lipsunõelad; Prossid [juveeltooted]; Märgid; Medaljonid; Medalid; Ripatsitega võtmerõngad; Mobiiltelefonimanused; Hortoloogilised ja kronomeetrilised instrumendid (kellad ja kronomeetrid); Käe-, taskukellad, Kellad, Kellarihmad, Kellarihmad, Käevõrud kellade jaoks; Kellakarbid; Kõigi eelnimetatud kaupade osad ja tarvikud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Korut; Korurasiat; Koruriipukset; Kalvosinnapit; Koristerintaneulat; Solmionpidikkeet; Rintaneulat [korut]; Rintamerkit; Medaljongit; Mitalit; Avainrenkaat; Matkapuhelinvarusteet; Kellot ja ajanmittauslaitteet; Kellot, Kellot, Rannekellojen hihnat, Rannekellojen hihnat, Rannekkeet kelloille; Kotelot rannekelloille ja kelloille; Osat ja tarvikkeet kaikille edellä mainituille tavaroille.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Joaillerie; Étuis à bijoux; Breloques pour la bijouterie; Boutons de manchettes; Épinglettes ornementales; Épingles de cravates; Broches [bijouterie]; Badges; Médaillons; Médailles; Anneaux de porte-clés; Accessoires pour téléphones mobiles; Horlogerie et instruments chronométriques; Montres, Horloges, Bracelets de montres, Bracelets de montres, Bracelets pour montres; Étuis pour montres et horloges; Pièces et parties constitutives pour tous les produits précités.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Nakit; Kutije za nakit i drago kamenje; Privjesci za ogrlice i narukvice [nakit]; Puceta za orukvice; Šila; Igle za kravate; Broševi [nakit]; Bedževi za nošenje; Medaljoni; Medalje; Privjesci za ključeve; Dodatci za mobilne telefone; Urarski proizvodi i kronometarski instrumenti; Satovi, Zidni satovi, Remeni za ručne satove, Remeni za ručne satove, Narukvice za satove; Kućišta za džepne i zidne satove; Dijelovi i oprema za sve prethodno navedene proizvode.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ékszerek; Dobozok ékszerekhez és; Függők ékszerekhez; Mandzsettagombok; Dekoratív tűk; Nyakkendőtűk; Brossok [ékszerek]; Jelvények; Nagy érmék, medalionok; Medálok; Kulcstartó gyűrűk; Mobiltelefonok tartozékai; Órák és más időmérő eszközök; Órák, Órák, Szíjak órákhoz, Szíjak órákhoz, Karkötők, szíjak órákhoz; Óratokok, óraházak; A fent említett összes áru alkatrészei és szerelvényei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Oreficeria; Astucci per articoli di gioielleria e gioielli; Ciondoli per la gioielleria; Bottoni per polsini; Spillette ornamentali; Spille da cravatte; Spillette [gioielleria]; Distintivi; Medaglioni; Medaglie; Portachiavi; Cellulari e accessori; Orologeria e strumenti cronometrici; Orologi [da polso e da tasca], Orologi, Braccialetti per orologi [cinturini], Braccialetti per orologi [cinturini], Braccialetti per orologi; Custodie per orologi; Parti e accessori per tutti i prodotti summenzionati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Dėklai juvelyriniams dirbiniams ir brangakmeniams; Juvelyriniai karuliai; Rankogalių sąsagos; Dekoratyviniai smeigtukai; Kaklaraiščių smeigtukai; Sagės [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Ženkleliai; Medalionai; Medaliai; Raktų žiedai; Mobiliųjų telefonų priedai; Laikrodžiai ir laikmačiai; Laikrodžiai [kišeniniai, rankiniai], Laikrodžiai [kišeniniai, rankiniai], Laikrodžių apyrankės, Laikrodžių apyrankės, Rankinių laikrodžių apyrankės; Laikrodžių dėklai; Visų anksčiau nurodytų prekių dalys ir priedai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Juvelierizstrādājumi; Dārglietu un dārgakmeņu lādītes; Juvelierizstrādājumu piekariņi; Aproču pogas; Dekoratīvas piespraudes; Kaklasaišu adatas; Brošas [juvelierizstrādājumi]; Nozīmītes; Medaljoni; Medaļas; Atslēgu riņķi; Mobilo telefonu aksesuāri; Pulksteņi un hronometriskie instrumenti; Rokas un kabatas pulksteņi, Pulksteņi, Rokas pulksteņu siksniņas, Rokas pulksteņu siksniņas, Pulksteņu aproces; Rokas pulksteņu un pulksteņu futrāļi; Visu iepriekš minēto preču daļas un piederumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ġojjelli; Kaxxetti għall-gojjelli; Pendenti tal-ġojjellerija; Buttuni għall-pulzieri ta' qmis (ta' metall prezzjuż); Labar ornamentali; Labar tal-ingravata; Labar ornamentali [ġojjellerija]; Beġġ; Midaljuni; Medalji; Ħoloq taċ-ċwievet; Aċċessorji tat-telefon ċellulari; Strumenti li juru l-ħin u kronometriċi; Arloġġi tal-polz, Arloġġi, Ċineg tal-arloġġ tal-idejn, Ċineg tal-arloġġ tal-idejn, Brazzuletti għall-arloġġi tal-idejn; Kaxxetti għall-arloġġi tal-idejn u għall-arloġġi; Partijiet u tagħmir għall-affarijiet kollha imsemmija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Juwelen; Kistjes voor sieraden en juwelen; Hangertjes [b.v. aan horlogekettingen]; Manchetknopen; Decoratieve spelden; Dasspelden; Broches [juwelierswaren]; Badges; Medaillons; Medailles; Sleutelhangers; Accessoires voor mobiele telefoons; Uurwerken en tijdmeetinstrumenten; Horloges, Klokken, Horlogebanden, Horlogebanden, Horlogebandjes; Etuis voor horloges en klokken; Onderdelen en accessoires voor alle voornoemde goederen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Biżuteria i wyroby jubilerskie; Szkatułki na biżuterię i klejnoty; Zawieszki [biżuteria]; Spinki do mankietów; Igły dekoracyjne; Szpilki do krawatów; Broszki [biżuteria]; Odznaki; Medaliony; Medale; Kółka do kluczy; Akcesoria do telefonów komórkowych; Przyrządy zegarmistrzowskie i chronometryczne; Zegarki, Zegarki, Paski do zegarków, Paski do zegarków, Bransolety do zegarków; Etui do zegarków i zegarów; Części i akcesoria do wszystkich wyżej wymienionych towarów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Jóias; Estojos para artigos de joalharia e joias; Amuletos em jóias; Botões de punho; Alfinetes decorativos; Alfinetes de gravatas; Broches [joalharia]; Emblemas; Medalhões; Medalhas; Porta-chaves; Acessórios para telemóveis; Relojoaria e instrumentos cronométricos; Relógios de pulso, Relógios, Correias para relógios, Correias para relógios, Pulseiras para relógios; Estojos para relógios e relógios de pulso; Peças e acessórios para todos os produtos atrás citados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Bijuterii; Casete pentru bijuterii şi podoabe; Pandantive; Butoni de manşetă; Insigne decorative; Cravată (Ace de -); Broşe [bijuterii]; Ecusoane; Medalioane; Medalii; Inele pentru chei; Accesorii pentru telefonul mobil; Ceasornicărie şi instrumente pentru măsurarea timpului; Brăţară (Ceasuri cu -), Brăţară (Ceasuri cu -), Brăţări de ceas, Brăţări de ceas, Brăţări pentru ceasuri de mână; Cutii pentru ceasuri de mână şi ceasornice; Piese şi accesorii pentru toate produsele menţionate anterior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Šperky; Puzdrá pre šperky; Prívesky (klenotnícke výrobky); Manžetové gombíky; Dekoratívne ihlice; Ihlice na kravaty; Brošne (klenotnícke výrobky); Odznaky; Medailóny; Medaily; Krúžky na kľúče; Príslušenstvo pre mobilné telefóny; Hodinárske výrobky a chronometre; Hodinky, Hodinky, Remienky na hodinky, Remienky na hodinky, Náramky na hodinky; Puzdrá na hodinky a hodiny; Časti a súčasti pre všetky vyššie uvedené výrobky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Nakit; Skrinjice za nakit in dragocenosti; Obeski [nakit]; Manšetni gumbi; Okrasne igle; Kravatne igle; Broške [nakit]; Značke; Medaljoni; Medalje; Obročki za ključe; Dodatki za mobilne telefone; Ure in kronometrski instrumenti; Ročne ure, Ročne ure, Paščki za ure, Paščki za ure, Zapestnice za ročne ure; Ohišja za ročne ure in ure na splošno; Deli in komponente za vse omenjeno blago.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Juvelerarvaror; Skrin för smycken och juveler; Berlocker [smycken]; Manschettknappar; Dekorativa broscher; Slipsnålar; Broscher [smycken]; Märken; Medaljonger; Medaljer; Nyckelringar; Mobiltelefontillbehör; Ur och tidmätningsinstrument; Ur, Ur, Remmar för armbandsur, Remmar för armbandsur, Armband för klockor; Etuier för ur och klockor; Delar och komponenter till alla nämnda varor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>18</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Багажи; Bсекидневни чанти; Ръчни дамски чанти; Раници; Раници; Плажни чанти; Ученически чанти; Багажи; Куфарчета за документи; Багажи; Калъфи за пренасяне; Портфейли и портмонета; Чадъри, слънчобрани; Дамски чантички за тоалетни принадлежности [неокомплектовани]; Калъфи за кредитни карти; Визитници; Кожени колани; Части и принадлежности за всички горепосочени стоки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zavazadla; Tašky; Kabelky; Batohy; Batohy; Plážové tašky; Školní tašky; Zavazadla; Aktovky; Cestovní tašky; Přepravní kufříky; Peněženky a náprsní tašky; Deštníky, slunečníky; Toaletní kufříky, nevybavené; Pouzdra na kreditní karty; Pouzdra na karty; Kožené pásky; Části a vybavení veškerého výše uvedeného zboží.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Bagage; Tasker; Håndtasker; Rygsække; Rygsække; Strandtasker; Skoletasker; Rejsekister [store kufferter]; Dokumentmapper; Rejsetasker; Transporttasker; Tegnebøger og punge; Paraplyer, parasoller; Toilettasker, ikke indbyggede; Kreditkortholdere; Postkort; Læderbælter; Dele og tilbehør til alle førnævnte varer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gepäck; Freizeittaschen; Handtaschen; Rucksäcke; Rucksäcke; Badetaschen; Schultaschen; Reisekoffer; Aktentaschen, Dokumentenmappen; Reisetaschen; Tragebehältnisse; Brieftaschen und Portemonnaies; Regenschirme, Sonnenschirme; Kosmetikkoffer; Kreditkartenetuis; Kartenhalter; Ledergürtel; Teile und Zusatzteile für alle vorstehend genannten Waren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αποσκευές· Τσάντες για ανεπίσημο ντύσιμο· Τσάντες· Σακίδια πλάτης· Σακίδια πλάτης· Παραλία (τσάντες -ας)· Σχολικές σάκες· Βαλίτσες· Χαρτοφύλακες· Βαλίτσες· Θήκες και τσάντες μεταφοράς· Πορτοφόλια και πορτοφόλια για κέρματα· Ομπρέλες, αλεξήλια· Βαλιτσάκια για είδη καλλωπισμού, χωρίς χωρίσματα· Θήκες για πιστωτικές κάρτες· Θήκες για κάρτες· Δερμάτινες ζώνες· Μέρη και εξαρτήματα για όλα τα προαναφερθέντα είδη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Luggage; bags; handbags; rucksacks; backpacks; beach bags; satchels; travelling trunks; briefcases; holdalls; carrying cases; wallets and purses; umbrellas, parasols; vanity cases (not fitted); credit card holders; card holders; leather belts; parts and fittings for the aforesaid goods.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Equipajes; Bolsas; Bolsos de mano; Mochilas; Mochilas; Bolsas de playa; Carteras escolares; Baúles de viaje; Portadocumentos; Bolsas de viaje; Maletines; Billeteras y monederos; Paraguas, sombrillas; Estuches para artículos de tocador; Fundas para tarjetas de crédito; Tarjeteros; Correas de cuero; Piezas y accesorios para todos los productos citados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reisikirstud; Vaba aja kotid; Käekotid; Seljakotid; Seljakotid; Rannakotid; Koolikotid; Reisikirstud; Portfellid; Reisikotid; Kandekotid; Rahakotid ja rahataskud; Vihmavarjud, päikesevarjud; Lahtriteta kosmeetikakotid, -karbid; Krediitkaardihoidjad; Kaardihoidikud; Nahkrihmad; Kõigi eelnimetatud kaupade osad ja tarvikud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Matkatavaralaukut; Vapaa-ajanlaukut; Laukut (Käsi -); Reput; Reput; Rantalaukut; Koululaisten olkalaukut; Matka-arkut; Salkut; Matkakassit; Kantolaukut; Lompakot ja kukkarot; Sateenvarjot, päivänvarjot; Meikkilaukut [varustamattomina]; Luottokorttikotelot; Korttitelineet; Nahkavyöt; Osat ja tarvikkeet kaikille edellä mainituille tavaroille.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bagages; Sacs de tous les jours; Sacs à main; Sacs à dos; Sacs à dos; Sacs de plage; Cartables; Coffres de voyage; Porte-documents; Fourre-tout; Valises de transport; Portefeuilles et porte-monnaie; Parapluies, parasols; Coffrets destinés à contenir des articles de toilette dits "vanity cases"; Étuis pour cartes de crédit (portefeuilles); Porte cartes; Ceintures en cuir; Pièces et parties constitutives pour tous les produits précités.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Prtljaga; Torbe; Ručne torbe; Ruksaci; Ruksaci; Torbe za plažu; Torbe na rame; Putni sanduci; Aktovke; Torbe za putovanja; Torbe za nošenje; Lisnice i ženske torbice; Kišobrani, suncobrani; Prazne kozmetičke torbice; Novčanici za kreditne kartice; Etuiji za kartice; Kožno remenje; Dijelovi i oprema za sve prethodno navedene proizvode.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Poggyász; Hétköznapi, utcai táskák; Kézitáskák; Hátizsákok, hátitáskák; Hátizsákok, hátitáskák; Strandtáskák; Satchel táskák; Poggyász; Irattáskák, aktatáskák; Poggyász; Hordozótokok, táskák; Pénztárcák és erszények; Esernyők, napernyők; Piperetáskák üresen; Bankkártyatartók; Kártyatartók; Bőrövek; A fent említett összes áru alkatrészei és szerelvényei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Bagagli; Borse casual; Borsette; Zaini; Zaini; Borse da spiaggia; Cartelle scolastiche; Bauli da viaggio; Cartelle, buste [articoli di pelle]; Sacchi da viaggio; Custodie per il trasporto; Portafogli e borsellini; Ombrelli, parasole; Bauletti destinati a contenere articoli da toilette detti vanity cases; Custodie per carte di credito; Portatessere; Cinture in cuoio; Parti e accessori per tutti i prodotti summenzionati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Bagažas; Kasdieniai krepšiai; Rankinukai; Kuprinės; Kuprinės; Paplūdimio krepšeliai; Mokyklinės kuprinės; Bagažas; Portfeliai; Bagažas; Nešiojamieji lagaminėliai; Piniginės ir sulenkiamos piniginės; Skėčiai, saulės skėčiai; Kišeninės tualetinės reikmeninės [tuščios]; Kreditinių kortelių laikikliai; Kortelių dėklai; Odiniai diržai; Visų anksčiau nurodytų prekių dalys ir priedai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Bagāžas somas un čemodāni; Somas; Rokassomas; Mugursomas; Mugursomas; Pludmales somas; Skolēnu somas; Kabatas portfeļi; Plakani dokumentu portfeļi; Kabatas portfeļi; Pārnēsāšanas somas; Naudasmaki un kabatas portfeļi; Lietussargi un saulessargi; Tualetes maciņi, bez tualetes piederumiem; Kredītkaršu maki; Karšu maciņi; Ādas jostas; Visu iepriekš minēto preču daļas un piederumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Valiġġi; Basktijiet ta' kuljum; Basktijiet tal-id; Barżakki ta' fuq id-dahar; Barżakki ta' fuq id-dahar; Basktijiet tal-baħar; Basktijiet tal-iskola [satchels]; Bagalji għall-ivvjaġġar; Kartieri tad-dokumenti; Valiġġi; Kaxxi tal-ġarr; Portmoni u portafolli; Umbrelel, parasols; Kaxxetti tal-kożmetiċi, mhux mgħammra; Portafolli għall-karti tal-kreditu; Kartieri tal-kards; Ċinturini tal-ġilda; Partijiet u tagħmir għall-affarijiet kollha imsemmija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Bagage; Vrijetijdstassen; Handtassen; Rugzakken; Rugzakken; Strandtassen; Schooltassen; Reiskoffers; Aktentassen; Reistassen; Draagkoffers; Portefeuilles en portemonnees; Paraplu's, parasols; Beauty-cases [leeg]; Houders voor credit cards; Kaartenstandaards; Ceintuurs van leder; Onderdelen en accessoires voor alle voornoemde goederen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Bagaż; Torby; Torebki; Plecaki; Plecaki; Torby plażowe; Torby szkolne [z paskiem na ramię]; Bagaż; Aktówki; Bagaż; Torby przenośne; Portfele i portmonetki; Parasolki, parasole przeciwsłoneczne; Kosmetyczki bez wyposażenia; Portfele na karty kredytowe; Etui na karty; Paski skórzane; Części i akcesoria do wszystkich wyżej wymienionych towarów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Malas para uso em viagem; Sacos de lazer; Sacos de mão; Mochilas [com duas alças]; Mochilas [com duas alças]; Sacos de praia; Pastas para estudantes; Cofres de viagem; Pastas [maletas]; Sacos de viagem; Estojos de transporte; Carteiras e porta-moedas; Chapéus de chuva, chapéus de sol; Estojos para maquilhagem, sem conteúdo; Carteiras para cartões de crédito; Porta-cartões; Cintos de couro; Peças e acessórios para todos os produtos atrás citados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole de voiaj; Genţi; Poşete; Rucsacuri; Rucsacuri; Genţi de plajă; Serviete pentru şcolari; Genţi; Documente (Mape pentru -); Genţi; Cutii de transport; Portofele şi portmonee; Umbrele de ploaie, umbrele de soare; Casete pentru accesorii de frumuseţe; Suporturi pentru cărţi de credit; Suport de carduri; Curele din piele; Piese şi accesorii pentru toate produsele menţionate anterior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Batožina; Tašky; Kabelky; Ruksaky; Ruksaky; Plážové tašky; Školské tašky (aktovky); Cestovné kufre; Aktovky (kožená galantéria); Batožina; Transportné puzdrá; Peňaženky a náprsné tašky; Dáždniky a slnečníky; Kufrík na toaletné potreby (prázdny); Puzdrá na kreditné karty; Puzdrá na vizitky; Kožené opasky; Časti a súčasti pre všetky vyššie uvedené výrobky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Prtljaga; Torbe; Ročne torbice; Nahrbtniki; Nahrbtniki; Torbe za plažo; Šolske torbe z jermenom; Prtljaga; Aktovke; Prtljaga; Nosilne torbe; Listnice in denarnice; Dežniki, sončniki; Kozmetični kovčki (prazni); Etuiji za kreditne kartice; Ovitki za kartice; Usnjeni pasovi; Deli in komponente za vse omenjeno blago.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Resekoffertar; Fritidsväskor; Handväskor; Ryggsäckar; Ryggsäckar; Strandväskor; Skolväskor med axelremmar; Bagage; Portföljer; Bagage; Transportväskor; Plånböcker och portmonnäer; Paraplyer, parasoller; Beautyboxar (oinredda); Kreditkortsfodral; Korthållare; Livremmar i läder; Delar och komponenter till alla nämnda varor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Облекло; Обувки; Шапки и други принадлежности за глава; Колани за кръста.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Oděvy; Obuv; Pokrývky hlavy; Pásky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beklædningsgenstande; Fodtøj; Hovedbeklædning; Livremme.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bekleidungsstücke; Schuhwaren; Kopfbedeckungen; Gürtel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ενδύματα· Υποδήματα· Είδη πιλοποιίας· Ζώνες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Clothing; footwear; headgear; belts.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Prendas de vestir; Calzado; Artículos de sombrerería; Cinturones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rõivad; Jalatsid; Peakatted; Rihmad, vööd [rõivaste juurde].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatteet; Jalkineet; Päähineet; Vyötärönauhat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vêtements; Chaussures; Chapellerie; Ceintures.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Odjeća; Obuća; Pokrivala za glavu; Pojasevi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ruházati cikkek; Lábbelik; Kalapáruk; Derékszíjak, övek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Abbigliamento; Calzature; Cappelleria; Cinture.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Drabužiai, apranga; Apavas; Galvos apdangalai; Liemens diržai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apģērbi; Kurpes; Galvassegas; Vidukļa jostas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ilbies; Xedd is-saqajn; Xedd ir-ras; Ċinturini ta' mal-qadd.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kleding; Schoeisel; Hoofddeksels; Ceintuurs, riemen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odzież; Obuwie; Nakrycia głowy; Paski.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vestuário; Calçado; Chapelaria; Cintos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole de îmbrăcăminte; Articole de încălţăminte; Articole pentru acoperirea capului; Curele (accesorii vestimentare).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Odevy, oblečenie; Obuv; Pokrývky hlavy; Opasky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oblačila; Obutev; Pokrivala; Pasovi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kläder; Fotbeklädnader; Huvudbonader; Midjebälten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за търговия на дребно и онлайн услуги за търговия на дребно, свързани с продажбата на козметика, парфюмерия, етерични масла, препарати за грижа за кожата, продукти за грижа и поддръжка на косата, сапун, продукти за вана и душ, препарати за грижа срещу слънцето, нелечебни тоалетни препарати, очила, слънчеви очила, калъфи и аксесоари за очила, рамки и лещи за очила и слънчеви очила, калъфи и капаци за телефони, калъфи и капаци за компютри и електронни устройства, бижута, калъфи за бижута и скъпоценни камъни, талисмани, копчета за ръкавели; Услуги за търговия на дребно и онлайн услуги за търговия на дребно, свързани с продажбата на декоративни игли, игли за вратовръзки, брошки, значки, медалиони, медали, ключодържатели, аксесоари за мобилни телефони, хронометрични и инструменти за отчитане на времето, часовници, ръчни часовници, каишки за ръчни часовници, верижки за ръчни часовници, гривни за ръчни часовници, калъфи за часовници и ръчни часовници, багажни принадлежности, всекидневни чанти, ръчни дамски чанти, раници, раници, чанти за плаж, ученицески чанти за носене на гръб, пътнически сандъци, куфарчета, големи пазарски чанти, чанти, портфейли и портмонета, чадъри, слънчобрани, тоалетни несесери (не оборудвани); Услуги за търговия на дребно и онлайн услуги за търговия на дребно, свързани с продажбата на държатели за кредитни карти, поставки за карти, кожени колани, дрехи, обувки, шапки, колани; Рекламни услуги, свързани със собственост; Услуги по програми за лоялност, стимули и бонуси; Информационни и съветнически услуги, свързани с горепосоченото.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Maloobchodní služby a on-line maloobchodní služby spojené s prodejem výrobků jako kosmetika, parfémy, éterické oleje, přípravky pro péči o pleť, přípravky pro péči o vlasy, mýdla, koupelové a sprchové přípravky, ochranné opalovací přípravky, neléčivé toaletní přípravky, výrobky oční optiky, sluneční brýle, pouzdra a příslušenství k výrobkům oční optiky, rámy a čočky pro brýle a sluneční brýle, pouzdra a kryty na telefony, pouzdra a kryty na počítače a elektronická zařízení, klenoty, kazety na klenoty a drahokamy, ozdoby na řetízky hodinek, manžetové knoflíky; Maloobchodní služby a on-line maloobchodní služby spojené s prodejem výrobků jako ozdobné špendlíky, špendlíky do kravat, brože, odznaky, medailonky, medaile, kroužky na klíče, příslušenství mobilních telefonů, hodinářské potřeby a chronometrické přístroje, hodinky, hodiny, řemínky na náramkové hodinky, řemínky na náramkové hodinky, náramky k náramkovým hodinkám, pouzdra na hodinky a hodiny, zavazadla, tašky, kabelky, batohy, batohy, plážové tašky, brašny, cestovní kufry, aktovky, objemné kabely, přepravní pouzdra, náprsní tašky a peněženky, deštníky, slunečníky, toaletní kufříky (nevybavené); Maloobchodní služby a on-line maloobchodní služby spojené s prodejem výrobků jako obaly na kreditní karty, obaly na karty, kožené opasky, oděvy, obuv, pokrývky hlavy, opasky; Reklamní a propagační služby vztahující se k tomuto zboží; Věrnostní, pobídkové a bonusové programy; Informační a poradenské služby ve výše uvedených oblastech.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Detailhandel og onlinedetailhandel i forbindelse med salg af kosmetiske præparater, parfumer, æteriske olier, præparater til hudpleje, præparater til hårpleje, sæbe, præparater til bad og brus, præparater til hudpleje i forbindelse med solbadning, ikke-medicinske toiletpræparater, briller og solbriller, etuier og tilbehør til briller, stel og glas til briller og solbriller, etuier og overtræk til telefoner, etuier og overtræk til computere og elektroniske apparater, juvelerarbejder, etuier til juvelerarbejder og juveler, smykkevedhæng, manchetknapper; Detailhandel og onlinedetailhandel i forbindelse med salg af pyntenåle, slipsnåle, brocher, emblemer, medaljoner, medaljer, nøgleringe, tilbehør til mobiltelefoner, ure og kronometriske instrumenter, armbåndsure, ure, urremme, urlænker, æsker til armbåndsure og ure, bagageartikler, tasker, håndtasker, rygtasker, rygsække, strandtasker, skråtasker, rejsekister, dokumentmapper, vadsække, transporttasker, tegnebøger og punge, paraplyer, parasoller, beautybokse (uden indhold); Detailhandel og onlinedetailhandel i forbindelse med salg af holdere til kreditkort, kortholdere,læderbælter, beklædningsgenstande, fodtøj og hovedbeklædning, bælter; Reklamevirksomhed og salgsfremme i forbindelse med disse varer; Loyaltitets-, incitaments- og bonusprogrammer; Informations- og rådgivningsvirksomhed vedrørende ovennævnte tjenester.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Online-Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Kosmetika, Parfüms, ätherische Öle, Hautpflegemittel, Haarpflegemittel, Seifen, Bade- und Duschpräparate, Sonnenschutzmittel, nicht medizinische Körperpflegemittel, Brillen und Kontaktlinsen, Sonnenbrillen, Etuis und Zubehör für Brillen und Kontaktlinsen, Brillen- und Sonnenbrillengestelle und -gläser, Etuis und Hüllen für Telefone, Etuis und Hüllen für Computer und elektronische Geräte, Juwelierwaren, Schmuckwaren, Schmuckkästen, Schmuckanhänger, Manschettenknöpfe; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Online-Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf dekorative Anstecknadeln, Krawattennadeln, Broschen, Abzeichen, Medaillons, Medaillen, Schlüsselringe, Zubehör für Mobiltelefone, Uhren und Zeitmessinstrumente, Taschen-/Armbanduhren, Uhren, Uhrenarmbänder, Uhrenarmbänder, Uhrarmbänder [Schmuckwaren], Etuis für Armbanduhren und Uhren, Gepäck, Taschen, Handtaschen, Rucksäcke, Reiserucksäcke, Badetaschen, Schultaschen, Reisekoffer, Aktentaschen, Reisetaschen, Tragebehältnisse, Brieftaschen und Geldbörsen, Regenschirme, Sonnenschirme, Kosmetikkoffer (ohne Inhalt); Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Online-Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Kreditkartenetuis, Kartentaschen, Ledergürtel, Bekleidungsstücke, Schuhwaren, Kopfbedeckungen, Gürtel; Werbung und Verkaufsförderung in Bezug auf die vorstehend genannten Waren; Dienstleistungen in Bezug auf Kundenbindungs-, Anreiz- und Bonusprogramme; Information und Beratung in Bezug auf das vorstehend Genannte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης και υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης επί γραμμής σε σχέση με καλλυντικά, αρώματα, αιθέρια έλαια, παρασκευάσματα περιποίησης του δέρματος, παρασκευάσματα περιποίησης των μαλλιών, σαπούνια, παρασκευάσματα για το μπάνιο και το ντους, αντηλιακά παρασκευάσματα, μη φαρμακευτικά παρασκευάσματα ατομικής περιποίησης, οπτικά είδη, γυαλιά ηλίου, θήκες και συμπληρώματα (αξεσουάρ) για οπτικά είδη, σκελετούς και φακούς γυαλιών όρασης και γυαλιών ηλίου, θήκες και καλύμματα για τηλέφωνα, θήκες και καλύμματα για ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές και ηλεκτρονικές διατάξεις, κοσμήματα, κοσμηματοθήκες, φυλαχτά, μανικετόκουμπα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης και υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης επί γραμμής σε σχέση με διακοσμητικές καρφίτσες πέτου, καρφίτσες για γραβάτες, γυναικείες καρφίτσες (πόρπες), κονκάρδες, μενταγιόν, μετάλλια, μπρελόκ για κλειδιά, εξαρτήματα κινητών τηλεφώνων, είδη ωρολογοποιίας και χρονομετρικά όργανα, ρολόγια χειρός, ρολόγια τοίχου ή επιτραπέζια, αλυσίδες για ρολόγια χειρός, λουράκια για ρολόγια χειρός, μπρασελέ για ρολόγια χειρός, θήκες για ρολόγια χειρός και ρολόγια τοίχου ή επιτραπέζια, αποσκευές, τσάντες, τσάντες χειρός, σακίδια, σακίδια πλάτης, τσάντες παραλίας, σάκες, κιβώτια ταξιδίου, χαρτοφύλακες-βαλιτσάκια, τσάντες για μεταφορά κάθε είδους, θήκες μεταφοράς, πορτοφόλια και γυναικεία τσαντάκια, ομπρέλες, αλεξήλια, τσαντάκια για καλλυντικά (χωρίς χωρίσματα)· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης και λιανικής πώλησης επί γραμμής σε σχέση με θήκες πιστωτικών καρτών, θήκες καρτών, δερμάτινες ζώνες, ενδύματα, υποδήματα, είδη πιλοποιίας, ζώνες· Διαφήμιση και προώθηση σε σχέση με τα είδη αυτά· Υπηρεσίες προγραμμάτων αφοσίωσης, κινήτρων και μπόνους· Υπηρεσίες πληροφόρησης και συμβουλευτικές σε σχέση με τα προαναφερθέντα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Retail services and online retail services connected with the sale of cosmetics, perfumes, essential oils, skin care preparations, hair care preparations, soaps, bath and shower preparations, sun care preparations, non-medicated toilet preparations, eyewear, sunglasses, cases and accessories for eyewear, spectacle and sunglasses frames and lenses, cases and covers for telephones, cases and covers for computers and electronic devices, jewellery, cases for jewellery and jewels, charms, cufflinks; Retail services and online retail services connected with the sale of decorative pins, tie pins, brooches, badges, medallions, medals, keyrings, mobile phone accessories, horological and chronometric instruments, watches, clocks, watch bands, watch straps, watch bracelets, cases for watches and clocks, luggage, bags, handbags, rucksacks, backpacks, beach bags, satchels, travelling trunks, briefcases, holdalls, carrying cases, wallets and purses, umbrellas, parasols, vanity cases (not fitted); Retail services and online retail services connected with the sale of credit card holders, card holders, leather belts, clothing, footwear, headgear, belts; advertising and promotion services relating to these goods; loyalty, incentive and bonus program services; information and advisory services relating to the aforesaid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de venta minorista y servicios de venta minorista en línea de cosméticos, perfumes, aceites esenciales, productos para el cuidado de la piel, productos para el cuidado del cabello, jabones, preparaciones para el baño y la ducha, productos de protección solar, productos de tocador no medicinales, artículos de óptica para la vista, gafas de sol, estuches y accesorios de artículos de óptica para la vista, monturas y lentes de gafas y gafas de sol, estuches y fundas para teléfonos, estuches y fundas para ordenadores y dispositivos electrónicos, joyería, joyeros y estuches para joyas, dijes [joyería], gemelos; Servicios de venta minorista y servicios de venta minorista en línea de alfileres decorativos [joyería], alfileres de corbata, prendedores, insignias, medallones, medallas, anillas para llaveros, accesorios para teléfonos móviles, artículos de relojería e instrumentos cronométricos, relojes de uso personal, relojes que no sean de uso personal, pulseras de reloj, estuches para relojes de pulsera y para relojes, equipajes, bolsas, bolsos de mano, mochilas, bolsas de playa, mochilas escolares, baúles de viaje, portafolios [artículos de marroquinería], bolsas de viaje, maletines, carteras y monederos, paraguas, estuches para artículos de tocador; Servicios de venta minorista y servicios de venta minorista en línea de fundas para tarjetas de crédito, tarjeteros, correas de cuero, prendas de vestir, calzado, artículos de sombrerería, cinturones; Servicios de publicidad y promoción relacionados con estos productos; Servicios relacionados con programas de bonos, incentivos y fidelización de clientes; Servicios de información y asesoramiento relacionados con lo anterior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Järgmiste kaupade jaemüügiteenused ja sidusjaemüügiteenused: kosmeetikavahendid, parfüümid, eeterlikud õlid, nahahooldusvahendid, juuksehooldusvahendid, seebid, vanni- ja dušipreparaadid, päikesekaitsevahendid, mittemeditsiinilised tualett-tarbed, prillid, päikeseprillid, prillitoosid ja -tarvikud, prillide ja päikeseprillide raamid ja läätsed, telefoniümbrised ja -katted, arvutite ja elektroonikaseadmete ümbrised ja katted, juveeltooted, ehtekarbid ja vääriskivide karbid, amuletid (ripatsid), mansetinööbid; Järgmiste kaupade jaemüügiteenused ja sidusjaemüügiteenused: ehisnõelad, lipsunõelad, prossid, märgid, medaljonid, medalid, võtmeripatsid, mobiiltelefonitarvikud, horoloogilised seadmed ja kronomeetrid, käe-, taskukellad, kellad, kellarihmad, kellavõrud, käekellade ja kellade korpused, reisitarbed, kotid, käekotid, seljakotid, rannakotid, ranitsad, reisikohvrid, mapid, reisikotid, kandekohvrid, rahakotid ja rahataskud, vihmavarjud, päikesevarjud, kosmeetikakotid (tühjad); Järgmiste kaupade jaemüügiteenused ja sidusjaemüügiteenused: krediitkaardihoidikud, kaardihoidikud, nahkvööd, rõivad, jalatsid, peakatted, vööd; Nende kaupadega seostuvad reklaami- ja müügiedendusteenused; Lojaalsusprogrammi-, ergutusprogrammi- ja boonusprogrammiteenused; Informatsiooni- ja nõustamisteenused seoses eelnevaga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Seuraavien myyntiin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut ja online-vähittäismyyntipalvelut: kosmetiikka, hajuvedet, eteeriset öljyt, ihonhoitovalmisteet, hiustenhoitovalmisteet, saippuat, kylpy- ja suihkuvalmisteet, hoitovalmisteet auringonottoon, lääkeaineettomat toilettivalmisteet, silmälasitarvikkeet, aurinkolasit, kotelot ja varusteet silmälasitarvikkeille, silmälasien ja aurinkolasien kehykset ja linssit, puhelinkotelot ja -suojukset, suojukset ja kotelot tietokoneille ja elektroniikkalaitteille, korut, kotelot koruille ja jalokiville, amuletit, kalvosinnapit; Seuraavien myyntiin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut ja online-vähittäismyyntipalvelut: koristeneulat, solmioneulat, rintakorut, merkit, medaljongit, mitalit, avainrenkaat, matkapuhelinvarusteet, kellot ja ajanmittauslaitteet, rannekellot, kellot, kellonrannekkeet, rannekellojen hihnat, rannekellojen rannekkeet, kotelot rannekelloille ja kelloille, matkalaukkutavarat, laukut, käsilaukut, reput, selkäreput, rantakassit, olkalaukut, matka-arkut, salkut, retkikassit, kantokotelot, lompakot ja kukkarot, sateenvarjot, päivänvarjot, meikkilaukut (sovittamattomat); Seuraavien myyntiin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut ja online-vähittäismyyntipalvelut: luottokorttikotelot, korttikotelot, nahkavyöt, vaatteet, jalkineet, päähineet, vyöt; Edellä mainittuihin tuotteisiin liittyvät mainonta- ja myynninedistämispalvelut; Kanta-asiakas-, kannuste- ja bonusohjelmapalvelut; Edellä mainittuun liittyvät tiedotus- ja neuvontapalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de vente au détail et services de vente au détail en ligne concernant la vente de cosmétiques, de parfums, d'huiles essentielles, de préparations pour le soin de la peau, de préparations et de traitements capillaires, de savons, de préparations pour le bain et la douche, de préparations de protection solaire, de produits de toilette non médicinaux, d'articles de lunetterie, de lunettes de soleil, d'étuis et d'accessoires pour articles de lunetterie, de montures et de verres pour lunettes et lunettes de soleil, d'étuis et de housses pour téléphones, d'étuis et de housses pour ordinateurs et dispositifs électroniques, d'articles de bijouterie, d'écrins pour articles de bijouterie et bijoux, de breloques pour la bijouterie, de boutons de manchettes; Services de vente au détail et services de vente au détail en ligne concernant la vente d'épingles décoratives, d'épingles de cravates, de broches, de badges, de médaillons, de médailles, de porte-clés, d'accessoires pour téléphones mobiles, d'instruments chronométriques et d'horlogerie, de montres, d'horloges, de bracelets de montres, de lanières de montres, de sangles de montres, d'étuis pour montres et horloges, de bagages, de sacs, de sacs à main, de havresacs, de sacs à dos, de sacs de plage, de serviettes d'écoliers, de coffres de voyage, de serviettes [maroquinerie], de sacs fourre-tout, de valises de transport, de portefeuilles et de portemonnaie, de parapluies, de parasols, de coffrets destinés à contenir des articles de toilette dits "vanity cases"; Services de vente au détail et services de vente au détail en ligne concernant la vente d'étuis pour cartes de crédit (portefeuilles), de porte-cartes, de ceintures en cuir, de vêtements, de chaussures, d'articles de chapellerie, de ceintures [vêtements]; Services publicitaires et promotionnels liés à ces produits; Services de programmes de fidélisation, de stimulation et de bonifications; Services d’information et de conseils dans tous les domaines précités.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Maloprodajne usluge i internetske maloprodajne usluge u vezi s prodajom kozmetike, parfema, esencijalnih ulja, preparata za njegu kože, preparata za njegu kose, sapuna, preparata za kupanje i tuširanje, preparata za zaštitu od sunca, nemedicinskih toaletnih pripravaka, naočala, sunčanih naočala, futrola i pribora za naočale, okvirima i lećama za naočale i sunčane naočale, futrolama i navlakama za telefone, futrolama i navlakama za računala i elektroničke uređaje, nakitom, kutijama za nakit i dragulje, privjescima, manžetama; Maloprodajne usluge i internetske maloprodajne usluge u vezi s prodajom ukrasnih igala, kravata, broševa, značaka, medaljona, medalja, privjesaka za ključeve, pribora za mobilne telefone, instrumenata za mjerenje vremena i kronometrijskih instrumenata, ručnih satova, zidnih satova, remena za ručne satove, traka za ručne satove, narukvica za satove, kućišta za ručne i zidne satove, prtljage, torbi, ručnih torbi, ruksaka, naprtnjača, torbi za plažu, torbi za nošenje na ramenu, putnih kovčega, aktovki, prtljažnih artikala, torbi za nošenje, novčanika i torbica, kišobrana, suncobrana, nesesera (praznih); Maloprodajne usluge i mrežne maloprodajne usluge u vezi s prodajom držača kreditnih kartica, držača kartica, kožnih remena, odjeće, obuće, pokrivala za glavu, remena; Usluge oglašavanja i promocije u vezi navedenih proizvoda; Usluge programa vjernosti, motivacije i bonusa; Informacije i savjetodavne usluge u vezi sa svim navedenim uslugama.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások és online kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások az alábbiak értékesítésével kapcsolatban: kozmetikumok, illatszer készítmények, esszenciális olajok, bőrápoló készítmények, hajápoló készítmények, szappanok, fürdő- és tusoló készítmények, napozáshoz való készítmények, nem gyógyhatású piperekészítmények, szemüvegek, napszemüvegek, tokok és tartók szemüvegekhez, szemüveg és napszemüveg keretei és lencsék, telefontoktok és tokok, számítógépes és elektronikus eszközök tokjai és burkolatai, ékszerek, ékszer- és ékszerdobozok, talizmánok, mandzsettagombok; Kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások és online kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások az alábbiak értékesítésével kapcsolatban: dísztűk, nyakkendőtűk, brossok, jelvények, érmek, érmék, kulcstartók, mobiltelefon-kiegészítők, órakészítő és időmérő műszerek, karórák, órák, karóra szíjak, óraszíjak, tokok órákhoz és karórákhoz, bőröndök, táskák, kézitáskák, hátitáskák, hátizsákok, strandtáskák, autóstáskák, utazótáskák, aktatáskák, sportszatyrok, hordtokok, pénztárcák és irattárcák, esernyők, napernyők, piperecikkek (felszerelés nélkül); Kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások és online kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások hitelkártya-tartók, kártyatartók, bőrövek, ruházat, lábbeli, fejfedők, övek eladásával kapcsolatban; Ezekhez az árukhoz kapcsolódó reklámozási és promóciós szolgáltatások; Hűségprogramok, ösztönző és bónusz program szolgáltatások; A fent említettekre vonatkozó információs és tanácsadási szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di vendita al dettaglio e servizi di vendita al dettaglio on-line connessi alla vendita di cosmetici, profumi, oli essenziali, preparati per la cura della pelle, preparati per la cura dei capelli, saponi, preparati da bagno e per la doccia, preparati solari, preparati non medicati per la toilette, articoli ottici, occhiali da sole, custodie e accessori per articoli ottici, occhiali e montature per occhiali da sole e lenti, custodie e astucci per telefoni, cofanetti e custodie per computer e dispositivi elettronici, articoli di gioielleria, custodie per gioielli e gioielli, portafortuna, gemelli da polso; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio e servizi di vendita al dettaglio on-line connessi alla vendita di spille decorative, spille per cravatte, fermagli, stemmi, medaglioni, medaglie, portachiavi ad anello, accessori per cellulari, strumenti da orologeria e cronometrici, orologi, orologi da arredo, braccialetti per orologi, cinturini, cinturini d'orologi, custodie per orologi e orologi da arredo, valigeria, borse, borse a mano, zaini, sacchi da spalla, borse da mare, cartelle, bauli da viaggio, cartelle per documenti, borsoni da viaggio, custodie per il trasporto, portafogli da uomo e borsellini, ombrelli da pioggia, ombrelli da sole, nécessaire per la toilette vuoti; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio e di vendita al dettaglio on-line in materia di porta carte di credito, porta carte, cinture in cuoio, calzature, abbigliamento, cappelleria, cinture; Pubblicità e promozione di prodotti; Servizi per fidi, incentivi ed indennità; Servizi di informazione e consulenza relativi ai servizi sopra menzionati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Mažmeninės prekybos ir internetinės mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, susijusios pardavimu tokių prekių kaip kosmetika, kvepalai, eteriniai aliejai, odos priežiūros preparatai, plaukų priežiūros preparatai, muilai, vonios ir dušo preparatai, preparatai nuo saulės [kosmetiniai], ne gydomieji tualetiniai preparatai, akiniai, akiniai nuo saulės, akinių dėklai ir aksesuarai, akinių ir saulės akinių rėmeliai bei lęšiai, telefonų dėklai ir dangteliai, kompiuterių ir elektroninių prietaisų dėklai, papuošalai, papuošalų ir papuošalų dėklai, pakabukai, rankogalių segtukai; Mažmeninės prekybos ir internetinės mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, susijusios pardavimu tokių prekių kaip dekoratyviniai segtukai, kaklaraiščių segtukai, sagės, ženkleliai, medalionai, medaliai, raktų pakabukai, mobiliųjų telefonų priedai, laikrodžių ir chronometriniai instrumentai, laikrodžiai, laikrodžiai, laikrodžių apyrankės, laikrodžių dirželiai, laikrodžių apyrankės, rankinių laikrodžių ir laikrodžių dėklai, lagaminai, rankinės, rankinės, kuprinės, kuprinės, paplūdimio krepšiai, mokyklinės kuprinės, kelioninės lagaminai, portfeliai, kelionmaišiai, nešiojamieji lagaminėliai, piniginės ir piniginės, skėčiai, saulės skėčiai, reikmeninės (kišeninės tualetinės -) [tuščios]; Mažmeninės prekybos ir internetinės mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, susijusios su kreditinių kortelių, kortelių laikiklių, odinių diržų, drabužių, avalynės, galvos apdangalų, diržų pardavimu; Su šiomis prekėmis susijusios reklamos ir pardavimų skatinimo paslaugos; Lojalumo, skatinimo ir premijavimo programų paslaugos; Informacijos ir patarimų paslaugos, susijusios su anksčiau nurodytomis paslaugomis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi un tiešsaistes mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar šo produktu tirgošanu: kosmētika, smaržas, ēteriskās eļļas, ādas kopšanas līdzekļi, matu kopšanas līdzekļi, ziepes, vannas un dušas līdzekļi, sauļošanās preparāti, ķermeņa kopšanas līdzekļi bez ārstnieciskas iedarbības, acu aizsegi, saulesbrilles, ietvari un briļļu piederumi, brilles un saulesbriļļu rāmji un lēcas, ietvari un telefonu somiņas, ietvari un datoru ietvari un elektroniskās ierīces, juvelierizstrādājumi, dārglietu lādītes un juvelierizstrādājumi, amuleti, aproču pogas; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi un tiešsaistes mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar šo produktu tirgošanu: dekoratīvās tapas, kaklasaišu adatas, piespraudes, nozīmītes, medaljoni, medaļas, atslēgu kabatiņas, mobilo tālruņu aksesuāri, homoloģiski un laika mērīšanas instrumenti, rokas pulksteņi, pulksteņi, rokas pulksteņu siksniņas, rokas pulksteņu siksniņas, rokas pulksteņu siksniņas, pulksteņu un rokas pulksteņu futrāļi, bagāžas piederumi un čemodāni, somas, rokassomas, mugursomas, skolas somas, pludmales somas, skolēnu somas, kabatas portfeļi, plakani dokumentu portfeļi, mantu somas, pārnēsājamas somas, kabatas portfeļi un maki, lietussargi, saulessargi, rokassomiņas [nav piemērots]; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi un tiešsaistes mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar kredītkaršu turētāju, karšu turētāju, ādas jostu, apģērba, apavu, galvassegu, jostu pārdošanu; Iepriekš minēto preču reklāma un veicināšana; Pakalpojumi lojalitātes, motivēšanas un bonusu programmu jomā; Informācijas sniegšana un konsultāciju pakalpojumi saistībā ar iepriekš minēto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi tal-bejgħ bl-imnut u servizzi tal-bejgħ bl-imnut onlajn relatati mal-bejgħ ta' kożmetiċi, fwejjaħ, żjut essenzjali, preparazzjonijiet għall-kura tal-ġilda, preparazzjonijiet għall-kura tax-xagħar, sapun, preparazzjonijiet tal-banju u tad-doċċa, preparazzjonijiet għall-kura tax-xemx, preparazzjonijiet tat-twaletta mhux medikati, ilbies tal-għajnejn, nuċċalijiet tax-xemx, kaxex u aċċessorji tax-xedd il-għajn, oqfsa u lentijiet tan-nuċċalijiet tax-xemx, kaxex u kavers għat-telefowns, kaxex u kavers għall-kompjuters u tagħmir elettroniku, ġojjelli, kaxxetti għall-ġojjellerija u gojjelli, amuleti, pulzieri; Servizzi tal-bejgħ bl-imnut u servizzi tal-bejgħ bl-imnut onlajn relatati mal-bejgħ ta' labar dekorattivi, labar tal-ingravata, brooches, baġġijiet, midaljuni, medalji, stoċċijiet għaċ-ċwievet, aċċessorji tat-telefowns ċellulari, strumenti oroloġiċi u kronometriċi, arloġġi tal-id, arloġġi, ċineg tal-arloġġ tal-idejn, ċineg tal-arloġġ tal-idejn, brazzuletti tal-arloġġ tal-id, kaxxi għall-arloġġi u arloġġi tal-id, valiġġi, basktijiet, basktijiet tal-id, barżakki ta' fuq id-dahar, barżakki ta' fuq id-dahar, basktijiet tal-baħar, saċils, valiġġi, kartieri tad-dokumenti, basktijiet għal kull użu, basktijiet għall-ġarr, portafolli u valiġġi, umbrelel, umbrelel tax-xemx, kaxxetti għall-oġġetti tas-sbuħija (mhux imwaħħlin); Servizzi tal-bejgħ bl-imnut u servizzi tal-bejgħ bl-imnut onlajn relatati mal-bejgħ ta' kontenituri għall-karti tal-kreditu, kontenituri tal-kards, ċinturini tal-ġilda, ħwejjeġ, xedd is-saqajn, xedd ir-ras, ċinturini; Servizzi ta' reklamar u promozzjoni relatati ma' dawn l-oġġetti; Servizzi ta' programmi ta' lealtà, inċentivi u bonus; Servizzi ta' informazzjoni u pariri relatati ma' dak hawn fuq imsemmi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Detail- en onlinedetailhandel in verband met de verkoop van cosmetische middelen, parfums, etherische oliën, huidverzorgingsproducten, haarverzorgingsproducten, zepen, bad- en doucheproducten, producten tegen zonnebrand, niet-medicinale producten voor de toiletverzorging, brillen, zonnebrillen, etuis en accessoires voor brillen, monturen en glazen voor brillen en zonnebrillen, etuis en hoesjes voor telefoons, etuis en hoezen voor computers en elektronische toestellen, juwelierswaren, etuis voor juwelierswaren en juwelen, hangers, manchetknopen; Detail- en onlinedetailhandel in verband met de verkoop van decoratieve spelden, dasspelden, broches, insignes, medaillons, medailles, sleutelringen, accessoires voor mobiele telefoons, uurwerken en tijdmeetinstrumenten, horloges, klokken, horlogebanden, horlogebandjes, armbanden voor horloges, etuis voor horloges en klokken, bagage, tassen, handtassen, rugzakken, rugzakken, strandtassen, schooltassen, reiskoffers, aktentassen, weekendtassen, draagkoffers, portefeuilles en beurzen, paraplu's, parasols, beautycases (zonder inhoud); Detail- en onlinedetailhandel in verband met de verkoop van etuis voor creditcards, kaarthouders, lederen ceintuurs, kledingstukken, schoeisel, hoofddeksels, ceintuurs; Reclame en promotie met betrekking tot de voornoemde goederen; Klantenbindings-, aanmoedigings- en bonusprogrammadiensten; Diensten op het gebied van informatie en advies met betrekking tot het voornoemde.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi handlu detalicznego i usługi handlu detalicznego online związane ze sprzedażą towarów, takich jak kosmetyki, perfumy, olejki eteryczne, preparaty do pielęgnacji skóry, środki do pielęgnacji włosów, mydła, preparaty do kąpieli i pod prysznic, preparaty do ochrony przeciwsłonecznej, nielecznicze preparaty toaletowe, okulary, okulary przeciwsłoneczne, etui i akcesoria do okularów, oprawki i szkła do okularów i okularów przeciwsłonecznych, etui i pokrowce na telefony, etui i pokrowce na komputery i urządzenia elektroniczne, biżuteria i wyroby jubilerskie, szkatułki na biżuterię i klejnoty, talizmany, spinki do mankietów; Usługi handlu detalicznego i usługi handlu detalicznego online związane ze sprzedażą towarów, takich jak ozdobne szpilki, szpilki do krawatów, broszki, odznaki, medaliony, medale, breloczki do kluczy, akcesoria do telefonów komórkowych, przyrządy zegarmistrzowskie i chronometryczne, zegarki, zegary, paski do zegarków, paski do zegarków, bransoletki do zegarków, etui do zegarków i zegarków, bagaż, torby, torebki, plecaki, plecaki, torby plażowe, tornistry, bagaż, aktówki, bagaż, torby przenośne, portfele i portmonetki, parasole, parasole, kuferki na kosmetyki (bez wyposażenia); Usługi handlu detalicznego i handlu detalicznego online związane ze sprzedażą etui na karty kredytowe, etui na karty, pasków skórzanych, odzieży, obuwia, nakryć głowy, pasków; Usługi reklamowe i promocyjne dotyczące tych towarów; Usługi programów lojalnościowych, motywacyjnych i promocyjnych; Usługi informacyjne i doradcze dotyczące uprzednio wymienionych [usług].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de venda a retalho e de venda a retalho em linha de cosméticos, perfumes, óleos essenciais, produtos para os cuidados da pele, produtos para os cuidados dos cabelos, sabões, produtos para banho e duche, protetores solares, produtos de toilette não medicinais, artigos de ótica, óculos de sol, estojos e acessórios para artigos de ótica, armações e lentes para óculos e óculos de sol, estojos e capas para telefones, estojos e capas para computadores e dispositivos eletrónicos, joalharia, estojos para artigos de joalharia e joias, berloques, botões de punho; Serviços de venda a retalho e de venda a retalho em linha de alfinetes de adereço, alfinetes de gravata, broches, emblemas, medalhões, medalhas, argolas para chaves, acessórios para telemóveis, relojoaria e instrumentos cronométricos, relógios de pulso ou de bolso, relógios de parede ou de mesa, pulseiras de relógios, correias para relógios de pulso, estojos para relógios, artigos de bagagem, sacos, sacos de mão, mochilas, sacos de praia, sacolas, malas (baús) de viagem, pastas para documentos, sacos multiusos, estojos de transporte, carteiras de bolso e porta-moedas, chapéus de chuva, chapéus de sol, estojos de toilette (não guarnecidos); Serviços de venda a retalho e de venda a retalho em linha de porta-cartões de crédito, porta-cartões, cintos em couro, vestuário, calçado, chapelaria, cintos; Serviços de publicidade e de promoção relacionados com estes produtos; Serviços de programas de fidelização, incentivo e oferta; Serviços de informação e assessoria relacionados com os serviços atrás referidos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de comerț cu amănuntul și servicii de comerț cu amănuntul online legate de vânzarea de cosmetice, parfumuri, uleiuri esențiale, preparate de îngrijire a pielii, produse pentru îngrijirea părului, săpunuri, geluri de baie și duș, produse pentru protecție solară, produse nemedicamentoase pentru toaletă, articole optice, ochelari de soare, cutii și accesorii pentru articole optice, rame și lentile pentru ochelari și ochelari de soare, cutii și huse pentru telefoane, cutii și huse pentru calculatoare și dispozitive electronice, bijuterii, casete pentru bijuterii și bijuterii, pandantive, nasturi pentru manșete; Servicii de comerț cu amănuntul și servicii de comerț cu amănuntul online legate de vânzarea de ace decorative, ace de cravată, broșe, insigne, medalioane, medalii, brelocuri pentru chei, accesorii pentru telefonul mobil, ceasornicărie și instrumente pentru măsurarea timpului, ceasuri cu brățară, ceasuri cu, brățări de ceas, brățări de ceas, curele de ceas, etuiuri sau tocuri pentru ceasuri cu brățară și ceasuri, bagaje, genți, poșete, rucsacuri, rucsacuri, genți de plajă, ghiozdane, genți, mape pentru documente, genți universale, genți pentru transport, portofele și genți, umbrele, umbrele de soare, genți de voiaj pentru cosmetice; Servicii de comerț cu amănuntul și servicii de comerț cu amănuntul online legate de vânzarea de suporturi pentru carduri de credit, suporturi pentru carduri, curele din piele, îmbrăcăminte, încălțăminte, articole care servesc la acoperirea capului, curele; Servicii publicitare şi promoţionale cu privire la aceste bunuri; Servicii de fidelizare, motivare şi recompensare; Servicii de informaţii şi consiliere în legătută cu cele menţionate anterior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Maloobchodné a on-line maloobchodné služby v oblasti predaja tovaru, akým sú kozmetické prípravky, voňavkárske výrobky, éterické oleje, prípravky na ošetrovanie pleti, prípravky pre starostlivosť o vlasy, mydlá, kúpele a prípravky na sprchovanie, ochranné opaľovacie prípravky, toaletné prípravky bez liečivých prísad, okuliare, slnečné okuliare, puzdrá a príslušenstvo pre okuliare, rámy pre okuliare a slnečné okuliare, puzdrá a kryty na telefóny, puzdrá a kryty na počítače a elektronické zariadenia, klenotnícke výrobky, šperkovnice a šperky, prívesky, manžetové gombíky; Maloobchodné a on-line maloobchodné služby v oblasti predaja tovaru, akým sú ozdobné ihlice, ihlice na kravaty, brošne, odznaky, medailóny, medaily, kľúčenky, príslušenstvo pre mobilné telefóny, hodinárske výrobky a chronometre, hodinky, hodiny, remienky na hodinky, remienky na hodinky, chrániče zápästia, puzdrá na hodinky a hodinky, kufre, tašky, kabelky, ruksaky, ruksaky, plážové tašky, školské tašky, batožina, aktovky, športové vaky, puzdrá na nosenie, peňaženky a peňaženky, dáždniky, slnečníky, kufríky na toaletné potreby (nevybavené); Maloobchodné a on-line maloobchodné služby v oblasti predaja tovaru, akým sú puzdrá na kreditné karty, puzdrá na karty, kožené opasky, odevy, obuv, pokrývky hlavy a opasky; Reklamné a propagačné slžuby v oblasti týchto tovarov; Služby vernostných, motivačných a odmeňovacích programov; Informačné a poradenské služby vo vyššie uvedených oblastiach.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve maloprodaje in spletne maloprodaje v zvezi s prodajo izdelkov, kot so kozmetični izdelki, parfumi, eterična olja, izdelki za nego kože, izdelki za nego las, mila, izdelki za kopanje in prhanje, izdelki za nego po sončenju, toaletna sredstva brez zdravilnih učinkovin, zaščitna oprema za oči, sončna očala, etuiji in dodatki za očala, okvirji in leče za očala in sončna očala, etuiji in ovitki za telefone, etuiji in prevleke za računalnike in elektronske aparate, zlatarski izdelki, nakit, skrinjice za zlatarske izdelke, nakit in dragulje, talismani, manšetni gumbi; Storitve maloprodaje in spletne maloprodaje v zvezi s prodajo izdelkov, kot so okrasne igle, kravatne igle, broške, kokarde, medaljoni, medalje, obročki za ključe, dodatki za mobilne telefone, ure in instrumenti za merjenje časa, ročne ure, ure, paščki za ročne ure, paščki za ročne ure, paščki za ročne ure, etuiji za ročne ure in urami, prtljaga, torbe, ročne torbice, nahrbtniki, nahrbtniki, torbe za plažo, torbe z jermenom, potovalni kovčki, aktovke, potovalne torbe, kovčki, denarnice in torbice, dežniki, sončniki, torbice z ogledali in kozmetiko (neopremljeni); Storitve maloprodaje in spletne maloprodaje v zvezi s prodajo izdelkov, kot so ovitki za kreditne kartice, držala za kartice, usnjeni pasovi, oblačila, obutev, pokrivala, pasovi; Reklamne in promocijske storitve v zvezi s tem blagom; Storitve programov zvestobe, spodbujevalnih in nagrajevalnih programov za potrošnike; Informacijske in svetovalne storitve v zvezi z omenjenim.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Detaljhandelstjänster och direktanslutna detaljhandelstjänster i samband med försäljning av kosmetika, parfymer, flyktiga oljor, hudvårdspreparat, hårvårdspreparat, tvål, bad- och duschpreparat, solvårdspreparat, icke medicinska toalettpreparat, glasögon, solglasögon, fodral och tillbehör för glasögon, bågar och linser för glasögon och solglasögon, fodral och överdrag för telefoner, fodral och överdrag för datorer och elektroniska anordningar, juvelerarvaror, smyckesskrin och juveler, berlocker, manschettknappar; Detaljhandelstjänster och direktanslutna detaljhandelstjänster i samband med försäljning av prydnadsnålar, slipsnålar, broscher, märken, medaljonger, medaljer, nyckelringar, mobiltelefontillbehör, ur och tidsinstrument, ur, ur, klockband, remmar för armbandsur, klockarmband, fodral för ur och ur, reseffekter, väskor, handväskor, bärmesar, ryggsäckar, strandväskor, axelväskor, kappsäckar, portföljer, stora bagar, bärväskor, plånböcker och portmonnäer, paraplyer, parasoller, sminkväskor (ej inredda); Detaljhandelstjänster och direktanslutna detaljhandelstjänster i samband med försäljning av kreditkortshållare, korthållare, läderbälten, kläder, fotbeklädnader och huvudbonader, bälten; Annons- och reklamtjänster relaterade till dessa varor; Lojalitets-, incitaments- och bonusprogramtjänster; Informations- och rådgivningstjänster avseende det tidigare nämnda.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PriorityDetails>
<Priority>
<PriorityCountryCode>GB</PriorityCountryCode>
<PriorityNumber>UK00003481665</PriorityNumber>
<PriorityDate>2020-04-15</PriorityDate>
<PriorityPartialIndicator>false</PriorityPartialIndicator>
<PriorityStatusCode>Claimed</PriorityStatusCode>
</Priority>
</PriorityDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/088</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-12</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/158</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-20</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080382</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>19496</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
