<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-05T16:31:27</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226278</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226278</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-31</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>SIWUTIAO</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>20</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Рафтове за складове; Офисмебели; Вътрешни текстилни щори за прозорци; Дюшеци, матраци; Дървени преградни стени за мебели; Поставки за табла за обяви; Рафтове за складове; Тоалетни масички, тоалетки; Бюфети.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Úložné police; Kancelářský nábytek; Interiérové textilní okenní rolety; Matrace; Dřevěné nábytkové příčky; Stojany na vystavení zboží; Police (k nábytku); Stolky a skříňky s umyvadlem [nábytek]; Příborníky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Hylder til opbevaring; Kontormøbler; Indendørs rullegardiner af tekstil; Madrasser; Paneler af træ til møbler; Udstillingsstativer; Møbelhylder; Servanter [møbler]; Buffeter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Ablageplatten; Büromöbel; Innenjalousien aus Stoff für Fenster; Matratzen; Möbelfächer aus Holz; Schaugestelle; Fachböden für Möbel; Waschtische [Möbel]; Buffets [Möbel].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ράφια για αποθήκευση· Έπιπλα, ειδικότερα έπιπλα γραφείου· Εσωτερικές περσίδες παραθύρων από ύφασμα· Στρώματα· Ξυλεπενδύσεις για έπιπλα· Προθήκες· Ράφια για αποθήκευση· Τραπέζια τουαλέτας· Σκευοθήκες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Shelves for storage; Office furniture; indoor window blinds of textile; Mattresses; Furniture partitions of wood; Display stands; Furniture shelves; Washstands [furniture]; Sideboards.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Estantes de almacenamiento; Muebles de oficina; Estores de materias textiles para ventanas; Colchones; Entrepaños de madera para muebles; Expositores [muebles]; Anaqueles [baldas] de muebles; Tocadores [muebles]; Aparadores [muebles].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Laoriiulid; Kontorimööbel; Tekstiilist aknarulood siseruumides kasutamiseks; Madratsid; Mööbli puitvaheseinad; Näitusestendid; Mööbliriiulid; Pesulauad [mööbel]; Puhvetkapid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Telineet; Toimistokalusteet; Tekstiilikaihtimet sisäkäyttöön; Patjat; Seinäkkeet huonekaluina, puuta; Näyttelytelineet; Kalustehyllyt; Pukeutumispöydät; Senkit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Tablettes de rangement; Meubles de bureau; Stores de fenêtre d'intérieur en matières textiles; Matelas; Pans de boiseries pour meubles; Présentoirs; Rayons de meubles; Tables de toilette [mobilier]; Buffets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Stalci; Uredski namještaj; Unutarnji tekstilni zastori za prozore; Madraci; Drvene ploče [paneli] za pokućstvo; Stalci za potrebe prikazivanja; Stalci; Stolići za umivanje [pokućstvo]; Ormari za stolno posuđe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Állványok, polcok; Irodabútorok; Beltéri ablaksötétítők textilből; Matracok; Faszerkezetek, elválasztók bútorokhoz; Árubemutató állványok; Állványok, polcok; Fésülködő asztalok; Pohárszékek, ebédlőszekrények.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Ripiani di riordino; Mobili per ufficio; Tende interne in stoffa per finestre; Materassi; Pannelli di legno per mobili; Espositori; Ripiani di mobili; Tavolini da toilette [mobili]; Buffet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Sandėlių lentynos; Biuro baldai; Vidinės kambarinės tekstilinės užuolaidos; Čiužiniai ir matracai; Medinės baldų pertvaros; Vitrinos; Baldų lentynos; Prausyklės [baldai su praustuvėmis]; Indaujos [bufetai].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Noliktavu plaukti; Biroja mēbeles; Iekštelpu logu žalūzijas no tekstilmateriāliem; Matrači; Mēbeļu starpsienas no koka; Izstāžu stendi; Mēbeļu plaukti; Mazgāšanās galdi (mēbeles); Bufetes skapji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Xkafef; Għamara tal-uffiċċju; Persjani li jdallmu tat-tessuti għat-twieqi ta' ġewwa; Saqqijiet; Taqsimiet tal-għamara tal-injam; Tagħmir għaż-żamm ta' xi ħaġa għall-wiri; Xkafef; Twaletti; Sajdbords.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Legplanken; Kantoormeubelen; Zonwering van textiel voor binnenshuis; Matrassen; Houten panelen voor meubelen; Displays [verkoopstandaards]; Planken voor meubelen; Wastafels [meubilair]; Buffetkasten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Stojaki, półki; Meble biurowe; Rolety okienne tekstylne wewnętrzne; Materace; Panele drewniane do mebli; Stoiska wystawowe; Stojaki, półki; Toaletki; Kredensy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Prateleiras para armazenagem; Mobiliário de escritório; Estores de janelas interiores em matérias têxteis; Colchões; Divisórias para móveis, em madeira; Expositores [móveis]; Prateleiras para mobiliário; Armários para lavatórios [mobiliário]; Aparadores [mobiliário].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Polițe; Mobile de birou; Jaluzele de interior, din material textil; Saltele; Panouri despărțitoare din lemn pentru mobilier; Standuri de prezentare; Polițe; Măsuțe de toaletă; Bufeturi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Police; Kancelársky nábytok; Interiérové okenné clony z textilných materiálov; Matrace; Drevené časti nábytku; Vystavovacie stojany; Nábytkové police; Skrinky s umývadlom (nábytok); Servírovacie stoly a pulty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Stojala; Pisarniško pohištvo; Notranja senčila za okna, iz blaga; Vzmetnice; Nekovinske pregrade za pohištvo; Razstavna stojala; Stojala; Toaletne mizice; Omare za namizno posodo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hyllor för lagring; Kontorsmöbler; Persienner av textil för inomhusbruk; Madrasser; Mellanväggar av trä för möbler; Skyltställ; Möbelhyllor; Kommoder [möbler]; Matsalsskänkar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/146</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080395</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>39103</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
