<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-08T07:37:03</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226519</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226519</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="1">Application published</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-08</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ZINQ microseal</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162318699</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226519/000162318699.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>26.03.23</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>29.01.98</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>2</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Бои, лакове, политури; Антикорозионни вещества и вещества, предпазващи дървения материал от повреждане; Оцветители; Байцове, необработени естествени смоли; Метали във вид на фолио и прах за бояджии, декоратори, печатари и художници; Антикорозионни средства за нанасяне върху железни и стоманени стоки чрез термична галванизация, термална предобработка, прахово покриване и/или мокро боядисване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Barvy, nátěry, laky; Ochranné výrobky proti korozi a proti deteriorizaci dřeva; Barviva; Mořidla, surové přírodní pryskyřice; Kovy lístkové a práškové pro malíře, dekoratéry a umělce; Ochranné výrobky proti korozi, pro nanášení na železné a ocelové předměty žárovým zinkováním, tepelnou předpřípravou, práškovým nátěrem a/nebo mokrým lakováním.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Malinger, fernisser, lakker; Rustbeskyttelsesmidler og træimprægneringsmidler; Farvestoffer; Bejdsemidler, naturlige harpikser i rå tilstand; Bladmetaller og metalpulver til brug for malere, dekoratører, trykkere og kunstnere; Rustbeskyttelsesmidler til påføring på jern- og stålgenstande ved hjælp af termisk forsænkning, termisk forbehandling, pulverlakering og/eller vådlakering.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Farben, Firnisse, Lacke; Rostschutzmittel, Holzkonservierungsmittel; Färbemittel; Beizen, Naturharze im Rohzustand; Blattmetalle und Metalle in Pulverform für Maler, Dekorateure, Drucker und Künstler; Rostschutzmittel zum Auftragen auf Artikel aus Eisen und Stahl durch Feuerverzinken, thermische Vorbehandlung, Pulverbeschichtung und/oder Nasslackierung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Χρώματα, βερνίκια, λάκες· Μέσα προφυλάξεως κατά της σκωρίας και μέσα συντηρήσεως ξύλου· Βαφές· Αντιδιαβρωτικές ουσίες, ακατέργαστες φυσικές ρητίνες· Μέταλλα σε φύλλα (ελάσματα) και σε μορφή σκόνης για ζωγράφους, διακοσμητές, τυπογράφους και καλλιτέχνες· Μέσα προφύλαξης κατά της σκωρίας, για εφαρμογή σε σιδερένια και χαλύβδινα είδη μέσω θερμού γαλβανισμού, θερμικής προεπεξεργασίας, επίστρωσης με εμβάπτιση σε σκόνη και/ή υγρής βαφής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Paints, varnishes, lacquers; Preservatives against rust and against deterioration of wood; Colorants; Mordants, raw natural resins; Metals in foil and powder form for painters, decorators, printers and artists; Preservatives against rust, for application to iron and steel goods by hot galvanisation, thermal pre-treatment, powder coating and/or wet painting.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pinturas, barnices, lacas; Productos antioxidantes y productos para conservar la madera; Colorantes; Mordientes, resinas naturales en estado bruto; Metales en hojas y en polvo para pintores, decoradores, impresores y artistas; Conservantes contra la herrumbre, para su aplicación a productos de hierro y acero mediante galvanización en caliente, pretratamiento térmico, recubrimiento de polvos o pintado en húmedo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Värvid, värnitsad, lakid; Korrosioonitõrje- ja puidukaitsevahendid; Värvained; Peitsid, looduslikud toorvaigud; Maalijaile, sisekujundajaile, trükkaleile ja kunstnikele mõeldud leht- ja pulbermetallid; Korrosioonitõrjevahendid kasutamiseks raua ja terase kuumtsinkimisel, termilisel eeltöötlemisel, pulberpindamisel ja/või värvimisel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Maalit, vernissat, lakat; Ruosteenesto- ja puunsuojavalmisteet; Pigmentit; Peittausaineet, raa'at luonnonhartsit; Lehtimetallit ja metallijauheet maalaus-, koristus-, kirjapaino- ja taidetarkoituksiin; Ruosteenestoaineet, joilla käsitellään rauta- ja teräsesineet termisen sinkityksen, termisen esikäsittelyn, jauhepinnoituksen ja/tai märkälakkauksen avulla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Peintures, vernis, laques; Produits antirouille et produits contre la détérioration du bois; Colorants; Mordants, résines naturelles à l'état brut; Métaux en feuilles et en poudre pour peintres, décorateurs, imprimeurs et artistes; Produits contre la corrosion, à appliquer sur des objets en fer et en acier par galvanisation thermique, prétraitement thermique, revêtement par pulvérisation et/ou peinture fraîche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Boje, lakovi, glazure; Zaštite od hrđe te od propadanja i truljenja drva; Bojila; Prirodne sirove smole; Metali u listovima i u prahu za slikare, dekoratere, tiskare i umjetnike; Sredstva za zaštitu od hrđe za nanošenje na proizvode od željeza i čelika vrućim pocinčavanjem, termičkom prethodnom obradom, praškastim lakiranjem i/ili mokrim lakiranjem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Festékek, kencék, lakkok; Rozsdagátló és fakonzerváló szerek; Színezőanyagok; Pácok, nyers, természetes rezinek; Fémlapok és fémporok festők, dekorátorok, nyomdászok és képzőművészek részére; Vas- vagy acéltermékekre termikus cinkezéssel, termikus előkezeléssel, porbevonással és/vagy nedves lakkozással felvihető rozsda elleni tartósítószerek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Colori, vernici, lacche; Prodotti preservanti dalla ruggine e dal deterioramento del legno; Coloranti; Mordenti, resine naturali allo stato grezzo; Metalli in fogli e in polvere per pittori, decoratori, tipografi e artisti; Prodotti preservanti dalla ruggine, da applicare su articoli in ferro ed acciaio tramite galvanizzazione a caldo, pretrattamento termico, rivestimento con polveri e/o pittura fresca.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Dažai, politūros, lakai; Antikorozinės medžiagos ir medieną nuo irimo saugančios medžiagos; Dažalai (dažai); Beicai [kandikai], žaliavinės natūralios dervos; Metalų folija ir milteliai dažytojams, dekoratoriams, spaustuvininkams ir dailininkams; Antikoroziniai preparatai, kuriais geležiniai ir plieniniai paviršiai dengiami karštai cinkuojant, iš anksto karštai apdorojant, dažant milteliniu būdu arba lakuojant ant drėgno sluoksnio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Krāsas, pernicas, lakas; Pretkorozijas līdzekļi, koksnes konservēšanas līdzekļi; Ķīmiskās krāsvielas; Kodnes, neapstrādāti dabiskie sveķi; Lokšņveida un pulverveida metāli mākslinieciskiem un dekoratīviem nolūkiem un iespieddarbiem; Pretkorozijas konservanti uzklāšanai uz dzelzs un tērauda precēm, izmantojot karsto galvanizāciju, termisku pirmsapstrādi, pulverveida pārklājumu un/vai mitro krāsošanu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Żebgħa, verniċ, żmalt; Preservanti kontra s-sadid u kontra d-deterjorazzjoni ta' l-injam; Sustanzi li minnhom issir iż-żebgħa; Mordenti, raża naturali mhux ipproċessata; Metalli f'folji rqaq u trab għall-bajjada, għad-dekoraturi, għall-istampaturi u għall-artisti; Preservanti kontra s-sadid, għall-applikazzjoni ma' oġġetti tal-ħadid u tal-azzar permezz tal-galvanizzazzjoni sħuna, it-trattament minn qabel termiku, kisi tat-trab u/jew żebgħa mxarrba.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verven, vernissen, lakken; Roestwerende middelen en houtconserveringsmiddelen; Kleurstoffen; Beitsen, natuurlijke harsen als grondstof; Metalen in blad- en poedervorm voor schilders, decorateurs, drukkers en kunstenaars; Corrosiewerende middelen, aan te brengen op ijzeren en stalen voorwerpen door thermisch verzinken, thermisch voorbehandelen, poedercoaten en/of natlakken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Farby, pokosty, lakiery; Środki zapobiegające korozji i zabezpieczające drewno; Barwniki; Bejce, żywice naturalne nieprzetworzone; Folie metalowe i formy proszkowe dla malarzy, dekoratorów, drukarzy i artystów; Środki zapobiegające korozji, do nanoszenia na towary żelazne i stalowe za pomocą cynkowania, obróbki termicznej, powlekania proszkowego i/lub lakierowania na mokro.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Tintas, vernizes, lacas; Preservativos contra a ferrugem e contra a deterioração da madeira; Corantes; Mordentes, resinas naturais em estado bruto; Metais em folhas e em pó para pintores, decoradores, impressores e artistas; Produtos de conservação contra a ferrugem, para aplicação em ferro e artigos de aço inoxidável através de galvanização a quente, pré-tratamento térmico, revestimento com pó e/ou pintura fresca.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Vopsele, firnisuri, lacuri; Substanţe de protecţie contra ruginii şi contra deteriorării lemnului; Pigmenți; Decapanţi, răşini naturale în stare brută; Metale sub formă de foiţe şi sub formă de pudră pentru pictori, decoratori, tipografi şi artişti; Produse anticorozive, care se aplică pe obiecte din fier şi oţel prin zincare termică, tratament termic prealabil, acoperire cu pudră şi/sau lăcuire umedă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Farby, fermeže, laky; Ochranné prostriedky proti hrdzi a poškodeniu dreva; Farbivá; Moridlá, prírodné živice v surovom stave; Kovy vo forme fólií a práškov pre maliarov, dekoratérov, tlačiarov a umelcov; Antikorózne prípravky, ktoré slúžia na nanášanie na železné a oceľové predmety pomocou galvanizácie za tepla, predbežnej tepelnej úpravy, práškového natierania za tepla a/alebo vlhkého natierania.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Barve, firneži, laki; Sredstva za zaščito proti rji in sredstva za konzerviranje lesa; Barvila; Lužilna sredstva, surove naravne smole; Kovine v obliki folij in prahu za pleskarje, dekoraterje, tiskarje in umetnike; Sredstva za zaščito proti rji za nanašanje na železne in jeklene izdelke z vročo galvanizacijo, toplotno predobdelavo, praškastim premazovanjem in/ali mokrim barvanjem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Målarfärger, fernissor och lacker; Rostskyddsmedel och skyddsmedel mot angrepp på trä; Färgämnen; Betningsmedel, obearbetade naturhartser; Metaller i folie- och pulverform för målare, dekoratörer, tryckare och konstnärer; Rostskyddsmedel, för anbringande på järn- och stålföremål genom termisk försinkning, termisk förbehandling, pulverbeläggning och/eller våtlackering.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>6</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Неблагородни метали и техните сплави; Метални материали за строителство и изграждане; Обков от метал за строителство; Строителни панели от метал; Метални конструкции; Преносими метални конструкции; Винкели от метал за строителство; Метални материали за железопътни линии; Неелектрически кабели и жици от неблагородни метали; Огнеупорни строителни материали от метал; Носещи стоманени конструкции; Скелета за кофраж от метал; Плочки от метал за строителство; Рамки от метал за строителство; Метални компоненти за сгради и инженерно строителство; Компоненти от метал на изграждането на машини, А именно тръби, Макари, Клапани, Тръбопроводи, Клапани за димоотводи, Кранове, Шайби; Железария, метална кинкалерия; Метални тръби; Сейфове [метални или неметални]; Стоки от метал, доколкото не са включени в други класове, а именно метални клинове, дюбели, халки, кутии, анкери, мрежи, прегради, фолиа, форми, нитове, вериги (от неблагородни метали), куки, решетки, табла, тунели, намотки, капаци; Руди за метали; Стоманени сплави; Стомана, необработена или полуобработена; Цинк; Сгради от стомана; Стоманени листове; Стоманена жица; Течна, лята стопена стомана; Стоманени топки [за топкови мелници]; Стоманени ленти, кръгове и обръчи от стомана; Стоманени конструкции; Профилна стомана; Стоманени тръби; Стоманени мачти; Въжета и дебели въжета от стомана и железни нишки; Облицовки от метал за конструкции и сгради; Метални рафтове за складове.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Obecné kovy a jejich slitiny; Kovové materiály pro stavebnictví; Kovová kování pro stavebnictví; Kovové stavební panely; Kovové konstrukce; Přenosné kovové stavby; Kovové konzoly pro stavebnictví; Kovové materiály pro železnice; Kabely a dráty z běžných kovů kromě elektrických; Kovové žáruvzdorné stavební materiály; Nosné ocelové konstrukce; Kovová lešení; Kovové obkladáčky pro stavebnictví; Kovové kostry budov pro stavebnictví; Součásti z kovu pro budovy a inženýrské stavby; Kovové součástky pro stavbu strojů, Jmenovitě trubky, Navijáky, Ventily, Dýmky, Šály (tlusté) na krk, Ventily, Disky; Kovové potřeby zámečnické a klempířské; Kovová potrubí a trubky; Sejfy [kovové i nekovové]; Výrobky z kovu, nezařazené do jiných tříd, jmenovitě kovové klíny, hmoždinky, kroužky, dózy, kotvy, sítě, trámy, fólie, formy, nýty, řetězy (z obecných kovů), motyky, mříže, tabule, tunely, cívky a víka; Rudy kovů; Slitiny oceli; Ocel, nezpracovaná nebo jako polotovar; Zinek; Ocelové budovy; Ocelové plechy; Ocelový drát; Ocelová litina, litá ocel, plávková ocel; Ocelové koule; Pásy ocelové, ocelové kruhy a obruče; Ocelové stavební konstrukce; Formovaná litá ocel; Ocelové trubky; Ocelové stožáry; Lana a provazy z ocele a drátů; Kovové obklady pro stavebnictví; Skladovací police z kovu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Uædle metaller og legeringer heraf; Bygge- og konstruktionsmaterialer, af metal; Metalbeslag til bygningsbrug; Bygningspaneler af metal; Bygninger af metal; Bygninger, transportable, af metal; Vinkelbeslag af metal til bygningsbrug; Materialer af metal til jernbanespor; Ikke-elektriske kabler og wirer af uædle metaller; Ildfaste konstruktionsmaterialer af metal; Bærende stålkonstruktioner; Stilladser af metal; Fliser af metal til bygningsbrug; Rammer af metal til bygningsbrug; Komponenter af metal til bygninger og byggetekniske konstruktioner; Komponenter af metal til byggeri af maskiner, Nemlig rør, Spoler, Ventiler, Ledninger, Trækregulatorer, Udtag, Plader; Klejnsmedearbejder, små genstande af metal (isenkramvarer); Rør og rørledninger af metal; Bankbokse [metaliske eller ikke metaliske]; Varer af metal, ikke indeholdt i andre klasser, nemlig metalkiler, -dyvler, -ringe, -dåser, -ankre, -net, -stænger, -folier, -forme, -nitter, -kæder (af uædle metaller), -hasper, -gitre, -tavler, -tunneller, -spoler og -dæksler; Metalmalme; Stållegeringer; Stål, uforarbejdet eller delvist forarbejdet; Zink; Stålbygninger; Stålplader; Ståltråd; Stålstøbegods i støbt og smeltet form; Stålkugler; Stålbånd, cirkler og tøndebånd af stål; Stålbygninger; Formstøbt stål; Stålrør; Stålmaster; Reb og tov af stål og af jerntråd; Beklædningsmaterialer af metal til bygningsbrug; Lagerstativer af metal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Unedle Metalle und deren Legierungen; Baumaterialien aus Metall; Baubeschläge aus Metall; Bauplatten aus Metall; Bauten aus Metall; transportable Bauten aus Metall; Eckschienen aus Metall für Bauzwecke; Schienenbaumaterial aus Metall; Kabel und Drähte aus Metall [nicht für elektrische Zwecke]; feuerfeste Baumaterialien aus Metall; Tragkonstruktionen für Bauten aus Metall; Baugerüste aus Metall; Kacheln aus Metall für Bauzwecke; Metallrahmen für Bauzwecke; Bauteile aus Metall für Gebäude und Ingenieurbauten; Bauteile aus Metall zum Bau von Maschinen, nämlich Rohre, Spulen, Ventile, Leitungen, Klappen, Hähne, Scheiben; Schlosserwaren und Kleineisenwaren; Metallrohre; Geldschränke; Waren aus Metall, soweit sie nicht in anderen Klassen enthalten sind, nämlich Metallkeile, -dübel, -ringe, -dosen, -anker, -netze, -barren, -folien, -formen, -nieten, -ketten (aus unedlen Metallen), -haspen, -gitter, -tafeln, -tunnel, -spulen und -deckel; Erze; Stahllegierungen; Stahl, roh oder teilweise bearbeitet; Zink; Stahlbauten; Stahlbleche; Stahldraht; Gussstahl, Formgussstahl, Stahlguss; Stahlkugeln; Bandstahl, Reifen, Bänder aus Stahl; Stahlkonstruktionen; Formgussstahl; Stahlröhren; Stahlmasten; Seile und Trossen aus Stahl und aus Eisendraht; Verkleidungsteile aus Metall für Bauzwecke; Lagergestelle aus Metall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κοινά μέταλλα και κράματα αυτών· Μεταλλικά υλικά οικοδομών και κατασκευών· Σιδηρές βάσεις κατασκευής· Φατνώματα κατασκευής μεταλλικά· Κατασκευές μεταλλικές· Κατασκευές λυόμενες μεταλλικές· Γωνιές μεταλλικές [κατασκευές]· Μεταλλικά υλικά για σιδηροτροχιές· Συρματόσκοινα και μεταλλικά σύρματα μη ηλεκτροφόρα· Πυρίμαχα μεταλλικά υλικά κατασκευών· Διαρθρωτικές κατασκευές από χάλυβα· Σκελετοί ικριωμάτων από μέταλλο· Πλακίδια κατασκευών μεταλλικά· Πλαίσια μεταλλικά [κατασκευή]· Δομικά μέρη από μέταλλο για κτίρια και έργα πολιτικού μηχανικού· Δομικά μέρη από μέταλλο για την κατασκευή μηχανών, Συγκεκριμένα άκαμπτοι σωλήνες, Πηνία, Βαλβίδες, Αγωγοί, Αποσβεστήρες, Κρουνοί, Δίσκοι· Είδη κλειθροποιίας και σιδηροπωλείου· Μεταλλικοί σωλήνες και σωληνώσεις· Μεταλλικά χρηματοκιβώτια· Μεταλλικά προϊόντα, μη περιλαμβανόμενα σε άλλες κλάσεις, συγκεκριμένα μεταλλικές σφήνες, πείροι, δακτύλιοι, κυλινδρικά κουτιά, άγκυρες, δίχτυα, μπάρες, μεμβράνες, καλούπια, πριτσίνια, αλυσίδες (από κοινά μέταλλα), κλειδαριές, πλέγματα, πίνακες, σήραγγες, πηνία και καπάκια· Μεταλλεύματα μεταλλικά· Χάλυβα κράματα· Χάλυβας ακατέργαστος ή ημικατεργασμένος· Ψευδάργυρος· Χαλύβδινα κτίσματα· Πλάκες σιδήρου· Χαλύβδινα σύρματα· Χυτοχάλυβας, χάλυβας διαμορφωμένος με καλούπι· Χάλυβα σφαιρίδια· Χαλύβδινες ταινίες, κυκλικές στεφάνες από χάλυβα· Χάλυβα (Κατασκευές από -)· Χάλυβας διαμορφωμένος με καλούπι· Χαλύβδινοι σωλήνες· Χαλύβδινες στήλες· Χαλύβδινα σχοινιά, συρματόσκοινα από σιδερένια σύρματα· Επενδύσεις μεταλλικές για κατασκευές και οικοδομές· Μεταλλικά ράφια αποθήκευσης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Common metals and their alloys; Metal materials for building and construction; Fittings of metal for building; Building panels of metal; Buildings of metal; Buildings, transportable, of metal; Brackets of metal for building; Railway material of metal; Non-electric cables and wires of common metal; Refractory construction materials of metal; Load-bearing framework of steel; Scaffolding of metal; Tiles of metal for building; Frames of metal for building; Metal components for buildings and civil engineering structures; Components of metal for construction of machines, Namely pipes, reels, Valves, Ducts, Clack valves, Taps, Discs; Ironmongery, small items of metal hardware; Pipes and tubes of metal; Safes [metal or non-metal]; Goods of metal, not included in other classes, namely metal wedges, metal dowels, metal rings, metal tins, metal anchors, metal nets, metal billets, metal foil, metal moulds, metal rivets, chains of common metal, metal hasps, metal lattices, metal plates, metal tunnels, metal coils, and metal lids; Ores of metal; Steel alloys; Steel, unwrought or semi-wrought; Zinc; Steel buildings; Steel sheets; Steel wire; Cast, moulded, melted steel; Balls of steel; Strips of steel, rings and hoops of steel; Steel buildings; Mould castings of steel; Steel tubes; Steel masts; Ropes of steel and iron wire; Linings of metal for building; Storage racks of metal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Metales comunes y sus aleaciones; Materiales de construcción y edificación metálicos; Herrajes para la construcción; Paneles metálicos para la construcción; Construcciones metálicas; Construcciones transportables metálicas; Escuadras metálicas para la construcción; Materiales metálicos para vías férreas; Cables e hilos metálicos no eléctricos; Materiales de construcción refractarios metálicos; Estructuras de carga de acero; Andamios metálicos; Azulejos metálicos para la construcción; Estructuras metálicas para la construcción; Partes estructurales metálicas de construcciones y estructuras de ingeniería civil; Componentes de metal para la construcción de máquinas, En concreto tubos, Bobinas, Válvulas, Tuberías, Válvulas de tachuela, Grifos, Discos; Artículos de cerrajería y ferretería metálicos; Tubos y tuberías metálicos; Cajas de caudales [metálicas o no metálicas]; Productos de metal, siempre que no estén contenidos en otras clases, en concreto cuñas, tacos, anillos, latas, anclas, redes, barras, láminas, moldes, remaches, cadenas (de metales comunes), goznes, rejillas, paneles, túneles, bobinas y tapas de metal; Minerales metalíferos; Aleaciones de acero; Acero en bruto o semielaborado; Zinc; Edificios de acero; Chapas de acero; Alambres de acero; Acero colado, moldeado, fundido; Canicas de acero; Flejes de acero, círculos y cercos de acero; Construcciones de acero; Acero moldeado; Tuberías de acero; Mástiles de acero; Cuerdas y cordajes de acero y de alambre de hierro; Revestimientos interiores metálicos para la construcción; Estanterías de almacén que no sean metálicas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Lihtmetallide sulamid; Metallist ehitusmaterjalid; Metallist ehitustarvikud; Metallist ehituspaneelid; Metallist ehitised, tarindid; Teisaldatavad metallehitised, -tarindid; Metallist ehitustoendid; Rööbasteede metallmaterjal; Lihtmetallist trossid ja traadid, v.a elektrilised; Metallist kuumuskindlad ehitusmaterjalid; Kandvad teraskonstruktsioonid; Metalltellingud; Ehitiste metallvoodrid, -katted; Metallist ehitusraamid; Hoonete ja tsiviilehitusrajatiste metallist ehitusdetailid; Masinaehituse metalldetailid, Nimelt torud, Rullid, Klapid, Torustikud, Sallid, Ventiilid (kraanid), Kettad; Rauakaubad, väikesed metallkaubad; Metalltorud; Metallist või muust materjalist seifid; Metallist kaubad, mis ei kuulu teistesse klassidesse, nimelt metallkiilud, -tüüblid, -rõngad, -karbid, -ankrud, -võrgud, -valandid, -fooliumid, -vormid, -needid, -ketid (lihtmetallidest), -hasplid, -võred, -tahvlid, -tunnelid, -poolid ja -kaaned; Metallimaagid; Terasesulamid, legeeritud teras; Teras (Töötlemata või osaliselt töödeldud); Tsink; Terashooned; Lehtteras; Terastraat; Valatud, vormitud, sulatatud teras; Terasest kuulid; Teraseribad, terasrõngad ja -seibid; Terasehitised, terastarindid; Vormvaluteras; Terastorud; Terasmastid; Terasest ja terastraadist köied ja taglased; Ehitiste metallist vooderdised; Metallist hoiuriiulid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Epäjalot metallit ja niiden seokset; Metalliset rakennustarvikkeet; Metallihelat rakentamiseen; Rakennuslevyt, metalliset; Rakennukset, metalliset; Siirrettävät metalliset rakennukset; Metalliulokkeet rakentamiseen; Metallitarvikkeet rautatiekiskoja varten; Ei-sähköiset kaapelit ja langat epäjalosta metallista; Tulenkestävät rakennusaineet, metalliset; Kantavat teräsrakenteet; Metalliset rakennustelineet; Metallilaatat rakentamiseen; Metalliset rakennusrungot; Metalliset rakenneosat rakennuksiin ja insinööritöihin; Rakenneosat metallista koneiden rakentamiseen, Nimittäin putket, Kelat, Venttiilit, Johdot, Kostuttimet, Hanat, Levyt; Rautatavarat, pienet metalliesineet; Metalliputket; Kassakaapit [metalliset tai ei-metalliset]; Metalliset tavarat, jotka eivät sisälly muihin luokkiin, nimittäin metallikiilat, -tulpat, -renkaat, -rasiat, -ankkurit, -verkot, -harkot, -kalvot, -muotit, -niitit, -ketjut (epäjaloista metalleista), -sinkilät, -ristikot, -taulut, -tunnelit, -kelat ja -kannet; Malmit; Teräslejeeringit [-seokset]; Teräs, käsittelemättömänä tai puolivalmisteena; Sinkki; Teräsrakennelmat; Teräslevyt; Teräslanka; Valuteräs, teräsvalu, valettu teräs; Teräskuulat; Teräsnauhat, teräsrenkaat ja -vanteet; Teräsrakennelmat; Teräsvalu; Teräsputket; Teräsmastot; Kudokset ja köydet teräksestä ja rautalangasta; Suojaverhoukset rakennuksiin, metalliset; Metalliset varastotelineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Métaux communs et leurs alliages; Matériaux métalliques pour la construction; Ferrures pour la construction; Panneaux métalliques pour la construction; Constructions métalliques; Constructions transportables métalliques; Équerres métalliques pour la construction; Matériaux pour voies ferrées métalliques; Câbles et fils métalliques non électriques; Matériaux de construction réfractaires métalliques; Structures porteuses en acier; Échafaudages métalliques; Carreaux métalliques pour la construction; Châssis métalliques pour la construction; Composants en métal pour bâtiments et structures de génie civil; Pièces en métal pour la construction de machines, À savoir tuyaux, Bobines, Vannes, Conduites, Clapets, Robinets, Disques; Serrurerie et quincaillerie métalliques; Tuyaux et tubes métalliques; Coffres-forts [métalliques ou non métalliques]; Produits en métal, non compris dans d'autres classes, à savoir cales, chevilles, bagues, boîtes, ancres, filets, barres, feuilles, moules, rivets, chaînes (en métaux communs), gonds, grilles, tableaux, tunnels, bobines et couvercles en métal; Minerais métalliques; Alliages d'acier; Acier brut ou mi-ouvré; Zinc; Bâtiments en acier; Tôles d'acier; Fils d'acier; Acier coulé, moulé, fondu; Billes d'acier; Bandes d'acier, cercles et cerceaux en acier; Constructions en acier; Moulage en acier; Tuyaux d'acier; Mâts en acier; Cordes et cordages en acier et en fil de fer; Revêtements de doublage métalliques pour la construction; Étagères de rangement métalliques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Obični metali i njihove legure; Metalni građevinski i konstrukcijski materijali; Okovi za građevinske potrebe; Metalne ploče za građevinu; Metalne građevine; Prenosive građevinske metalne strukture; Metalni kutnici za graditeljstvo; Metalni materijali za tračnice; Neelektrični kablovi i žice od neplemenitog materijala; Vatrostalni metalni građevinski materijali; Građevinske čelične konstrukcije; Metalni okvir skela; Pločice (metalne pločice za gradnju); Metalne oplate za građevinarstvo; Metalne komponente za zgrade i inženjerske konstrukcije; Elementi od metala za gradnju strojeva, Naime cijevi, Vitla, Ventili, Vodovi, Šiltovi, Kape, Ploče; Željezarija, sitni metalni predmeti; Metalne cijevi; Sefovi [metalni ili nemetalni]; Metalni proizvodi koji nisu obuhvaćeni ostalim razredima, i to metalni klinovi, zatici, prsteni, kutije, sidra, mreže, poluge, folije, kalupi, zakovice, lanci (od neplemenitih metala), preklopci, rešetke, ploče, tuneli, kalemi i poklopci; Metalna ruda; Legure čelika; Čelik, sirovi ili poluobrađeni; Cink; Čelične konstrukcije; Čelični lim; Čelična žica; Lijevani čelik, oblikovani lijevani čelik, čelični lijev; Čelične kuglice; Trakasti čelik, obruč, trake od čelika; Metalne konstrukcije; Oblikovani lijevani čelik; Čelične cijevi; Čelični jarboli; Užad i debela brodska užad od čelika i željezne žice; Građevinske metalne obloge; Metalne skladišne police.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Közönséges fémek és ezek ötvözetei; Fémanyagok építéshez és építkezéshez; Fémszerelvények építményekhez; Építőelemek fémből; Fémépítmények; Hordozható, mobil fémszerkezetek; Csőbilincsek, konzolok építményekhez; Fémanyagok vasúti vágányokhoz; Nem elektromos fémkábelek és fémvezetékek; Tűzálló építőanyagok fémből; Teherhordó acélszerkezet; Vázas fémállványzatok; Burkolólapok fémből, épületekhez; Fém vázszerkezetek, keretek építéshez; Fém szerkezeti alkatrészek épületekhez és mérnöki szerkezetekhez; Fém szerkezeti elemek gépek megépítéséhez, Nevezetesen csövek, Tekercsek, Szelepek, Vezetékek, Csappantyúk, Csapok, Lemezek; Lakatosipari termékek, fém tömegcikkek; Fémcsövek és csővezetékek; Széfek [fém vagy nem fém]; Áruk fémből, amennyiben nem tartoznak más osztályokba, mégpedig fémből készült ékek, dübelek, gyűrűk, dobozok, horgonyok, hálók, rudak, fóliák, formák, szegecsek, láncok (nem nemesfémekből), lakatok, rácsok, táblák, hengerek, tekercsek és fedelek; Fémércek; Acélötvözetek; Acél nyers vagy félig megmunkált állapotban; Cink; Épületek acélból; Acéllemezek; Acélhuzalok; Öntött, formaöntött, olvasztott acél; Acélgolyók; Acélszalagok, acélkarikák és -abroncsok; Építmények acélból; Öntött acél; Acélcsövek; Acélrudak; Kötelek és kötélzetek acélból és vashuzalból; Fémburkolatok építményekhez; Fém tárolópolcok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Metalli comuni e loro leghe; Materiali metallici per l'edilizia e la costruzione; Guarnizioni in ferro per la costruzione; Pannelli in metallo per la costruzione; Costruzioni metalliche; Costruzioni metalliche trasportabili; Mensole in metallo [costruzione]; Materiale per strade ferrate [in metallo]; Cavi e fili metallici non elettrici; Materiali da costruzione refrattari in metallo; Costruzioni di sostegno in acciaio; Impalcature metalliche; Piastrelle/mattonelle in metallo per la costruzione; Telai metallici per la costruzione; Elementi strutturali in metallo per edifici e opere d'ingegneria civile; Componenti metallici per la costruzione di macchine, Ovvero tubi, Bobine, Valvole, Condutture, Valvole, Rubinetti, Dischi; Serrami e chincaglieria metallica; Tubi e condotte metalliche; Casseforti [metalliche o non metalliche]; Prodotti in metallo, non compresi in altre classi ovvero cunei, tasselli, anelli, scatole, ancore, reti, barre, pellicole, stampi, rivetti e catene di metallo (in metalli comuni), cardini, griglie, tavole, tunnel, bobine e coperchi in metallo; Minerali grezzi metallici; Leghe d'acciaio; Acciaio grezzo o semilavorato; Zinco; Edifici in acciaio; Lamiere d'acciaio; Fili d'acciaio; Acciaio colato, molato, fuso; Palle d'acciaio; Moiette d'accaio, cerchi in acciaio; Costruzioni in acciaio; Acciaio molato; Tubi d'acciaio; Pali d'acciaio; Corde e funi in acciaio e in fil di ferro; Rivestimenti metallici per la costruzione; Scaffalature in metallo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Netaurieji metalai ir jų lydiniai; Metalinės statybinės medžiagos; Metalinė statybinė armatūra; Metaliniai statybiniai skydai; Metaliniai statiniai; Kilnojamieji metaliniai statiniai; Metaliniai statybų kronšteinai; Metalinės geležinkelio tiesimo medžiagos; Neelektriniai metaliniai lynai ir viela; Ugniai atsparios metalinės statybinės medžiagos; Plieninės karkasų konstrukcijos; Metaliniai pastoliai; Metalinės statybinės plytelės; Metaliniai statybiniai karkasai; Metaliniai pastatų ir inžinerinių statinių komponentai; Metalinės sudėtinės dalys mašinų montavimo reikmėms, Būtent vamzdžiai, Ritės, Vožtuvai, Pypkės, Duslintuvai, Čiaupai, Diskai; Smulkūs geležies dirbiniai ir smulkios metalinės detalės; Metaliniai vamzdžiai; Seifai [metaliniai ar ne metaliniai]; Metaliniai gaminiai, nepriskirti prie kitų klasių, būtent metaliniai pleištai, kaiščiai, žiedai, skardinės, inkarai, tinklai, luitai, plėvelės, formos, kniedės, grandinės (iš nebrangiųjų metalų), skląsčiai, grotelės, lentelės, tuneliai, ritės ir dangteliai; Metalų rūdos; Plieno lydiniai; Plienas (Neapdirbtas ar iš dalies apdirbtas -); Cinkas; Statiniai iš plieno; Plieno lakštai; Geležinė viela; Lydytas, nulietas, ištirpdintas plienas; Plieniniai rutuliai; Plieninės juostos, apskritimai ir lankai iš plieno; Plieniniai pastatai; Plieno liejiniai; Plieniniai vamzdžiai; Plieniniai stiebai; Lynai ir virvės iš plieno bei geležinė viela; Metalinės pastatų dangos; Metalinės saugojimo lentynos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Parastie metāli un to sakausējumi; Būvmateriāli un konstrukciju materiāli no metāla; Metāla furnitūra būvniecībai; Metāla paneļi būvniecībai; Metāla būves; Pārvietojamas metāla būves; Metāla kronšteini būvniecībai; Sliežu ceļu materiāli no metāla; Parastu metālu troses un stieples (ne elektriskiem nolūkiem); Ugunsizturīgi būvmateriāli no metāla; Nesošās tērauda konstrukcijas; Metāla sastatnes; Metāla flīzes būvniecībai; Metāla rāmji būvniecībai; Metāla konstrukciju daļas ēkām un civilajām inženierbūvēm; Būvelementi no metāla mašīnu būvei, Proti, caurules, Spoles, Vārsti, Caurules, Atvāžami vāki, Krāni, Diski; Būvapkalumi, atslēdznieku izstrādājumi; Metāla cauruļvadi un caurules; Metāla un nemetāliski seifi; Metālizstrādājumi, kas nav iekļauti citās klasēs, proti, metāla ķīļi, dībeļi, gredzeni, kārbas, enkuri, tīkli, stieņi, folijas, formas, kniedes, ķēdes (no parastajiem metāliem), skavas, režģi, tāfeles, kanāli, spoles un vāki; Metālu rūdas; Tērauda sakausējumi; Tērauds, neapstrādāts vai daļēji apstrādāts; Cinks; Tērauda konstrukcijas; Tērauda plātnes; Tērauda stieples; Tērauda lējumi, tērauda stiegrojums, lietais tērauds; Tērauda lodes; Tērauda loksnes, tērauda riņķi un stīpas; Tērauda būves; Formēti tērauda lējumi; Tērauda caurules; Tērauda masti; Tērauda un dzelzs drāšu stieples un troses; Metāla apdares materiāli būvniecībai; Plaukti no metāla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Metalli komuni u l-ligi tagħhom; Materjali tal-metall għall-bini u l-kostruzzjoni; Tagħmir tal-metall għall-bini; Pannelli tal-metall għall-bini; Bini tal-metall; Strutturi trasportabbli tal-metall; Mensula tal-metall għall-bini; Materjal tal-metall għall-binarji tal-ferroviji; Kejbils u wajers mhux tal-elettriku tal-metall komuni; Materjali tal-kostruzzjoni refrattarji, tal-metall; Strutturi magħmula mill-azzar għall-ġarr ta' tagħbijiet; Qafas tal-iskafolding tal-metall; Madum metalliku għall-bini; Oqfsa [strutturi] tal-metall għall-bini; Komponenti tal-metall għall-bini u strutturi tal-inġinerija ċivili; Komponenti tal-metall għall-kostruzzjoni ta' magni, Jiġifieri pajpijiet, Kolji, Valvoli, Pajpijiet, Shock absorbers, Viti, Diski; Ironmongery, oġġetti żgħar tal-metall; Pajpijiet u tubi tal-metall; Kaxxaforti [tal-metall jew mhux tal-metall]; Prodotti tal-metall, mhux inklużi fi Klassijiet oħra, jiġifieri kunjardi, kavilji, ħoloq, laned, ankri, xbieki, vireg, fojls, forom, imsiemer irbattuti, ktajjen tal-metall (ta' metalli komuni), lukketti, gradi, bords, mini, irkiekel u għotjien; Minerali tal-metall; Ligi tal-azzar; Azzar, mhux ipproċessat jew parzjalment ipproċessat; Żingu; Bini tal-azzar; Folji tal-azzar; Wajer tal-azzar; Azzar maħlul, iffurmat, fondut; Blalen tal-azzar; Tejpijiet tal-azzar, ċrieki tal-azzar; Kostruzzjoniet tal-azzar; Azzar tal-ikkastjar nodulari; Pajpijiet tal-azzar; Arbli tal-azzar; Rumnelli u ħbula tal-azzar u tal-fildiferru; Kisi minn barra tal-metall, għal kostruzzjoni u bini; Xkafef tal-metall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Onedele metalen en hun legeringen; Metalen materialen voor bouw en constructie; Beslag van metaal voor de bouw; Panelen van metaal voor de bouw; Constructies van metaal; Verplaatsbare constructies van metaal; Winkelhaken van metaal [voor de bouw]; Spoorwegmateriaal van metaal; Niet-elektrische metalen kabels en draden; Vuurvaste bouwmaterialen van metaal; Dragende staalconstructies; Steigers van metaal; Tegels van metaal, voor de bouw; Raamwerken van metaal [voor de bouw]; Componenten van metaal voor gebouwen en civieltechnische constructies; Bouwonderdelen van metaal voor de bouw van machines, Te weten buizen, Haspels, Kleppen, Leidingen, Trekregelinrichtingen, Kranen, Schijven; Slotenmakerswaren van metaal en kleinijzerwaren; Metalen buizen; Brandkasten [van metaal en niet van metaal]; Goederen van metaal, voor zover niet begrepen in andere klassen, te weten metalen keggen, deuvels, ringen, bussen, ankers, netten, staven, folies, vormen, klinknagels, kettingen (van onedele metalen), deurhengsels, roosters, panelen, tunnels, spoelen en deksels; Metaalertsen; Staallegeringen; Staal [ruw of halfbewerkt]; Zink; Gebouwen van staal; Staalplaten; Staaldraad; Gegoten staal, gietstaal, gesmolten staal; Stalen kogels; Staalband, cirkels en hoepels van staal; Staalconstructies; Gietstaal; Buizen van staal; Masten van staal; Touw en touwwerk van staal en ijzerdraad; Bekledingen van metaal, voor de bouw; Opslagstellingen van metaal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Metale nieszlachetne i ich stopy; Materiały metalowe do celów budowlanych i konstrukcyjnych; Okucia stosowane w budownictwie, metalowe; Panele konstrukcyjne metalowe; Konstrukcje metalowe; Przenośne struktury metalowe; Wsporniki metalowe dla budownictwa; Materiały metalowe do budowy szlaków kolejowych; Przewody nieelektryczne i przewody drutowe z metali nieszlachetnych; Metalowe materiały konstrukcyjne, ogniotrwałe; Stalowe konstrukcje nośne; Szkieletowe rusztowania metalowe; Płytki metalowe do użytku w budownictwie; Szkielety metalowe [budownictwo]; Elementy konstrukcyjne z metalu do budynków i inżynierii lądowej; Metalowe elementy konstrukcyjne przeznaczone do budowy maszyn, Mianowicie rury, Bębny do zwijania, Zawory, Przewody, Szale, Krany, Dyski; Drobne wyroby żelazne, pojedyncze drobne wyroby metalowe; Metalowe przewody i rury; Kasy pancerne [metalowe lub niemetalowe]; Towary z metalu, nieujęte w innych klasach, mianowicie metalowe kliny, kołki, pierścienie, puszki, kotwy, siatki, sztabki, folie, formy, nity, łańcuchy (nie z metali szlachetnych), szpule, kraty, płytki, tunele, szpule i pokrywy; Rudy metali; Stopy stali; Stal surowa lub półprzetworzona; Cynk (Zn); Budynki ze stali; Blacha stalowa cienka; Drut ze stali; Staliwo, stal odlewana, stal topiona; Kule stalowe; Taśmy stalowe, koła i obręcze stalowe; Konstrukcje stalowe [budownictwo]; Stal do odlewów kształtowych; Rury i rurki ze stali; Maszty ze stali; Liny i olinowania ze stali i drutu żelaznego; Okładziny metalowe [konstrukcyjne i budowlane]; Stojaki magazynowe metalowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Metais comuns e suas ligas; Materiais metálicos para construção; Ferragens metálicas para construção; Painéis para a construção metálicos; Construções metálicas; Construções transportáveis metálicas; Suportes [esquadros] de metal para construção; Materiais metálicos para vias férreas; Cabos e fios metálicos não eléctricos; Materiais de construção metálicos refratários; Estruturas portantes em aço; Andaimes metálicos; Ladrilhos metálicos para a construção; Caixilhos metálicos para construção; Componentes metálicos para edifícios e construções de engenharia civil; Componentes metálicos para a construção de máquinas, Especificamente tubos, Bobinas, Válvulas, Cachimbos, Válvulas de retenção, Torneiras, Disquetes; Serralharia e quinquilharia metálica; Canos e tubos metálicos; Cofres-fortes [metálicos ou não metálicos]; Produtos metálicos, não incluídos noutras classes, nomeadamente cunhas, buchas, anilhas, caixas, âncoras, redes, barras, películas, moldes, rebites, correntes (em metais comuns), gonzos, grelhas, painéis, túneis, bobinas e tampas metálicos; Minerais metálicos; Ligas de aço; Aço em bruto ou semi-forjado; Zinco; Edifícios em aço; Chapas de aço; Fios de aço; Aço vazado, moldado, fundido; Esferas de aço; Barras em aço, círculos e aros em aço; Construções em aço; Aço fundido em molde; Tubos de aço; Postes de aço; Cordas e cordames em aço e fio de ferro; Revestimentos interiores metálicos para a construção; Suportes em metal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Metale comune și aliajele lor; Materiale metalice pentru edificare și construcții; Feronerie pentru construcții; Plăci metalice de construcție; Construcții metalice; Structuri metalice transportabile; Console metalice [construcții]; Materiale pentru căile ferate; Cabluri și fire metalice neelectrice; Materiale metalice refractare pentru construcții; Structuri portante din oţel; Cadre de eșafodaj din metal; Plăci metalice pentru construcții; Cadre metalice [construcții]; Componente din metal pentru clădiri și tehnică civilă; Componente metalice pentru construcții de mașini, Şi anume ţevi, Bobine, Supape, Conducte, Amortizoare, Robinete, Şaibe; Produse de lăcătuşerie şi feronerie metalică; Țevi și tuburi metalice; Seifuri [metalice sau nemetalice]; Produse metalice, necuprinse în alte clase, și anume pene, dibluri, inele, cutii, ancore, plase, bare, folii, forme, nituri, lanțuri (din metale comune), cleme, grilaje, panouri, tuneluri, bobine și capace metalice; Minereuri metalifere; Oțel (Aliaje de -); Oţel brut sau semifabricat; Zinc; Clădiri din oţel; Oțel (Table din -); Oțel (Sârme din -); Oţel turnat, matriţat, topit; Bile de oțel; Benzi de oţel, cercuri şi inele din oţel; Construcții din oțel; Oţel de turnat în forme; Oțel (Țevi din -); Oțel (Stâlpi din -); Corzi şi funii din oţel şi din fir de fier; Căptușeli metalice [construcții]; Polite pentru depozitare din metal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Obyčajné kovy a ich zliatiny; Kovové materiály pre stavebníctvo; Kovania pre stavebníctvo; Kovové stavebné panely; Kovové stavebné konštrukcie; Kovové prenosné stavby; Kovové uholníky pre stavebníctvo; Kovové materiály na železničné trate; Káble a drôty z obyčajných kovov s výnimkou elektrických; Žiaruvzdorné kovové stavebné materiály; nosné oceľové konštrukcie; Kovové lešenia; Kovové obkladačky pre stavebníctvo; Kovové kostry stavieb; Kovové stavebné diely pre budovy a inžinierske stavby; Komponenty z kovu na stavbu strojov, Menovite rúry, Cievky, Ventily, Fajky, Teplé šály, Kohútiky, Disky; Železiarsky tovar, drobný železiarsky tovar; Kovové potrubia a rúry; Trezory (kovové alebo nekovové); Tovary z kovu, ktoré nie sú zaradené do iných tried, menovite kovové kliny, rozperky, krúžky, kapsuly, kotvy, siete, ingoty, fólie, formy, nity, reťaze (z obyčajných kovov), závory, mreže, panely, tunely, cievky, a poklopy; Kovové rudy; Zliatiny ocele; Oceľ nespracovaná alebo ako polotovar; Zinok; Oceľové stavby; Oceľový plech; Oceľový drôt; Liata oceľ, liata oceľ, plávková oceľ; Oceľové guľky; Oceľové pásy, oceľové kruhy a obruče; Oceľové stavebné konštrukcie; Oceľ na odliatky; Oceľové rúrky; Oceľové stožiare; Laná a povrazy z ocele a železného drôtu; Kovové obklady pre stavebníctvo; Skladovacie regály z kovu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Navadne kovine in njihove zlitine; Kovinski materiali za stavbeništvo in gradbeništvo; Oprema iz kovine za gradbeništvo; Gradbene plošče iz kovine; Zgradbe iz kovine; Prenosne kovinske strukture; Kovinski nosilci za gradbeništvo; Kovinski materiali za železniške tračnice; Neelektrični kabli in žice iz nežlahtnih kovin; Kovinski ognjevzdržni gradbeni materiali; Nosilne jeklene konstrukcije; Kovinsko ogrodje za gradbeni oder; Kovinske ploščice za gradbeništvo; Okvirji iz kovine za gradbeništvo; Sestavni deli iz kovine za zgradbe in inženirske strukture; Kovinski konstrukcijski deli za izdelavo strojev, In sicer cevi, Tuljave, Ventili, Pipe, Palčniki (rokavice), Pipe, Diski; Ključavničarski izdelki in drobni kovinski predmeti; Kovinske cevi; Sefi [kovinski ali nekovinski]; Blago iz kovine, ki ga ne obsegajo drugi razredi, in sicer kovinske zagozde, čepi, obroči, doze, sidra, mreže, palice, folije, forme, zakovice, verige (iz navadnih kovin), vretena, rešetke, plošče, tuneli, tulci in pokrovi; Kovinske rude; Jeklene zlitine; Jeklo, nepredelano ali delno predelano; Cink; Stavbe iz jekla; Jeklena pločevina; Jeklena žica; Lito, ulito, taljeno jeklo; Krogle iz jekla; Jekleni trakovi, obodi in obroči iz jekla; Jeklene zgradbe (konstrukcije); Oblikovano jeklo; Jeklene cevi; Jekleni stebri; Vrvi in vrvi iz jekla in iz jeklene žice; Obloge iz kovine za konstrukcijo in gradbeništvo; Čepi iz kovine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Oädla metaller och deras legeringar; Material av metall för byggnation och konstruktion; Metallbeslag för byggnader; Byggpaneler av metall; Byggnader av metall; Flyttbara byggnadskonstruktioner av metall; Vinkelstöttor av metall för byggnation; Material av metall för järnvägsspår; Icke-elektriska kablar och metalltrådar; Eldfasta byggmaterial av metall; Bärande stålkonstruktioner; Stommar för byggnadsställningar av metall; Plattor av metall för byggnation; Ramar av metall för byggnation; Konstruktionsdelar av metall för byggnader och ingenjörskonstruktioner; Byggnadsdelar av metall för konstruktion av maskiner, Nämligen rör, Spolar, Ventiler, Ledningar, Spjäll, Kranar, Skivor; Små smidesvaror av järn och metall; Rör och rörledningar av metall; Kassaskåp [av metall eller inte av metall]; Varor av metall, ej ingående i andra klasser, nämligen metallkilar, -pluggar, -ringar, -dosor, -ankare, -nät, -tackor, -folier, -formar, -nitar, -kedjor (av oädla metaller), -haspar, -galler, -tavlor, -tunnlar, -spolar och -lock; Malmer av metall; Stållegeringar; Obearbetat eller delvis bearbetat stål; Zink; Byggnader av stål; Stålark; Ståltråd; Gjutet, format och gjutet stål; Kulor av stål; Band av stål, band och tunnband av stål; Stålbyggnader; Formgjutstål; Ståltuber; Stålmaster; Rep och linor av stål och järntråd; Inklädnader av metall för konstruktion och byggnation; Reglar av metall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>12</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Компоненти от метал за моторни превозни средства.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kovové součástky pro motorová vozidla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Komponenter af metal til motorkøretøjer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bauteile aus Metall für Kraftfahrzeuge.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δομικά μέρη από μέταλλο για μηχανοκίνητα οχήματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Components of metal for motor vehicles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Componentes metálicos para automóviles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Mootorsõidukite metalldetailid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Rakenneosat metallista moottoriajoneuvoja varten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Pièces en métal pour les véhicules motorisés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Elementi od metala za motorna vozila.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Fém szerkezeti elemek gépjárművekhez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Componenti metallici per autoveicoli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Metalinės automobilių sudėtinės dalys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Būvelementi no metāla automašīnām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Komponenti tal-metall għal vetturi bil-mutur.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Bouwonderdelen van metaal voor motorvoertuigen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Metalowe elementy konstrukcyjne przeznaczone do pojazdów silnikowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Componentes metálicos para veículos automóveis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Componente metalice pentru autovehicule.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Komponenty z kovu pre automobily.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kovinski konstrukcijski deli za motorna vozila.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Byggnadsdelar av metall för motorfordon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>14</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Благородни метали, необработени или полуобработени; Сплави от благородни метали.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Drahé kovy, surové nebo jako polotovar; Slitiny drahých kovů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Ædle metaller, uforarbejdede og halvforarbejdede; Legeringer af ædle metaller.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Edelmetalle [roh oder teilweise bearbeitet]; Legierungen aus Edelmetall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μέταλλα πολύτιμα ακατέργαστα ή ημιεπεξεργασμένα· Κράματα πολύτιμων μετάλλων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Precious metals, unwrought or semi-wrought; Alloys of precious metal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Metales preciosos en bruto o semielaborados; Aleaciones de metales preciosos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Töötlemata või pooltöödeldud väärismetallid; Väärismetallisulamid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Jalometallit, käsittelemättöminä tai puolivalmisteina; Jalometalliseokset.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Métaux précieux bruts ou mi-ouvrés; Alliages de métaux précieux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Plemeniti metali sirovi ili poluobrađeni; Legure plemenitih metala.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nyers vagy félig megmunkált nemesfémek; Nemesfém ötvözetek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Metalli preziosi grezzi o semilavorati; Leghe di metalli preziosi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Brangieji metalai (neapdirbti ar iš dalies apdirbti); Lydiniai (tauriųjų metalų).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Neapstrādāti vai daļēji apstrādāti dārgmetāli; Dārgmetālu sakausējumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Metall prezzjuż, mhux maħdum jew parzjalment maħdum; Ligi ta' metall prezzjuż.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Edele metalen, ruw of halfbewerkt; Legeringen van edele metalen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Metale szlachetne, nieprzetworzone lub półprzetworzone; Stopy metali szlachetnych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Metais preciosos em bruto ou semitrabalhados; Ligas de metais preciosos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Metale prețioase brute sau semiprelucrate; Aliaje din metale prețioase.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Drahé kovy (surovina alebo polotovar); Zliatiny drahých kovov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Žlahtne kovine, neobdelane ali polobdelane; Zlitine iz plemenitih kovin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Obearbetade eller delvis bearbetade ädelmetaller; Legeringar ädelmetall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Рекламиране и рекламни услуги; Търговска бизнес администрация; Консултиране и бизнес мениджмънт съдействие; Търговска администрация; Административна дейност; Помощ при управлението на производствени или търговски компании; Услуги за бизнес управление и организационна консултация; Съвети относно управлението на бизнеса; Професионална бизнес консултация; Услуги за организиране на изложби с търговска или рекламна цел; Организиране на салони с търговски цели; Търговия на дребно и маркетингова помощ за търговия на едро с химически продукти; Търговия на дребно и маркетингова помощ за търговия на едро с бои, Изкуствени смоли в необработено състояние, Бои и лакове, Препарати за предотвратяване на ръжда, Стоманени профили, стоманени тръби, стоманени прътове, Стоманени пръти, Стоманени греди, Стоманени скелета и Стоманени конструкции, Стоманен парапет, Стоманени решетки, Стоманени огради, Болтове, Пирони и шарнири, както и машини за металната промишленост и/или металургичната промишленост и/или желязната и стоманената промишленост; Търговия на дребно и маркетингова помощ за търговия на едро, свързани с галванични бани, соли за галванични батерии, галванични препарати, Стомана, Метали, Сгради от стомана, Жици от сплавна стомана, Чугун, Стоманени капси, стоманени ленти, гуми и ленти от стомана, въжета и кабели от стомана.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Propagace; Řízení obchodních záležitostí; Poradenství a pomoc v řízení obchodní činnosti; Obchodní administrativa; Kancelářské práce; Pomoc při řízení průmyslových nebo obchodních podniků; Poradenství v organizaci a při řízení podniků; Poradenství při vedení obchodní činnosti; Odborné poradenství pro obchodní činnost; Organizování obchodních nebo reklamních výstav; Organizování veletrhů pro komerční účely; Služby maloobchodu a pomoc při prodeji pro velkoobchod s ohledem na chemické výrobky; Služby maloobchodu a pomoc při prodeji pro velkoobchod s ohledem na nátěry, Pryskyřice, Barvy a laky, Antikorozní látky, Ocelové profily, ocelové stožáry, ocelové tyče, Ocelové stožáry, Ocelové nosníky, Ocelová leštění a Ocelové konstrukce, Ocelová zábradlí, Ocelové mřížoví, Ocelové ploty, Šrouby, Hřebíky a kloubové závěsy, jakož i stroje pro kovový průmysl a/nebo hutní průmysl a/nebo železářský průmysl; Služby maloobchodu a pomoc při prodeji pro velkoobchod s ohledem na galvanické lázně, soli pro galvanické baterie, galvanické přípravky, Ocel, Kovů, Ocelové konstrukce, Ocelový drát, Ocel na odlitky, Ocelová oka, ocelové pásy, obruče a pásy z oceli, lana a provazy z oceli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Reklamevirksomhed; Forretningsadministration; Rådgivning og bistand i forretningsledelse; Forretningsadministration; Varetagelse af kontoropgaver; Bistand ved ledelse af industri- eller handelsvirksomheder; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsorganisation og -ledelse; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsledelse; Professionel rådgivning vedrørende forretningsvirksomhed; Organisering af udstillinger med kommercielle eller reklamemæssige formål; Organisering af messer med kommercielle formål; Detailhandel og hjælp i forbindelse med markedsføring for engroshandel med kemiske produkter; Detailhandel og hjælp i forbindelse med markedsføring for engroshandel med malevarer, Harpikser, Maling og lak, Rustbeskyttelsesmidler, Stålprofiler, stålpæle, stålstænger, Stålmaster, Ståldragere, Stålstilladser og Stålkonstruktioner, Stålgelændere, Stålgitre, Stålhegn, Skruer, Søm og hængsler samt maskiner til metalindustrien og/eller højovnsindustrien og/eller jernhøjovnsindustrien; Detailhandel og hjælp i forbindelse med markedsføring for engroshandel med galvaniske bade, batterier (salte til galvaniske), galvaniske præparater, Stål, Metaller, Stålbygninger, Ståltråd, Støbestål, Såløskener, bånd af stål, dæk og bånd af stål, reb og trosser af stål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werbung; kaufmännische Geschäftsverwaltung; Beratung und Hilfe bei der Verwaltung; Unternehmensverwaltung; Büroarbeiten; Hilfe bei der Leitung von Industrie- oder Handelsunternehmen; Beratung bei der Organisation und Leitung der Geschäftstätigkeit; Beratung bei der Leitung der Geschäftstätigkeit; fachliche Beratung in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Organisation von Ausstellungen für kommerzielle oder Werbezwecke; Organisation von Fachmessen für kommerzielle Zwecke; Leistungen des Einzelhandels und Hilfe bei der Vermarktung für den Großhandel bezogen auf chemische Erzeugnisse; Leistungen des Einzelhandels und Hilfe bei der Vermarktung für den Großhandel bezogen auf Anstriche, Harze, Farben, Lacke, Korrosionsschutzmittel, Stahlprofile, Stahlpfähle, Stahlstangen, Stahlmasten, Stahlträger, Stahlgerüste und Stahlkonstruktionen, Stahlgeländer, Stahlgitterroste, Stahlzäune, Schrauben, Nägel und Scharniere sowie Maschinen für die Metallindustrie und/oder die Hüttenindustrie und/oder die Eisenhüttenindustrie; Leistungen des Einzelhandels und Hilfe bei der Vermarktung für den Großhandel bezogen auf galvanische Bäder, Salze für galvanische Batterien, galvanische Präparate, Stahl, Metalle, Stahlbauten, Stahldraht, Stahlguss, Stahlösen, Stahlbänder, Reifen und Bänder aus Stahl, Seile und Trossen aus Stahl.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαφήμιση· Διαχείριση εμπορικών επιχειρήσεων· Συμβουλευτικές υπηρεσίες και βοήθεια κατά τη διαχείριση της εμπορικής δραστηριότητας· Διαχείριση επιχειρήσεων· Εργασίες γραφείου· Υποστήριξη κατά τη διεύθυνση βιομηχανικών ή εμπορικών επιχειρήσεων· Συμβουλευτικές υπηρεσίες σε θέματα οργάνωσης και διοίκησης επιχειρήσεων· Παροχή συμβουλών κατά τη διεύθυνση επιχειρηματικής δραστηριότητας· Παροχή επαγγελματικών συμβουλών σε θέματα επιχειρήσεων· Διοργάνωση εκθέσεων για εμπορικούς ή διαφημιστικούς σκοπούς· Διοργάνωση εκθεσιακών σαλονιών για εμπορικούς σκοπούς· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης και υπηρεσίες παροχής βοηθείας σε θέματα εμπορευματοποίησης για το χονδρικό εμπόριο, παρεχόμενες σε σχέση με χημικά προϊόντα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης και υπηρεσίες παροχής βοηθείας σε θέματα εμπορευματοποίησης για το χονδρικό εμπόριο, παρεχόμενες σε σχέση με βαφές, Ρητίνες, Χρώματα και λάκες, Μέσα προφυλάξεως κατά της διάβρωσης, Χαλύβδινες διατομές, χαλύβδινους πασσάλους, χαλύβδινες ράβδους, Χαλύβδινοι πάσσαλοι, Χαλύβδινες δοκοί, Χαλύβδινα ικριώματα και Χαλύβδινες κατασκευές, Χαλύβδινα κιγκλιδώματα, Χαλύβδινα πλέγματα, Περιφράξεις από χάλυβα, Κοχλίες, Ήλους και μεντεσέδες καθώς και μηχανές για τη μεταλλουργία και/ή τη μεταλλουργική βιομηχανία και/ή τη βιομηχανία χυτηρίων σιδήρου· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης και υπηρεσίες παροχής βοηθείας σε θέματα εμπορευματοποίησης για το χονδρικό εμπόριο, παρεχόμενες σε σχέση με γαλβανικά λουτρά, άλατα για γαλβανικές μπαταρίες, γαλβανικά παρασκευάσματα, Χάλυβας, Μέταλλα, Κατασκευές από χάλυβα, Ατσαλόσυρμα, Χυτός χάλυβας, Χαλύβδινους δακτυλίους, χαλύβδινες ταινίες, επίσωτρα και ταινίες από χάλυβα, σχοινιά και συρματόσχοινα από χάλυβα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Advertising; Managing commercial business; Business management consultancy and assistance; Business administration; Office functions; Assistance in the management of industrial or commercial enterprises; Business management and organisation consultancy; Advice on the management of business activities; Professional business consultancy; Arranging of exhibitions for commercial or advertising purposes; Arranging of trade shows for commercial purposes; Retailing and marketing assistance for wholesaling relating to chemical preparations; Retailing and marketing assistance for wholesaling relating to paints, resins, paints and lacquers, Anti-corrosive preparations, Steel sections, steel poles, steel bars, Steel poles, Steel girders, Steel towers and Steel work, Steel railings, Steel grating, Steel fences, screws, Nails and journals and machines for the metal industry and/or the metallurgical industry and/or the steel industry; Retailing and marketing assistance for wholesaling relating to galvanic baths, salts for galvanic batteries, galvanic preparations, Steel, Metals, Steel buildings, steel wire, Cast steel, Steel rings, steel strips, hoops and strips of steel, ropes and hawsers of steel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicidad; Administración de negocios comerciales; Asesoramiento y asistencia para la dirección de los negocios; Administración de negocios; Trabajos de oficina; Asistencia en la gestión de empresas industriales o comerciales; Servicio de asesoramiento para la organización y dirección de negocios; Consultoría en materia de dirección de negocios; Consultoría profesional de negocios; Organización de exposición con fines comerciales o publicitarios; Organización de salones con fines comerciales; Servicios minoristas y ayuda para la comercialización para el comercio mayorista en relación con productos químicos; Servicios minoristas y ayuda para la comercialización para el comercio mayorista en relación con pinturas, Resinas, Colores y lacas, Productos anticorrosivos, Perfiles acanalados de acero, postes de acero, barras de acero, Mástiles de acero, Vigas de acero, Torres de acero y Construcciones de acero, Barandillas de acero, Rejillas de acero, Verjas de acero, Tornillos, Clavos y bisagras, así como máquinas para la industria del metal y/o la industria metalúrgica y/o la industria siderúrgica; Servicios minoristas y ayuda en la comercialización para el comercio mayorista en relación con baños de galvanización, sales para baterías galvánicas, preparados galvánicos, Acero, metales, Construcciones de acero, Alambre de acero, Fundición de acero, Argollas de acero, cintas de acero, neumáticos y cintas de acero, cuerdas y cabos de acero.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reklaam; Kaubanduslik ärihaldus; Nõustamine ja abi äritegevuse juhtimisel; Ärijuhtimine; Kontoriteenused; Tööstus- või äriettevõtete juhtimisabi; Ärijuhtimise alased nõustamisteenused; Äritegevuse juhtimise konsultatsioonid; Professionaalne ärikonsultatsioon; Kaubandus- või reklaamiotstarbeliste näituste korraldamine; Kaubandusotstarbeliste esitluste korraldamine; Jaemüügiteenused ja hulgimüügi turundusabi seoses järgmiste kaupadega: kemikaalid; Jaemüügiteenused ja hulgimüügi turundusabi seoses järgmiste kaupadega: värvid, Vaigud, Värvid ja lakid, Korrosioonitõrjevahendid, Terasprofiilid, teraspostid, terasvardad, Terasmastid, Terastalad, Terastellingud ja Terastarindid, Teraspiirded, Terasrestid, Terasaiad, Kruvid, Naelad ja liigendid, samuti metallitööstuse ja/või sulatustööstuse ja/või rauasulatustööstuse masinad; Jaemüügiteenused ja hulgimüügi turundusabi seoses järgmiste kaupadega: galvaanimisvannid, galvaaniliste patareide soolad, galvaanipreparaadid, Teras, Metallid, Terasehitised, terastarindid, Terastraat, Terasevalandid, terasevalu, Terasaasad, lintteras, terasvõrud ja -lindid, terasköied ja -trossid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mainonta; Kaupallinen liikkeen hallinnointi; Yrityskonsultointi ja johdon neuvonta; Yrityshallinto; Toimistotehtävät; Avustaminen teollisuus- tai kauppayritysten johdossa; Liiketoiminnan organisointiin ja liikkeenjohtoon liittyvät neuvontapalvelut; Neuvonta liiketoiminnan johdossa; Ammattimainen liikkeenjohdon konsultointi; Näyttelyjen järjestäminen kaupallisiin tai mainontatarkoituksiin; Messujen järjestäminen kaupallisiin tarkoituksiin; Vähittäiskaupan palvelut ja avustaminen tukkukaupan markkinoinnissa liittyen seuraaviin: kemialliset tuotteet; Vähittäiskaupan palvelut ja avustaminen tukkukaupan markkinoinnissa liittyen seuraaviin: maalit, Hartsit, Maalit ja lakat, Korroosionestoaineet, Teräsprofiilit, teräspaalut, terästangot, Teräspaalut, Teräskannatinpalkit, Terästelineet ja Teräsrakenteet, Teräskaiteet, Teräsristikot, Teräsaidat, Ruuvit, Naulat ja saranat sekä koneet metalliteollisuuteen ja/tai sulattoteollisuuteen ja/tai rauta- ja terästeollisuuteen; Vähittäiskaupan palvelut ja avustaminen tukkukaupan markkinoinnissa liittyen seuraaviin: galvaaniset kylvyt, suolat galvaanisiin akkuihin, galvaaniset valmisteet, Teräs, Metallit, Teräsrakennukset, Teräslanka, Teräsvalut, Terässilmukat, teräsnauhat, teräsrenkaat ja -vanteet, teräsköydet ja -kaapelit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publicité; Gestion des affaires commerciales; Conseils et assistance en gestion d'activités commerciales; Administration commerciale; Travaux de bureau; Aide à la direction d'entreprises industrielles et commerciales; Service de conseil en organisation et direction des affaires; Conseil lors de la direction d'activités commerciales; Consultation professionnelle d'affaire; organisation d ‘exposition à but commercial ou de publicité; organisation de salons à des fins commerciales; Services de vente au détail et assistance à la commercialisation pour la vente en gros en relation avec des produits chimiques; Services de vente au détail et assistance à la commercialisation pour la vente en gros en relation avec des peintures, Résines, Couleurs et laques, Produits anti-corrosion, Profilés en acier, piquets en acier, barres en acier, Mâts en acier, Poutres en acier, Échafaudages en acier et Fabrications en acier, Rambardes en acier, Grilles en acier, Clôtures en acier, Vis, Clous et charnières ainsi que machines pour l'industrie métallurgique et/ou industrie de l'acier et/ou sidérurgie; Services de vente au détail en commerces et assistance à la commercialisation pour la vente en gros en relation avec des bains de galvanisation, sels pour batteries galvaniques, préparations galvaniques, Acier, Métaux, Constructions en acier, Fils d´aciers, Fonte d'acier, Œillets en acier, bandes d'acier, cerceaux et bandes en acier, cordes et tresses en acier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Oglašavanje; Komercijalno poslovno upravljanje; Savjetovanje i pomoć u vođenju gospodarske djelatnosti; Upravljanje poduzećima; Uredski poslovi; Pomoć pri vođenju industrijskih ili trgovačkih poduzeća; Savjeti o organizaciji i vođenju poslova; Savjetovanje pri vođenju poslovne djelatnosti; Stručne poslovne konzultacije; Organiziranje izložbi u komercijalne ili reklamne svrhe; Organiziranje sajmova za komercijalne potrebe; Usluge maloprodaje i pomoć prilikom marketinga za veleprodaju u vezi s kemijskim proizvodima; Usluge maloprodaje i pomoć prilikom marketinga za veleprodaju u vezi s premazima, Smole, Boje i lakovi, Antikorozivni proizvodi, Čelični profili, čelični stupovi, čelične šipke, Čelični jarboli [potpornji], Uzdužne grede od čelika, Čelične skele i Čelične konstrukcije, Čelične ograde, Čelične rešetke, Čelične ograde, Vijci, Čavli i šarke te strojevi za metalnu industriju i/ili metaluršku industriju i/ili industriju željeza i čelika; Usluge maloprodaje i pomoć prilikom veleprodaje u vezi s galvanskim kupkama, solima za galvanske baterije, galvanskim pripravcima, Čelik, Metala, Čeličnim konstrukcijama, Čelična žica, Čelik (lijevani čelik), Čeličnim ušicama, čeličnim trakama, obručima i trakama od čelika, užadi i brodskom užadi od čelika.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hirdetési- és reklámszolgáltatások; Kereskedelmi ügyletek intézése; Tanácsadás és segítségnyújtás üzleti tevékenység irányításában; Üzleti adminisztráció; Irodai munkák; Ipari- vagy kereskedelmi vállalatok irányításával kapcsolatos segítségnyújtás; Üzletszervezési és -vezetési tanácsadás; Üzleti tevékenység vezetésével kapcsolatos tanácsadás; Professzionális üzleti szaktanácsadás; Kereskedelmi vagy reklámcélú kiállítások szervezése; Szakkiállítások szervezése kereskedelmi céllal; Kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások és segítségnyújtás a következők nagykereskedelmi értékesítésében: vegyi termékek; Kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások és segítségnyújtás a következők nagykereskedelmi értékesítésében: festékek, Gyanták, Festékek és lakkok, Korróziógátló készítmények, Acélprofilok, acélcölöpök, acélrudak, Acélrudak, Acélgerendák, Acélállványok és Acélszerkezetek, Acélkorlátok, Acélrács, Acélkerítések, Csavarok, Szögek és zsanérok, valamint fémipari és/vagy kohászati és/vagy vaskohászati gépek; Kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások és segítségnyújtás a következők nagykereskedelmi értékesítésében: galván fürdők, sók galván elemekhez, galván készítmények, Acél, Fémek, Építmények acélból, Acélhuzalok, Öntött acél, Acélszemek, acélszalagok, pántok és szalagok acélból, kötelek és sodronyok acélból.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicità; Gestione degli affari commerciali; Consulenza e assistenza nella direzione d'affari commerciali; Amministrazione commerciale; Lavori di ufficio; Assistenza nella direzione d'imprese industriali o commerciali; Consulenza relativa all'organizzazione e alla direzione aziendale; Consulenza nella direzione dell'attività societaria; Consulenza professionale in materia d'affari; Organizzazione d'esposizioni per scopi commerciali o pubblicitari; Organizzazione di saloni per scopi commerciali; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio e assistenza alla commercializzazione per la vendita all'ingrosso di prodotti chimici; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio e assistenza alla messa in commercio per la vendita all'ingrosso di vernici, Resine, Colori e lacche, Prodotti contro la corrosione, Profili in acciaio, pali in acciaio, tondini in acciaio, Pali d'acciaio, Travi in acciaio, Ponteggi in acciaio e Costruzioni in acciaio, Ringhiera in acciaio, Grate in acciaio, Recinzioni in acciaio, Viti, Chiodi e cerniere e macchine per l'industria metallurgica e/o dell'acciaio e/o siderurgica; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio e assistenza alla messa in commercio per la vendita all'ingrosso dì bagni galvanici, sali per batterie galvaniche, preparati galvanici, Acciaio, Metalli, Costruzioni in acciaio, Fili d'acciaio, Colate d'acciaio, Occhielli d'acciaio, cinghie d'acciaio, pneumatici e nastri d'acciaio, funi e cavi d'acciaio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Reklama; Komercinis verslo administravimas; Patariamoji veikla ir pagalba komercinėje veikloje; Verslo tvarkyba; Įstaigų veikla; Pagalba vadovaujant pramonės arba prekybos įmonėms; Konsultacijos verslo organizavimo ir vadybos klausimais; Konsultacijos vadovaujant verslo veiklai; Profesionalus verslo konsultavimas; Parodų komerciniams ir reklaminiams tikslams organizavimas; Parodų organizavimas komerciniais tikslais; Mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos ir pagalba vykdant didmeninę prekybą, susijusią su chemijos produktais; Mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos ir pagalba vykdant didmeninę prekybą, susijusią su dažais, Dervos, Dažai ir lakas, Antikorozinės medžiagos, Plieniniais profiliais, plieniniais stulpais, plieniniais strypais, Plieniniai stiebai, Plieno strypai, Plieniniais pastoliais ir Plieniniai pastatai, Plieniniais turėklais, Plieninės grotos, Plieninės tvoros, Varžtai, Vinimis ir lankstais bei mašinomis metalo pramonės ir / arba liejyklų pramonės, ir / arba geležies dirbinių pramonės reikmėms; Mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos ir pagalba vykdant didmeninę prekybą, susijusią su galvanizavimo vonelėmis, galvaninių elementų druska, galvaniniais preparatais, Plienas, Metalais, Plieniniai pastatai, Plieninė viela, Plieno liejiniai, Plieninėmis kilputėmis, plieno juostomis, padangomis ir juostomis iš plieno, lynais ir trosais iš plieno.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reklāma; Komerciāla uzņēmumu pārvaldīšana; Konsultācijas un palīdzība uzņēmējdarbības vadībā; Uzņēmumu pārvaldīšana; Biroja darbi; Palīdzība rūpniecības vai tirdzniecības uzņēmumu vadībā; Uzņēmējdarbības vadības konsultēšana; Konsultācijas uzņēmējdarbības vadībā; Profesionālā uzņēmējdarbības konsultēšana; Izstāžu organizēšana komerciālos vai reklāmas nolūkos; Sarīkojumu organizēšana komerciālos nolūkos; Mazumtirdzniecības darbības un atbalsts tirdzniecības veicināšanā vairumtirdzniecībā attiecībā uz ķīmiskajiem izstrādājumiem; Mazumtirdzniecības darbības un atbalsts tirdzniecības veicināšanā vairumtirdzniecībā attiecībā uz krāsām, Sveķi, Krāsas un lakas, Antikorozīvi, Profilēti tērauda izstrādājumi, tērauda pāļi, tērauda stieņi, Tērauda masti, Tērauda stieņi, Tērauda sastatnes un Tērauda būves, Tērauda margas, Tērauda režģis, Tērauda žogi, Skrūves, Naglas un eņģes, kā arī mašīnas metālražošanas nozarei un/vai metalurģijas nozarē, un/vai dzelzs metalurģijas nozarē; Mazumtirdzniecības darbības un atbalsts tirdzniecības veicināšanā vairumtirdzniecībā attiecībā uz galvaniskajām vannām, sāļiem galvaniskajām baterijām, galavaniskajiem izstrādājumiem, Tērauds, Metāli, Tērauda būves, Tērauda stieple, Tērauda lējums, Tērauda cilpas, tērauda lentes, riepas un saites no tērauda, virves un troses no tērauda.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reklamar; Ġestjoni ta' negozju kummerċjali; Pariri u għajnuna fil-ġestjoni ta' attività tan-negozju; Amministrazzjoni ta' negozju; Funzjonijiet ta' uffiċċju; Assistenza fit-tmexxija ta' intrapriżi industrijali jew kummerċjali; Servizz ta' konsulenza fl-organizzazzjoni u fil-ġestjoni ta' negozju; Konsulenza fit-tmexxija tal-attività tan-negozju; Konsulenza professjonali dwar in-negozju; L-organizzazzjoni ta' esebizzjonijiet għal skopijiet kummerċjali jew ta' reklamar; Organizzazzjoni ta' fieri għal skopijiet kummerċjali; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut u assistenza fil-bejgħ għall-bejgħ bl-ingrossa ta' prodotti kimiċi; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut u assistenza fil-bejgħ għall-bejgħ bl-ingrossa ta' żebgħa, Raża, Kuluri u żmalti, Anti-korrużivi, Profili tal-azzar, pilastri tal-azzar, staneg tal-azzar, Arbli tal-azzar, Travi ta' l-azzar, Armar tal-azzar u Kostruzzjonijiet tal-azzar, Puġġamani tal-azzar, Spralli tal-azzar, Ċnut tal-azzar, Viti, Imsiemer u ċappetti u magni għall-industrija tal-metall u/jew l-industrija tal-ħadid u l-azzar u/jew l-industrija tal-ħadid u l-azzar; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut u assistenza fil-bejgħ għall-bejgħ bl-ingrossa ta' banjijiet galvaniċi, melħ għal batteriji galvaniċi, preparazzjonijiet galvaniċi, Azzar, Metalli, Bini tal-azzar, Wajer ta' l-azzar, Ikkastjar tal-azzar, Eyelets tal-azzar, strixxi tal-azzar, tajers u tejps tal-azzar, ħbula u kejbils tal-azzar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Publiciteit; Het beheer van commerciele zaken; Consultancy en hulp bij de besturing van handelsactiviteiten; Zakelijke administratie; Administratieve diensten; Ondersteuning bij de leiding van industriële of handelsondernemingen; Bedrijfsorganisatorische en -bestuurlijke adviezen; Advisering bij de leiding van handelsactiviteiten; Professionele consultatie op het gebied van zaken; Organisatie van tentoonstellingen voor commerciële of reclamedoeleinden; Organisatie van beurzen voor commerciële doeleinden; Diensten van de detailhandel en ondersteuning bij de verkoop voor de groothandel in verband met chemische producten; Diensten van de detailhandel en ondersteuning bij de verkoop voor de groothandel in verband met verven, Harsen, Verven en lakken, Corrosiewerende middelen, Staalprofielen, stalen palen, stalen stangen, Stalen masten, Stalen steunbalken, Stalen frames en Constructies van staal, Hekwerken van staal, Stalen roosters, Stalen hekwerk, Schroeven, Spijkers en scharnieren alsmede machines voor de metaalindustrie en/of de metallurgische industrie en/of de metaalsmelterijsector; Diensten van de detailhandel en ondersteuning bij de verkoop voor de groothandel in verband met galvanische baden, zouten voor galvanische batterijen, galvanische preparaten, Staal, Metalen, Staalconstructies, Staaldraad, Gietstaal, Stalen ringen, staalbanden, beslag en bandstaal, draden en trossen van staal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Reklama; Administracja handlowa; Doradztwo i pomoc w zarządzaniu działalnością gospodarczą; Administrowanie działalnością gospodarczą; Prace biurowe; Pomoc w zarządzaniu przedsiębiorstwami przemysłowymi lub handlowymi; Doradztwo w zakresie organizacji i prowadzenia działalności gospodarczej; Doradztwo w zakresie zarządzania działalnością gospodarczą; Profesjonalne doradztwo w zakresie działalności gospodarczej; Organizacja wystaw w celach komercyjnych lub reklamowych; Organizowanie salonów w celach handlowych; Usługi handlu detalicznego i pomoc przy wprowadzaniu na rynek hurtowy odnośnie do produktów chemicznych; Usługi handlu detalicznego i pomoc przy wprowadzaniu na rynek hurtowy odnośnie do powłok, Żywice, Farby i lakiery, Środki antykorozyjne, Kształtowników stalowych, pali stalowych, prętów stalowych, Maszty ze stali, Stalowe belki nośne, Rusztowań stalowych i Konstrukcje stalowe, Balustrad stalowych, Kraty stalowe, Stalowe płoty, Śruby, Gwoździ i zawiasów oraz maszyn dla przemysłu metalowego i/lub przemysłu hutniczego i/lub przemysłu żelaznego i stalowego; Usługi handlu detalicznego i pomoc przy wprowadzaniu na rynek hurtowy odnośnie do kąpieli galwanicznych, soli do baterii galwanicznych, preparatów galwanicznych, Stal, Metali, Stal (konstrukcje -), Drut ze stali, Staliwo, Uchwytów stalowych, taśm stalowych, opon i taśm ze stali, lin i grubych lin stalowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicidade; Serviços de gestão dos negócios comerciais; Assessoria e assistência na gestão de negócios comerciais; Administração de empresas; Trabalhos de escritório; Assistência na direção de empresas industriais ou comerciais; Serviço de consultadoria em organização e direcção de negócios; Consultadoria para a direção dos negócios comerciais; Consultadoria profissional de negócios; Organização de exposição com fins comerciais ou publicitários; Organização de salões com fins comerciais; Serviços de comércio retalhista e apoio à comercialização para o comércio grossista de produtos químicos; Serviços de comércio retalhista e apoio à comercialização para o comércio grossista de tintas, Resinas, Tintas e lacas, Produtos anticorrosão, Perfis de aço, postes em aço, barras de aço, Mastros em aço, Vigas principais de aço, Andaimes de aço e Construções em aço, Grades de aço, Grades de aço, Vedações em aço, Parafusos, Pregos e dobradiças, bem como máquinas para a metalurgia e/ou indústria metalúrgica e/ou indústria siderúrgica; Serviços de comércio retalhista e apoio à comercialização para o comércio grossista de banhos de galvanização, sais para baterias galvânicas, produtos galvânicos, Aço, Metais, Construções metálicas, Fios de aço, Peças em aço fundido, Ilhós de aço, fitas de aço, pneus e folhas de aço, cordas e amarras de aço.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicitate; Gestionarea afacerilor comerciale; Consultanţă şi asistenţă în gestionarea activităţii comerciale; Administrarea afacerilor; Lucrări de birou; Asistență pentru conducerea întreprinderilor industriale sau comerciale; Servicii de gestionare comercială şi consultanţă organizaţională; Consultanță privind administrarea activităților comerciale; Consultanta profesionala despre afaceri; Organizare de expoziţii în scop comercial sau publicitar; Organizare de saloane în scopuri comerciale; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul și asistență la comercializare pentru comerțul cu ridicata cu privire la produse chimice; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul și asistență la comercializare pentru comerțul cu ridicata cu privire la produse de vopsit, Răşini, Vopsele şi lacuri, Decapanţi, Profiluri din oțel, stâlpi din oțel, bare din oțel, Oţel (Stâlpi din -), Otel balot, Suporturi din oțel şi Oţel (Construcţii din -), Bare din oțel, Grilaje din oțel, Garduri din oţel, Şuruburi, Cuie și șarniere, precum și mașini pentru industria metalelor și/sau industria siderurgică și/sau industria metalurgică; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul și asistență la comercializare pentru comerțul cu ridicata cu privire la băi galvanice, săruri pentru baterii galvanice, preparate galvanice, Oţel, Metale, Cladiri din otel, Sârmă din oţel, Oţel (Piese turnate din -), Cârlige din oțel, benzi din oțel, anvelope și benzi din oțel, funii și frânghii din oțel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reklama; Obchodná správa obchodov; Poradenstvo a pomoc pri riadení obchodnej činnosti; Obchodná administratíva; Kancelárske práce; Pomoc pri vedení priemyselných alebo obchodných spoločností; Poradenstvo pri organizovaní a riadení obchodných záležitostí; Poradenstvo pri vedení obchodnej činnosti; Odborné obchodné poradenstvo; Organizovanie výstav pre obchodné alebo reklamné účely; Organizovanie prehliadok na obchodné účely; Služby maloobchodu a pomoc pri predaji v oblasti veľkoobchodu v oblasti chemických výrobkov; Služby maloobchodu a pomoc pri predaji v oblasti veľkoobchodu v oblasti náterov, Živice, Farby a laky, Hrdza (prípravky proti -), Oceľové profily, oceľové koly, oceľové tyče, Oceľové stožiare, Oceľové nosníky, Oceľové lešenia a Oceľové konštrukcie, Oceľové zábradlia, Oceľové mreže, Oceľové ploty, Skrutky, Klince a pánty, ako aj stroje pre kovopriemysel a/alebo hutnícky priemysel a/alebo železiarsky priemysel; Služby maloobchodu a pomoc pri predaji v oblasti veľkoobchodu v oblasti galvanických kúpeľov, solí pre galvanické batérie, galvanických prípravkov, Oceľ, Kovy, Oceľové stavby, Oceľový drôt, Oceloliatina, oceľ na odliatky, Oceľové krúžky, oceľové pásy, prúžky a stuhy z ocele, laná a laná z ocele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oglaševanje in oglaševalske storitve; Komercialno poslovno upravljanje; Svetovanje in pomoč pri vodenju komercialnih poslov; Poslovna administracija; Pisarniški posli; Pomoč pri vodenju industrijskih ali komercialnih podjetij; Storitev svetovanja pri organiziranju in vodenju poslovanja; Nasveti o vodenju podjetja; Strokovno poslovno svetovanje; Organizacija razstave v komercialne ali reklamne namene; Organizacija salonov za komercialne namene; Storitve maloprodaje in pomoč pri trženju za veleprodajo v zvezi s kemičnimi proizvodi; Storitve maloprodaje in pomoč pri trženju za veleprodajo v zvezi z barvami, Umetna smola, Barve in laki, Sredstva proti rji, Jekleni profili, jeklene palice, jekleni drogovi, Jekleni jambori, Jekleni tramovi, Jeklena ogrodja in Jeklene konstrukcije, Jeklene ograje, Jeklene rešetke, Jeklene ograje, Vijaki, Žeblji in tečaji ter stroji za kovinsko industrijo in/ali metalurško in/ali železarsko industrijo; Storitve maloprodaje in pomoč pri trženju za veleprodajo v zvezi z galvanskimi kopelmi, solmi za galvanske baterije, galvanskimi pripravki, Jeklo, Kovine, Jeklene zgradbe (konstrukcije), Jeklene žice, Lito jeklo, Jeklena ušesca, jekleni trakovi, pnevmatike in trakovi iz jekla, vrvi in kabli iz jekla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Reklam; Kommersiell företagsadministration; Rådgivning och hjälp vid ledning av affärsverksamhet; Företagsadministration; Kontorstjänster; Hjälp vid ledning av industri- eller handelsföretag; Rådgivningstjänster avseende företagsorganisation och -ledning; Rådgivning vid ledning av affärsverksamhet; Professionella affärskonsultationer; Anordnande av utställningar för kommersiella ändamål eller reklamändamål; Anordnande av mässor för kommersiella ändamål; Detaljhandelstjänster och hjälp vid marknadsföring för grosshandel relaterade till kemiska produkter; Detaljhandelstjänster och hjälp vid marknadsföring för grosshandel relaterade till bestrykningsmedel, Hartser, Målarfärger och lacker, Rostskyddsmedel, Stålprofiler, stålstolpar, stålstänger, Stålmaster, Stålbalkar, Byggnadsställningar av stål och Stålkonstruktioner, Stålräcken, Stålgaller, Stängsel av stål, Skruvar, Spikar och gångjärn samt maskiner för metallindustrin och/eller den metallurgiska industrin och/eller järnbruk; Detaljhandelstjänster och hjälp vid marknadsföring för grosshandeln med avseende på galvaniska bad, salter för galvaniska batterier, galvaniska preparat, Stål, Metaller, Stålbyggnader, Ståltråd, Stålgjutgods, Stålöljetter, band av stål, däck och band av stål, tågvirke och trossar av stål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>37</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Антикорозионна обработка, а именно нанасяне на покритие върху метални части чрез прилагане на боя с цел защита от корозия; Строеж на сгради; Ремонт, а именно услуги във връзка със запазване и възстановяване на сгради, технически и промишлени инсталации и машини и запазване и възстановяване на части от сгради, технически и промишлени инсталации и машини; Монтажни услуги, а именно услуги във връзка с вграждане на запазени, възстановени и нови части в сгради и в технически и промишлени инсталации и машини.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Ošetřování proti korozi, jmenovitě potahování kovových dílů nanášením barev pro účely ochrany proti korozi; Stavebnictví; Opravy, jmenovitě služby v souvislosti se zachováním a renovací budov, technických a průmyslových zařízení a strojů a zachováním a renovací komponentů budov, technických a průmyslových zařízení a strojů; Instalační služby, jmenovitě služby v souvislosti s vestavbou zachovalých, renovovaných a nových komponentů do budov a technických a průmyslových zařízení a strojů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Korrosionsbeskyttende behandlinger, nemlig beklædning af metaldele ved påføring af maling til korrosionsbeskyttelse; Tjenesteydelser vedrørende byggeri; Reparationsvirksomhed, nemlig tjenesteydelser i forbindelse med vedligeholdelse og renovering af bygninger, tekniske og industrielle anlæg og maskiner samt vedligeholdelse og renovering af komponenter til bygninger, tekniske og industrielle anlæg og maskiner; Installationsvirksomhed, nemlig tjenesteydelser i forbindelse med montering af vedligeholdte, renoverede og nye komponenter i bygninger, tekniske og industrielle anlæg og maskiner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Korrosionsschutzbehandlung, nämlich Beschichtung von Metallteilen durch Aufbringen von Farbe zum Zwecke des Korrosionsschutzes; Bauwesen; Reparaturwesen, nämlich Dienstleistungen im Zusammenhang mit der Erhaltung und Wiederherstellung von Gebäuden, technischer und industrieller Anlagen und Maschinen und der Erhaltung und Wiederherstellung von Bauteilen von Gebäuden, technischer und industrieller Anlagen und Maschinen; Installationsarbeiten, nämlich Dienstleistungen im Zusammenhang mit dem Einbau von erhaltenen, wiederhergestellten und neuen Bauteilen in Gebäuden und in technische und industrielle Anlagen und Maschinen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Επεξεργασία για προστασία έναντι διαβρώσεως, συγκεκριμένα επίστρωση μεταλλικών μερών μέσω εφαρμογής χρώματος για σκοπούς προστασίας έναντι διαβρώσεως· Οικοδομικές εργασίες· Επισκευές, συγκεκριμένα υπηρεσίες σε σχέση με τη συντήρηση και αποκατάσταση κτιρίων, τεχνικών και βιομηχανικών εγκαταστάσεων και μηχανών για τη συντήρηση και αποκατάσταση κατασκευαστικών στοιχείων κτιρίων, τεχνικών και βιομηχανικών εγκαταστάσεων και μηχανών· Υπηρεσίες εγκατάστασης, συγκεκριμένα υπηρεσίες σε σχέση με την τοποθέτηση συντηρημένων, επισκευασμένων και νέων κατασκευαστικών στοιχείων σε κτίρια και σε τεχνικές και βιομηχανικές εγκαταστάσεις και μηχανές.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Anti-corrosion treatment, namely coating of parts of metal through applying of paint for purposes of corrosion protection; Construction services; Repair, namely services in connection with the preservation and restoration of buildings, technical and industrial installations and machines, and the conservation and restoration of components for buildings, technical and industrial installations and machines; Installation, namely services in connection with the installation of preserved, restored and new components in buildings and technical and industrial installations and machines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Tratamientos para la protección anticorrosiva, en concreto revestimiento de piezas de metal mediante la aplicación de pintura para proteger contra la corrosión; Servicios de construcción; Reparación, en concreto servicios relacionados con la conservación y restauración de edificios, instalaciones y máquinas técnicas e industriales, y la conservación y restauración de componentes de edificios e instalaciones y máquinas técnicas e industriales; Servicios de instalación, en concreto servicios relacionados con la instalación de componentes conservados, restaurados y nuevos en edificios e instalaciones y máquinas técnicas e industriales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Korrosioonitõrjetöötlus, nimelt korrosioonitõrjeks metallosade pindamine värvides; Ehitus; Remont, nimelt teenused seoses hoonete, tehniliste ja tööstuslike rajatiste ja masinate säilitamise ja taastamisega ning hoonete, tehniliste ja tööstuslike rajatiste ja masinate (ehitus)detailide säilimise ja taastamisega; Paigaldustööd, nimelt teenused seoses säilinud, taastatud ja uute detailide paigaldamisega hoonesse ja tehnilistesse ja tööstuslikesse rajatistesse ja masinatesse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Syöpymisenestokäsittely, nimittäin metalliosien pinnoitus levittämällä väriä syöpymisenestotarkoituksissa; Rakentamispalvelut; Huolto ja korjaus, nimittäin rakennusten, teknisten ja teollisten laitteistojen ja koneiden ylläpitoon ja alkuperäiseen tilaansa palauttamiseen liittyvät palvelut, rakennusten, teknisten ja teollisten laitteistojen ja koneiden rakenneosien ylläpitoon ja alkuperäiseen tilaansa palauttamiseen liittyvät palvelut; Asennuspalvelut, nimittäin palvelut, jotka liittyvät ylläpidettyjen, alkuperäiseen tilaansa palautettujen ja uusien rakenneosien rakentamiseen teollisiin laitteistoihin ja koneisiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Traitement de protection contre la corrosion, à savoir revêtement de pièces métalliques par l'application de couleur destinée à la protection anti-corrosion; Construction; Réparation, à savoir services en rapport avec la préservation et la rénovation de bâtiments, installations et machines techniques et industrielles et la préservation et la rénovation de composants de bâtiments, installations et machines techniques et industrielles; Travaux d'installation, à savoir services en rapport avec l'incorporation de composants préservés, rénovés et nouveaux dans des bâtiments et installations et machines techniques et industrielles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Antikorozivni tretmani, i to premazivanje dijelova metala bojama za antikorozivnu zaštitu; Usluge gradnje; Popravci, i to u vezi održavanja i restauriranja zgrada, tehničkih i industrijskih postrojenja i strojeva i održavanja i restauracije građevinskih dijelova zgrada, tehničkih i industrijskih postrojenja i strojeva; Postavljanje, i to usluge u vezi s ugradnjom očuvanih, restauriranih i novo izrađenih građevinskih dijelova u zgradama i tehničkim i industrijskim postrojenjima i strojevima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Korróziógátló kezelés, azaz a fém alkatrészek bevonása festékek felvitele révén korrózióvédelmi célokra; Építőipari szolgáltatások; Javítás, nevezetesen szolgáltatások épületek karbantartásával és újraépítésével kapcsolatban, műszaki és ipari berendezések és gépek és épületkomponensek karbantartásával és újraépítésével kapcsolatban, műszaki és ipari berendezések és gépek; Szerelési szolgáltatások, nevezetesen szolgáltatások karbantartott, újraépített és új épületkomponensek beépítésével kapcsolatban és műszaki és ipari berendezésekkel és gépekkel kapcsolatban.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Trattamento anticorrosivo, ovvero rivestimento di parti di metallo con del colore con azione anticorrosiva; Servizi di edilizia e di costruzione; Servizi di riparazione, ovvero servizi legati al mantenimento e al restauro di edifici, macchine e impianti tecnici e industriali e al mantenimento e al restauro di componenti di edifici, macchine e impianti tecnici e industriali; Servizi d'installazione, ovvero servizi legati all'installazione di componenti conservati, restaurati e nuovi negli edifici e in macchine e impianti tecnici e industriali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Antikorozinis dengimas apsaugine danga, būtent metalinių detalių dengimas dažais apsaugos nuo korozijos reikmėms; Statybos paslaugos; Taisymas (remontas), būtent paslaugos, susijusios su pastatų, techninių ir pramoninių įrenginių ir mašinų išlaikymu ir rekonstravimu bei pastatų, techninių ir pramoninių įrenginių ir mašinų konstrukcinių dalių išlaikymu ir rekonstravimu; Įtaisymas ir įrengimas, būtent paslaugos, susijusios su išlaikytų, rekonstruotų ir naujų konstrukcinių dalių įmontavimu į pastatus, techninius ir pramoninius įrenginius ir mašinas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apstrāde aizsardzībai pret koroziju, proti, metāla daļu pārklāšana, uzklājot pretkorozijas krāsu; Būvniecības pakalpojumi; Remonta nozare, proti, pakalpojumi saistībā ar ēku, tehnisku un rūpniecisku iekārtu un mašīnu saglabāšanu un atjaunošanu un ēku, tehnisko un rūpniecisko iekārtu un mašīnu būvelementu saglabāšanu un atjaunošanu; Uzstādīšanas darbi, proti, pakalpojumi saistībā ar saglabātu, atjaunotu un jaunu būvelementu iebūvēšanu ēkās un tehniskās un rūpnieciskās iekārtās un mašīnās.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Trattament kontra l-korrużjoni, jiġifieri, kisi ta' partijiet tal-metall bl-applikazzjoni ta' żebgħa għal skopijiet ta' protezzjoni mill-korrużjoni; Kostruzzjoni; Tiswija, jiġifieri servizzi relatati mal-preservazzjoni u r-restawr ta' bini, impjanti u magni tekniċi u industrijali, u l-preservazzjoni u r-restawr ta' komponenti ta' bini, impjanti u magni tekniċi u industrijali; Xogħlijiet ta' installazzjoni, jiġifieri servizzi relatati mal-installazzjoni ta' komponenti ppreservati, restawrati u ġodda f'bini u f'impjanti u magni tekniċi u industrijali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Roestwerende behandeling, te weten coating van metaaldelen door middel van het opbrengen van verf ter bescherming tegen roest; Bouw; Reparaties, te weten diensten in verband met het conserveren en herstellen van gebouwen, technische en industriële installaties en machines en het conserveren en herstellen van constructieonderdelen van gebouwen, technische en industriële installaties en machines; Installatiewerkzaamheden, te weten diensten in verband met het inbouwen van geconserveerde, herstelde en nieuwe constructieonderdelen in gebouwen en in technische en industriële installaties en machines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Obróbka przeciwkorozyjna, mianowicie powlekanie części metalowych poprzez nakładanie farby w celu zabezpieczania przed korozją; Usługi budowlane; Naprawy, mianowicie usługi związane z ochroną i konserwacją budynków, instalacji oraz maszyn technicznych i przemysłowych oraz ochroną i konserwacją metalowych komponentów budowlanych, instalacji oraz maszyn technicznych i przemysłowych; Usługi instalacyjne, mianowicie usługi związane z instalacją zachowanych, odrestaurowanych i nowych komponentów budowlanych w budynkach oraz maszyn i urządzeń technicznych i przemysłowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Tratamento anticorrosão, especificamente revestimento de peças metálicas através da aplicação de tintas anticorrosivas; Construção; Serviços de reparação, especificamente serviços relacionados com a conservação e recuperação de edifícios, instalações técnicas e industriais, máquinas, assim como com a conservação e recuperação de componentes de edifícios, instalações técnicas e industriais e máquinas; Serviços de instalação, especificamente serviços no contexto da montagem de componentes conservados, recuperados e novos em edifícios, assim como em instalações técnicas e industriais e máquinas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Tratament anticoroziv, şi anume stratificare de piese metalice prin aplicare de vopsea în scopuri anticorozive; Servicii de construcții; Reparaţii, şi anume servicii în legătură cu întreţinerea şi renovarea de clădiri, de instalaţii şi utilaje tehnice şi industriale şi cu întreţinerea şi renovarea de componente de clădiri, de instalaţii şi utilaje tehnice şi industriale; Lucrări de instalare, şi anume servicii în legătură cu montarea componentelor recuperate, renovate şi noi în clădiri şi în instalaţii şi utilaje tehnice şi industriale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ochranné prostriedky proti hrdzi, menovite nanášanie ochranných vrstiev na kovové časti nanášaním farieb na ochranu proti hrdzi; Stavebníctvo; Opravy, menovite služby v súvislosti so zachovaním a obnovou budov, technických a priemyselných zariadení a strojov a zachovaním a obnovou komponentov budov a priemyselných zariadení a strojov; Inštalačné práce, menovite služby v súvislosti so zabudovaním zachovaných, obnovených a nových komponentov v budovách a v technických a priemyselných zariadeniach a strojoch.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Obdelava za zaščito proti koroziji, in sicer prevleke za kovinske dele z nanašanjem barve za namen zaščite proti koroziji; Stavbeništvo; Popravila, in sicer storitve v zvezi z vzdrževanjem in obnovo stavb, tehnične in industrijske opreme in strojev in v zvezi z vzdrževanjem in obnovo gradbenih delov/sestavnih delov stavb, tehnične in industrijske opreme in strojev; Instalacijska dela, in sicer storitve v povezavi z vgradnjo ohranjenih, obnovljenih in novih gradbenih delov/sestavnih delov v stavbe in v tehnično in industrijsko opremo in stroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Korrosionsskyddsbehandling, nämligen beläggning av metalldelar genom applicering av färg för korrosionsskydd; Byggnationstjänster; Reparationsverksamhet, nämligen tjänster i samband med bevarande och återställande av byggnader, tekniska och industriella anläggningar samt maskiner och bevarande och återställande av komponenter till byggnader, tekniska och industriella anläggningar och maskiner; Installationstjänster, nämligen tjänster i samband med inbyggnad av bevarade, återställda och nya komponenter i byggnader och i tekniska och industriella anläggningar och maskiner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>39</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Транспорт; Транспортна логистика; Опаковане и съхраняване на стоки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přeprava; Logistika v dopravě; Balení a skladování zboží.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Transport; Transportlogistik; Pakning og opbevaring af varer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Transportwesen; Transportlogistik; Verpackung und Lagerung von Waren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μεταφορές· Εφοδιαστική σε σχέση με μεταφορές· Συσκευασία και αποθήκευση εμπορευμάτων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Transport; Transportation logistics; Packaging and storage of goods.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de transporte; Servicios logísticos de transporte; Envasado y almacenamiento de mercancías.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Transport; Transpordilogistika; Kaupade pakendamine ja ladustamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kuljetus; Kuljetuslogistiikka; Tavaroiden pakkaus ja varastointi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Transports; Services de logistique en matière de transport; Emballage et entreposage de marchandises.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Prijevoz; Logističke usluge u svezi s prijevozom; Pakiranje i skladištenje robe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szállítás; Szállítási logisztikai szolgáltatások; Áruk csomagolása és tárolása.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Trasporto; Organizzazione di trasporti; Imballaggio e deposito di merci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vežimas; Transporto logistika; Prekių pakavimas ir sandėliavimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Transporta pakalpojumi; Transporta loģistikas pakalpojumi; Preču iesaiņošana un uzglabāšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Trasport; Loġistika tat-trasportazzjoni; L-ippakkjar u l-ħażna ta' oġġetti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Transport; Logistieke diensten op het gebied van transport; Verpakking en opslag van goederen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Transport; Logistyka transportu; Pakowanie i składowanie towarów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Transporte; Logística de transporte; Embalagem e entreposto de mercadorias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Transport; Logistică de transport; Ambalarea și depozitarea mărfurilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Dopravné služby; Logistické služby v doprave; Balenie a skladovanie tovaru.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Transport; Transportna logistika; Pakiranje in skladiščenje blaga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Transporter; Transportlogistik; Emballering/paketering och förvaring av gods.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>40</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Обработване на материали, А именно термична обработка и полагане на покритие на метал; Полиране на метални повърхности; Металургична обработка; Обработка на материали чрез лазерен лъч; Галванизация; Третиране чрез потапяне в горещ разтвор; Прахови покрития на метал; Покриване с боя на метал [освен бояджийски дейности]; Завъшваща обработка на метал; Галванизация; Завъшваща обработка на метал; Металолеене; Щамповане на метал; Екструдерни метални профили; Метализация; Металургично топене; Щампиране; Щанцоване; Профилиране на метали; Формоване на метал; Коване; Закаляване; Темпериране; Щамповане и емайлиране на метали; Обработка и облицоване на материали чрез пулверизация; Обработка на метални части с цел защита от корозия чрез горещо поцинковане и облицоване с прах; Поцинковане по негалванични методи; Анодизиране; Покриване по мокър метод; Пасивиране и плакиране на метали; Услуги в областта на защитата от корозия на метални части, а именно, горещо поцинковане; Прахово и цветно покриване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zpracování materiálů, Jmenovitě tepelné ošetření a potahování výrobků; Leštění povrchů z kovu; Metalurgické zpracování; Úprava materiálů laserovým paprskem; Galvanizace; Žárové zinkování; Práškové nátěry kovu; Nanášení barev na kovy [s výjimkou malířských prací]; Konečná úprava kovů; Pokovování; Konečná úprava kovů; Odlévání kovů; Lisování kovů; Kovové výlisky; Pokovování; Metalurgické tavení; Lisovací práce; Lisování; Profilování kovů; Tváření s ohledem na kovy; Kovářství; Kalení; Temperování; Ražení a smaltování kovů; Zpracování a pokrytí materiálů postřikem; Zpracování kovových dílů pro účely ochrany karoserií žárovým zinkováním a práškovým potahováním; Pozinkování v nekovových procesech; Anodická oxidace; Potahování za mokra; Pasivování a pokovování kovů; Služby v oblasti ochrany proti korozi u kovových dílů, jmenovitě žárové zinkování; Práškové a barevné potahování.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Forarbejdning og behandling af materialer og genstande, Nemlig varmebehandling og coating af metal; Polering af overflader af metal; Metallurgisk forarbejdning; Behandling af materialer med laserstråler; Galvanisering; Varmdypning; Pulverbelægning af metal; Farvebelægninger af metal (dog ikke malerarbejde); Overfladebehandling af metal; Plettering af metal; Overfladebehandling af metal; Metalstøbning; Metalprægning; Ekstruderinger af metal; Metalcoating; Metallurgisk smeltning; Trykning; Stansning; Profilering af metaller; Omformning af metal; Smedevirksomhed; Hærdning; Udglødning; Prægning og emaljering af metal; Behandling og belægning af materialer ved hjælp af pulverisering; Bearbejdning af metaldele med henblik på korrosionsbeskyttelse i form af varmgalvanisering og pulverbelægning; Forzinkning i en ikke-galvanisk proces; Anodisering; Vådcoating; Passivering og plettering af metal; Korrosionsbeskyttelse af metaldele, nemlig varmgalvanisering; Coating med pulver og maling.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Materialbearbeitung, nämlich Wärmebehandlung und Beschichtung von Metall; Polieren von Oberflächen aus Metall; metallurgische Verarbeitung; Materialbearbeitung mit Laserstrahlen; Galvanisieren; Feuerverzinken; Pulverbeschichtung von Metall; Farbbeschichtung von Metall [außer Malerarbeiten]; Metallveredelung; Metallbeschichtungsarbeiten; Metallnachbearbeitung; Metallgießen; Metallstanzen; Metallpressen; Metallisierung; metallurgisches Schmelzen; Stanzarbeiten; Stanzen; Umformen von Metall; Umformarbeiten in Bezug auf Metall; Schmieden; Härten; Tempern; Prägen und Emaillieren von Metall; Behandlung und Beschichtung von Werkstoffen mit Hilfe von Spritzverfahren; Bearbeitung von Metallteilen zum Zwecke des Korrosionsschutzes durch Feuerzinken und Pulverbeschichtung; Verzinken in nichtgalvanische Verfahren; Anodisieren; Nassbeschichten; Passivieren und Plattieren von Metallen; Dienstleistungen auf dem Gebiet des Korrosionsschutzes von Metallteilen, nämlich Feuerverzinken; Pulver- und Farbbeschichtung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Επεξεργασία υλικών, Συγκεκριμένα θερμική επεξεργασία και επίστρωση μετάλλου· Στίλβωση επιφανειών από μέταλλο· Μεταλλουργική επεξεργασία· Επεξεργασία υλικών με ακτίνες λέιζερ· Επιμετάλλωση· Θερμή εμβάπτιση· Επίστρωση μετάλλων με υλικά σε μορφή σκόνης· Βαφή μετάλλων [εκτός από εργασίες ελαιοχρωματισμού]· Τελική επεξεργασία (φινίρισμα) μετάλλων· Επιμετάλλωση· Τελική επεξεργασία (φινίρισμα) μετάλλων· Χύτευση μετάλλων· Αποτύπωση μετάλλων με πρεσάρισμα· Προϊόντα εξώθησης από μέταλλο· Επίστρωση μη μεταλλικών αντικειμένων με μέταλλο· Τήξη σε εφαρμογές μεταλλουργίας· Υπηρεσίες χάραξης· Πυγμαχίας· Μεταλλικές κατατομές· Εργασίες παραμόρφωσης σε σχέση με μέταλλο· Σφυρηλάτησης (Εργασίες -)· Σκλήρυνση· Θερμική κατεργασία· Ανάγλυφη αποτύπωση και επισμάλτωση μετάλλου· Επεξεργασία και επικάλυψη υλικών με τη μέθοδο του ψεκασμού επιφανείας· Επεξεργασία μεταλλικών εξαρτημάτων με σκοπό την προστασία από διάβρωση μέσω επιψευδαργύρωσης εν θερμώ και επίστρωσης επιχρίσματος σε σκόνη· Επιψευδαργύρωση σε μη γαλβανικές μεθόδους· Ανοδίωση· Υγρή επίστρωση· Αδρανοποίηση και επίστρωση μετάλλων· Υπηρεσίες στον τομέα της αντιδιαβρωτικής προστασίας μεταλλικών μερών, συγκεκριμένα θερμή επιψευδαργύρωση· Επίστρωση με σκόνη και επίστρωση χρώματος.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Treatment of materials, Namely heat treatment and coating of metals; Polishing of surfaces of metal; Metallurgical processing; Treatment of materials by laser beam; Galvanization; Hot dipping; Powder coating of metal; Colour coating of metal (not painting); Metal finishing; Metal plating; Metal finishing; Metal casting; Metal stamping; Extrusions of metal; Metallizing; Metallurgical smelting; Stamping; Punches; Shaping of metal; Shaping relating to metal; Blacksmithing; Tempering; Tempering; Embossing and enamelling of metal; Treatment and coating of materials by spraying; Processing of metal parts for corrosion protection purposes by means of hot-dip galvanising and powder coating; Galvanising in non-galvanic processes; Anodising; Wet coating; Passivating and plating of metal; Services in the field of corrosion protection for metal parts, namely hot-dip galvanising; Powder and colour coating.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Tratamiento de materiales, En concreto tratamiento térmico y revestimiento de metales; Pulido de superficies metálicas; Procesados metalúrgicos; Tratamiento de materiales con rayos láser; Galvanización; Galvanizado en caliente; Revestimiento en polvo de metales; Revestimiento de color de metal [excepto trabajos de pintura]; Acabado de metales; Chapado de metales; Acabado de metales; Colada de metales; Estampación de metales; Extrusiones metálicas; Trabajos de metalizado; Fundición metalúrgica; Servicios de estampación; Punzones; Perfilado de metales; Moldeado de metales; Servicios de forja; Temple; Temperado; Repujado y esmaltado de metales; Tratamiento y revestimiento de materiales mediante pulverización; Tratamiento de protección contra la corrosión de piezas metálicas mediante cincado al fuego y recubrimiento por pulverización; Cincado mediante un proceso distinto de la galvanización; Anodización; Revestimiento en húmedo; Pasivación y chapado de metales; Servicios en materia de protección anticorrosión de piezas metálicas, en concreto galvanizado en caliente; Revestimientos en polvo y de color.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Materjalitöötlus, Nimelt metallide kuumtöötlemine ja pinnakatmine; Metallpindade poleerimine; Metallurgiline töötlus; Materjalide töötlus laserkiirega; Galvaanimine; Kuumsöövitus; Metallipindade katmine pulbermeetodil; Metalli värviga katmine [v.a maalritööd]; Metalli viimistlemine; Metalliga katmine, plakeerimine; Metalli viimistlemine; Metallivalamine, metallivalutööd; Metalli stantsimine; Ekstrudeeritud profiil [metall]; Metalliseerimine; Metallurgiline sulatamine; Kohrutamine; Stantsimine; Metallide profileerimine; Metalliga seotud ümbervormimistööd; Sepatööd; Karastamine; Lõõmutamine; Metalli reljeefpressimine ja emailimine; Materjalide töötlemine ja katmine pulverisatsiooniga; Metalldetailide töötlemine korrosioonitõrjena kuumtsinkimise ja pulberpinnete abil; Tsinkimine, v.a galvaanitehnoloogiat rakendades; Anoodimine; Mägipinnakatmine; Metallide passiveerimine ja plakeerimine; Metallosade korrosioonitõrje, nimelt kuumtsinkimine; Pulber- ja värvkatmine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Aineiden ja esineiden käsittely, Nimittäin metallin lämpökäsittely ja päällystys; Metallipintojen kiillotus; Metallurginen käsittely; Aineiden käsittely lasersäteen avulla; Galvanointi; Upotusmetallointi; Metallin päällystäminen jauheella; Metallien maalipinnoitus (paitsi maalaustyöt); Metallien viimeistely; Metallointi; Metallien viimeistely; Metallinvalu; Metallien meistäminen; Metallipuristeet; Metallointi; Metallurginen sulatus; Meistopalvelut; Rei´itys; Metalliprofilointi; Metalliin liittyvät muodonmuutostyöt; Pajatyö [taonta]; Karkaisu; Temperointi; Metallin kohokuviointi ja emalointi; Aineiden käsittely ja päällystäminen sumuttamalla; Kuumasinkityksen ja pulveripäällystyksen avulla tehtävä metalliosien käsittely suojaamaan korroosiolta; Sinkitys ei-galvaanisella menetelmällä; Anodisointi; Märkäpinnoitus; Metallien passivointi ja päällystäminen; Palvelut metalliosien korroosiosuojauksen alalla, nimittäin kuumasinkitys; Jauhe- ja maalipinnoitus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Traitement de matériaux, À savoir traitement thermique et revêtement de métaux; Polissage de surfaces en métal; Traitement métallurgique; Traitement de matériaux par rayons laser; Galvanisation; Immersion à chaud de métaux; Revêtement de poudre métallique; Peinture sur le métal [excepté travaux de peintre]; Finissage des métaux; Revêtement [placage] des métaux; Finissage des métaux; Coulage des métaux; Emboutissage de métaux; Métal extrudé; Services de métallisation; Services de fonte métallurgique; Services d'impression; Estampage; profilage de métaux; Remodelage en relation avec le métal; Travaux de forge; Trempe; Tempérage; Embossage et émaillage de métaux; Traitement et revêtement de matériaux par pulvérisation; Traitement de pièces métalliques pour les protéger de la corrosion par zingage à chaud et revêtement en poudre; Galvanisation en procédé non galvanique; Anodisation; Revêtement en voie humide; Passivation et placage des métaux; Services dans le domaine de la protection de pièces métalliques contre la corrosion, à savoir galvanisation à chaud; Revêtement de poudre et de peinture.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Obrada materijala, Odnosno obrada toplinom i oblaganje metala; Poliranje površina od metala; Metalurška prerada; Obrada materijala laserskim snopom; Oblaganje metala; Obrada galvanizacijom; Premazi u prahu za metale; Premazi bojom metala [izuzev usluge ličenja]; Završna obrada metala; Oblaganje metala; Završna obrada metala; Lijevanje; Obrada metala ("štancanje"); Metalne ekstruzije; Metaliziranje; Metalurško taljenje; Označavanje; Uređaji za bušenje papira; Oblikovanje metala; Poslovi preoblikovanja u vezi s metalom; Kovački radovi; Stvrdnjivanje; Žarenje; Utiskivanje i emajliranje metala; Tretmani i premazivanje radnih materijala raspršivanjem; Obrada metalnih dijelova za zaštitu od korozije putem galvanizacije i oblaganjem prahom; Pocinčavanje u postupke koji nisu galvanski; Anodiziranje; Mokro oblaganje; Pasiviziranje i oblaganje metala; Usluge na području zaštite metalnih dijelova od korozije, odnosno vruće pocinčavanje; Oblaganje prahom i bojom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Anyagmegmunkálás, Azaz fém hőkezelése és bevonása; Fémből készült felületek polírozása; Kohászati feldolgozás; Anyagok lézersugaras kezelése; Fémek bevonása; Forró galvanizálás; Porbevonatok készítése fémekre; Fémek festékkel való bevonása [festési munkák kivételével]; Fémek utómunkálatai; Fémek bevonása; Fémek utómunkálatai; Fémöntés; Fémek sajtolása; Sajtolt fémelemek; Fémezés; Kohászati olvasztás; Préselés; Stancolás; Fémek formázása; Átformázási munkálatok fémekkel kapcsolatban; Kovácsolás; Keményítés; Lágyítás; Fémek dombornyomása és zománcozása; Anyagok kezelése és bevonása permetezés révén; Fémalkatrészek megmunkálása korrózióvédelem céljára tüzihorganyzás és porbevonás által; Galvanizálás galvánmentes eljárásban; Anodizálás; Nedves bevonás; Fémek passziválása és pácolása; Szolgáltatások a fémelemek korrózió elleni védelme terén, azaz forró galvanizálás; Por- és színezett bevonatok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Trattamento di materiali, Ovvero trattamento termico e rivestimento di metalli; Levigazione di superfici in metallo; Trattamento metallurgico; Trattamento di materiali a raggio laser; Galvanizzazione; Immersione a caldo; Rivestimento in polvere di metalli; Verniciatura di metallo [tranne lavori di pittura]; Finitura del metallo; Rivestimento [placcatura] dei metalli; Finitura del metallo; Fusione di metalli; Stampaggio di metalli; Estrusioni in metallo; Metallizzazione; Fusione metallurgica; Servizi di stampa; Punzoni; Profilatura di metalli; Lavori di formatura in metallo; Lavori di forgia; Tempratura; Tempra; Punzonatura e smaltatura di metalli; Trattamento e rivestimento di materiali mediante polverizzazione; Lavorazione di parti di metallo per proteggerle dalla corrosione mediante zincatura a fuoco e rivestimenti in polvere; Zincatura in procedimenti non galvanici; Anodizzazione; Rivestimento a umido; Passivazione e placcatura dei metalli; Interventi di protezione dalla corrosione di pezzi metallici, ovvero zincatura a caldo; Rivestimento con polveri e con pitture.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Medžiagų apdirbimas ir apdorojimas, Būtent šiluminis metalo apdirbimas ir dengimas; Metalo paviršių poliravimas; Metalurginis apdirbimas; Medžiagų apdorojimas lazerio spinduliu; Galvanizavimas; Galvanizavimas karšto panardinimo būdu; Metalo dengimas milteliais; Metalų padengimas dažais [išskyrus dažymą]; Metalų apdaila; Metalizavimas; Metalų apdaila; Metalų liejimas; Metalų štampavimas; Ekstruziniai metalo gaminiai; Dengimas metalu; Metalurginis lydymas; Štampavimo paslaugos; Vinių kalimo įtaisai; Metalo apdirbimas; Performavimo darbai, susiję su metalu; Kalvystės darbai; Grūdinimas; Temperavimas; Metalo formavimas ir dengimas emale; Medžiagų dorojimas ir dengimas pulverizacijos būdu; Metalinių detalių apdirbimas naudojant karštojo cinkavimo ir padengimo milteliais procesus antikorozijos reikmėms; Cinkavimas taikant negalvaninį metodą; Anodinimas; Dengimas šlapiuoju būdu; Metalų pasyvinimas ir dengimas; Paslaugos metalinių dalių apsaugos nuo korozijos, būtent cinkavimo karštuoju būdu srityje; Dengimas milteliniu būdu ir dažais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Materiālu apstrāde, Proti, metālu termiskā apstrāde un pārklāšana; Metāla virsmu pulēšana; Metalurģiskā apstrāde; Materiālu apstrāde ar lāzera staru; Galvanizācija; Karstā galvanizācija; Metāla pulvera pārklājums; Metāla pārklāšana ar krāsu [izņemot krāsošanas darbus]; Metāla apdare; Metalizēšana; Metāla apdare; Metālliešana; Metāla štancēšana; Štancējumi no metāla; Metalizācija; Metalurģiskā kausēšana; Štancēšana; Štancēšana; Metāla profilēšanas veidnes; Presēšanas darbā saistībā ar metālu; Kalēju darbi; Rūdīšana; Termiskā apstrāde; Reljefa veidošana un metāla emaljēšana; Materiālu apstrāde un pārklāšana ar apsmidzināšanas metodi; Metāla daļu apstrāde aizsardzībai pret koroziju, izmantojot karsto cinkošanu un pulverizācijas pārklāšanu; Cinkošana, neizmantojot galvaniskos procesus; Anodēšana; Pārklāšana kodinot; Metālu pasivēšana un pārklāšana ar citiem metāliem; Pakalpojumi metāla detaļu pretkorozijas apstrādes jomā, proti, karstā cinkošana; Pārklāšana ar pulveri un krāsu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Trattament ta' materjali, Jiġifieri trattament bis-sħana u kisi ta' metalli; Lostru ta' wċuħ tal-metall; Proċessar metallurġiku; Trattament ta' materjali bir-raġġ tal-lejżer; Kisi tal-metall; Galvanizzar biż-żingu mdewweb; Kisi tat-trab tal-metall; Kisi tal-metall biż-żebgħa [bl-eċċezzjoni tax-xogħol taż-żebgħa]; Finitura ta' metall; Kisi tal-metall; Finitura ta' metall; It-tidwib tal-metalli; Stampar ta' metalli; Estrużjonijiet tal-metall; Metallizzar; Xogħlijiet ta' tidwib metallurġiku; Servizzi ta' pressa; Qtugħ bil-forom; Profili tal-metall; Xogħol ta' rimodellar relatat mal-metall; Xogħol tal-ħaddied; Ittemprar; Ittemprar; Intaljar u kisi ta' metalli bl-enamel; Trattament u kisi ta' materjali permezz tal-pulverizzazzjoni; Trattament ta' partijiet tal-metall għal skopijiet ta' protezzjoni minn korrużjoni permezz tal-iggalvanizzar bis-sħana u tal-kisi bi trab; Galvanizzar fi proċessi mhux galvaniċi; Anodizzar; Kisi mxarrab; Passivazzjoni u kisi ta' metalli; Servizzi fil-qasam tal-protezzjoni ta' partijiet tal-metall kontra l-korrużjoni, jiġifieri, galvanizzar bis-sħana; Kisi bit-trab u ż-żebgħa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Behandeling van materialen, Te weten warmtebehandeling en coating van metaal; Polijsten van oppervlakken van metaal; Metallurgische verwerking; Behandeling van materialen met laserstralen; Galvanisatie; Thermisch verzinken; Poedercoating van metaal; Het verven van metaal [uitgezonderd schilderwerk]; Afwerken van metalen; Bekleding van metaal; Afwerken van metalen; Metaalgieterij; Stampen van metalen; Extrusies van metaal; Metalliseren; Metallurgisch uitsmelten; Stanswerkzaamheden; Ponsen; Steken van metaal; Forceerwerkzaamheden met betrekking tot metaal; Smeedwerk; Het temperen; Temperen; Inpersen en emailleren van metaal; Behandeling en bedekking van materialen middels poedercoating; Bewerking van metalen onderdelen ten behoeve van corrosiewering door middel van thermisch verzinken en poedercoating; Verzinken in niet-galvanische procedés; Anodiseren; Natlakken; Passiveren en bekleden van metaal; Diensten op het gebied van de corrosiebescherming van metalen onderdelen, te weten thermisch verzinken; Poeder- en verfcoating.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Obróbka materiałów, Mianowicie obróbka cieplna i powlekanie metalu; Polerowanie powierzchni metalowych; Obróbka metalurgiczna; Obróbka materiałów wiązką laserową; Powlekanie metalu; Powlekanie ogniowe; Powłoki metalowe w proszku; Powlekanie metali farbami [poza pracami malarskimi]; Wykańczanie metali; Powlekanie metalu; Wykańczanie metali; Odlewanie metali; Tłoczenie metalu; Metalowe profile wyciskane; Metalizacja; Wytapianie metali; Usługi plombowania; Tłoczenie; Kształtowanie metali; Obróbka plastyczna w odniesieniu do metalu; Kowalstwo; hartowanie; Uplastycznianie; Wytłaczanie i emaliowanie metalu; Obróbka i powlekanie materiałów przez opryskiwanie; Obróbka części metalowych do celu ochrony karoserii poprzez cynkowanie ogniowe i powlekanie proszkowe; Cynkowanie w procesach niegalwanicznych; Anodowanie; Powlekanie na mokro; Pasywacja i platerowanie metali; Usługi w dziedzinie ochrony przed korozją części metalowych, mianowicie cynkowanie ogniowe; Powlekanie farbami i proszkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Tratamento de materiais, Nomeadamente tratamento térmico e revestimento de metais; Polimento de superfícies metálicas; Transformação metalúrgica; Tratamento de materiais por raio laser; Galvanização; Imersão a quente de metais; Revestimento com pó de metal; Revestimento de coloração de metais [exceto trabalhos de pintura]; Acabamento metálico; Revestimento [placagem] de metais; Acabamento metálico; Colagem de metais; Estampagem de metais; Extrusões metálicas; Metalização; Fundição metalúrgica; Serviços de estampagem; Furadores; Perfilagem de metais; Trabalhos de moldagem de metal; Trabalhos de forja; Têmpera; Maleabilização; Estampagem e esmaltagem de metais; Tratamento e revestimento de materiais por pulverização; Tratamento de peças metálicas para fins de protecção contra a corrosão através da galvanização a quente e revestimento a pó; Galvanização em processos não galvânicos; Anodização; Revestimento a molhado; Passivação e revestimento [placagem] de metais; Serviços no domínio da proteção contra a corrosão de peças metálicas, nomeadamente galvanizadas a quente; Revestimento de pó e tinta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Tratament de materiale, Și anume tratamente termice și placarea metalelor; Lustruire de suprafețe metalice; Prelucrare metalurgică; Tratarea materialelor cu raze laser; Acoperirea metalelor; Cufundare la cald; Produse de acoperire a metalului sub forma de pulbere; Acoperirea cu vopsea a metalelor [cu excepţia lucrărilor de vopsitorie]; Finisarea metalelor; Acoperirea metalelor; Finisarea metalelor; Turnarea metalelor; Ștanțarea metalelor; Extrudări metalice; Metalizare; Turnare în metalurgie; Servicii de imprimare; Ştanţare; Profilarea metalelor; Formare în legătură cu metalul; Lucrări de forjare; Călire; Maleabilizare; Impregnare și emailare de metale; Tratare şi acoperire de materiale prin pulverizare; Prelucrare de piese metalice pentru protecţie anticorozivă prin zincat la cald şi stratificare prin pulverizare; Servicii de zincare în procese negalvanice; Acoperire anodică; Acoperire umedă; Pasivizare şi placare de metale; Servicii în domeniul protecției anticorozive a pieselor metalice, și anume galvanizare la cald; Acoperire cu pulbere și vopsea colorată.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Spracovanie a úprava materiálov, Menovite tepelná úprava a povrchové nanášanie kovu; Leštenie povrchov z kovu; Metalurgické spracovanie; Spracovanie materiálov laserovým lúčom; Galvanizácia, elektrolytické pokovovanie; Pokovovanie ponorom; Práškové nanášanie kovov; Nanášanie farieb na kovy [okrem maliarskych prác]; Konečné opracovanie kovových výrobkov; Pokovovanie; Konečné opracovanie kovových výrobkov; Odlievanie kovov; Lisovanie kovov; Kovové výlisky; Metalizácia; Metalurgické tavenie; Služby pre potlač; Razenie; Profilovanie kovov; Práce, týkajúce sa zmien tvarov kovov; Kováčstvo; Kalenie; Temperovanie; Razenie a emailovanie kovu; Úprava a poťahovanie materiálov postrekom; Spracovanie kovových častí za účelom protikoróznej ochrany prostredníctvom žiarovéh pozinkovania a práškového nanášania; Pozinkovanie negalvanickým procesom; Anodizácia; Povrchová úprava za mokra; Pasivovanie kovov a pokovovanie; Služby v oblasti ochrany protikoróznej ochrany kovových častí, menovite žiarové pozinkovanie; Práškové nanášanie a nanášanie farieb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Obdelava materialov, In sicer toplotna obdelava in premazovanje kovin; Poliranje kovinskih površin; Metalurška obdelava; Obdelava materialov z laserskimi žarki; Premazovanje kovin; Vroče omakanje; Prašni premazi iz kovine; Premazovanje kovin z barvo [razen pleskarskih del]; Končna obdelava kovin; Premazovanje kovin; Končna obdelava kovin; Ulivanje kovin; Štancanje kovin; Kovinski deli, dobljeni z ekstruzijo; Metaliziranje; Metalurško taljenje; Storitve tiskanja; Izsekovanje; Kovinski profili; Oblikovalska dela v zvezi s kovino; Kovaštvo; Kaljenje; Tempranje; Vtiskanje in emajliranje kovin; Obdelava in prevlečenje materialov z razprševanjem; Obdelava kovinskih delov z namenom protikorozijske zaščite s pocinkanjem v ognju in prašnim premazovanjem; Pocinkanje v negalvanskih postopkih; Anodiziranje; Mokro premazovanje; Pasiviranje in nanašanje prevlek na kovine; Storitve na področju zaščite kovinskih delov proti koroziji, in sicer ognjeno cinkanje; Prašno in barvno premazovanje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Behandling av ämnen och material, Nämligen värmebehandling och beläggning av metall; Polering av ytor av metall; Metallurgisk bearbetning; Behandling av material med laserstråle; Galvanisering; Varmdoppning; Pulverlackering av metall; Färgbeläggning av metall [ej måleriarbeten]; Ytbehandling av metaller; Metallbeläggning; Ytbehandling av metaller; Metallgjutning; Metallstansning; Formpressade metalldelar; Metallisering; Metallurgisk smältning; Stanstjänster; Stansar; Metallprofiler; Omformningsarbeten med avseende på metall; Smedtjänster; Härdning; Temperering; Prägling och emaljering av metall; Behandling och beläggning av material genom pulverisering; Bearbetning av metalldelar för korrosionsskydd genom varmgalvanisering och pulverpåläggning; Förzinkning i icke-galvaniska förfaranden; Anodisering; Våtbeläggning; Passivering och plätering av metall; Tjänster inom området för korrosionsskydd för metalldelar, nämligen varmförzinkning; Pulver- och färgbeläggning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Научни и технологически услуги и свързани с тях изследователски и проектантски услуги; Услуги за промишлени анализи и изследвания; Проектиране и разработване на компютърен софтуер и хардуер; Изпитване на материали; Проучване в областта на физиката; Химически изследвания; Проучвания на технически проекти; Инженеринг; Изследвания в областта на механиката; Проучване и разработване (за трети лица); Технически консултации в областта на строителното инженерство.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vědecké a technologické služby a související výzkum a projektování; Analytické a výzkumné služby v průmyslu; Navrhování a vývoj počítačového hardwaru a softwaru; Testování materiálů; Fyzikální výzkum; Chemický výzkum; Technické projektové studie; Inženýrské služby; Výzkum ve strojírenství; Vývoj a výzkum nových výrobků; Technické poradenství v oboru stavebního inženýrství.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Videnskabelige og teknologiske tjenesteydelser samt forskning og design i forbindelse dermed; Industriel analyse og forskning; Design og udvikling af computer hardware og computer software; Afprøvning af materialer; Fysik (forskning); Kemiske undersøgelser; Tekniske projektundersøgelser; Ingeniørtjenesteydelser; Forskning vedrørende mekanik; Forskning i og udvikling af nye produkter (for andre); Teknisk rådgivning inden for bygningsingeniørvirksomhed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wissenschaftliche und technologische Dienstleistungen und Forschungsarbeiten und diesbezügliche Designerdienstleistungen; industrielle Analyse- und Forschungsdienstleistungen; Entwurf und Entwicklung von Computerhardware und -software; Materialprüfung; physikalische Forschungen; Forschungen auf dem Gebiet der Chemie; technische Projektstudien; Dienstleistungen von Ingenieuren; Forschungen auf dem Gebiet des Maschinenbaus; Entwicklungs- und Recherchedienste für Dritte bezüglich neuer Produkte; Technische Beratungsdienstleistungen im Bauingenieurswesen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Τεχνολογικές και επιστημονικές υπηρεσίες και σχετικές υπηρεσίες έρευνας και σχεδιασμού· Υπηρεσίες βιομηχανικής ανάλυσης και έρευνας· Σχεδιασμός και ανάπτυξη υλισμικού και λογισμικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Υλικών δοκιμασία· Έρευνες στον τομέα της φυσικής· Χημικές (Έρευνες -)· Μελέτες τεχνικών έργων· Μηχανολογικές υπηρεσίες· Μηχανολογικής (Έρευνες -)· Έρευνα και ανάπτυξη νέων προϊόντων για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Υπηρεσίες παροχής τεχνικών συμβουλών στον τομέα των έργων πολιτικού μηχανικού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Scientific and technological services and research and design relating thereto; Industrial analysis and research services; Design and development of computer hardware and software; Material testing; Research physics; Chemical research; Technical project studies; Engineering services; Mechanical research; Research and development (for others); Technical consultancy with regard to structural engineering.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios científicos y tecnológicos, así como servicios de investigación y diseño en estos ámbitos; Servicios de análisis e investigación industriales; Diseño y desarrollo de equipos informáticos y de software; Ensayo de materiales; Investigaciones de física; Investigación química; Estudios de proyectos técnicos; Servicios de ingeniería; Investigación en mecánica; Investigación y desarrollo de nuevos productos para terceros; Servicios de asesoría técnica en obras de ingeniería de construcción.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Teaduslikud ja tehnoloogilised uuringud ja projekteerimine teenusena; Tööstusanalüüside ja -uuringute teenused; Arvutiriistvara ja -tarkvara projekteerimine ja arendus; Materjalitestid, materjalide teimimine, testimine, katsetamine; Füüsikalised uuringud; Keemilised uuringud; Tehnilised projektiuuringud; Inseneriteenused; Mehaanikauuringud; Uurimine ja väjaarendamine (teenusena); Ehitustehnika tehniline nõustamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tieteelliset ja teknologiset palvelut sekä niihin liittyvä tutkimus ja suunnittelu; Teolliset analyysi- ja tutkimuspalvelut; Tietokonelaitteistojen ja -ohjelmistojen suunnittelu ja kehittäminen; Tekstiilien koestus; Fysiikan tutkimus; Kemiallinen tutkimus; Teknisten hankkeiden hanketutkimukset; Insinööripalvelut; Mekaniikkaan liittyvä tutkimus; Uusien tuotteiden tutkimus ja kehittely muiden lukuun; Tekniset neuvontapalvelut rakennustekniikan alalla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services scientifiques et technologiques ainsi que services de recherches et de conception y relatifs; Services d'analyses et de recherches industrielles; Conception et développement d'ordinateurs et de logiciels; Essai de matériaux; Recherches en physique; Recherches en chimie; Étude de projets techniques; Services d'ingénierie; Recherches en mécanique; Recherche et développement de nouveaux produits pour des tiers; Services de conseils techniques dans le domaine du génie civil.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Znanstvene i tehnološke usluge kao i pripadajuće usluge istraživanja i koncepcije; Usluge industrijskih analiza i istraživanja; Koncepcija i razvoj računala i računalnih programa [softvera]; Ispitivanje materijala; Istraživačka fizika; Istraživanje u kemiji; Studije tehničkih projekata; Inženjerske usluge; Istraživanja u mehanici; Istraživanje i razvoj novih proizvoda za treće osobe; Usluge tehničkog savjetovanja u građevinskom inženjeringu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tudományos és műszaki szolgáltatások, valamint az idetartozó tervezői és kutatói tevékenység; Ipari elemző és kutató szolgáltatások; Számítástechnikai hardver és szoftver tervezés és fejlesztés; Anyagtesztelés; Fizikai kutatások; Vegyészeti kutatás; Műszaki tervtanulmányok készítése; Mérnöki munkák, szolgáltatások; Mechanikai kutatás; Kutatás és fejlesztés (mások számára); Műszaki tanácsadási szolgáltatások építőmérnöki területen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi scientifici e tecnologici e servizi di ricerca e progettazione ad essi relativi; Servizi di analisi e ricerche industriali; Progettazione e sviluppo di hardware e software; Collaudi di materiali; Ricerche in fisica; Ricerche in chimica; Studi di progetti tecnici; Servizi di ingegneria; Ricerche in meccanica; Ricerca e sviluppo di nuovi prodotti per conto terzi; Servizi di consulenza tecnica in materia d'ingegneria edile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Mokslo ir technologijų paslaugos ir su tuo susiję tyrimai ir projektavimas; Pramoninės analizės ir tyrimų paslaugos; Kompiuterių programinės ir aparatinės įrangos projektavimas ir tobulinimas; Medžiagų bandymai; Fizikos tyrimai; Cheminiai tyrimai; Techninių projektų studijos; Inžinerijos paslaugos; Mechanikos tyrimai; Tyrimai ir vystymas (paslaugos kitiems); Techninių konsultacijų paslaugos statybos inžinerijos srityje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Zinātniskie un tehnoloģiskie pakalpojumi, izpēte un projektēšana šajās jomās; Rūpnieciskās analīzes un izpētes pakalpojumi; Datoru aparatūras un programmatūras projektēšana, izstrāde un pilnveidošana; Materiālu pārbaude; Fizikas pētījumi; Ķīmiskā izpēte; Tehnisko projektu izpēte; Inženiertehniskie pakalpojumi; Izpēte mehānikas jomā; Izpēte un izstrāde (citu vajadzībām); Tehniski konsultatīvie pakalpojumi būvinženierijas jautājumos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi xjentifiċi u teknoloġiċi u riċerka u disinn relatati ma' l-istess; Analiżi industrijali u servizzi ta' riċerka; Disinn u żvilupp ta' ħardwer u softwer tal-kompjuter; Testijiet ta' materjali; Riċerka dwar il-fiżika; Riċerka kimika; Studji tekniċi ta' proġetti; Servizzi ta' Inġinerija; Riċerka fil-mekkanika; Riċerka u żvilupp (għal ħaddieħor); Servizzi ta' konsulenza teknika fil-qasam tal-inġinerija ċivili.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Wetenschappelijke en technologische diensten, alsmede bijbehorende onderzoeks- en ontwerpdiensten; Industriële analyse en onderzoek; Ontwerpen en ontwikkelen van computers en van software; Testen van materialen; Fysisch onderzoek; Chemisch onderzoek; Technische projectstudies; Ingenieursdiensten; Onderzoek op het gebied van de mechanica; Onderzoek en ontwikkeling van nieuwe producten voor derden; Technische adviesdiensten op het gebied van civiele techniek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Naukowe i techniczne usługi i badania oraz ich projektowanie; Przemysłowe analizy i usługi badawcze; Projektowanie i rozwój komputerowego sprzętu i oprogramowania; Testowanie materiałów; Badania fizyczne; Badania chemiczne; Opracowywanie projektów technicznych; Usługi inżynieryjne; Badania w dziedzinie mechaniki; Działalność badawczo-rozwojowa (dla osób trzecich); Usługi doradztwa technicznego w zakresie inżynierii budowlanej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços científicos e tecnológicos bem como serviços de pesquisas e de concepção a eles referentes; Serviços de análises e pesquisas industriais; Concepção e desenvolvimento de computadores e de programas de computadores; Testes a materiais; Pesquisas em física; Investigação química; Estudos de projectos técnicos; Serviços de engenharia; Investigação mecânica; Pesquisa e desenvolvimento de novos produtos para terceiros; Serviços de consultadoria técnica no domínio da engenharia civil.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii ştiinţifice şi tehnologice, precum şi servicii de cercetare şi de creaţie, referitoare la acestea; Servicii de analiză și cercetare industrială; Crearea şi dezvoltarea calculatoarelor şi a programelor de calculator; Testarea materialelor textile; Cercetare în fizică; Cercetări chimice; Studii de proiecte tehnice; Inginerie; Studii în domeniul mecanicii; Cercetare si dezvoltare (pentru terti); Servicii de consultanţă tehnică în construcţii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vedecké a technologické služby a s nimi súvisiaci výskum a projektovanie; Priemyselné analýzy a priemyselný výskum; Návrh a vývoj počítačového hardvéru a softvéru; Testovanie materiálov; Výskum v oblasti fyziky; Chemický výskum; Technické projektové štúdie; Inžinierske činnosti; Strojársky výskum; Prieskum a vývoj (pre iných); Technické poradenstvo v oblasti výstavby inžinierskych stavieb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Znanstvene in tehnološke storitve ter raziskave in storitve oblikovanja - projektiranja v zvezi s tem; Industrijske analize in raziskave; Oblikovanje in razvoj računalniške strojne in programske opreme; Testiranje materialov; Fizikalne raziskave; Kemične raziskave; Študije tehničnih projektov; Inženirske storitve; Raziskave na področju strojništva; Raziskave in razvoj (za druge); Tehnične svetovalne storitve na področju gradbenega inženiringa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Vetenskapliga och teknologiska tjänster och därtill relaterad forskning och design; Industriella analyser och forskningstjänster; Design och utveckling av datahårdvaror och mjukvaror; Materialprovning; Fysikvetenskapliga forskningstjänster; Kemisk forskning; Tekniska projektstudier; Ingenjörstjänster; Forskning avseende mekanik; Forsknings- och utvecklingsjänster avseende nya produkter; Tekniska rådgivningstjänster inom byggnadsingenjörsverksamhet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/171</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-08</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>365903</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>31672</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
