<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-03T23:06:45</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226534</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226534</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="2" status="6">Application under examination</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-04-17</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>GREENTESTING</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162319020</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226534/000162319020.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.11</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.13</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.14</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>25.05.94</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>29.01.03</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>29.01.08</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Стендове за изпитване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Testovací stanoviště.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Prøvebænke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Prüfstände; Prüfanlagen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Τράπεζες δοκιμών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Test benches.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bancos de ensayo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Katsestendid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Koepenkit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bancs d'essai [appareils de contrôle].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Mjerne ploče.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Próbapadok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Banchi di prova.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Bandymų stendai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pārbaudes stendi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Banek tat-testijiet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Testapparatuur.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Stanowiska do prób.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Bancos de ensaio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Bancuri de probe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Skúšobné lavice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Testne delovne mize.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Provbänkar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за разработване на методи за тестване; Услуги по технически изпитвания; Научни и технологични услуги; Инженерно чертане; Консултантски услуги, свързани с инженеринга на продукти; Оценяване в областта на технологията, предоставено от инженери; Услуги за инженерен дизайн с помощта на компютър; Инженерни консултантски услуги; Инженерно тестване; Изготвяне на инженерни доклади; Инженерни услуги, свързани с проектиране на сгради; Инженерни услуги, свързани с анализиране на машини; Инженерни услуги в областта на двигателната сила; Технически инженерни услуги; Инженерно проектантски услуги и консултации; Планиране на технически проекти в областта на инженерството; Услуги, свързани с управление на инженерни проекти; Оценки в областта на технологията, предоставени от инженери; Консултантски услуги в областта на технологичното развитие; Консултантски услуги, свързани с използването на електричество; Консултантски услуги, относно енергоефективността; Консултантски услуги, свързани с технологични изследвания; Промишлен анализ с помощта на компютър; Провеждане на промишлени тестове; Професионални консултации, свързани с технологии; Професионални консултации относно енергийна ефективност на сгради; Строително проектиране; Планиране на технически проекти; Технически консултации, свързани с разработването на продукти; Технологични услуги; Провеждане на промишлени експерименти; Анализ на разработката на продукти; Услуги за технологични анализи; Анализ и оценка на разработването на продукти; Извличане на данни; Консултиране в областта на строителното проектиране; Промишлени изпитания; Промишлено изпитване, с помощта на компютър; Услуги за техническо измерване и тестване; Тестване на нови продукти; Проектиране и тестване, свързани с разработка на нов продукт; Тестване на превозни средства; Тестване на компютърно оборудване; Тестване на апаратура; Тестване на апарати в областта на електроинженерството; Тестване на функционалността на машини; Разработване на методи за тестване; Разработване на измервателни и тестови методи; Услуги свързани с компютърна диагностика и проби; Контрол на качеството и тестване; Услуги за анализ и тестване във връзка с електроинженерни апарати; Услуги за контролно тестване на качеството за промишлени машини; Тестване, анализ и оценка на стоки и услуги на други с цел сертифициране; Услуги за техническо измерване; Технически инспекционни услуги; Компютърно подпомагани услуги за инженерено проектиране; Инженерно проектиране и чертане с помощта на компютри; Инженерни услуги за трети лица; Чертожни услуги от рода на техническо чертане; Машинен инженер; Инженерно проучване; Инженерни услуги и инженерни услуги с помощта на компютри; Технологични инженерни анализи; Разработване на нови технологии за трети лица; Измервателни услуги; Услуги по проучване на гуми; Услуги за изследване и разработване в областта на инженеринга; Мониторинг на състоянието на течности; Мониторинг на състоянието на смазки; Инженеринг; Дизайн и тестване на нови продукти; Услуги за неразрушително тестване; Изпитване, удостоверяване и контрол на качеството; Услуги за тестване за сертифициране на качество или стандарти; Проектиране и разработване на методи за тестване и анализ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby vývoje testovacích metod; Služby v oblasti technických zkoušek; Vědecké a technologické služby; Technické kreslení; Poradenské služby v oblasti projektování výrobků; Hodnocení v oblasti technologie prováděné inženýry; Služby v oblasti počítačem podporovaných konstrukčních návrhů; Služby v oblasti technických konzultací; Inženýrské testování; Příprava inženýrských zpráv; Inženýrské služby týkající se návrhu konstrukcí; Inženýrské služby týkající se analýz strojního zařízení; Inženýrské služby v oblasti hnacích energií; Technické inženýrství; Konstrukční návrhy a konzultace; Technické projektové plánování v oboru inženýrství; Služby v oblasti řízení inženýrských projektů; Odhady v oblasti technologie prováděné inženýry; Konzultační služby v oblasti technologického vývoje; Poradenské služby vztahující se k využívání energie; Poradenské služby vztahující se k energetické účinnosti; Konzultační služby v oblasti technologického výzkumu; Počítačem podporovaná průmyslová analýza; Provádění průmyslových testů; Odborné poradenství vztahující se k technologiím; Odborné poradenství vztahující se k zachování energie; Projektování ve výstavbě; Technické projektové plánování; Technické poradenství vztahující se k vývoji výrobků; Technologické služby; Provádění průmyslových experimentů; Analýza vývoje produktů; Služby v oblasti technologické analýzy; Analýza a hodnocení v oblasti vývoje výrobků; Získávání dat (Data mining); Poradenství v oblasti stavebního projektování; Průmyslové testování; Průmyslové testování pomocí počítače; Služby technického měření a testování; Testování nových výrobků; Návrhy a testování pro vývoj nových produktů; Testování vozidel; Testování výpočetního vybavení; Testování strojního vybavení; Testování přístrojů v oblasti elektrotechniky; Testování funkčnosti strojů; Vývoj testovacích metod; Vývoj měřicích a testovacích metod; Služby v oblasti počítačem podporovaného diagnostického testování; Kontrola kvality a testování; Analýza a testování vztahující se k elektrotechnickým přístrojům; Kontrola kvality průmyslových strojů; Testování, analyzování a hodnocení zboží a služeb druhých pro účely certifikace; Služby technického měření; Služby v oblasti technické inspekce; Služby v oblasti počítačem podporovaného konstrukčního návrhářství; Služby v oblasti počítačem podporovaného konstrukčního návrhářství a kreslení; Inženýrské služby pro třetí osoby; Služby projektantů ve formě technických výkresů; Strojní inženýrství; Technický průzkum; Inženýrské práce a služby počítačem podporovaných inženýrských prací; Technologické inženýrské analýzy; Vývoj nových technologií pro třetí osoby; Služby v oblasti měření; Služby v oblasti výzkumu pneumatik; Služby výzkumu a vývoje v oblasti inženýrství; Kontrola stavu kapalin; Kontrola stavu lubrikantů; Inženýrské služby; Návrhy a testování nových produktů; Služby nedestruktivního testování; Služby testování, služby ověřování a služby kontroly kvality; Testovací služby pro certifikaci kvality nebo standardů; Navrhování a vývoj testovacích a analytických metod.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tjenesteydelser vedrørende udvikling af metoder til testning; Tjenesteydelser inden for tekniske tests; Videnskabelige og teknologiske tjenesteydelser; Ingeniørteknisk tegning; Konsulentvirksomhed vedrørende produktudvikling; Teknologiske vurderinger foretaget af ingeniører; Ingeniørvirksomhed vedrørende computerstøttet design; Rådgivning vedrørende ingeniørvirksomhed; Teknisk testning; Udarbejdelse af ingeniørrapporter; Ingeniørvirksomhed vedrørende design af konstruktioner; Ingeniørvirksomhed vedrørende analyse af maskiner; Ingeniørvirksomhed inden for mekanisk fremdrift; Teknisk ingeniørvirksomhed; Design og rådgivning inden for ingeniørvirksomhed; Teknisk projektplanlægning inden for ingeniørvirksomhed; Ingeniørmæssig projektledelse; Teknologiske estimeringer udført af ingeniører; Rådgivning vedrørende teknologisk udvikling; Rådgivning vedrørende anvendelse af energi; Rådgivningsvirksomhed vedrørende energieffektivitet; Konsulentbistand vedrørende teknologisk forskning; Tjenester vedrørende computerstøttede industrianalyser; Gennemførelse af industrielle test; Ekspertrådgivning vedrørende teknologi; Professionel konsulentbistand vedrørende energibevarelse; Udarbejdelse af byggeplaner; Teknisk projektplanlægning; Teknisk rådgivning inden for produktudvikling; Teknologiske tjenesteydelser; Gennemførelse af industrielle eksperimenter; Analyse af produktudvikling; Teknologisk analyse; Analyse og bedømmelse af produktudvikling; Vidensafdækning (datamining); Konsulentbistand inden for udarbejdelse af bygningsplaner; Industriel testning; Computerstøttet industriafprøvning; Tjenester vedrørende teknisk måle- og testvirksomhed; Afprøvning af nye produkter; Design og afprøvning vedrørende udviklingen af nye produkter; Testning af befordringsmidler; Testning af udstyr til computeranvendelse; Afprøvning af maskiner; Afprøvning af apparater inden for elektroteknik; Afprøvning af maskiners funktionalitet; Udvikling af afprøvningsmetoder; Udvikling af måle- og afprøvningsmetoder; Computerstøttet, diagnostisk testning; Kvalitetskontrol og -afprøvning; Analyse- og afprøvningsvirksomhed vedrørende elektrotekniske apparater; Kvalitetskontrol og afprøvning af industrimaskiner; Afprøvning, analyse og vurdering af andres varer og tjenesteydelser med henblik på certificering; Tjenester vedrørende teknisk måling; Teknisk inspektion; Computerstøttede bygningsingeniørdesigntjenester; Computerstøttet virksomhed inden for ingeniørdesign og -tegning; Ingeniørvirksomhed for andre; Teknisk designvirksomhed i form af teknisk tegning; Mekanisk ingeniørvirksomhed; Forskning inden for bygningsingeniørvirksomhed; Ingeniørvirksomhed og computerstøttet ingeniørvirksomhed; Teknologisk analyse inden for ingeniørvirksomhed; Udvikling af ny teknologi for andre; Målingsvirksomhed; Forskning inden for dæk; Forskning og udvikling inden for ingeniørarbejde; Overvågning af væsketilstande; Tilstandsovervågning af smøremidler; Ingeniørtjenesteydelser; Design og afprøvning af nye produkter; Ikke-destruktiv afprøvning (NDT); Afprøvning, verificering og kvalitetskontrol; Afprøvningsvirksomhed i forbindelse med certificering af kvalitet eller standarder; Design og udvikling af afprøvnings- og analysemetoder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Entwicklung von Prüfverfahren; Technische Tests; Wissenschaftliche und technologische Dienstleistungen; Anfertigung von technischen Zeichnungen; Beratungsdienstleistungen bezüglich Produktentwicklung; Bewertungsdienste von Ingenieuren im technologischen Bereich; Computergestützte Konstruktionsplanung; Dienstleistungen im Bereich der ingenieurtechnischen Beratung; Durchführung technischer Prüfungen; Erstellung von ingenieurtechnischen Berichten; Ingenieurdienstleistungen für den Entwurf von Konstruktionen; Ingenieurdienstleistungen für die Analyse von Maschinen; Ingenieurleistungen zur Antriebsenergie; Technische Ingenieurdienstleistungen; Technische Planung und Beratung; Technische Projektplanung im Ingenieurwesen; Technisches Projektmanagement; Von Ingenieuren vorgenommene Bewertungen im technologischen Bereich; Beratung im Bereich der technologischen Entwicklung; Beratungsdienste bezüglich des Energieeinsatzes; Beratungsdienste in Bezug auf die Energieeffizienz; Beratungsdienstleistungen bezüglich technologischer Forschung; Computergestützte industrielle Analysedienstleistungen; Durchführung industrieller Tests; Fachliche Beratung bezüglich Technologie; Fachliche Beratung bezüglich der Energieeinsparung; Konstruktionsplanung; Planung technischer Projekte; Technische Beratung in Bezug auf Produktentwicklung; Technologische Dienstleistungen; Durchführung von industriellen Versuchen; Analyse der Produktentwicklung; Durchführung technologischer Analysen; Evaluation und Analyse von Produktentwicklung; Analyse großer Datenmengen hinsichtlich der Beziehungen der Daten untereinander; Beratung auf dem Gebiet der Konstruktionsplanung; Durchführung technischer Tests; Technische Prüfung; Computergestützte technische Prüfungen; Durchführung technischer Messungen und Prüfungen; Prüfung neuer Produkte; Entwurf und Prüfung für die Entwicklung neuer Produkte; Prüfung von Fahrzeugen; Prüfung von Computergeräten; Prüfung von Geräten; Prüfung von Geräten im Bereich der Elektrotechnik; Prüfung von Maschinen; Prüfung von maschinellen Apparaten; Prüfung der Funktionalität von Maschinen; Entwicklung von Prüfmethoden; Entwicklung von Mess- und Prüfmethoden; Computergestützte diagnostische Prüfungsdienstleistungen; Durchführung von Qualitätskontrollen und -prüfungen; Analysen und Prüfdienste bezüglich elektrotechnischer Geräte; Prüfleistungen zur Qualitätskontrolle von industriellen Geräten; Prüfung, Analyse und Bewertung von Waren und Dienstleistungen Dritter für Zertifizierungszwecke; Durchführung von technischen Messungen; Technische Kontrolle; Computergestütztes Konstruieren; Computergestütztes Konstruieren und technisches Zeichnen; Dienstleistungen eines Ingenieurs für andere; Dienstleistungen eines technischen Zeichners; Ingenieurdienstleistungen im Maschinenbau; Ingenieurtechnische Forschung; Ingenieurtechnische und computergestützte ingenieurtechnische Dienstleistungen; Ingenieurtechnologische Analysen; Entwicklung neuer Technologien für Dritte; Durchführung von Messungen; Erforschung von Reifen; Forschungs- und Entwicklungsdienste im Bereich Ingenieurwesen; Zustandsmessung von Flüssigkeiten; Zustandsmessung von Schmiermitteln; Dienstleistungen von Ingenieuren; Entwurf und Prüfung neuer Produkte; Zerstörungsfreie Prüfverfahren; Prüfung, Authentifizierung und Qualitätskontrolle; Prüfdienste zur Qualitäts- und Standardszertifizierung; Entwurf und Entwicklung von Prüf- und Analyseverfahren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες ανάπτυξης μεθόδων δοκιμής· Υπηρεσίες τεχνικών δοκιμών· Επιστημονικές και τεχνολογικές υπηρεσίες· Μηχανολογικό σχέδιο· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σχετικά με το μηχανικό σχεδιασμό προϊόντων· Αξιολογήσεις μηχανικών στον τομέα της τεχνολογίας· Υπηρεσίες μηχανολογικού σχεδιασμού με τη βοήθεια ηλεκτρονικού υπολογιστή· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών μηχανικής· Μηχανικές δοκιμές· Σύνταξη εκθέσεων μηχανικών· Υπηρεσίες μηχανικής για το σχεδιασμό κατασκευών· Υπηρεσίες μηχανικής για την ανάλυση μηχανημάτων· Υπηρεσίες μηχανικής στον τομέα της κινητήριας ισχύος· Τεχνική μηχανική· Παροχή συμβουλών και σχεδιασμός σε θέματα μηχανικής· Σχεδιασμός τεχνικών έργων στον τομέα της μηχανικής· Υπηρεσίες διαχείρισης μηχανικών έργων· Εκτιμήσεις μηχανικών στον τομέα της τεχνολογίας· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών στον τομέα της τεχνολογικής ανάπτυξης· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σχετικά με τη χρήση ενέργειας· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σε σχέση με την ενεργειακή απόδοση· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σχετικά με την τεχνολογική έρευνα· Υπηρεσίες βιομηχανικής ανάλυσης με τη βοήθεια ηλεκτρονικού υπολογιστή· Διεξαγωγή βιομηχανικών δοκιμών· Παροχή συμβουλών από ειδικούς σε σχέση με την τεχνολογία· Παροχή επαγγελματικών συμβουλών σε σχέση με την εξοικονόμηση ενέργειας· Σύσταση σχεδίων κατασκευών· Τεχνικός σχεδιασμός έργων· Παροχή τεχνικών συμβουλών σε σχέση με ανάπτυξη προϊόντων· Τεχνολογικές υπηρεσίες· Διεξαγωγή βιομηχανικών πειραμάτων· Ανάλυση ανάπτυξης προϊόντων· Υπηρεσίες τεχνολογικής ανάλυσης· Ανάλυση και αξιολόγηση της ανάπτυξης προϊόντων· Εξόρυξη δεδομένων· Παροχή συμβουλών στον κλάδο του σχεδιασμού κτιρίων· Βιομηχανικές δοκιμές· Βιομηχανικοί έλεγχοι με τη βοήθεια υπολογιστή· Υπηρεσίες τεχνικών μετρήσεων και δοκιμών· Δοκιμή νέων προϊόντων· Υπηρεσίες σχεδιασμού και δοκιμών για την ανάπτυξη νέων προϊόντων· Δοκιμές οχημάτων· Δοκιμές εξοπλισμού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Δοκιμές συσκευών· Δοκιμή συσκευών στον τομέα της ηλεκτρολογικής μηχανικής· Δοκιμή λειτουργικότητας μηχανών· Ανάπτυξη μεθόδων δοκιμής· Ανάπτυξη μεθόδων μέτρησης και δοκιμής· Υπηρεσίες διαγνωστικών δοκιμών με τη βοήθεια υπολογιστή· Ποιοτικός έλεγχος και Δοκιμή· Υπηρεσίες ανάλυσης και δοκιμής σε σχέση με εξοπλισμό ηλεκτρολογικής μηχανικής· Υπηρεσίες δοκιμής ελέγχου ποιότητας για βιομηχανικά μηχανήματα· Δοκιμή, ανάλυση και αξιολόγηση των αγαθών και υπηρεσιών άλλων για σκοπούς πιστοποίησης· Υπηρεσίες τεχνικών μετρήσεων· Υπηρεσίες τεχνικής επιθεώρησης· Υπηρεσίες μηχανικού σχεδίου με τη βοήθεια υπολογιστή· Υπηρεσίες μηχανικού σχεδιασμού και σχεδίου με τη βοήθεια υπολογιστή· Υπηρεσίες μηχανικού για τρίτους· Υπηρεσίες σχεδιαστή με τη μορφή κατάρτισης τεχνικών σχεδίων· Υπηρεσίες μηχανολόγου μηχανικού· Έρευνα στον τομέα της μηχανικής· Μηχανική και υπηρεσίες μηχανικής με τη βοήθεια υπολογιστή· Τεχνολογική μηχανική ανάλυση· Ανάπτυξη νέων τεχνολογιών για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Υπηρεσίες μέτρησης· Υπηρεσίες έρευνας ελαστικών· Υπηρεσίες έρευνας και ανάπτυξης στον κλάδο της Μηχανικής· Παρακολούθηση κατάστασης σε σχέση με ρευστά· Παρακολούθηση κατάστασης σε σχέση με λιπαντικά· Μηχανολογικές υπηρεσίες· Σχεδιασμός και δοκιμή νέων προϊόντων· Υπηρεσίες μη καταστρεπτικών δοκιμών· Δοκιμές, πιστοποίηση και ποιοτικός έλεγχος· Υπηρεσίες δοκιμής για την πιστοποίηση ποιότητας ή συμμόρφωσης με πρότυπα· Σχεδιασμός και ανάπτυξη μεθόδων δοκιμής και ανάλυσης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Services for the development of methods of testing; Technical testing services; Science and technology services; Engineering drawing; Consultancy services relating to product engineering; Assessment in the field of technology provided by engineers; Computer assisted engineering design services; Engineering consultancy services; Engineering testing; Preparation of engineering reports; Engineering services for the design of structures; Engineering services for the analysis of machinery; Engineering services in the field of motive power; Technical engineering; Engineering design and consultancy; Technical project planning in the field of engineering; Engineering project management services; Estimations in the field of technology provided by engineers; Consultancy services in the field of technological development; Advisory services relating to the use of energy; Advisory services relating to energy efficiency; Consultancy services relating to technological research; Computer aided industrial analysis services; Conducting industrial tests; Professional consultancy relating to technology; Professional consultancy relating to the conservation of energy; Construction drafting; Technical project planning; Technical consultancy relating to product development; Technological services; Conducting industrial experiments; Analysis of product development; Technological analysis services; Analysis and evaluation of product development; Data mining; Consultancy in the field of construction drafting; Industrial testing; Computer aided industrial testing; Technical measuring and testing; New products (Testing of -); Design and testing for new product development; Testing of vehicles; Testing of computing equipment; Testing of machinery; Testing of apparatus in the field of electrical engineering; Testing the functionality of machines; Development of testing methods; Development of measuring and testing methods; Computer aided diagnostic testing services; Quality checking and testing; Analysis and testing services relating to electrical engineering apparatus; Quality control testing services for industrial machinery; Testing, analysis and evaluation of the goods and services of others for the purpose of certification; Technical measuring; Technical inspection services; Computer-aided engineering design services; Computer-aided engineering design and drawing services; Engineering services for others; Draftsman's services in the nature of technical drawing; Mechanical engineering; Engineering research; Engineering and computer-aided engineering services; Technological engineering analysis; Development of new technology for others; Measurement services; Tyre research services; Research and development services in the field of engineering; Condition monitoring relating to fluids; Condition monitoring relating to lubricants; Engineering services; Design and testing of new products; Non-destructive testing services; Testing, authentication and quality control; Testing services for the certification of quality or standards; Design and development of testing and analysis methods.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de desarrollo de métodos de pruebas; Servicios de ensayo técnico; Servicios científicos y tecnológicos; Dibujo de ingeniería; Servicios de consultoría en materia de ingeniería de productos; Peritajes tecnológicos realizados por ingenieros; Servicios de diseño de ingeniería asistida por ordenador; Servicios de consultoría de ingeniería; Ensayos de ingeniería; Preparación de informes de ingeniería; Servicios de ingeniería para el diseño de estructuras; Servicios de ingeniería para el análisis de maquinaria; Servicios de ingeniería en materia de fuerzas motrices; Ingeniería técnica; Servicios de consultoría sobre ingeniería y diseño técnico; Planificación de proyectos técnicos en el sector de la ingeniería; Servicios de gestión de proyectos de ingeniería; Estimaciones tecnológicas realizadas por ingenieros; Servicios de consultoría en el ámbito del desarrollo tecnológico; Servicios de asesoramiento relacionados con el consumo de energía; Servicios de asesoramiento en materia de eficacia energética; Servicios de consultoría en materia de investigación tecnológica; Servicios de análisis industriales asistidos por ordenador; Realización de ensayos industriales; Consultas profesionales relativas a la tecnología; Consultoría profesional en materia de ahorro energético; Elaboración de planos para la construcción; Planificación de proyectos técnicos; Consultoría técnica en desarrollo de productos; Servicios tecnológicos; Realización de experimentos industriales; Análisis del desarrollo de productos; Servicios de análisis tecnológicos; Análisis y evaluación del desarrollo de productos; Minería de datos (depuración de datos); Consultoría sobre elaboración de planos de construcción; Ensayos industriales; Ensayo industrial asistido por ordenador; Mediciones y ensayos técnicos; Ensayo de nuevos productos; Diseño y pruebas para el desarrollo de nuevos productos; Prueba de vehículos; Comprobación de equipos informáticos; Ensayos de máquinas; Comprobación de aparatos en el campo de la ingeniería eléctrica; Ensayo de la funcionalidad de máquinas; Desarrollo de métodos de pruebas; Desarrollo de métodos de medición y ensayo; Servicios de pruebas de diagnóstico asistidas por ordenador; Controles y pruebas de calidad; Servicios de análisis y prueba de aparatos de ingeniería eléctrica; Pruebas de control de calidad de maquinaria industrial; Pruebas, análisis y evaluación de productos y servicios de terceros para certificación; Mediciones técnicas; Servicios de inspección técnica; Servicios de diseño técnico asistidos por ordenador; Servicios de diseño técnico y dibujo asistidos por ordenador; Servicios de ingeniería para terceros; Servicios de dibujantes [dibujo técnico]; Ingeniería mecánica; Investigación de ingeniería; Servicios de ingeniería y de ingeniería asistida por ordenador; Análisis de ingeniería tecnológica; Desarrollo de nuevas tecnologías para terceros; Servicios de mediciones; Servicios de investigación de neumáticos; Servicios de investigación y desarrollo en el ámbito de la ingeniería; Monitorización del estado de fluidos; Monitorización del estado de lubricantes; Servicios de ingeniería; Diseño y pruebas de nuevos productos; Servicios de ensayo no destructivo; Pruebas, autenticaciones y control de calidad; Servicios de comprobación para certificar la calidad o normativas; Diseño y desarrollo de métodos de prueba y análisis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Testimismeetodite arendamine; Tehnilise testimise teenused; Teadus- ja tehnoloogiateenused; Tehniline joonestamine; Tootetehnikakonsultatsioonid; Inseneride tehnikahinnangute teenused; Arvutipõhised projekteerimisteenused; Insener-tehnilised konsultatsioonid; Insener-tehniline testimine; Insener-tehniliste aruannete koostamine; Inseneriteenused tarindite projekteerimiseks; Inseneriteenused masinate analüüsimiseks; Mootoritehnika inseneriteenused; Insener-tehnilised teenused; Projekteerimine ja insenerikonsultatsioonid; Tehnikavaldkondade tehniline projekteerimine; Tehniliste projektide juhtimisteenused; Inseneride tehnikaprognooside teenused; Tehnoloogilise arendamise konsultatsiooniteenused; Energiatarbimisalane nõustamine; Energiatõhususalane nõustamine; Tehnoloogiliste uuringute konsultatsiooniteenused; Arvutipõhise tööstusanalüüsi teenused; Tööstuskatsete läbiviimine; Professionaalsed tehnoloogiaalased konsultatsioonid; Professionaalsed energiasäästlikkuse konsultatsioonid; Ehitusprojekteerimine, tarindustööd; Tehniline projekteerimine; Tootearenduse tehniline nõustamine; Tehnoloogilised teenused; Tööstuslike eksperimentide korraldamine; Tootearenduse analüüs; Tehnoloogilised analüüsid; Tootearenduse analüüsimine ja hindamine; Andmekaeve; Ehitusprojekteerimise konsultatsioonid; Tööstuslik katsetamine; Arvutipõhised tööstuskatsed; Tehnilised mõõte- ja katseteenused; Uute toodete testimine; Uute toodete disainimine ja testimine; Sõidukite testimine; Arvutiseadmete testimine; Aparatuuri testimine; Elektrotehnikaseadmete katsetamine; Masinate funktsioonide katsetamine; Testimismeetodite väljatöötamine; Mõõte- ja katsemeetodite arendamine; Diagnostilised testid arvuti abil; Kvaliteedikontroll ja -testimine; Elektrotehnikaseadmete analüüsi- ja katsetamisteenused; Tööstusseadmete kvaliteedikontrolli testimisteenused; Kolmandate isikute kaupade ja teenuste katsetamine, analüüsimine ja hindamine sertifitseerimiseks; Tehnilise mõõtmise teenused; Tehnilise inspektsiooni teenused; Arvutipõhised insenertehnilised projekteerimisteenused; Arvutipõhiste tehniliste tööde projekteerimine ja visandamine; Inseneriteenused tellimisel; Joonestajateenused; Masinaehitus; Tehnilised uuringud, inseneriteaduse uurimustööd; Inseneriteenused ja arvutipõhised insenertehnilised teenused; Tehnoloogilise projekteerimise analüüs; Uute tehnoloogiate väljatöötamine; Mõõtmisteenused; Rehvide teadustegevus; Teadus- ja arendusteenused inseneriteaduste valdkonnas; Vedelike seisundi seire; Määrdeainete seisundi seire; Inseneriteenused; Uute toodete projekteerimine ja testimine; Mittepurustava katsetamise teenused; Testimine, autentimine ja kvaliteedikontroll; Kvaliteedi- või standardisertifitseerimise katseteenused; Katse- ja analüüsimeetodite väljatöötamine ja arendamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Testausmenetelmien kehittämispalvelut; Tekniset testauspalvelut; Tieteelliset ja teknologiset palvelut; Tekninen piirustus; Tuotetekniikkaan liittyvät konsultointipalvelut; Insinöörien tekemät tekniset arvioinnit; Tietokoneavusteiset tekniset suunnittelupalvelut; Tekniset konsultointipalvelut; Tekninen testaus; Insinööriraporttien suunnittelu; Tekniset suunnittelupalvelut rakenteiden suunnittelua varten; Tekniset suunnittelupalvelut koneiden analysointia varten; Tekniset suunnittelupalvelut käyttövoiman alalla; Tekninen suunnittelu; Tekninen suunnittelu ja konsultointi; Tekninen hankkeiden suunnittelu teknisen suunnittelun alalla; Teknisten hankkeiden hallintapalvelut; Insinöörien tekemät tekniset arviot; Teknologian kehittämiseen liittyvät konsultointipalvelut; Energian käyttöä koskevat neuvontapalvelut; Energiatehokkuuteen liittyvät neuvontapalvelut; Teknologiseen tutkimukseen liittyvät konsultointipalvelut; Tietokoneavusteiset teolliset analysointipalvelut; Teollisten testien hoitaminen; Teknologiaan liittyvä ammattimainen konsultointi; Energiansäästöön liittyvä ammattimainen konsultointi; Rakennuspiirustus; Tekninen hankesuunnittelu; Tuotekehittelyä koskeva tekninen konsultointi; Teknologiset palvelut; Teollisten kokeiden hoitaminen; Tuotekehityksen analysointi; Teknologiset analysointipalvelut; Tuotekehittelyä koskeva analysointi ja arviointi; Tiedonrikastus; Rakennuspiirustuksiin liittyvä neuvonta; Teollinen testaus; Tietokoneavusteinen teollinen testaus; Tekniset mittaus- ja testauspalvelut; Uusien tuotteiden testaus; Suunnittelu ja testaus uusien tuotteiden kehitystä varten; Ajoneuvojen testaus; Tietokonelaitteiden testaaminen; Koneistojen testaus; Laitteiden testaus sähkötekniikan alalla; Koneiden toimivuuden testaus; Testausmenetelmien kehittäminen; Mittaus- ja testausmenetelmien kehittäminen; Tietokoneavusteiset diagnostiset testauspalvelut; Laadun tarkastus ja testaus; Sähköteknisiin laitteisiin liittyvät analysointi- ja testauspalvelut; Teollisuuskoneisiin liittyvät laadunvalvonta- ja testauspalvelut; Muiden tarjoamien tavaroiden ja palvelujen testaus, analysointi ja arviointi sertifiointitarkoituksiin; Tekniset mittauspalvelut; Tekniset tarkastuspalvelut; Tietokoneavusteisen teknisen suunnittelun palvelut; Tietokoneavusteisen teknisen suunnittelun ja piirustuksen palvelut; Insinööripalvelut kolmansille osapuolille; Piirtäjän palvelut teknisten piirrosten muodossa; Koneinsinöörin palvelut; Teknillinen tutkimus; Tekniset suunnittelupalvelut ja tietokoneavusteisen teknisen suunnittelun palvelut; Teknologiaan liittyvä tekninen analysointi; Uuden teknologian kehitys muille; Mittauspalvelut; Renkaiden tutkimuspalvelut; Tekniikkaan liittyvät tutkimus- ja kehittämispalvelut; Nesteiden kuntoon liittyvä seuranta; Voiteluaineiden kuntoon liittyvä seuranta; Insinööripalvelut; Uusien tuotteiden suunnittelu ja testaus; Säilyttävät testauspalvelut; Testaus, todentaminen ja laadunvalvonta; Laadun tai standardien sertifiointiin liittyvät testauspalvelut; Testaus- ja analyysimenetelmien suunnittelu ja kehittäminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de développement de méthodes de test; Services d'essais techniques; Services scientifiques et technologiques; Dessin industriel; Services de conseil en matière d'ingénierie de produits; Évaluations dans les domaines technologiques fournies par des ingénieurs; Services de conception assistée par ordinateur dans le domaine de l'ingénierie; Services de conseil en ingénierie; Tests d'ingénierie; Préparation de rapports d'ingénierie; Services d'ingénierie pour la conception de structures; Services d'ingénierie pour l'analyse de machines; Services d'ingénierie dans le domaine des forces motrices; Ingénierie technique; Conception et conseils en ingénierie; Développement de projets techniques dans le domaine de l'ingénierie; Services de gestion de projets d'ingénierie; Estimations dans les domaines technologiques fournies par des ingénieurs; Services de conseils dans le domaine du développement technologique; Services de conseil en matière de consommation énergétique; Services de conseil en matière d'efficacité énergétique; Services de conseil concernant la recherche technologique; Services d'analyse industrielle assistée par ordinateur; Conduite de tests industriels; Conseils professionnels en technologie de l'information; Conseils professionnels dans le domaine de l'économie énergétique; Établissement de plans pour la construction; Planification de projets techniques; Services de conseils techniques en matière de développement de produits; Services technologiques; Conduite d'expériences industrielles; Analyse (contrôle de qualité) du développement de produits; Services d'analyses technologiques; Analyse et évaluation du développement de produits; Exploration de données; Consultation dans le domaine de l’établissement de plans pour la construction; Tests industriels; Essais industriels assistés par ordinateur; Essais et mesurages techniques; Tests de nouveaux produits; Conception et essais dans le cadre du développement de nouveaux produits; Test de véhicules; Test d'équipements informatiques; Réalisation de tests d'appareils; Essais d'appareils dans le domaine du génie électrique; Test de la fonctionnalité de machines; Développement de méthodes d'essai; Développement de méthodes de mesurage et d'essai; Services de tests de diagnostic assistés par ordinateur; Contrôle de la qualité et Tests; Services d'analyse et d'essai en matière d'appareils de génie électrique; Tests de contrôle de qualité de machines industrielles; Test, analyse et évaluation des produits et services de tiers à des fins de certification; Mesurages techniques; Services d'inspection technique; Services de conception d'ingénierie assistée par ordinateur; Services de conception assistée par ordinateur en matière d'ingénierie et de dessin industriels; Services d'ingénierie pour le compte de tiers; Services de dessinateurs pour dessin technique; Génie mécanique; Recherche en ingénierie; Services d'ingénierie et d'ingénierie assistée par ordinateur; Analyses dans le domaine du génie technologique; Développement de nouvelles technologies pour des tiers; Services de mesurage; Services de recherche relatifs aux pneus; Services de recherche et développement dans le domaine de l’ingénierie; Contrôle de qualité de l'état des fluides; Contrôle de qualité de l'état des lubrifiants; Services d'ingénierie; Conception et essais de nouveaux produits; Services d'essais non destructifs; Tests, authentification et contrôle de la qualité; Services de test pour la certification de qualité ou de normes; Conception et développement de méthodes d'analyse et d'essai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge za razvoj metoda testiranja; Usluge tehničkog testiranja; Usluge znanosti i tehnologije; Tehničko crtanje; Konzultantske usluge u svezi s projektiranjem proizvoda; Ocjenivanje u području tehnologije koje provode inženjeri; Usluge računalno potpomognutog inženjerskog dizajna; Usluge inženjerskog savjetovanja; Inženjersko testiranje; Priprema inženjerskih izvještaja; Inženjerske usluge za dizajn struktura; Inženjerske usluge za analizu strojeva; Inženjerske usluge u području pogonske energije; Tehnički inženjering; Inženjerski dizajn i savjetovanje; Planiranje tehničkih projekata u području inženjeringa; Usluge upravljanja inženjerskim projektom; Procjene u području tehnologije koje provode inženjeri; Konzultantske usluge u području tehnološkog razvoja; Savjetodavne usluge u svezi s korištenjem energije; Savjetodavne usluge u svezi s energetskom učinkovitosti; Konzultantske usluge u svezi s tehnološkim istraživanjem; Usluge računalno potpomognute industrijske analize; Izvođenje industrijskih testova; Stručni savjeti u svezi s tehnologije; Stručno savjetovanje u svezi s očuvanjem energije; Planovi (izrada građevinskih planova); Planiranje tehničkih projekata; Tehničke konzultantske usluge o razvoju proizvoda; Tehnološke usluge; Izvođenje industrijskih eksperimenata; Analiza razvoja proizvoda; Usluge tehnološke analize; Analiza i ocjenjivanje razvoja proizvoda; Rudarenje podataka; Savjetovanje u području izrade građevinskih planova; Industrijsko testiranje; Računalno potpomognuto industrijsko ispitivanje; Usluge tehničkih mjerenja i ispitivanja; Novi proizvodi (Testiranje -); Dizajn i testiranje razvoja novog proizvoda; Ispitivanje vozila; Ispitivanje računalne opreme; Ispitivanje uređaja; Ispitivanje uređaja u području električnog inženjeringa; Testiranje funkcionalnosti strojeva; Razvoj metoda testiranja; Razvoj metoda mjerenja i ispitivanja; Usluge računalno potpomognutog dijagnostičkog testiranja; Provjera i testiranje kvalitete; Usluge analize i testiranja koje se odnose na uređaje za električni inženjering; Usluge kontrole kvalitete za industrijske strojeve; Testiranje, analiza i ocjena robe i usluga za druge u svrhu certifikacije; Usluge tehničkih mjerenja; Usluge tehničkog pregleda; Usluge računalno potpomognutog tehničkog projektiranja; Računalno potpomognute usluge tehničkog projektiranja i crtanja; Inženjerske usluge za druge; Usluge crtača u obliku tehničkog crtanja; Strojarstvo; Inženjersko istraživanje; Usluge inženjeringa i računalno potpomognutog inženjeringa; Tehnološke inženjerske analize; Razvoj nove tehnologije za druge; Usluge mjerenja; Usluge istraživanja u svezi s pneumaticima; Usluge istraživanja i razvoja u području inženjeringa; Praćenje stanja tekućina; Nadgledanje stanja maziva; Inženjerske usluge; Dizajn i testiranje novih proizvoda; Usluge testiranja bez uništavanja; Ispitivanje, provjera autentičnosti i kontrola kvalitete; Usluge ispitivanja za certifikaciju kvalitete ili normi; Dizajn i razvoj metoda za ispitivanje i analizu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szolgáltatások tesztelési módszerek kifejlesztéséhez; Műszaki vizsgálat, tesztelési szolgáltatások; Tudományos és technológiai szolgáltatások; Műszaki rajzolás; Terméktervezéshez kapcsolódó szaktanácsadói szolgáltatások; Mérnökök által végzett értékelések technológiai területeken; Számítógéppel támogatott műszaki tervező szolgáltatások; Mérnöki tanácsadó szolgáltatások; Műszaki tesztelés; Műszaki jelentések, beszámolók készítése; Szerkezetek tervezésével kapcsolatos műszaki szolgáltatások; Gépezetek elemzésével kapcsolatos mérnöki szolgáltatások; Mérnöki szolgáltatások a hajtóerő területén; Műszaki mérnöki tevékenység; Mérnöki tervezés és konzultáció; Műszaki projekttervezés a mérnöki tevékenység területén; Mérnöki projektmenedzsment szolgáltatások; Mérnöki becslések technológiai területeken; Technológiai fejlesztéssel kapcsolatos szaktanácsadási szolgáltatások; Tanácsadási szolgáltatások az energiafelhasználással kapcsolatban; Tanácsadási szolgáltatások az energiahatékonysággal kapcsolatban; Technológiai kutatáshoz kapcsolódó szaktanácsadói szolgáltatások; Számítógéppel segített ipari elemzés; Ipari vizsgálatok lebonyolítása; Technológiával kapcsolatos szaktanácsadás; Energiamegőrzéssel kapcsolatos szaktanácsadás; Építési tervkészítés; Műszaki tervtanulmányok készítése; Termékfejlesztéssel kapcsolatos műszaki tanácsadás; Technológiai szolgáltatások; Ipari kísérletek végzése; Termékfejlesztés elemzése; Technológiai elemzés; Termékfejlesztés elemzése és értékelése; Adatbányászat; Építészeti tervrajzok készítésével kapcsolatos konzultáció; Ipari tesztelés; Számítógéppel támogatott ipari tesztelés; Műszaki mérő- és tesztelő szolgáltatások; Új termékek tesztelése; Tervezés és tesztelés új termék fejlesztéséhez; Járművek tesztelése; Számítástechnikai eszközök tesztelése; Berendezések tesztelése; Készülékek tesztelése az elektrotechnika területén; Gépek funkcióinak ellenőrzése; Tesztelési módszerek kifejlesztése; Mérési és tesztelő módszerek fejlesztése; Számítógéppel támogatott diagnosztikai tesztelési szolgáltatások; Minőségellenőrzés és -vizsgálat; Elektrotechnikai készülékekhez kapcsolódó elemzési és tesztelési szolgáltatások; Ipari gépekkel kapcsolatos minőségellenőrzési tesztelési szolgáltatások; Mások áruinak és szolgáltatásainak tesztelése, elemzése és értékelése tanúsítási célokra; Műszaki mérési szolgáltatások; Műszaki vizsgálati szolgáltatások; Számítógéppel támogatott műszaki tervezés mint szolgáltatás; Számítógéppel támogatott műszaki tervező és rajzoló szolgáltatás; Mérnöki szolgáltatások, munkák; Műszaki rajzolói szolgáltatások műszaki rajz formájában; Gépészmérnökség; Mérnöki kutatás; Mérnöki és számítógépes mérnöki szolgáltatások; Technológiai mérnöki elemzés; Szolgáltatás új technológiák kifejlesztésére; Mérési szolgáltatások; Abroncsokkal kapcsolatos kutatási szolgáltatások; Kutatási és fejlesztési szolgáltatások a mérnöki tevékenységek területén; Folyadékokkal kapcsolatos állapot-monitorozás; Kenőanyagokkal kapcsolatos állapotmegfigyelés [monitorozás]; Mérnöki munkák, szolgáltatások; Új termékek tervezése és tesztelése; Roncsolásmentes vizsgálati szolgáltatások; Tesztelés, hitelesítés és minőségellenőrzés; Tesztelési szolgáltatások minőség vagy szabványok tanúsításához; Vizsgálati és elemzési módszerek tervezése és fejlesztése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi per lo sviluppo di metodi di collaudo; Servizi di collaudo tecnico; Servizi di scienza e tecnologia; Progettazione ingegneristica; Servizi di consulenza in progettazione del prodotto; Stime in ambito tecnologico effettuate da ingegneri; Servizi tecnici di progettazione ingegneristica assistita da computer; Servizi di consulenza di ingegneria; Test tecnici; Stesura di perizie tecniche; Servizi tecnici relativi alla progettazione di strutture; Servizi tecnici per l'analisi di macchine; Servizi di ingegneria in tema di forze motrici; Ingegneria tecnica; Progettazione tecnica e servizi di consulenza tecnica; Pianificazione di progetti tecnici in ambito ingegneristico; Servizi di gestione di progetti tecnici; Valutazioni in ambito tecnologico effettuate da ingegneri; Servizi di consulenza nel settore dello sviluppo tecnologico; Servizi di consulenza in materia di utilizzo di energia; Servizi di consulenza in materia di efficienza energetica; Consulenza riguardante la ricerca tecnologica; Analisi con supporto informatico in ambito industriale; Conduzione di test industriali; Consulenza professionale in materia di tecnologia; Consulenza professionale in materia di conservazione dell'energia; Progettazione per la costruzione; Pianificazione di progetti tecnici; Consulenze tecniche in tema di sviluppo di prodotti; Servizi tecnologici; Conduzione di esperimenti industriali; Analisi dello sviluppo di prodotti; Servizi di analisi tecnologiche; Analisi e valutazione dello sviluppo di prodotti; Estrazione di dati; Consulenza in materia di progettazione per la costruzione; Analisi industriali; Analisi industriali assistite da computer; Servizi di misurazione e testing tecnici; Collaudo di nuovi prodotti; Progettazione e collaudo per lo sviluppo di nuovi prodotti; Collaudo di veicoli; Verifica di apparecchiature informatiche; Collaudo di macchinari; Testing di apparecchiature nell'ambito dell'ingegneria elettrica; Prova della funzionalità delle macchine; Sviluppo di metodi di collaudo; Sviluppo di metodi di misurazione e testing; Servizi computerizzati di analisi diagnostiche; Controllo della qualità e collaudi; Servizi d'analisi e verifica inerenti le apparecchiature di ingegneria elettrica; Servizi di testing del controllo qualità per attrezzature industriali; Testing, analisi e valutazione di prodotti e servizi di terzi a scopo di certificazione; Servizi di misurazione tecnica; Servizi di ispezione tecnica; Servizi di progettazione ingegneristica assistita dal computer; Servizi di progettazione e di disegno industriale assistiti da computer; Servizi di ingegneria per conto terzi; Servizi di disegnatore sotto forma di disegno tecnico; Ingegneria meccanica; Ricerca nel campo dell'ingegneria; Servizi tecnici e progettazione assistita da computer; Analisi tecniche tecnologiche; Sviluppo di nuove tecnologie per conto terzi; Servizi di misurazione; Servizi di ricerca in materia di pneumatici; Servizi di ricerca e sviluppo in materia di ingegneria; Monitoraggio delle condizioni in materia di fluidi; Monitoraggio delle condizioni in materia di lubrificanti; Servizi di ingegneria; Progettazione e sperimentazione di nuovi prodotti; Servizi di collaudo non distruttivo; Collaudi, certificazioni e controllo di qualità; Servizi di testing per la certificazione della qualità o degli standard; Progettazione e sviluppo di metodi di testing e analisi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Testavimo metodų tobulinimo paslaugos; Techninio testavimo paslaugos; Mokslo ir technologijų paslaugos; Techninių brėžinių rengimas; Gaminių inžinerijos konsultacijos; Inžineriniai technologiniai vertinimai; Kompiuterizuoto inžinerinio dizaino paslaugos; Inžinerinių konsultacijų paslaugos; Inžineriniai bandymai; Inžinerinių ataskaitų rengimas; Konstrukcijų projektavimo inžinerinės paslaugos; Inžinerijos paslaugos, skirtos mechanizmams analizuoti; Varomosios jėgos srities techninės paslaugos; Techninė inžinerija; Inžinerinis projektavimas ir konsultacijos; Inžinerijos srities techninių projektų planavimas; Inžinerinių projektų vadybos paslaugos; Inžinerinės technologinės sąmatos; Konsultacijų paslaugos technologijų plėtros reikmėms; Energijos vartojimo konsultacijos; Energijos efektyvumo konsultacijos; Technologinių tyrimų konsultacijos; Kompiuterinės pramoninės analizės paslaugos; Pramoninių bandymų atlikimas; Specialistų konsultacijos technologijų klausimais; Specialistų konsultacijos, susijusios su energijos taupymu; Statybų projektavimas; Techninių projektų planavimas; Techninės konsultacijos, susijusios su gaminio kūrimu ir plėtra; Technologijų paslaugos; Pramoninių eksperimentų vykdymas; Produktų kūrimo analizė; Technologinės analizės paslaugos; Produktų kūrimo analizė ir vertinimas; Didelių duomenų kiekių analizė; Statybų projektavimo konsultacijos; Pramoniniai bandymai; Kompiuterizuoti pramoniniai bandymai; Techninės matavimo ir tikrinimo paslaugos; Naujų produktų bandymai; Naujų gaminių projektavimas ir testavimas tobulinimo reikmėms; Transporto priemonių testavimas; Skaičiavimo įrangos bandymai; Įrangos bandymai; Elektros inžinerijos srities aparatų bandymai; Mašinų funkcionalumo testavimas; Bandymų metodų tobulinimas; Matavimo ir tikrinimo metodų kūrimas ir plėtra; Kompiuterizuotų diagnostinių tyrimų paslaugos; Kokybės tyrimai ir tikrinimas; Analizės ir bandymų paslaugos, susijusios su elektros inžinerijos aparatais; Pramonės mašinų kokybės tikrinimo bandymų paslaugos; Prekių ir paslaugų kitiems bandymas, analizė ir vertinimas sertifikatų išdavimo tikslais; Techninių matavimų paslaugos; Techninio tikrinimo paslaugos; Kompiuterizuoto inžinerinio projektavimo paslaugos; Kompiuterizuoto inžinerinio projektavimo ir braižymo paslaugos; Inžinerinės paslaugos kitiems; Techninio braižymo pobūdžio projektuotojų paslaugos; Mechaninė inžinerija; Tyrimai inžinerijos srityje; Inžinerija ir kompiuterinės inžinerijos paslaugos; Technologinė inžinerijos analizė; Naujų technologijų tobulinimas kitiems; Matavimo paslaugos; Padangų tyrimai; Inžineriniai tyrimai ir plėtra; Skysčių būklės stebėjimas; Tepalų būklės stebėjimas; Inžinerijos paslaugos; Naujų gaminių projektavimas ir testavimas; Neardomųjų bandymų paslaugos; Bandymai, autentifikavimas ir kokybės tikrinimas; Sertifikavimo kokybės ar standartų tikrinimo paslaugos; Bandymų ir tyrimų metodų kūrimas ir tobulinimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pārbaudes metožu izstrādes pakalpojumi; Tehniskās testēšanas pakalpojumi; Zinātniskie un tehnoloģiskie pakalpojumi; Inženiertehniskā rasēšana; Konsultācijas saistībā ar produktu projektēšanu; Inženieru veikti novērtējumi tehnoloģijas jomā; Datorizēti inženiertehniskās projektēšanas pakalpojumi; Inženierpakalpojumu konsultācijas; Inženierijas testēšana; Inženiertehnisko atskaišu sagatavošana; Inženierijas pakalpojumi celtņu projektēšanai; Inženierijas pakalpojumi iekārtu analīzei; Inženiertehniskie pakalpojumi dzinējspēka jomā; Tehniskās inženierijas pakalpojumi; Inženierprojektēšana un konsultēšana; Tehniskā projekta plānošana inženierzinātnes jomā; Inženierijas projektu vadība; Inženieru veiktās aplēses tehnoloģiju jomā; Konsultāciju pakalpojumi tehnoloģijas izstrādes jomā; Konsultāciju pakalpojumi saistībā ar enerģijas izmantošanu; Konsultāciju pakalpojumi saistībā ar enerģijas efektivitāti; Konsultāciju pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar tehnoloģisko izpēti; Datorizēti rūpnieciskās analīzes pakalpojumi; Rūpniecisko testu veikšana; Profesionālās konsultācijas, kas saistītas ar tehnoloģijām; Profesionālas konsultācijas saistībā ar enerģijas saglabāšanu; Būvniecības projektu izstrāde; Tehnisko projektu plānošana; Tehniskās konsultācijas saistībā ar produktu izstrādi; Tehnoloģiskie pakalpojumi; Rūpniecisko eksperimentu veikšana; Produkta izstrādes analīze; Tehnoloģiskā analīze; Produktu izstrādes analīze un novērtēšana; Datizrace; Konsultāciju sniegšana par būvniecības pānu izstrādi; Rūpnieciskā testēšana; Datorizēta rūpnieciskā testēšana; Tehniski mērīšanas un testēšanas pakalpojumi; Jaunu produktu izmēģināšana; Projektēšana un testēšana jaunu produktu izstrādnēm; Transportlīdzekļu pārbaudes veikšana; Skaitļošanas tehnikas pārbaude; Mašīnu testēšana; Aparātu pārbaude elektrotehnikas jomā; Mašīnu funcionalitātes testēšana; Pārbaudes metožu izstrāde; Mērīšanas un testēšanas metožu izstrāde; Datorizēti diagnostiskās testēšanas pakalpojumi; Kvalitātes kontrole un testēšana; Analīzes un testēšanas pakalpojumi saistībā ar elektrotehniskiem aparātiem; Rūpniecisko iekārtu kvalitātes kontroles pārbaudes pakalpojumi; Trešo personu preču un pakalpojumu pārbaude, analizēšana un novērtēšana sertifikācijas nolūkam; Tehniskie mērīšanas pakalpojumi; Tehnisko inspekciju pakalpojumi; Datorizēti inženierprojektēšanas pakalpojumi; Datorizētas inženierprojektēšanas un rasēšanas pakalpojumi; Inženierpakalpojumi citiem; Rasētāja pakalpojumi tehnisko rasējumu veidā; Pakalpojumi mašīnbūves jomā; Pētniecība inženierzinātnēs; Inženierpakalpojumi un datorizēti inženierpakalpojumi; Tehnoloģiskās inženierijas analīzes; Jaunu tehnoloģiju izstrāde trešajām personām; Mērīšanas pakalpojumi; Riepu izpētes pakalpojumi; Pētniecības un izstrādes pakalpojumi inženiertehnikas jomā; Šķidrumu stāvokļa uzraudzība; Smērvielu stāvokļa uzraudzība; Inženiertehniskie pakalpojumi; Jaunu produktu projektēšana un izmēģināšana; Nedestruktīvās pārbaudes pakalpojumi; Testēšana, autentifikācija un kvalitātes kontrole; Pārbaudes pakalpojumi kvalitātes vai standartu sertificēšanai; Pārbaudes un analīžu metožu projektēšana un izstrāde.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi għall-iżvilupp ta' metodi ta' ttestjar; Servizzi ta' testijiet tekniċi; Servizzi xjentifiċi u teknoloġiċi; Tpinġija għall-inġinerija; Servizzi ta' konsulenza marbut mal-inġinerija ta' prodott; Evalwazzjoni fil-qasam tat-teknoloġija pprovduta mill-inġiniera; Servizzi ta' disinn għall-inġinerija bl-assistenza tal-kompjuter; Konsultazzjoni dwar l-inġinerija; Ittestjar ta' inġinerija; Tħejjija ta' rapporti tal-inġinerija; Servizzi ta' inġinerija għad-disinn ta' strutturi; Servizzi ta' inġinerija għall-analiżi ta' makkinarju; Servizzi ta' inġinerija fil-qasam tat-teknoloġija tal-enerġija motiva; Inġinerija teknika; Disinni u konsulenza fl-inġinerija; L-ippjanar ta' proġetti tekniċi fil-qasam tal-inġinerija; Servizzi ta' ġestjoni ta' proġetti ta' inġinerija; Stimi fil-qasam tat-teknoloġija pprovduti mill-inġiniera; Servizzi ta' konsulenza fil-qasam tal-iżvilupp teknoloġiku; Servizzi ta' pariri relatati mal-użu tal-enerġija; Servizzi ta' pariri relatati mal-effiċjenza tal-enerġija; Servizzi ta' konsulenza relatata mar-riċerka teknoloġika; Servizzi ta' analiżi industrijali bl-għajnuna tal-kompjuter; Tmexxija ta' testijiet industrijali; Konsulenza professjonali relatata mat-teknoloġija; Konsulenza professjonali dwar il-konservazzjoni tal-enerġija; Disinn ta' bini; Pjanar ta' proġetti tekniċi; Konsulenza teknika relatata mal-iżvilupp ta' prodotti; Servizzi teknoloġiċi; Tmexxija ta' esperimenti industrijali; Analiżi tal-iżvilupp ta’ prodott; Servizzi ta' analiżi teknoloġika; Analiżi u evalwazzjoni tal-iżvilupp ta' prodotti; Tiftix ta' data; Konsulenza fil-qasam tad-disinjar arkitettoniku; Ittestjar industrijali; Ittestjar industrijali permezz tal-kompjuter; Servizzi tekniċi għall-kejl u l-ittestjar; Prodotti ġodda (L-ittestjar ta' -); Id-disinn u l-ittestjar ta' l-iżvilupp ta' prodott ġdid; Ittestjar ta' vetturi; Ittestjar ta' tagħmir tal-kompjuter; Ittestjar ta' makkinarju; L-ittestjar ta' apparat fil-qasam tal-inġinerija elettrika; L-ittestjar tal-funzjonalità tal-magni; L-iżvilupp ta' metodi ta' ittestjar; Żvilupp ta' metodi tal-kejl u tal-analiżi; Servizzi ta' testijiet dijanjostiċi bl-għajnuna ta' kompjuter; Kontroll tal-kwalità u testijiet; Servizzi ta' analiżi u ttestjar relatati ma' apparat tal-inġinerija elettrika; Servizzi tal-ittestjar għall-kontroll tal-kwalità għall-makkinarju industrijali; L-ittestjar, l-analiżi u l-valutazzjoni ta' oġġetti u servizzi għall-oħrajn għal skopijiet ta' ċertifikazzjoni; Servizzi ta' kejl tekniku; Servizzi ta' spezzjoni teknika; Servizzi ta' disinn u tal-inġinerija bl-għajnuna tal-kompjuter; Servizzi ta' disinn u tpinġija tal-inġinerija bl-għajnuna tal-kompjuter; Servizzi ta' inġinerija għal oħrajn; Servizzi ta' disinjatur fl-għamla ta' disinni tekniċi; Inġinerija mekkanika; Riċerka dwar l-inġinerija; Inġinerija u servizzi ta' inġinerija bl-għajnuna tal-kompjuter; Analiżi tal-inġinerija teknoloġika; Żvilupp ta' teknoloġiji ġodda għal terzi persuni; Servizzi ta' kejl; Servizzi ta' riċerka dwar it-tajers; Servizzi ta’ riċerka u żvilupp fil-qasam tal-inġinerija; Monitoraġġ tal-kundizzjoni ta' fluwidi; Monitoraġġ tal-kondizzjoni [ta' magna] relatat mal-lubrikanti; Servizzi ta' Inġinerija; Id-disinn u l-ittestjar ta' prodotti ġodda; Servizzi ta' testijiet li ma jeqirdux; Ittestjar, awtentikazzjoni u kontroll tal-kwalità; Servizzi ta' ttestjar għaċ-ċertifikazzjoni tal-kwalità jew tal-istandards; Disinn u żvilupp ta' metodi tal-ittestjar u tal-analiżi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Ontwikkeling van testmethodes; Technische testdiensten; Wetenschappelijke en technologische diensten; Technisch tekenen; Advisering met betrekking tot productontwikkeling; Beoordeling op technologisch gebied door ingenieurs; Computerondersteund technisch ontwerpen; Consultancy inzake engineering; Technische testen; Opstellen van ingenieurtechnische rapporten; Ingenieursdiensten voor het ontwerp van structuren; Ingenieursdiensten voor de analyse van machines; Engineering op het gebied van aandrijfkracht; Technische ingenieursdiensten; Ontwerp en advisering op het gebied van engineering; Technische ontwikkeling van projecten op het gebied van engineering; Beheer van engineering projecten; Evaluatie op technologisch gebied door ingenieurs; Adviesdiensten op het gebied van technologische ontwikkeling; Advisering met betrekking tot het gebruik van energie; Advisering met betrekking tot energie-efficiëntie; Advisering met betrekking tot technologisch onderzoek; Computerondersteunde industriële analysediensten; Industriële tests (Uitvoering van -); Professionele raadgeving op het gebied van technologie; Professionele raadgeving met betrekking tot energiebesparing; Bouwplanning; Planning van technische projecten; Technische advisering met betrekking tot productontwikkeling; Technologische diensten; Industriële experimenten (Uitvoering van -); Analyse van productontwikkeling; Technologische analyse; Analyse en evaluatie van productontwikkeling; Datamining; Advisering op het gebied van bouwplanning; Industriële testen; Uitvoering van computerondersteunde industriële tests; Technisch meten en testen; Nieuwe producten (Testen van -); Ontwerpen en testen ten behoeve van de ontwikkeling van nieuwe producten; Testen van vervoermiddelen; Testen van computerinstallaties; Testen van apparaten; Testen van apparatuur op het gebied van de elektrotechniek; Het testen van de functionaliteit van machines; Testmethoden (Ontwikkelen van -); Ontwikkeling van meet- en testmethoden; Diagnostische tests (Computerondersteunde -); Kwaliteitscontrole en Beproevingen; Analyse en testen met betrekking tot elektrotechnische apparaten; Kwaliteitscontrole voor industriële machines; Testen, analyseren en evalueren van goederen en diensten van anderen voor certificeringdoeleinden; Technische meetdiensten; Technische inspectiediensten; Dienstverlening inzake computerondersteund technisch ontwerpen; Dienstverlening inzake computerondersteund technisch ontwerpen en tekenen; Ingenieursdiensten voor derden; Diensten van technisch tekenaars; Werktuigbouwkunde; Technisch onderzoek; Ingenieursdiensten en computerondersteunde ingenieursdiensten; Analyse inzake technologische engineering; Ontwikkeling van nieuwe technologie voor derden; Meetdiensten; Onderzoek van banden; Onderzoeks- en ontwikkelingsdiensten op het gebied van engineering; Statuscontrole met betrekking tot vloeistoffen; Controle van de toestand van smeermiddelen; Ingenieursdiensten; Ontwerpen en testen van nieuwe producten; Uitvoeren van niet-destructieve proeven; Testen, authenticatie en kwaliteitscontrole; Testen voor de certificering van kwaliteit of normen; Ontwerp en ontwikkeling van test- en analysemethoden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi w zakresie opracowywania metod testowania; Usługi w zakresie testów technicznych; Usługi naukowe i technologiczne; Rysunek techniczny; Usługi konsultacyjne w zakresie technologii; Oceny w dziedzinie technologii wykonywane przez inżynierów; Usługi projektowania technicznego wspomaganego komputerowo; Usługi w zakresie doradztwa technicznego; Testy inżynieryjne; Sporządzanie raportów technicznych; Usługi inżynieryjne w zakresie projektowania konstrukcji; Usługi inżynieryjne w zakresie analizy maszyn; Usługi inżynieryjne w dziedzinie mocy napędowej; Inżynieria techniczna; Projektowanie techniczne i doradztwo; Planowanie projektów technicznych w dziedzinie inżynierii; Usługi zarządzania projektami inżynieryjnymi; Oszacowania w dziedzinie technologii wykonywane przez inżynierów; Usługi doradztwa w dziedzinie rozwoju technologicznego; Usługi doradcze dotyczące zużycia energii; Usługi doradcze związane z wydajnością energetyczną; Usługi konsultacyjne dotyczące badań technologicznych; Usługi analiz przemysłowych wspomaganych komputerowo; Przeprowadzanie testów przemysłowych; Profesjonalne doradztwo dotyczące technologii; Profesjonalne doradztwo związane z zachowaniem energii; Projektowanie budowlane; Planowanie projektów technicznych; Konsultacje techniczne z zakresu rozwoju produktu; Usługi technologiczne; Przeprowadzanie doświadczeń przemysłowych; Analiza opracowywania produktu; Usługi analizy technologicznej; Analiza i ocena dotycząca opracowywania produktów; Eksploracja danych; Doradztwo w zakresie projektowania konstrukcyjnego; Testowanie przemysłowe; Testowanie przemysłowe wspomagane komputerowo; Usługi w zakresie pomiarów i testów technicznych; Testowanie nowych produktów; Projektowanie i testowanie w zakresie opracowywania nowych produktów; Testowanie pojazdów; Testowanie sprzętu informatycznego; Testowanie maszyn; Testowanie urządzeń w dziedzinie inżynierii elektrycznej; Testowanie funkcjonalności maszyn; Opracowywanie metod testowych; Opracowywanie metod pomiarowych i testujących; Usługi testowania diagnostycznego wspomagane komputerowo; Kontrola i testowanie jakości; Usługi analiz i testów związane z urządzeniami inżynierii elektrycznej; Usługi testowania maszyn przemysłowych w ramach kontroli jakości; Testowanie, analiza i wycena towarów i usług osób trzecich do celów certyfikacji; Usługi pomiarów technicznych; Usługi w zakresie inspekcji technicznej; Usługi w zakresie wspomaganego komputerem projektowania technicznego; Usługi w zakresie wspomaganego komputerem projektowania i rysunku technicznego; Usługi inżynieryjne dla osób trzecich; Usługi kreślarskie w postaci rysunku technicznego; Inżynieria mechaniczna; Badania inżynieryjne; Usługi inżynieryjne oraz usługi inżynieryjne wspomagane komputerowo; Analizy w zakresie inżynierii technologicznej; Opracowywanie nowych technologii dla osób trzecich; Usługi pomiarowe; Usługi badania opon; Usługi w zakresie badań i opracowywania w obszarze inżynierii; Monitorowanie stanu cieczy; Monitorowanie stanu środków nawilżających; Usługi inżynieryjne; Projektowanie i testowanie nowych produktów; Usługi w zakresie testów nieniszczących; Testowanie, stwierdzanie autentyczności i kontrola jakości; Usługi testowania w celu certyfikacji jakości lub standardów; Projektowanie i opracowywanie metod do testów i analiz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços para o desenvolvimento de métodos de testes; Serviços de ensaios técnicos; Serviços de ciência e tecnologia; Desenho de engenharia; Serviços de consultoria relacionados com engenharia de produtos; Avaliações no domínio tecnológico realizadas por engenheiros; Serviços de design em engenharia assistidos por computador; Serviços de consultadoria no domínio da engenharia; Testes de engenharia; Elaboração de relatórios de engenharia; Serviços de engenharia para o design de estruturas; Serviços de engenharia para a análise de maquinaria; Serviços de engenharia na área da força motriz; Engenharia técnica; Design e consultadoria de engenharia; Planeamento de projetos técnicos na área da engenharia; Serviços de gestão de projetos de engenharia; Estimativas no domínio tecnológico realizadas por engenheiros; Serviços de consultadoria no domínio do desenvolvimento tecnológico; Serviços de assessoria relacionados com o consumo de energia; Serviços de assessoria no domínio da eficiência energética; Serviços de consultadoria relacionados com investigação tecnológica; Análise industrial assistida por computador; Realização de testes industriais; Consultadoria profissional em matéria de tecnologia; Consultadoria profissional relacionada com a conservação de energia; Elaboração de planos para construção; Planeamento de projetos técnicos; Consultoria técnica em matéria de desenvolvimento de produtos; Serviços tecnológicos; Realização de experiências industriais; Análises de desenvolvimento de produtos; Serviços de análise tecnológico; Análise e avaliação do desenvolvimento de produtos; Mineração de dados; Consultoria na área de projetos de construção; Testes industriais; Testes industriais assistidos por computador; Serviços de medição técnica e testes; Teste de novos produtos; Conceção e testes para desenvolvimento de novos produtos; Ensaios a veículos; Ensaio de equipamento informático; Ensaio de maquinaria; Testes de aparelhos na área da engenharia elétrica; Teste da funcionalidade de máquinas; Desenvolvimento de métodos de ensaio; Desenvolvimento de métodos de medição e testes; Serviços de testes de diagnóstico assistidos por computador; Controlo da qualidade e Ensaios; Serviços de análise e teste relacionados com aparelhos de engenharia elétrica; Serviços de teste de controlo de qualidade para maquinaria industrial; Teste, análise e avaliação dos produtos e serviços de outros para certificação; Serviços de medição técnica; Serviços de inspeção técnica; Serviços de design de engenharia assistidos por computador; Serviços de projeto e de design de engenharia assistidos por computador; Serviços de engenharia por conta de outrem; Serviços de desenhador na área do desenho técnico; Engenharia mecânica; Investigação de engenharia; Serviços de engenharia e de engenharia assistida por computador; Análises de engenharia tecnológica; Desenvolvimento de novas tecnologias para terceiros; Serviços de medição; Serviços de investigação de pneus; Serviços de pesquisa e desenvolvimento no campo da engenharia; Monitorização de condições de fluidos; Monitorização de condições relativas a lubrificantes; Serviços de engenharia; Conceção e ensaio de novos produtos; Serviços de ensaio não destrutivo; Testes, autenticação e controlo de qualidade; Serviços de teste para certificação da qualidade e cumprimento de normativas; Conceção e desenvolvimento de métodos de ensaio e análise.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii pentru dezvoltarea de metode de testare; Servicii de testare tehnică; Servicii în domeniul științei și tehnologiei; Desen tehnic; Servicii de consultanță în materie de inginerie a produselor; Evaluări în domeniul tehnologic efectuate de ingineri; Servicii de proiectare tehnică asistată de calculator în domeniul ingineriei; Servicii de consultanță tehnică; Teste de inginerie; Elaborare de rapoarte tehnice; Servicii de inginerie în materie de proiectare de structuri; Servicii tehnice pentru analiza utilajelor; Servicii de inginerie în domeniul tehnologiei pentru motoare; Inginerie tehnică; Proiectare și consultanță în inginerie; Planificare de proiecte tehnice în domeniul ingineriei; Servicii de management al proiectelor de inginerie; Estimări în domeniul tehnologic efectuate de ingineri; Servicii de consultanță în domeniul dezvoltării tehnologice; Servicii de consultanță în materie de utilizare a energiei; Servicii de consultanță în materie de eficiență energetică; Servicii de consultanță în materie de cercetare tehnologică; Servicii de analize industriale asistate de calculator; Efectuare de teste industriale; Consultanță profesională privind tehnologia; Consultanță profesională privind conservarea energiei; Planuri (realizarea de -) [construcții]; Planificare de proiecte tehnice; Consultanță tehnică cu privire la dezvoltarea de produse; Servicii tehnologice; Efectuarea de experimente industriale; Analiză a dezvoltării produselor; Servicii de analiză tehnologică; Analiza și evaluarea dezvoltării produselor; Exploatare de date; Consultanță în domeniul desenului tehnic în construcții; Teste industriale; Testare industrială asistată de calculator; Servicii tehnice de măsurare și testare; Testare de produse noi; Proiectare și testare în vederea dezvoltării de produse noi; Testare de vehicule; Testare de echipamente informatice; Testare de utilaje; Testare de aparate în domeniul ingineriei electrice; Testarea funcționalității mașinilor; Dezvoltare de metode de testare; Dezvoltare de metode de măsurare și de testare; Servicii de testare în scopul diagnosticării asistată de calculator; Control de calitate și Testare; Servicii de analiză și de testare referitoare la aparate pentru ingineria electrică; Servicii de testare de control al calității de utilaje industriale; Testare, analiză și evaluare de produse și servicii ale altor persoane, în scopul certificării; Servicii tehnice de măsurare; Servicii de inspecție tehnică; Servicii de proiectare tehnică asistată de calculator; Servicii de proiectare și desen tehnic asistate de calculator; Servicii tehnice pentru terți; Servicii prestate de un proiectant sub formă de desen tehnic; Inginerie mecanică; Cercetare în domeniul ingineriei; Servicii de inginerie și inginerie asistată de calculator; Analize în domeniul ingineriei tehnologice; Dezvoltare de noi tehnologii pentru terți; Servicii de măsurători; Servicii de cercetare în domeniul anvelopelor; Servicii de cercetare și dezvoltare în domeniul ingineriei; Monitorizarea stării fluidelor; Monitorizarea stării lubrifianților; Inginerie; Proiectare și testare de produse noi; Servicii de testare nedistructivă; Testare, autentificare și controlul calității; Servicii de testare pentru certificarea calității sau a standardelor; Proiectare și dezvoltare de metode de testare și analiză.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vývoj skúšobných metód; Technické skúšky; Vedecké a technologické služby; Technické kreslenie; Konzultačné služby v oblasti projektovania výrobkov; Hodnotenie inžinierov so zameraním na technologické oblasti; Inžinierske projektovacie služby za pomoci počítača; Inžinierske poradenské služby; Inžinierske testovanie; Vypracovanie inžinierskych správ; Inžinierske služby v oblasti navrhovania konštrukcií; Inžinierske služby v oblasti analýzy strojov; Inžinierske služby v oblasti hnacej energie; Technické inžinierstvo; Inžiniersky dizajn a poradenstvo; Plánovanie technických projektov v oblasti inžinierstva; Služby riadenia inžinierskych projektov; Odhady inžinierov so zameraním na technologické oblasti; Konzultačné služby v oblasti technologického vývoja; Poradenstvo týkajúce sa využívania energie; Poradenstvo v oblasti energetickej účinnosti; Poradenské služby v oblasti technologického výskumu; Počítačom podporované priemyselné analytické služby; Realizácia priemyselných testov; Odborné poradenstvo v oblasti technológií; Odborné poradenstvo v oblasti šetrenia energiou; Vypracovanie stavebných výkresov; Technické projektové plánovanie; Technické poradenstvo v oblasti vývoja produktov; Technologické služby; Vykonávanie priemyselných experimentov; Analýza vývoja výrobku; Technologické analytické služby; Analýza a hodnotenie vývoja produktov; Hĺbková analýza dát [data mining]; Poradenstvo v oblasti stavebného projektovania; Priemyselné testovanie; Priemyselné testovanie s počítačovou podporou; Technické meracie a testovacie služby; Skúšanie nových výrobkov; Dizajn a testovanie pre vývoj nového produktu; Testovanie vozidiel; Testovanie výpočtových zariadení; Testovanie strojov; Testovanie zariadení v oblasti elektrotechnického inžinierstva; Testovanie funkčnosti strojov; Vývoj testovacích metód; Vývoj meracích a skúšobných metód; Počítačom podporované diagnostické testovanie; Kontrola kvality a testovanie; Analytické a testovacie služby v oblasti elektrotechnických zariadení; Služby testovania kontroly kvality pre priemyselné stroje; Testovanie, analýza a hodnotenie výrobkov a služieb klientov za účelom certifikácie pre tretie osoby; Technické meracie služby; Technické inšpekčné služby; Služby v oblasti inžinierskeho dizajnu za pomoci počítača; Služby v oblasti dizajnu a rysovania za pomoci počítača; Inžinierske služby pre iných; Projektantské služby v podobe technických výkresov; Strojné inžinierstvo; Inžiniersky výskum; Inžinierske práce a inžinierske služby s pomocou počítača; Technologické inžinierske analýzy; Vývoj nových technológií pre iných; Meracie služby; Služby v oblasti výskumu pneumatík; Výskumné a vývojové služby v oblasti inžinierstva; Sledovanie stavu kvapalín; Sledovanie stavu lubrikantov; Inžinierske činnosti; Navrhovanie a skúšanie nových výrobkov; Nedeštruktívne testovacie služby; Skúšobníctvo, overovanie a kontrola kvality; Testovacie služby v oblasti certifikácie kvality alebo štandardov; Navrhovanie a vývoj testovacích a analytických metód.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve za razvoj testnih metod; Storitve tehničnih testiranj; Znanstvene in tehnološke storitve; Inženirsko risanje; Svetovalne storitve v zvezi inženiringom izdelkov; Ocenjevanje na podočju tehnologije, ki ga nudijo inženirji; Storitve računalniško podprtega inženirskega oblikovanja; Storitve inženirskega svetovanja; Inženirsko testiranje; Priprava inženirskih poročil; Inženirske storitve za oblikovanje struktur; Inženirske storitve za analizo strojev; Inženirske storitve na področju pogonske moči; Tehnični inženiring; Inženirsko oblikovanje in svetovanje; Načrtovanje tehničnega projekta na področju inženiringa; Storitve upravljanja inženirskih projektov; Presoja na področju tehnologije, ki jo nudijo inženirji; Svetovalne storitve na področju tehnološkega razvoja; Svetovalne storitve v zvezi z uporabo energije; Svetovalne storitve v zvezi z energetsko učinkovitostjo; Posvetovalne storitve v zvezi s tehnološkimi raziskavami; Računalniško podprte industrijske analize; Izvajanje industrijskih testov; Strokovno svetovanje v zvezi s tehnologijo; Strokovno svetovanje v zvezi z varčevanjem z energijo; Načrtovanje konstrukcij; Načrtovanje tehničnega projekta; Tehnično svetovanje v zvezi z razvojem izdelkov; Tehnološke storitve; Izvajanje industrijskih eksperimentov; Analize razvoja izdelka; Storitve tehnološke analize; Analiza in vrednotenje razvoja izdelka; Podatkovno rudarjenje; Svetovanje na področju izdelave gradbenih načrtov; Industrijsko testiranje; Računalniško podprto industrijsko testiranje; Storitve tehničnega merjenja in testiranja; Testiranje novih izdelkov; Oblikovanje in testiranje za razvoj novih izdelkov; Testiranje vozil; Testiranje računalniške opreme; Testiranje strojev; Testiranje aparatov na področju električnega inženiringa; Preskušanje funkcionalnosti strojev; Razvoj testnih metod; Razvoj merilnih in testnih metod; Storitve računalniško podprtega diagnostičnega testiranja; Kontrola kvalitete in Testiranje; Analitične in testne storitve v zvezi z električnimi inženirskimi aparati; Storitve testiranja industrijskih strojev za nadzor kakovosti; Testiranje, analiza in ocenjevanje blaga in storitev drugih za namene certificiranja; Storitve tehničnega merjenja; Storitve tehničnega pregleda; Računalniško podprte storitve inženirskega oblikovanja; Računalniško podprte storitve inženirskega oblikovanja in risanja; Inženirske storitve za druge; Storitve tehničnega risanja; Strojni inženiring; Inženirske raziskave; Inženirske in računalniško podprte inženirske storitve; Analiza tehnološkega inženiringa; Razvoj novih tehnologij za druge; Merilne storitve; Storitve raziskave pnevmatik; Storitve raziskav in razvoja na področju strojništva; Spremljanje stanja tekočin; Spremljanje stanja maziv; Inženirske storitve; Oblikovanje in testiranje novih izdelkov; Storitve nedestruktivnega testiranja; Testiranje, preverjanje avtentičnosti in kontrola kakovosti; Testne storitve za certificiranje kakovosti ali standardov; Oblikovanje in razvoj preizkusnih in analitičnih metod.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Utvecklingstjänster avseende metoder för provning; Teknisk provning; Vetenskapliga och tekniska tjänster; Maskinritning; Konsultation avseende produktionsteknik; Tekniska utvärderingar utförda av ingenjörer; Datorstödda konstruktionstekniska tjänster; Maskinteknisk konsultation; Ingenjörsprovningar; Utarbetande av ingenjörsrapporter; Ingenjörstjänster för utformning/design av konstruktioner; Ingenjörstekniska tjänster för analys av maskiner; Ingenjörstjänster inom drivkraftsområdet; Teknisk ingenjörsverksamhet; Teknisk utformning och konsultation; Planering av tekniska projekt inom det teknologiska området; Ingenjörstjänster för projektledning; Tekniska uppskattningar utförda av ingenjörer; Konsultation avseende teknisk utveckling; Rådgivning avseende energianvändning; Rådgivning avseende energieffektivitet; Konsulttjänster avseende teknologisk forskning; Datorstödda industriella analystjänster; Utförande av industriella provningar; Professionell konsultation rörande teknik; Professionell konsultation rörande energisparande; Konstruktionsritning; Planering av tekniska projekt; Teknisk konsultation avseende produktutveckling; Teknologiska tjänster; Utförande av industriella experiment; Analyser av produktutveckling; Teknologiska analystjänster; Analys och utvärdering av produktutveckling; Datautvinning; Konsultationer inom området konstruktionsritning; Industriell provning; Datorstödd industriell testning; Tekniska mät- och provningstjänster; Provning av nya produkter; Design och provning för ny produktutveckling; Inspektion av fordon; Provning av databehandlingsutrustning; Provning av maskiner; Apparatprovning inom området för elektroteknik; Testning av funktionen hos maskiner; Utveckling av testmetoder; Utveckling av mät- och kontrollmetoder; Datorstödd diagnostisk provning; Kvalitetskontroll och provning; Analys- och provningstjänster avseende elektroteknologiska apparater; Kvalitetskontrollstjänster för industriell utrustning; Provning, analys och utvärdering av andras varor och tjänster för certifieringsändamål; Tekniska mätningstjänster; Tekniska inspektionstjänster; Datorstödd teknisk designtjänst; Datorstödda maskinkonstruktions- och -ritningstjänster; Ingenjörstjänster för andras räkning; Ritningstjänster i form av tekniska ritningar; Maskiningenjörstjänster; Ingenjörsteknisk forskning; Ingenjörsverksamhet och datorstödd ingenjörsverksamhet; Teknologiska ingenjörsanalyser; Utveckling av ny teknik för andras räkning; Mätningstjänster; Däckforskning; Forsknings- och utvecklingstjänster inom teknikområdet; Övervakning av vätskors tillstånd; Övervakning av smörjmedels tillstånd; Ingenjörstjänster; Design och testning av nya produkter; Oförstörande provning; Testning, verifieringstjänster och kvalitetskontroll; Testtjänster för certifiering av kvalitet eller standarder; Design och utveckling av provnings- och analysmetoder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080446</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>95827</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>95828</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
