<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-07T08:34:33</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226766</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226766</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-05</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-07</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>MINI GLOBE RACE</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162316465</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226766/000162316465.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>26.07.03</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Лаптопи; Мобилни приложения; Компютърен приложен софтуер за телевизия; USB памет; Костюми за гмуркане; Ръкавици за водолази; Спасителни шамандури; Морски компаси; Калъфи за смартфони; Калъфи за смартфони; Шнурове за пенснета; Калъфи за очила; Телефони; Хендс-фри комплекти за телефони; Оптични фенери; DVD плейъри; Компактдиск плейъри; Оптични стоки; Слънчеви очила; Смарт часовници; Портативни радиотелефони [уоки-токи]; Апарати за температурен контрол; Очила [оптични]; Всички изброени са свързани с мореплавателна навигация.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Počítače; Mobilní aplikace; Počítačový aplikační software pro televizory; USB flash disky; Potápěčské obleky; Potápěčské rukavice; Záchranné vesty; Námořní kompasy; Pouzdra na chytré telefony (smartphony); Kryty na chytré telefony (smartphony); Šňůrky na skřipce; Pouzdra na brýle; Telefonní sluchátka; Handsfree sady pro telefony; Optické lampy; DVD přehrávače; Přehrávače kompaktních disků; Výrobky oční optiky; Sluneční brýle; Chytré hodinky; Vysílačky walkie-talkie; Termostaty; Brýle; Vše výše uvedené se přitom vztahuje k mořské navigaci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Computere; Mobilapplikationer; Tv-computerapplikationssoftware; USB flash drivere; Dykkerdragter; Handsker til dykkere; Redningsveste; Maritime kompasser; Etuier til smartphones; Covers til smartphones; Brillesnore; Etuier til briller; Telefonrør; Håndfri sæt til telefoner; Optiske lanterner; DVD afspillere; CD-afspillere; Optikervarer; Solbriller; Smartwatches; Walkie-talkies; Termostater; Briller [optik]; Idet alt det foregående er relateret til havsejlads.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Computer; Mobile Apps; TV-Computeranwendungssoftware; USB-Sticks; Taucheranzüge; Taucherhandschuhe; Rettungswesten; Schiffskompasse; Schalen für Smartphones; Hüllen für Smartphones; Brillenkordeln; Brillenetuis; Telefonhörer; Freisprecheinrichtung für Telefone; Optische Lampen; DVD-Spieler, DVD-Player; CD-Player; Optikerwaren; Sonnenbrillen; Smartwatches; Tragbare Sprechfunkgeräte; Temperaturregelungsgeräte; Brillen [Optik]; Alles vorstehend Genannte in Bezug auf die Seeschifffahrt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ηλεκτρονικοί υπολογιστές· Εφαρμογές κινητών· Λογισμικό εφαρμογών ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για τηλεόραση· Οδηγοί USB (καθολικού σειριακού αγωγού)· Φόρμες κατάδυσης· Γάντια κατάδυσης· Ζώνες σωστικές· Ναυτικά όργανα μέτρησης· Θήκες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Καλύμματα για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Κορδόνια για γυαλιά οράσεως· Επιρρίνιων γυαλιών οράσεως θήκες· Ακουστικά τηλεφώνου· Σετ ανοικτής ακρόασης για τηλέφωνα· Οπτικοί λαμπτήρες· Συσκευές αναπαραγωγής ψηφιακών βιντεοδίσκων· Συσκευές για σύμπυκνους δίσκους (CD)· Οπτικά είδη· Γυαλιά ηλίου· Έξυπνα ρολόγια χειρός· Σύστημα ασύρματης τηλεπικοινωνίας [γουόκι-τώκι]· Συσκευές ρύθμισης θερμοκρασίας· Διόπτρες· Τα προαναφερόμενα στο σύνολό τους σε σχέση με θαλάσσια πλοήγηση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Computers; mobile apps; computer application software for TV; USB flash drives; diving suits; gloves for divers; life vests; marine compasses; cases for smartphones; covers for smartphones; eyeglass cords; spectacle cases; telephone receivers; hands free kits for phones; optical lanterns; DVD players; compact disc players; optical goods; sunglasses; smartwatches; walkie-talkies; temperature controlling apparatus; spectacles [optics]; all the foregoing being related to maritime navigation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Ordenadores; Aplicaciones de móviles; Software de aplicaciones informáticas para televisión; Memorias USB; Trajes de buceo; Guantes de buceo; Chalecos salvavidas; Brújulas marinas; Carátulas para teléfonos inteligentes; Fundas para teléfonos inteligentes; Anteojos (Cordones para -); Estuches para gafas; Receptores telefónicos; Kits manos libres para teléfonos; Linternas ópticas; Lectores de DVD; Reproductores de discos compactos; Artículos de óptica para la vista; Gafas de sol; Relojes inteligentes; Radioteléfonos portátiles [walkie-talkies]; Termostatos; Gafas [óptica]; Todos los mencionados están relacionados con la navegación marítima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arvutid, raalid; Mobiilirakendused; Telerite arvutirakendustarkvara; USB-mälupulgad; Skafandrid, tuukriülikonnad; Kindad sukeldujatele; Päästevestid; Merekompassid; Nutitelefonide ümbrised; Nutitelefonide katted; Näpitsprillide paelad; Prillitoosid; Telefonide kuuldetorud; Mobiiltelefonide hands-free-komplektid; Optilised lambid; DVD-mängijad; Kompaktplaadimängijad, laserplaadimängijad; Optikakaubad; Päikeseprillid; Nutikellad; Raadiotelefonid; Termostaadid; Prillid [optika]; Kõik eelnimetatu seoses meresõiduga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sylimikrot; Mobiilisovellukset; Tietokonesovellusohjelmistot televisiota varten; USB-muistit; Sukelluspuvut; Käsineet (Sukellus -); Pelastusliivit; Laivakompassit; Älypuhelinten kuoret; Älypuhelinten suojukset; Nenälasipunokset; Silmälasikotelot; Puhelinkuulokkeet; Hands-free -laitteet puhelimia varten; Optiset lyhdyt; DVD-soittimet; CD-levysoittimet; Optikon tavarat; Aurinkolasit; Älykellot; Kannettavat radiopuhelimet; Lämpötilan säätölaitteet; Silmälasit [optiikka]; Kaikki edellä mainitut liittyvät merenkulun navigointiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Ordinateurs; Applications logicielles pour téléphones mobiles; Logiciel d'application informatique pour la télévision; Clés USB; Combinaisons de plongée; Gants de plongée; Gilets de sauvetage; Compas de marine; Étuis pour smartphones; Coques pour smartphones; Cordons de pince-nez; Étuis à lunettes; Combinés téléphoniques; Nécessaires mains libres pour téléphones; Lanternes optiques; Lecteurs DVD; Lecteurs de disques compacts; Articles de lunetterie; Lunettes de soleil; Montres intelligentes; Talkies-walkies; Appareils de réglage de la température; Lunettes [optique]; Tous les produits précités étant liés à la navigation maritime.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Računala; Mobilne aplikacije; Računalne softverske aplikacije za TV; USB uređaji [USB stickovi]; Skafanderi za ronnjenje; Rukavice za ronioce; Prsluci za spašavanje; Pomorski kompasi; Etuiji za pametne telefone; Navlake za pametne telefone; Uzice za cvikere [monokle]; Etuiji za naočale; Telefonski prijemnici; Kompleti za telefone za telefoniranje bez ruku; Optičke svjetiljke; DVD plejeri; Uređaji za reprodukciju kompaktnih diskova; Optički proizvodi; Sunčane naočale; Pametni ručni satovi; Toki-voki; Instrumenti za kontrolu temperature; Naočale [optika]; Sve prethodno navedeno u vezi je s pomorskom navigacijom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Számítógépek; Mobil alkalmazások; Számítógépes szoftver alkalmazások TV-hez; USB pendrive-ok; Búvárruhák; Búvárkesztyűk; Mentőmellények; Tengerészeti iránytűk; Tokok okostelefonhoz; Tokok okostelefonokhoz; Zsinórok csíptetős szemüveghez; Szemüvegtokok; Telefonkagylók; Kihangosító készletek telefonokhoz; Optikai lámpák; DVD-lejátszók; CD-lejátszók; Optikai cikkek; Napszemüvegek; Okoskarórák; Kézi adó-vevők [walkie-talkie készülékek]; Hőmérséklet szabályozó készülékek; Szemüvegek [optika]; Az említettek mindegyike a tengeri hajózással kapcsolatos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Elaboratori elettronici; Applicazioni per cellulari; Software applicativi per TV; Chiavi USB; Scafandri; Guanti per subacquei; Giubotti salvagente; Bussole marine; Custodie per smartphone; Coperchi per smartphone; Cordoncini per occhiali a molle; Astucci per occhiali; Ricevitori telefonici; Kit viva voce; Lampade ottiche; Lettori dvd; Lettori di compact disc; Prodotti ottici; Occhiali da sole; Orologi intelligenti; Ricetrasmittenti; Apparecchi di controllo della temperatura; Occhiali [ottica]; Tutti i suddetti articoli in materia di navigazione marittima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kompiuteriai; Mobiliųjų įrenginių taikomoji programinė įranga; Kompiuterių taikomoji programinė įranga televizoriams; Atmintukai [USB]; Narų kostiumai; Nardytojų pirštinės; Gelbėjimo liemenės; Jūriniai kompasai; Išmaniųjų telefonų dėklai; Išmaniųjų telefonų dangteliai; Akinių virvelės; Akinių dėklai; Telefono rageliai; Laisvų rankų įrangos rinkiniai telefonams; Optiniai žibintai; DVD grotuvai; Kompaktinių diskų leistuvai; Optikos prekės; Saulės akiniai; Išmanieji laikrodžiai; Nešiojamieji radijo aparatai; Termostatai; Akiniai [optika]; Visi prieš tai paminėti yra susiję su jūrų (laivybos) navigacija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Datori; Mobilas lietotnes; Datoru lietojumprogrammatūra televizoriem; USB zibatmiņas diski; Niršanas kostīmi; Ūdenslīdēju cimdi; Glābšanas vestes; Jūras kompasi; Ietvari viedtālruņiem; Maciņi viedtālruņiem; Pensneju auklas; Briļļu maki; Telefona klausules; Telefonu brīvroku sistēmas; Optiskie gaismekļi; Atskaņotāji (DVD atskaņotāji); Kompaktdisku atskaņotāji; Optikas preces; Saulesbrilles; Viedie rokaspulksteņi; Portatīvi radioraidītāji un uztvērēji; Temperatūras kontroles aparatūra; Brilles; Viss iepriekš minētais ir saistīts jūras navigāciju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kompjuters; Applikazzjoni tat-tagħmir ċellulari; Softwer ta' applikazjoni tal-kompjuter għat-TV; Flash drives tal-USB; Ħwejjeġ tal-għaddasa; Ingwanti għall-għaddasa; Salvawomi; Kumpassi marini; Kaxxi għall-ismartphones; Kavers għal smartfowns; Kordi għan-nuċċalijiet; Kontenituri tan-nuċċalijiet; Riċevituri tat-telefon; Kitts li ma jinżammux fl-idejn għat-telefowns; Fanali ottiċi; Plejers (DVD); Apparat li jdoqq id-diski kumpatti; Prodotti tat-tobba li jieħdu ħsieb il-kura tal-għajnejn; Nuċċalijiet tax-xemx; Arloġġi tal-idejn tat-tip smart; Radju żgħir li jinġarr u li jittrasmetti u jirċievi (walkie-talkies); Apparat għall-kontroll tat-temperatura; Nuċċalijiet [ottiċi]; Dak kollu msemmi qabel hu relatat ma' navigazzjoni marittima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Computers; Mobiele applicaties; Computer applicatiesoftware voor televisies; USB-sticks; Duikpakken; Duikerhandschoenen; Reddingsvesten; Scheepskompassen; Etuis voor smartphones; Hoezen voor smartphones; Koorden voor knijpbrillen; Brillenkokers; Telefoonhoorns; Handsfree kits voor telefoons; Optische lampen; Dvd-spelers; Cd-spelers; Optische producten; Zonnebrillen; Smartwatches; Walkie-talkies; Temperatuurregulerende apparatuur; Brillen; Al het voornoemde met betrekking tot scheepvaartnavigatie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Komputery; Mobilne aplikacje; Komputerowe oprogramowanie użytkowe do telewizji; Pamięci zewnętrzne USB; Skafandry dla nurków; Rękawice dla nurków; Kamizelki ratunkowe; Kompasy okrętowe; Etui na smartfony; Pokrowce na smartfony; Sznureczki do binokli; Etui na okulary; Słuchawki telefoniczne; Zestawy do korzystania z telefonu bez użycia rąk; Lampy optyczne; Odtwarzacze płyt DVD; Odtwarzacze płyt kompaktowych; Artykuły optyczne; Okulary przeciwsłoneczne; Zegarki inteligentne; Walkie-talkie; Aparatura do kontrolowania temperatury; Okulary [optyka]; Wszystkie wyżej wymienione związane z nawigacją morską.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Computadores; Aplicações móveis; Software aplicativo para TV; Unidades de disco amovível [USB flash drives]; Fatos de mergulhador; Luvas para mergulho; Coletes de salvação; Compassos marítimos; Capas para smartphones; Capas para smartphones; Cordões para óculos pince-nez; Estojos para óculos; Auscultadores telefónicos; Kits de mãos livres para telefones; Lâmpadas óticas; Leitores de dvd; Leitores de discos compactos [leitores de cd]; Artigos de optometrista; Óculos de sol; Relógios de pulso inteligentes; Walkie-talkies; Aparelhos para controlo da temperatura; Óculos [ótica]; Todos os produtos atrás referidos relacionados com navegação marítima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Computere; Aplicatii mobile; Software de aplicaţii informatice pentru televizor; Memorii USB; Costume de scafandru; Mănuşi de scafandru; Veste de salvare; Compasuri de navigaţie; Carcase pentru telefoane inteligente; Huse pentru telefoane inteligente; Cordoane pentru ochelari; Tocuri pentru ochelari fără braţe; Receptoare telefonice; Dispozitive mâini libere pentru telefoane; Lanterne optice; DVD playere; Dispozitive de redare pentru discuri compacte; Produse de optică; Ochelari de soare; Ceasuri inteligente; Staţii de radio portative; Aparate de reglare a temperaturii; Ochelari [optică]; Toate cele menţionate anterior având legătură cu navigaţia maritimă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Počítače; Mobilné aplikácie; Počítačové aplikačný softvér pre televízory; USB kľúče; Potápačské kombinézy; Potápačské rukavice; Záchranné bóje; Námorné kompasy; Puzdrá na smartfóny; Kryty na smartfóny; Šnúrky na cvikre; Puzdrá na okuliare; Telefónne slúchadlá; Handsfree (slúchadlá so zabudovaným mikrofónom na telefonovanie bez držania telefónu); Optické lampy; DVD prehrávače; Prehrávač kompaktných diskov; Výrobky očnej optiky; Slnečné okuliare; Inteligentné hodinky; Prenosné krátkovlnné vysielačky; Termostaty; Okuliare; Všetko vyššie uvedené súvisí s námornou navigáciou.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Računalniki; Mobilna aplikacija; Računalniška aplikacijska programska oprema za televizije; USB ključki; Potapljaške obleke; Rokavice za potapljače; Rešilni jopiči; Pomorski kompasi; Etuiji za pametne telefone; Ohišja za pametne telefone; Vrvice za naočnike; Etuiji za očala; Telefonske slušalke; Oprema za prostoročno telefoniranje; Optične svetilke; DVD predvajalniki; Predvajalniki CD-jev; Proizvodi za optiko; Sončna očala; Pametne zapestne ure; Prenosen radijski sprejemni in oddajni aparat (radiotelefon); Aparati za uravnavanje temperature; Očala [optika]; Vse omenjeno je v zvezi s pomorsko navigacijo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Datorer; Mobil-appar; Programvara för datorapplikationer för tv; USB-minnen; Dykardräkter; Handskar för dykare; Flytvästar; Nautiska kompasser; Skal för smartphones; Fodral för smartphones; Pincenésnoddar; Glasögonfodral; Telefonhörlurar; Handsfree för telefoner; Optiska lampor; DVD spelare; Cd-spelare; Optikervaror; Solglasögon; Smarta klockor; Walkie-talkies; Apparater för temperaturkontroll; Glasögon; Samtliga nämnda avseende sjöfartsnavigation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Канцеларски принадлежности; Плакати; Фотографии [отпечатани]; Албуми; Тетрадки; Бележници [канцеларски принадлежности]; Държачи за хартиени листа; Книжки; Тетрадки; Тефтери за писане или чертане; Календари; Карти; Пощенски картички; Печатни произведения; Вестници; Книги; Чанти [пликове, торбички] от хартия или полиетилен за опаковане пакетиране; Всички изброени са свързани с мореплавателна навигация.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Papírenské zboží; Plakáty; Fotografie [tištěné]; Alba; Bloky na kreslení; Bloky [kancelářské potřeby]; Pomůcky na přidržování rozevřených stránek; Brožury; Zápisníky (notesy); Sešity; Kalendáře; Karty; Pohlednice; Tiskárenské výrobky; Noviny; Knihy; Sáčky [obálky, váčky] z papíru nebo plastických hmot na balení; Vše výše uvedené se přitom vztahuje k mořské navigaci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Papirhandlervarer (skriveredskaber og papirvarer); Plakater; Fotografier [trykte]; Albummer; Tegneblokke; Blokke [papirvarer]; Sideholdere; Pjecer [tryksager]; Notesbøger; Skrive- eller tegnehæfter; Kalendere; Kort; Postkort; Tryksager; Aviser; Bøger; Sække af papir eller plastic til emballering; Idet alt det foregående er relateret til havsejlads.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Schreibwaren; Plakate; Fotografien [Abzüge]; Alben; Zeichenblöcke; Blöcke [Papier- und Schreibwaren]; Seitenhalter; Broschüren; Notizbücher; Schreibhefte; Kalender; Karten; Postkarten; Druckereierzeugnisse; Zeitungen; Bücher; Verpackungsbeutel,- hüllen, -taschen aus Papier oder Kunststoff; Alles vorstehend Genannte in Bezug auf die Seeschifffahrt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Είδη χαρτοπωλείου· Αφίσες· Φωτογραφίες [εκτυπωμένες]· Λευκώματα τυπογραφικά· Σημειωματάρια· Σημειωματάρια [μπλοκ] είδη χαρτοπωλείου· Κλιπ στερέωσης σελίδας· Φυλλάδια· Σημειωματάρια· Τετράδια για γράψιμο ή σχέδιο· Ημεροδείκτες· Κάρτες· Ταχυδρομικές κάρτες (καρτ ποστάλ)· Έντυπο υλικό· Εφημερίδες· Βιβλία· Σακουλάκια [φάκελλοι,θήκες] για συσκευασία από χαρτί ή πλαστικό· Τα προαναφερόμενα στο σύνολό τους σε σχέση με θαλάσσια πλοήγηση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Stationery; posters; photographs (printed); scrapbooks; drawing pads; pads (stationery); page holders; pamphlets; notebooks; writing or drawing books; calendars; cards; postcards; printed matter; newspapers; books; bags [envelopes, pouches] of paper or plastics, for packaging; all the foregoing being related to maritime navigation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Artículos de papelería; Pósters; Fotografías [impresas]; Álbumes; Blocs de dibujo; Blocs [artículos de papelería]; Sujetapáginas; Folletos; Libretas; Cuadernos; Calendarios; Tarjetas; Postales (Tarjetas -); Productos de imprenta; Periódicos; Libros; Bolsas [sobres, bolsitas] de papel o materias plásticas para empaquetar; Todos los mencionados están relacionados con la navegación marítima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kirjatarbed; Plakatid, müürilehed; Trükitud fotod; Albumid; Joonistusplokid; Plokid [kirjatarbed]; Leheküljehoidjad; Pisitrükised, brošüürid; Märkmikud; Märkmikud, märkmeplokid; Kalendrid; Kaardid, joongraafikud; Postkaardid; Trükised; Ajalehed; Raamatud; Paberist või plastist kotid pakkimiseks [ümbrised, vutlarid]; Kõik eelnimetatu seoses meresõiduga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Paperitavarat (kirjoitus- ja toimistotarvikkeet); Julisteet; Valokuvat [painetut]; Albumit; Muistikirjat; Lehtiöt; Sivunpidikkeet; Kirjaset; Muistikirjat; Kirjoitus- ja piirustuslehtiöt; Kalenterit; Kortit; Postikortit; Painotuotteet; Sanomalehdet; Kirjat; Kassit (Paperi- tai muovi -), pakkaamiseen [kirjekuoret,pussit]; Kaikki edellä mainitut liittyvät merenkulun navigointiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Papeterie; Affiches; Photographies [imprimées]; Albums; Blocs à dessin; Blocs [papeterie]; Bloque-pages; Brochures; Carnets; Livres pour le dessin et l'écriture; Calendriers; Cartes; Cartes postales; Produits de l'imprimerie; Journaux; Livres; Sachets [enveloppes, pochettes] en papier ou en matières plastiques pour l'emballage; Tous les produits précités étant liés à la navigation maritime.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pribor za pisanje; Posteri; Fotografije [tiskane]; Albumi; Blokovi za skiciranje; Blokovi [papirnati proizvodi]; Držači stranica knjiga; Brošure; Bilježnice; Bilježnice; Kalendari; Karte; Razglednice; Tiskarski proizvodi; Novine; Knjige; Vrećice [omotnice, torbice], od papira ili plastike za ambalažu; Sve prethodno navedeno u vezi je s pomorskom navigacijom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Papíripari cikkek; Poszterek; Fényképek [nyomtatott]; Scrapbook [családi albumok]; Noteszok; Blokkok [papíráruk]; Könyvlaprögzítők; Könyvecskék, brosúrák; Noteszok; Füzetek, könyvek íráshoz vagy rajzoláshoz; Naptárak; Kártyák; Képeslapok, levelezőlapok; Nyomdaipari termékek; Újságok; Könyvek; Zacskók csomagolásra papírból vagy műanyagból; Az említettek mindegyike a tengeri hajózással kapcsolatos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cartoleria; Cartelloni; Fotografie [stampate]; Album; Blocchi da disegno; Blocchi [cartoleria]; Ferma-pagina; Opuscoli; Taccuini; Quaderni; Calendari; Carte; Cartoline postali; Stampati; Giornali; Libri; Sacchetti [buste, bustine, borsette] per imballaggio di carta o di materie plastiche; Tutti i suddetti articoli in materia di navigazione marittima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Raštinės reikmenys; Afišos; Fotonuotraukos [spausdintos]; Albumai; Piešimo, braižymo bloknotai; Bloknotai [raštinės reikmenys]; Puslapių laikikliai; Brošiūros; Užrašų knygutės; Rašymo ir piešimo sąsiuviniai; Kalendoriai; Kortos; Pašto atvirukai; Spaudiniai; Laikraščiai; Knygos; Popieriniai ar plastikiniai pakavimo maišeliai; Visi prieš tai paminėti yra susiję su jūrų (laivybos) navigacija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Rakstāmlietas; Plakāti; Iespiesti fotoattēli; Albumi; Piezīmju grāmatiņas; Bloknoti [kancelejas preces]; Lappušu turētāji; Pamfleti; Piezīmju grāmatiņas; Burtnīcas rakstīšanai un zīmēšanai; Kalendāri; Kartītes; Pastkartes; Iespiedprodukcija; Avīzes; Grāmatas; Iesaiņošanas maisiņi [aploksnes, kabatiņas] no papīra vai plastmasas; Viss iepriekš minētais ir saistīts jūras navigāciju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kartoleriji; Kartelluni; Ritratti [stampati]; Ktieb bil-folji vojta għal użu fi twaħħil ta' stampi; Takkwini; Folji tal-karti mehmużin flimkien [kartolerija]; Ħowlders tal-paġni; Kotba żgħar; Takkwini; Kotba għall-kitba u għat-tpinġija; Kalendarji; Kartolini; Kartolini; Materjal stampat; Gazzetti; Kotba; Boroż (enveloppi, boroż żgħar) tal-karta jew tal-plastik għall-ippakkjar; Dak kollu msemmi qabel hu relatat ma' navigazzjoni marittima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Schrijfbehoeften; Aanplakbiljetten; Foto's [afgedrukt]; Albums; Tekenblokken; Blocnotes; Klemmen voor het openhouden van boeken; Brochures; Notitieboekjes; Schriften; Kalenders; Kaarten; Briefkaarten; Drukwerken; Kranten; Boeken; Zakken [omslagen, zakjes] van papier of plastic, voor verpakking; Al het voornoemde met betrekking tot scheepvaartnavigatie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Materiały biurowe; Afisze, plakaty; Fotografie [wydrukowane]; Albumy do wklejania; Notatniki [notesy]; Bloki [artykuły papiernicze]; Zakładki do stron; Broszury; Notatniki [notesy]; Zeszyty do pisania lub rysowania; Kalendarze; Karty; Karty pocztowe; Druki; Gazety; Książki; Torebki do pakowania [koperty, woreczki] z papieru lub tworzyw sztucznych; Wszystkie wyżej wymienione związane z nawigacją morską.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Papelaria; Cartazes; Fotografias impressas; Álbuns; Blocos para desenho; Blocos [papelaria]; Apoios de páginas de livros; Panfletos [brochuras]; Blocos de notas; Cadernos para escrever ou desenhar; Calendários; Cartões; Cartões postais; Produtos de impressão; Jornais; Livros; Sacos [invólucros, bolsas] em papel ou plástico, para embalagens; Todos os produtos atrás referidos relacionados com navegação marítima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Papetărie; Afişe; Fotografii imprimate; Albume; Carnete de notiţe; Blocuri [papetărie]; Articole pentru prinderea paginilor; Broşuri; Carnete de notiţe; Cărţi de desenat sau de scris; Calendare; Carduri; Poştal (cărţi -e); Produse de imprimerie; Ziare; Cărţi; Pungi [învelitoare, săculeţe] de ambalaj din hârtie sau material plastic; Toate cele menţionate anterior având legătură cu navigaţia maritimă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Papiernický tovar a písacie potreby; Plagáty; Fotografie (tlačoviny); Albumy; Skicáre; Útržkové bloky; Držiaky stránok otvorenej knihy; Brožúry; Poznámkové zošity; Zošity; Kalendáre; Mapy; Pohľadnice; Tlačoviny; Noviny; Knihy; Papierové alebo plastové vrecká a tašky na balenie; Všetko vyššie uvedené súvisí s námornou navigáciou.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pisarniški material; Plakati (posterji); Fotografije [tiskane]; Albumi; Zvezki; Bloki [pisarniški material]; Držala za liste; Knjižice; Zvezki; Zvezki za pisanje ali risanje; Koledarji; Karte; Razglednice; Tiskovine (izdelki tiskarn); Časopisi; Knjige; Vrečke [ovojnice, torbice] iz papirja ali plastike za pakiranje; Vse omenjeno je v zvezi s pomorsko navigacijo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Pappersvaror (skriv- och kontorsmaterial); Affischer; Fotografier [tryckta]; Album; Anteckningsböcker; Block [pappersvaror]; Sidhållare; Häften; Memo-böcker; Skriv- eller ritböcker; Kalendrar; Kort; Vykort; Trycksaker; Tidningar; Böcker; Påsar [omslag, kuvert] av papper eller plast för emballering; Samtliga nämnda avseende sjöfartsnavigation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Облекло; Обувки; Бельо; Колани за кръста; Спортни обувки; Пояси, широки платнени колани с висящи краища; Къси чорапи; Панделки, ленти за глава; Шапки и други принадлежности за глава; Обувки; Ръкавици [облекло]; Всички изброени са свързани с мореплавателна навигация.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Oděvy; Obuv; Spodní prádlo; Pásky; Sportovní vyšší obuv; Šerpy; Ponožky; Čelenky [oděvy]; Pokrývky hlavy; Boty; Rukavice [oděvy]; Vše výše uvedené se přitom vztahuje k mořské navigaci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beklædningsgenstande; Fodtøj; Undertøj; Livremme; Sportsstøvler; Skærf til brug som beklædning; Sokker; Pandebånd [beklædning]; Hovedbeklædning; Sko; Handsker [beklædning]; Idet alt det foregående er relateret til havsejlads.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bekleidungsstücke; Schuhwaren; Unterwäsche; Gürtel; Sportschuhe; Schals, Schärpen; Socken; Stirnbänder [Bekleidung]; Kopfbedeckungen; Schuhe [Halbschuhe]; Handschuhe [Bekleidung]; Alles vorstehend Genannte in Bezug auf die Seeschifffahrt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ενδύματα· Υποδήματα· Εσώρουχα· Ζώνες· Αθλητικά υποδήματα· Υφασμάτινες κορδέλες (ζώνες)· Κάλτσες· Περίδεμα κεφαλιού [είδη ένδυσης]· Είδη πιλοποιίας· Υποδήματα· Γάντια· Τα προαναφερόμενα στο σύνολό τους σε σχέση με θαλάσσια πλοήγηση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Clothing; footwear; underwear; waist belts; athletics shoes; sashes for wear; socks; headbands [clothing]; headgear; shoes; gloves [clothing]; all the foregoing being related to maritime navigation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Prendas de vestir; Calzado; Lencería; Cinturones; Calzado de deporte; Fajas [bandas]; Calcetines; Cintas para la cabeza; Artículos de sombrerería; Zapatos; Guantes [prendas de vestir]; Todos los mencionados están relacionados con la navegación marítima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rõivad; Jalatsid; Alusrõivad, -riided, -pesu; Rihmad, vööd [rõivaste juurde]; Spordisaapad; Ehisvööd, õlavööd, särbid (rõivaste juurde); Sokid; Peapaelad [rõivad]; Peakatted; Kingad; Kindad (rõivad); Kõik eelnimetatu seoses meresõiduga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatteet; Jalkineet; Alusvaatteet; Vyötärönauhat; Lenkkitossut; Kangasvyöt; Sukat; Päänauhat [hikinauhat]; Päähineet; Jalkineet; Käsineet; Kaikki edellä mainitut liittyvät merenkulun navigointiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vêtements; Chaussures; Sous-vêtements; Ceintures; Chaussures de sport; Écharpes; Chaussettes; Bandeaux pour la tête [habillement]; Chapellerie; Souliers; Gants [habillement]; Tous les produits précités étant liés à la navigation maritime.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Odjeća; Obuća; Donje rublje; Pojasevi; Sportska obuća; Lente [odjeća]; Kratke čarape; Trake za glavu; Pokrivala za glavu; Obuća; Rukavice; Sve prethodno navedeno u vezi je s pomorskom navigacijom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ruházati cikkek; Lábbelik; Alsóruházat, fehérneműk; Derékszíjak, övek; Sportcipők; Selyemövek, vállszalagok; Zoknik; Fejszalagok [ruházat]; Kalapáruk; Lábbelik; Kesztyűk [ruházat]; Az említettek mindegyike a tengeri hajózással kapcsolatos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Abbigliamento; Calzature; Biancheria intima; Cinture; Calzature per lo sport; Sciarpe; Calzini; Fasce per la testa [abbigliamento]; Cappelleria; Scarpe; Guanti [abbigliamento]; Tutti i suddetti articoli in materia di navigazione marittima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Drabužiai, apranga; Apavas; Apatiniai marškiniai; Liemens diržai; Sportiniai batai; Diržai [juostos]; Puskojinės; Galvajuostės [drabužiai]; Galvos apdangalai; Avalynė; Pirštinės [drabužiai]; Visi prieš tai paminėti yra susiję su jūrų (laivybos) navigacija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apģērbi; Kurpes; Apakšveļa; Vidukļa jostas; Sporta apavi; Drēbes jostas-lentes; Īsās zeķes; Saites ap galvu; Galvassegas; Kurpes; Cimdi; Viss iepriekš minētais ir saistīts jūras navigāciju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ilbies; Xedd is-saqajn; Ħwejjeġ ta' taħt; Ċinturini ta' mal-qadd; Żraben għall-atletika; Trieħi (lbies); Kalzetti; Bandò [lbies]; Xedd ir-ras; Xedd is-saqajn; Ingwanti; Dak kollu msemmi qabel hu relatat ma' navigazzjoni marittima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kleding; Schoeisel; Ondergoed; Ceintuurs, riemen; Sportschoeisel; Sjerpen; Sokken; Hoofdbanden [kleding]; Hoofddeksels; Schoenen; Handschoenen [kleding]; Al het voornoemde met betrekking tot scheepvaartnavigatie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odzież; Obuwie; Bielizna osobista; Paski; Buty sportowe; Szarfy [do ubrania]; Skarpetki; Opaski na głowę; Nakrycia głowy; Obuwie; Rękawiczki [odzież]; Wszystkie wyżej wymienione związane z nawigacją morską.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vestuário; Calçado; Roupa interior; Cintos; Botas para desporto; Echarpes; Meias; Fitas para cabeça [vestuário]; Chapelaria; Sapatos; Luvas [vestuário]; Todos os produtos atrás referidos relacionados com navegação marítima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole de îmbrăcăminte; Articole de încălţăminte; Lenjerie de corp; Curele (accesorii vestimentare); Încălţăminte de sport; Eşarfe; Şosete; Bentiţe pentru cap; Articole pentru acoperirea capului; Articole de încălţăminte; Mănuşi [articole de îmbrăcăminte]; Toate cele menţionate anterior având legătură cu navigaţia maritimă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Odevy, oblečenie; Obuv; Spodná bielizeň; Opasky; Športová obuv; Šerpy; Ponožky; Čelenky (oblečenie); Pokrývky hlavy; Topánky; Rukavice; Všetko vyššie uvedené súvisí s námornou navigáciou.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oblačila; Obutev; Spodnje perilo; Pasovi; Športni čevlji; Ešarpe; Kratke nogavice; Naglavni trakovi [oblačila]; Pokrivala; Obutev; Rokavice; Vse omenjeno je v zvezi s pomorsko navigacijo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kläder; Fotbeklädnader; Underkläder; Midjebälten; Sportskor; Ordensband; Sockor; Pannband [kläder]; Huvudbonader; Fotbeklädnader; Handskar; Samtliga nämnda avseende sjöfartsnavigation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Развлечение; Информационни услуги в областта на развлеченията; Развлекателни услуги и развлечения, спортни и културни дейности; Осигуряване на радио и телевизионни развлекателни услуги; Организиране на спортни състезания; Организиране на състезания (с образователни, културни или развлекателни цели),; Организация и провеждане на конгреси, семинари, конференции; Отдаване под наем на спортни съоръжения [с изключение на превозни средства]; Производство на филми; Фотография; Фоторепортажи; Публикуване на текстове; Издаване на книги; Онлайн публикуване на електронни книги и периодични издания; Доставка на онлайн електронни публикации [без възможност да бъдат прехвърляни върху друг носител]; Репортерски услуги; Резервация на места за представления; Горепосочените услуги са предназначени за морски курсове; Всички изброени са свързани с мореплавателна навигация.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zábava; Informace o možnostech zábavy; Zábavní, sportovní a kulturní aktivity; Služby v oblasti poskytování rozhlasové a televizní zábavy; Pořádání sportovních soutěží; Organizování soutěží (pro výchovné, kulturní nebo zábavní účely); Organizování a vedení kongresů, seminářů, konferencí; Půjčování sportovního vybavení, s výjimkou vozidel; Výroba filmů, s výjimkou reklamních; Služby fotografa; Obrazové zpravodajství; Vydávání textů; Vydávání knih; Vydávání elektronických knih a časopisů online; Provozování online elektronických publikací bez možnosti stažení; Služby reportérů (zpravodajství); Rezervace vstupenek na estrády; Výše uvedené služby je určené pro námořní kurzy; Vše výše uvedené se přitom vztahuje k mořské navigaci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Underholdningsvirksomhed; Information om underholdning; Underholdningsvirksomhed, sportsarrangementer og kulturelle arrangementer; Radio- og tv-underholdningsvirksomhed; Organisering af sportskonkurrencer; Organisering af konkurrencer til undervisning, kultur og underholdningsområdet; Arrangering og ledelse af kongresser, seminarer, konferencer; Udlejning af sportsudstyr, undtagen befordringsmidler; Filmproduktion, andre end reklamefilm; Fotografvirksomhed; Fotografisk reportage; Udgivelse af tekster; Udgivelse af bøger; Online publicering af elektroniske bøger og tidsskrifter; Tilvejebringelse af online elektroniske publikationer, ikke downloadable; Nyhedsformidling; Pladsreservation til shows; Alle førnævnte tjenesteydelser møntet på maritime konkurrencer; Idet alt det foregående er relateret til havsejlads.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Unterhaltung; Informationen über Unterhaltungsveranstaltungen; Unterhaltung, sportliche und kulturelle Aktivitäten; Radio- und TV-Unterhaltung; Veranstaltung sportlicher Wettkämpfe; Veranstaltung von Wettbewerben [für Bildungs-, kulturelle oder Unterhaltungszwecke]; Organisation und Leitung von Kongressen, Seminaren und Konferenzen; Vermietung von Sportausrüstungen, ausgenommen Fahrzeuge; Filmproduktion, ausgenommen Werbefilmproduktion; Fotografieren; Erstellen von Bildreportagen; Herausgabe von Texten; Veröffentlichung von Büchern; Online-Veröffentlichung von elektronischen Büchern und Zeitschriften; Online Bereitstellen von elektronischen, nicht herunterladbaren Publikationen; Dienstleistungen eines Zeitungsreporters; Platzreservierungen für Unterhaltungsveranstaltungen; Wobei alle vorstehend genannten Dienstleistungen für Hochseeregatten bestimmt sind; Alles vorstehend Genannte in Bezug auf die Seeschifffahrt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ψυχαγωγία· Πληροφόρηση σχετικά με την ψυχαγωγία· Διασκέδαση, αθλητικές και πολιτιστικές δραστηριότητες· Ραδιοφωνικές και τηλεοπτικές ψυχαγωγικές υπηρεσίες· Διοργάνωση αθλητικών αγώνων· Διοργάνωση αναμετρήσεων για εκπαιδευτικούς, πολιτιστικούς ή ψυχαγωγικούς σκοπούς· Οργάνωση και διεξαγωγή συνεδρίων, σεμιναρίων και διαλέξεων· Εκμίσθωση αθλητικού εξοπλισμού, εκτός οχημάτων· Παραγωγή ταινιών, εκτός από διαφημιστικές ταινίες· Υπηρεσίες φωτογράφου· Φωτοειδησεογραφία· Έκδοση κειμένων· Δημοσίευση βιβλίων· Έκδοση ηλεκτρονικών βιβλίων και επιθεωρήσεων Έκδοση ηλεκτρονικών βιβλίων και εφημερίδων (οn-line) χωρίς δυνατότητα τηλεφόρτωσης· Παροχή ηλεκτρονικών εκδόσεων on-line μη τηλεφορτώσιμων· Ανταποκριτών (Υπηρεσίες -)· Κράτηση θέσεων σε θεάματα· Οι προαναφερόμενες υπηρεσίες παρέχονται στο πλαίσιο θαλασσίων αγώνων δρόμου· Τα προαναφερόμενα στο σύνολό τους σε σχέση με θαλάσσια πλοήγηση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Entertainment; entertainment information; entertainment, sporting and cultural activities; provision of radio and television entertainment services; organizing sports competitions; organization of competitions (for educational, cultural or entertainment purposes); arranging and conducting of congresses, seminars and conferences; rental of sports equipment (except vehicles); film production, other than advertising films; photography; photographic reporting; publication of texts; publication of books; publication of electronic books and journals on-line; providing on-line electronic publications, not downloadable; news reporters services; booking of seats for shows; the aforesaid services being for maritime races; all the foregoing being related to maritime navigation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de entretenimiento; Información sobre actividades de entretenimiento; Servicios de entretenimiento y esparcimiento, actividades deportivas y culturales; Servicios de entretenimiento televisivo y radiofónico; Organización de competiciones deportivas; Organización de competiciones (con fines educativos, culturales o lúdicos); Organización y dirección de congresos, seminarios, conferencias; Alquiler de equipos deportivos, excepto vehículos; Producción de películas que no sean publicitarias; Servicios fotográficos; Reportajes fotográficos; Servicios de edición de textos; Publicación de libros; Publicación de libros y diarios electrónicos en línea (no descargables); Puesta a disposición de publicaciones electrónicas no descargables desde una red informática mundial o Internet; Servicios de reporteros; Reserva de localidades para espectáculos; Los servicios antes mencionados son para carreras marítimas; Todos los mencionados están relacionados con la navegación marítima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meelelahutus; Meelelahutusteave, -info; Meelelahutus, spordi- ja kultuuritegevus; Televisiooni- ja raadiomeelelahutus; Spordivõistluste korraldamine; Võistluste korraldamine (hariduslikel, kultuurilistel või meelelahutuslikel eesmärkidel); Konverentside, seminaride, konverentside korraldamine ja läbiviimine; Spordivarustuse üürimine, laenutus, v.a sõidukid; Filmitootmine, -produtseerimine, v.a reklaamfilmide tootmine; Fotograafiteenused; Fotoreporteriteenused; Tekstide kirjastamine, avaldamine; Raamatute kirjastamine, avaldamine; Elektrooniliste raamatute ja ajakirjade avaldamine arvutivõrgus (v.a allalaaditavad); Elektronväljaannete pakkumine arvutivõrgus, v.a allalaaditavad; Uudistereporterite teenused; Kohtade broneerimine etendustele; Eelnimetatud teenused on mõeldud merendusega seotudkursuste jaoks; Kõik eelnimetatu seoses meresõiduga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ajanviete; Ajanvieteneuvonta; Ajanviete, urheilu- ja kulttuuritoiminnat; Radio- ja televisioviihdepalvelujen tarjoaminen; Urheilukilpailujen järjestäminen; Kilpailujen järjestäminen (koulutus-, kulttuuri- ja ajanvietetarkoituksiin); Kongressien, seminaarien, konferenssien järjestäminen ja pitäminen; Vuokraus (urheiluvälineiden) [paitsi ajoneuvojen]; Elokuvatuotanto, muu kuin mainosfilmien; Valokuvaus; Kuvatoimittajan palvelut; Tekstien julkaisu; Kirjojen julkaisu; Elektronisten kirjojen ja lehtien julkaiseminen online-periaatteella; Elektronisten julkaisujen (muiden kuin ladattavien) tarjoaminen online-periaatteella; Uutistoimittajan palvelut; Lippujen varaus esityksiin; Edellä mainitut palvelut on tarkoitettu merenkulkukursseille; Kaikki edellä mainitut liittyvät merenkulun navigointiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Divertissement; Informations en matière de divertissement; Activités de divertissement, sportives et culturelles; Services de divertissement télévisé et radiophonique; Organisation de compétitions sportives; organisation de compétitions (à des fins d'éducation, culturelles ou de divertissement); Organisation et conduite de congrès, de séminaires, de conférences; Location d'équipement de sport autre que véhicules; Production de films autres que films publicitaires; Photographie; Reportages photographiques; Publication de textes autres que publicitaires; Publication de livres; Publication en ligne de livres et de revues électroniques (non téléchargeables); Fourniture de publications électroniques non téléchargeables; Services de reportages d'actualité; Réservation de places de spectacles; les services précitées étant destinés aux courses maritimes; Tous les produits précités étant liés à la navigation maritime.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Razonoda; Informacije o razonodi; Zabavne, sportske i kulturne aktivnosti; Pružanje radijskih i televizijskih zabavnih sadržaja; Organizacija sportskih natjecanja; Organiziranje natjecanja (u obrazovne, kulturne ili zabavne svrhe); Organizacija i vođenje kongresa, seminara, konferencija; Iznajmljivanje sportske opreme [osim vozila]; Filmska produkcija, osim reklamnih filmova; Fotografske usluge; Fotografske reportaže; Objavljivanje tekstova; Izdavanje knjiga; Online objavljivanje elektroničkih knjiga i časopisa; Pružanje online elektroničkih publikacija [nisu za preuzimanje]; Usluge informativnog izvještavanja; Rezerviranje sjedala za priredbe; Sve su navedene usluge namijenjene za pomorske tečajeve; Sve prethodno navedeno u vezi je s pomorskom navigacijom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szórakoztatás; Szórakozási, szórakoztatási információk; Szórakoztatási, sport és kulturális tevékenységek; Rádiós és televíziós szórakoztató szolgáltatások; Sportversenyek rendezése; Versenyek szervezése (oktatási, kulturális vagy szórakoztatási céllal); Konferenciák, kongresszusok, szemináriumok szervezése és tartása; Sportfelszerelések kölcsönzése, a járművek kivételével; Filmgyártás, kivéve reklámfilmek; Fényképészet; Fotóriportok készítése; Szövegek kiadása; Könyvkiadás; Elektronikus könyvek és folyóiratok online megjelentetése; On-line elérhető elektronikus publikációk, nem letölthetők; Riporteri szolgáltatások; Helyfoglalás show-műsorokra; A fent említett szolgáltatásokat tengeri körutak keretein belül nyújtják; Az említettek mindegyike a tengeri hajózással kapcsolatos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Divertimento; Informazioni in materia di intrattenimento; Servizi di intrattenimento e divertimento, attività sportive e culturali; Servizi nell' ambito dell'intrattenimento radiofonico e televisivo; Organizzazione di competizioni sportive; Organizzazione di concorsi (a fini didattici, culturali o di divertimento); Organizzazione e direzione di seminari, congressi e convegni; Noleggio di equipaggiamenti per lo sport ad eccezione dei veicoli; Produzione di films non per scopi pubblicitari; Fotografia; Reportage fotografici; Pubblicazione di testi; Pubblicazione di libri; Pubblicazione elettronica di libri e di riviste online; Fornitura di pubblicazioni elettroniche non scaricabili da una rete informatica globale o internet; Servizi di cronisti; Prenotazione di posti per spettacoli; Tutti i suddetti servizi sono destinati ai corsi marittimi; Tutti i suddetti articoli in materia di navigazione marittima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Pramogos; Pramogų informacija; Pramoginė, sportinė ir kultūrinė veikla; Televizijos ir radijo pramogų paslaugos; Sporto varžybų rengimas; Varžybų rengimas (švietimo, kultūros ar pramogų tikslais); Konferencijų, kongresų, seminarų organizavimas ir vedimas; Sporto įrenginių nuoma [išskyrus transporto priemones]; Filmų kūrimas (išskyrus reklaminius); Fotografavimas; Fotoreportažų rengimas; Tekstų leidyba; Knygų leidyba; Elektroninių knygų ir žurnalų tiesioginis publikavimas; Elektroninių publikacijų tiesioginis pateikimas per kompiuterių tinklą (ne parsisiunčiamųjų); Reporterių paslaugos; Vietų užsakymas spektakliams; Visos pirmiau nurodytos paslaugos skirtos jūrinėms reikmėms; Visi prieš tai paminėti yra susiję su jūrų (laivybos) navigacija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Izpriecas; Informācijas pakalpojumi izklaides nolūkiem; Izklaides, sporta un kultūras pasākumi; Radio un televīzijas izklaides pakalpojumu nodrošināšana; Sporta sacensību organizēšana; Sacensību organizēšana (izglītības, kultūras vai izklaides vajadzībām); Konferenču, kongresu vai semināru rīkošana un vadīšana; Sporta aprīkojuma (izņemot transportlīdzekļu) iznomāšana; Filmu ražošana, izņemot reklāmfilmas; Fotogrāfa pakalpojumi; Fotoreportāžu sagatavošana; Tekstu izdošana; Grāmatu izdošana; Elektronisko grāmatu un laikrakstu publicēšana tiešsaistē (nav lejupielādējami); Nelejupielādējamu elektronisku publikāciju nodrošināšana tiešsaistē; Ziņu reportieru pakalpojumi; Vietu rezervēšana izklaides pasākumiem; Iepriekš minētie pakalpojumi jūrniecības kursiem; Viss iepriekš minētais ir saistīts jūras navigāciju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Divertiment; Informazzjoni dwar id-divertiment; Attivitajiet ta' divertiment, sports u kultura; Provvista ta' servizzi ta' divertiment għar-radju u għat-televiżjoni; Arranġament ta' kompetizzjonijiet sportivi; Organizzazzjoni ta' kompetizzjonijiet (għal skopijiet ta' edukazzjoni, kulturali jew ta' divertiment); L-organizzazzjoni u t-tmexxija ta' kungressi, ta' seminars, ta' konferenzi; Il-kiri ta' tagħmir sportiv, minbarra vetturi; Il-produzzjoni tal-films, għajr għal films tar-reklamar; Fotografija; Rappurtaġġ fotografiku; Il-pubblikazzjoni ta' testi; Il-pubblikazzjoni ta' kotba; Servizzi ta' pubblikazzjoni ta' kotba u gazzetti elettroniċi onlajn; Provvista ta' pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi (li ma jistgħux jitniżżlu mill-internet); Servizzi ta' korrispondent tal-aħbarijiet; Prenotazzjoni ta' postijiet bil-qiegħda għall-ispettakli; Is-servizzi kollha msemmija qabel ikunu maħsuba għall-korsijiet marittimi; Dak kollu msemmi qabel hu relatat ma' navigazzjoni marittima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Ontspanning; Informatie op het gebied van amusement; Ontspanning, sportieve en culturele aktiviteiten; Diensten op het gebied van radio- en televisieamusement; Organisatie van sportcompetities; Organisatie van wedstrijden (voor educatieve, culturele of ontspanningsdoeleinden); Het organiseren en houden van congressen, seminars, conferenties; Verhuur van sportuitrustingen, behalve vervoermiddelen; Filmproductie, anders dan voor reclamedoeleinden; Fotografie; Fotoreportages; Uitgeven van teksten; Uitgave van boeken; Online-publicatie van elektronische boeken en tijdschirften (niet-downloadbaar); Elektronische publicaties (niet downloadbaar) ter beschikking stellen van -; Diensten van reporters; Plaatsreservering voor voorstellingen; De voornoemde diensten zijn bestemd voor watersportwedstrijden; Al het voornoemde met betrekking tot scheepvaartnavigatie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Rozrywka; Rozrywka (Informacja o -); Usługi rozrywkowe, zajęcia sportowe i kulturalne; Świadczenie usług w zakresie rozrywki radiowej i telewizyjnej; Organizowanie zawodów sportowych; Organizowanie konkursów (w celach edukacyjnych, kulturowych lub rozrywkowych); Organizowanie i prowadzenie konferencji, seminariów, zjazdów; Sport (Wypożyczanie sprzętu -) [z wyjątkiem pojazdów]; Produkcja filmów, innych niż reklamowe; Usługi fotografów; Fotoreportaże; Publikowanie tekstów; Publikowanie książek; Publikacja książek i czasopism elektronicznych online (nie do pobrania); Udostępnianie publikacji elektronicznych z globalnej sieci komputerowej lub Internetu, nie do pobrania; Usługi reporterskie; Rezerwowanie miejsc na pokazy; Uprzednio wymienione usługi przeznaczone na potrzeby zajęć żeglarskich; Wszystkie wyżej wymienione związane z nawigacją morską.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Divertimento; Informação sobre entretenimento; Atividades de diversão, desportivas e culturais; Prestação de serviços de entretenimento de rádio e de televisão; Organização de competições desportivas; Organização de competições (com fins educativos, culturais ou de divertimento); Organização e direcção de congressos, seminários e conferências; Aluguer de equipamento de desporto, exceto veículos; Produção de filmes; Fotografia; Reportagens fotográficas; Publicação de textos; Publicação de livros; Publicação de livros e revistas eletrónicas on-line; Disponibilização de publicações electrónicas não descarregáveis na internet ou em uma rede global de comunicação; Serviços de reportagens de informação; Reserva de lugares para espetáculos; Sendo todos os serviços atrás referidos destinados a corridas marítimas; Todos os produtos atrás referidos relacionados com navegação marítima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Divertisment; Informaţii în materie de divertisment; Activităţi de divertisment, sportive şi culturale; Divertisment de radio şi televiziune; Organizarea de concursuri sportive; Organizare de competiţii (în scopuri de educaţie, culturale sau de divertisment); Organizarea şi conducerea de congrese, de seminarii, de conferinţe; Închirierea de echipament pentru sport [cu excepţia vehiculelor]; Producţii de film, altele decât filmele publicitare; Servicii ale unui fotograf; Fotoreportaje; Publicare de texte; Publicare de cărţi; Publicare de cărți și periodice electronice online; Furnizare de publicații electronice dintr-o rețea globală de calculatoare sau de pe internet, nedescărcabile; Servicii de reporteri de ştiri; Rezervare de locuri pentru spectacole; Serviciile menţionate anterior fiind destinate curselor maritime; Toate cele menţionate anterior având legătură cu navigaţia maritimă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zábava; Informácie o možnostiach zábavy; Zábavná, športová a kultúrna činnosť; Služby v oblasti rozhlasovej a televíznej zábavy; Organizovanie športových súťaží; Organizovanie súťaží (na účely vzdelávania, kultúry alebo zábavy); Organizovanie a vedenie kongresov, seminárov, konferencií; Požičiavanie športového výstroja (okrem dopravných prostriedkov); Produkcia filmov (nie reklamných); Služby fotografov; Fotografické reportáže; Vydávanie textov; Vydávanie kníh; Publikácia elektronických kníh a denníkov na internete [bez možnosti stiahnuť ich]; Poskytovanie elektronických publikácií prostredníctvom globálnej počítačovej siete alebo internetu bez možnosti prevzatia; Reportérske služby; Rezervácie vstupeniek na zábavné predstavenia; Všetky vyššie uvedené služby sú určené pre preteky lodí na mori; Všetko vyššie uvedené súvisí s námornou navigáciou.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Razvedrilo; Informacije o prireditvah; Razvedrilo, športne in kulturne dejavnosti; Nudenje storitev radijskega in televizijskega razvedrila; Prirejanje športnih tekmovanj; Organizacija tekmovanj (za izobraževalne, kulturne ali razvedrilne namene); Organizacija in vodenje kongresov, seminarjev, konferenc; Izposoja športne opreme (razen vozil); Filmska produkcija, razen oglaševalskih filmov; Fotografske storitve; Fotografske reportaže; Objavljanje besedil; Objavljanje knjig; Spletno objavljanje elektronskih knjig in časopisov (nenaložljivih); Nudenje nenaložljivih elektronskih publikacij z globalnega računalniškega omrežja ali interneta; Storitve novinarskih poročevalcev; Rezervacija sedežev za predstave; Prej navedene storitve so za pomorske dirke; Vse omenjeno je v zvezi s pomorsko navigacijo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Underhållning; Nöjes- och underhållningsinformation; Underhållning, sport- och kulturaktiviteter; Tillhandhållande av radio- och tv-underhållning; Anordnande av idrottstävlingar; Anordnande av tävlingar (för utbildnings-, kulur- och underhållningsändamål); Anordnade och ledning av seminarier, kongresser och konferenser; Uthyrning av sportutrustning, inte fordon; Filmproduktion, andra än reklamfilmer; Fotografverksamhet; Fotoreportage; Publicering av texter; Publicering av böcker; Publicering online av elektroniska böcker och tidskrifter (inte nedladdningsbara); Tillhandahållande av elektroniska publikationer via ett globalt datornät eller internet, inte nedladdningsbara; Nyhetsreportertjänster; Bokning av biljetter till teater- och andra nöjesföreställningar; Alla nämnda varor avsedda för sjöfartskurser; Samtliga nämnda avseende sjöfartsnavigation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/078</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-27</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/148</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-06</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>37449</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
