<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-28T11:45:20</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226747</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226747</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-23</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-28</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Breevin</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Оборудване за физиотерапия; Подложки за акупресура; Дюшеци за масаж в парна баня; Възглавници за терапевтични цели; Инструменти за акупунктура; Инструменти за акупунктура; Инструменти за акупунктура; Апарати за акупресурна терапия; Ортопедични подложки; Подложки за медицински цели; Подплатени възглавници за медицински цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Fyzioterapeutické přístroje; Akupresurní podložky; Podložky pro perličkové koupelové masáže; Polštáře pro terapeutické účely; Nástroje na akupunkturu; Nástroje na akupunkturu; Nástroje na akupunkturu; Přístroje pro akupresurní léčbu; Ortopedické polštáře; Podušky pro lékařské účely; Podušky s výplní pro lékařské účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Udstyr til fysisk terapi; Akupressurmåtter; Måtter til boblebadsmassage; Puder til terapeutiske formål; Akupunkturinstrumenter; Akupunkturinstrumenter; Akupunkturinstrumenter; Apparater til akupressurbehandling; Ortopædiske puder; Puder til medicinske formål; Polstrede puder til medicinske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Geräte für physikalische Therapie; Akupressurmatten; Einlagen für medizinische Luftsprudel-Massagebäder; Kissen für therapeutische Zwecke; Akupunkturgeräte; Akupunkturgeräte; Akupunkturgeräte; Apparate für die Akupressurtherapie; Orthopädische Polster; Kissen für medizinische Zwecke; Gepolsterte Kissen für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εξοπλισμός φυσικοθεραπείας· Υποθέματα για πιεσοθεραπεία (χειρομαλάξεις μέσω άσκησης δακτυλικής πίεσης)· Υποθέματα για μαλάξεις (μασάζ) σε αναβράζον λουτρό· Μαξιλάρια για θεραπευτική χρήση· Όργανα βελονισμού· Όργανα βελονισμού· Όργανα βελονισμού· Εξοπλισμός πιεσοθεραπείας· Ορθοπεδικά μαξιλάρια· Μαξιλάρια για χρήση ιατρική· Μαξιλάρια όχι φουσκωτά για ιατρική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Physical therapy equipment; Acupressure mats; Mats for effervescent bath massage; pillows for therapeutic use; acupuncture equipment; acupuncture instruments; acupuncture apparatus; apparatus for acupressure therapy; orthopedic cushions; cushions for medical purposes; padded cushions for medical purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Equipos de terapia física; Esteras de acupresión; Colchonetas para el masaje en baño de burbujas; Almohadas para uso terapéutico; Instrumentos para la acupuntura; Instrumentos para la acupuntura; Instrumentos para la acupuntura; Aparatos para terapia por acupresión; Almohadillas ortopédicas; Almohadones para uso médico; Cojines acolchados para fines médicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Füsioteraapiaseadmed; Punktimassaažimatid; Mullivannimassaažimatid; Ravipadjad; Akupunktuuriseadmed; Akupunktuuriseadmed; Akupunktuuriseadmed; Punktmassaažraviseadmed; Ortopeedilised padjad; Meditsiinilised padjad; Raviotstarbelised polsterpadjad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Fysioterapiassa käytettävät välineet; Piikkimatot akupainantaan; Hierovat porekylpyalustat; Tyynyt hoitokäyttöön; Akupunktiolaitteet; Akupunktiolaitteet; Akupunktiolaitteet; Laitteet akupainantahoitoon; Ortopediset tyynyt; Tyynyt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Pehmustetyynyt lääketieteelliseen käyttöön.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Équipement de thérapie physique; Tapis d'acupression; Tapis pour massages par bain bouillonnant; Oreillers à usage thérapeutique; Instruments d'acupuncture; Instruments d'acupuncture; Instruments d'acupuncture; Appareils médicaux pour la thérapie par digitopuncture; Coussins orthopédiques; Coussins à usage médical; Coussins rembourrés à usage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Oprema za fizikalnu terapiju; Prostirke za akupresuru; Podloge za pjenušave masažne kupke; Jastuci za terapijsku uporabu; Instrumenti za akupunkturu; Instrumenti za akupunkturu; Instrumenti za akupunkturu; Uređaji za akupresuru; Ortopedski jastuci; Jastuci za medicinske potrebe; Podstavljeni jastuci za medicinsku uporabu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Fizikoterápiás készülékek; Akupresszúrás szőnyegek; Csúszásgátló szőnyegek pezsgőfürdős masszázshoz; Párnák terápiás használatra; Akupunktúrás készülékek; Akupunktúrás készülékek; Akupunktúrás készülékek; Akupresszúrás terápiás berendezések; Ortopédiai párnák; Párnák gyógyászati használatra; Párnák gyógyászati célokra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Attrezzatura per terapie fisiche; Tappetini per acupressione; Tappetini per idromassaggi; Guanciali per uso terapeutico; Strumenti per l'agopuntura; Strumenti per l'agopuntura; Strumenti per l'agopuntura; Apparecchi per terapia di agopuntura; Cuscini ortopedici; Cuscini per uso medico; Cuscini imbottiti per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Fizioterapijos įranga; Akupresūros kilimėliai; Perlinių vonių masažo paklotai; Pagalvės terapijos reikmėms; Akupunktūros instrumentai; Akupunktūros instrumentai; Akupunktūros instrumentai; Akupresūros terapijos aparatai; Ortopedinės pagalvėlės; Medicininės pagalvėlės; Minkštos pagalvėlės medicinos reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Fizikālās terapijas iekārtas; Akupresūras paklājiņi; Paklājiņi vannas masāžai ar burbuļiem; Pagalvji terapeitiskam nolūkam; Akupunktūras ierīces; Akupunktūras ierīces; Akupunktūras ierīces; Akupresūras terapijas aparāti; Ortopēdiskie spilveni; Medicīnā izmantojamie spilveni; Polsterēti spilveni medicīniskiem nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tagħmir għat-terapija fiżika; Twapet żgħar tal-agupressa; Twapet għall-massaġġi f'banju ta' ilma bil-bżieżaq; Imħaded għall-użu terapewtiku; Strumenti għall-akupuntura; Strumenti għall-akupuntura; Strumenti għall-akupuntura; Apparat għat-terapija bl-akupressjoni; Kuxxini ortopediċi; Kuxxini għal skopijiet mediċi; Kuxxini kkuttunati għal skopijiet mediċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Apparaten voor lichamelijke behandeling; Acupressuurmatten; Matten voor bubbelbadmassage; Hoofdkussens voor therapeutisch gebruik; Acupunctuurinstrumenten; Acupunctuurinstrumenten; Acupunctuurinstrumenten; Apparaten voor acupressuurtherapie; Orthopedische kussens; Kussens voor medisch gebruik; Kussentjes en kussens voor medisch gebruik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia i przyrządy do fizjoterapii; Maty do akupresury; Maty do masażu w kąpieli z pianą; Poduszki do użytku terapeutycznego; Przyrządy do akupunktury; Przyrządy do akupunktury; Przyrządy do akupunktury; Aparatura do terapii akupresurą; Poduszki ortopedyczne; Poduszki do celów medycznych; Poduszki wyściełane do celów medycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Equipamento de fisioterapia; Esteiras para terapia de acupressão; Tapetes para banhos de hidromassagem; Almofadas para uso terapêutico; Equipamento de acupunctura; Equipamento de acupunctura; Equipamento de acupunctura; Aparelhos para terapia de acupressão; Almofadas ortopédicas; Almofadas para uso medicinal; Produtos almofadados para uso medicinal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Echipament pentru exerciţii fizice; Covoraşe pentru acupresiune; Covoraşe pentru băi de masaj efervescente; Perne de uz terapeutic; Instrumente pentru acupunctură; Instrumente pentru acupunctură; Instrumente pentru acupunctură; Aparate pentru terapia prin acupresiune; Perne ortopedice; Perne de uz medical; Perne căptuşite de uz medical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Fyzioterapeutické zariadenia; Akupresúrne podložky; Podložky pre perličkové kúpeľné masáže; Vankúše na terapeutické účely; Nástroje na akupunktúru; Nástroje na akupunktúru; Nástroje na akupunktúru; Zariadenia pre akupresúrnu terapiu; Ortopedické vankúše; Podušky na lekárske použitie; Vypchaté podušky na lekárske účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Naprave za fizikalno terapijo; Akupresurne blazine; Podloge za masaže v šumeči kopeli; Blazine za terapevtske namene; Instrumenti za akupunkturo; Instrumenti za akupunkturo; Instrumenti za akupunkturo; Aparati za akupresurno terapijo; Ortopedske blazine; Blazine za medicinske namene; Polnjene blazine za medicinske namene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Utrustning för fysioterapi; Spikmattor; Mattor för bubbelbadmassage; Kuddar för terapeutisk användning; Akupunkturinstrument; Akupunkturinstrument; Akupunkturinstrument; Apparater för akupressurterapi; Ortopediska kuddar; Kuddar för medicinska ändamål; Stoppade kuddar för medicinska ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>27</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Килими, черги и изтривалки; Постелки за йога; Постелки за упражнения за гимнастически салони; Подови настилки [рогозки] за ползване при спортни дейности; Настилки от корк.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Koberce, předložky, rohožky; Podložky na jógu; Tělocvičné žíněnky na cvičení; Podlahové krytiny (rohože) používané při sportovních aktivitách; Korkové rohože.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tæpper og måtter; Yogamåtter; Måtter til gymnastik; Gulvbelægning [måtter] til brug ved sportsaktiviteter; Korkmåtter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Teppiche, Vorleger und Matten; Yogamatten; Übungsmatten für das Turnen; Bodenmatten für Sportzwecke; Matten aus Kork.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Τάπητες, ψάθες και χαλάκια· Χαλάκια για γιόγκα· Επιστρώσεις δαπέδου [στρώματα] που προορίζονται για γυμναστικές δραστηριότητες· Επιστρώσεις δαπέδου για χρήση σε αθλητικές δραστηριότητες [χαλάκια]· Χαλάκια από φελλό.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Carpets, rugs and mats; Yoga mats; Personal exercise mats; Floor coverings [mats] for use in sporting activities; Cork mats.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Alfombras, alfombrillas y tapetes; Esteras de yoga; Colchonetas de ejercicios para gimnasios; Recubrimientos de suelos para su uso en actividades deportivas [esteras]; Esteras de corcho.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Vaibad ja matid; Joogamatid; Võimla harjutusmatid; Spordi harrastamisel kasutatavad põrandakatted [matid]; Korkmatid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Matot; Joogamatot; Voimisteluharjoittelumatot; Lattianpäällysteet [matot] käytettäviksi urheilussa; Korkkimatot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Tapis, paillassons et nattes; Tapis de yoga; Tapis d'exercice pour gymnases; Revêtements de sol sous forme de tapis pour activités sportives; Tapis en liège.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Tepisi, sagovi i otirači; Podloge za jogu; Strunjače; Podne podloge [strunjače] za upotrebu u sportu; Pluteni prostirači za pod.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szőnyegek, pokrócok, lábtörlők; Jógaszőnyegek; Tornaszőnyegek, tornatermi edzőszőnyegek; Padlóburkolatok [szőnyegek] sporttevékenységekhez; Parafa lábtörlők, szőnyegek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Tappeti, zerbini e stuoie; Tappetini da yoga; Tappeti per attività ginniche; Rivestimenti per pavimenti da utilizzare in attività sportive [tappeti]; Sottobicchieri di sughero.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kilimai, kilimėliai, patiesalai; Jogos kilimėliai; Gimnastikos pratimų čiužiniai; Grindų dangos [patiesalai], skirti sporto reikmėms; Kamštiniai patiesalai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Paklāji, grīdsegas un pīteņi; Jogas paklāji; Vingrošanas paklājiņi; Grīdas segums [paklājiņi] sporta nodarbībām; Korķa paklājiņi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Twapet; Mattijiet tal-joga; Twapet żgħar tal-ġinnastika; Kisi tal-paviment [twapet żgħar] għall-użu f'attivitajiet sportivi; Twapet żgħar tas-sufra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Tapijten. vloerkleden en matten; Yogamatten; Vloerbedekking [matten] te gebruiken bij gymnastische activiteiten; Vloerbedekkingen [matten] voor gebruik bij sportactiviteiten; Kurkmatten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dywany, chodniki i maty; Maty do jogi; Maty do ćwiczeń gimnastycznych; Pokrycia podłogowe [maty] na zajęcia sportowe; Maty korkowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Tapetes, carpetes e esteiras; Esteiras para ioga; Tapetes de exercício para ginásios; Revestimentos de pavimento [esteiras] para utilização em atividades desportivas; Esteiras de cortiça.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Covoare, carpete şi preşuri; Covoraşe de yoga; Saltele de exerciţii pentru săli de sport; Acoperiri de podele [rogojini] folosite pentru activităţi sportive; Covoraşe din plută.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Koberce, koberčeky a rohožky; Podložky na jogu; Telocvičné žinenky na cvičenie; Podlahové krytiny (rohože) na športové aktivity; Korkové rohožky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Preproge, tekači in predpražniki; Blazine za jogo; Blazine za vadbo, za telovadnico; Talne podlage, ki se uporabljajo pri športnih aktivnostih; Predpražniki iz plute.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Mattor, inkluderande dörrmattor och heltäckningsmattor; Yogamattor; Gymnastikmattor; Golvbeläggningar för användning vid sportaktiviteter [mattor]; Korkmattor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Спортни артикули и оборудване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Sportovní potřeby a vybavení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sportsartikler og -udstyr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Sportartikel und -ausrüstungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Είδη και εξοπλισμός άθλησης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Sporting articles and equipment.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Equipamientos y artículos deportivos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sporditarbed ja -riistad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Urheiluvälineet ja -varusteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Articles et équipement de sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sportski artikli i oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Sportcikkek és felszerelések.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Articoli e attrezzature sportive.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Sporto reikmenys ir įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Sporta preces un sporta inventārs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Artikli u tagħmir sportivi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Sportartikelen en -uitrustingen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Artykuły i sprzęt sportowy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Artigos e equipamento de desporto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole şi echipament de sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Športové potreby a športový výstroj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Športne potrebščine in oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Sportartiklar och sportutrustning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/112</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/184</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-25</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>93916</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
