<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-05T09:34:34</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226265</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226265</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-11-03</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-11-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>LogisALL Combi PAC</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162306500</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226265/000162306500.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.01</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>39</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Опаковане и транспорт на стоки; Складиране на стоки; Отдаване под наем на контейнери [за съхранение/транспорт]; Отдаване под наем на палети [за съхранение/транспорт]; Наемане на кораби за превоз на стоки; Отдаване под наем на оборудване и уреди за транспорт; Складиране на стоки; Транспортна логистика; Логистично опаковане и съхранение; Услуги за консултации относно транспортната логистика; Транспортни логистични услуги; Логистични услуги, състоящи се от складиране, транспорт и доставка на стоки; Консултантски услуги свързани с транспорт и складиране на стоки; Отдаване под наем на складови контейнери.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Balení a doprava zboží; Uskladnění zboží; Pronájem nádob [skladovacích /dopravních]; Pronájem palet [skladovacích/dopravních]; Doprava zboží; Pronájem přepravních zařízení a vybavení; Provoz skladů; Logistika v dopravě; Logistika balení a skladování; Poradenství se zaměřením na logistiku v dopravě; Dopravní logistické služby; Logistické služby, sestávající ze skladování, dopravy a expedice zboží; Poradenství zaměřené na dopravu a skladování zboží; Pronájem skladovacích nádob.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Emballering og transport af varer; Oplagring af varer; Udlejning af beholdere (oplagring, transport); Udlejning af paller (oplagring, transport); Befragtning; Udlejning af transportenheder og -udstyr; Oplagring; Transportlogistik; Emballering og opbevaring af logistik; Rådgivning inden for transportlogistik; Transportlogistik; Logistikvirksomhed, herunder opbevaring, transport og udlevering af varer; Rådgivning om transport og opbevaring af varer; Udlejning af opbevaringscontainere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Verpackung und Transport von Waren; Einlagerung von Waren; Vermietung von Behältern [Lagerung/Transport]; Vermietung von Paletten [Lagerung/Transport]; Befrachtung [Vermittlung von Schiffsladungen]; Vermietung von Transportgeräten und -ausrüstungen; Lagerung; Transportlogistik; Verpackungs- und Lagerlogistik; Beratung in Bezug auf die Transportlogistik; Logistikdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Transport; Logistikdienstleistungen, bestehend aus der Lagerung, Beförderung und Auslieferung von Gütern; Beratungsdienstleistungen bezogen auf den Transport und die Lagerung von Waren; Vermietung von Lagercontainern.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευασία και μεταφορά προϊόντων· Αποθήκευση αγαθών· Εκμίσθωση εμπορευματοκιβωτίων [αποθήκευση/μεταφορά]· Εκμίσθωση παλετών [αποθήκευση/μεταφορά]· Ναύλωση· Εκμίσθωση διατάξεων και εξοπλισμού μεταφοράς· Αποθήκευση αγαθών· Εφοδιαστική σε σχέση με μεταφορές· Συσκευασία και αποθήκευση στο πλαίσιο εφοδιαστικής· Υπηρεσίες συμβουλευτικής αναφορικά με τη διοικητική και υλικοτεχνική μέριμνα στον τομέα των μεταφορών· Υπηρεσίες παροχής υλικοτεχνικής υποδομής για μεταφορές· Υπηρεσίες εφοδιαστικής, που συνίστανται στην αποθήκευση, τη μεταφορά και την παράδοση εμπορευμάτων· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σε σχέση με τη μεταφορά και την αποθήκευση εμπορευμάτων· Μίσθωση εμπορευματοκιβωτίων αποθηκευτικών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Transport and packaging of goods; Storage of goods; Rental of containers for storage or transport; Rental of pallets for storage or transport; Freighting; Rental of transportation devices and equipment; Warehousing; Transportation logistics; Packaging and storage of logistics; Consultancy services relating to transportation logistics; Transportation logistics services; Logistics services consisting of the storage, transport and delivery of goods; Consultancy relating to the storage and transportation of goods; Rental of storage containers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Embalaje y transporte de productos; Almacenamiento de mercancías; Alquiler de contenedores [almacenamiento/transporte]; Alquiler de paletas [almacenamiento/transporte]; Fletamento; Alquiler de dispositivos y equipos de transporte; Almacenamiento; Servicios logísticos de transporte; Embalaje y almacenamiento de logística; Servicios de asesoramiento relativos a la logística en materia de transporte; Servicios de logística de transporte; Servicios de logística, compuestos por almacenaje, facilitación de transporte y entrega de mercancías; Servicios de asesoramiento relacionados con el transporte y el almacenamiento de productos; Alquiler de contenedores de almacenamiento.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kaupade pakendamine ja transport; Kaupade ladustamine; Mahutite rentimine [ladustamine/transport]; Kaubaaluste rentimine [ladustamine/transport]; Prahtimine [laevandus]; Transpordiseadmete ja -vahendite rentimine; Ladustamine, ladustus; Transpordilogistika; Logistiline pakendamine ja ladustamine; Transpordialase logistikaga seotud nõustamisteenused; Transpordilogistikateenused; Logistikateenused, mis koosnevad kaupade ladustamisest, transportimisest ja tarnimisest; Kaupade transpordi ja ladustamisega seotud nõustamisteenused; Ladustuskonteinerite üürimine, laenutus, rentimine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tavaroiden kuljetus ja pakkaus; Varastointi; Säiliöiden (säilytykseen/kuljetukseen tarkoitettujen) vuokraaminen; Lavojen (säilytykseen/kuljetukseen tarkoitettujen) vuokraaminen; Rahtaus; Kuljetuslaitteiden ja -välineiden vuokraus; Varastointi; Kuljetuslogistiikka; Logistiikkaan liittyvä pakkaus ja varastointi; Kuljetuslogistiikkaan liittyvät neuvontapalvelut; Kuljetuslogistiikkapalvelut; Logistiikkapalvelut, joihin sisältyvät tavaroiden varastointi, kuljetus ja toimitus; Tavaroiden kuljetusta ja varastointia koskevat neuvontapalvelut; Varastokonttien vuokraus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Emballage et transport de marchandises; Dépôt de marchandises; Location de conteneurs [stockage/transport]; Location de palettes [stockage/transport]; Affrètement; Location de dispositifs et d'équipements de transport; Stockage; Services de logistique en matière de transport; Emballage et entreposage de produits de logistique; services de conseils concernant la logistique en matière de transport; Services de logistique en matière de transport; Services de logistique, à savoir entreposage, acheminement et livraison de marchandises; Conseils relatifs au transport et à l'entreposage de produits; Location de conteneurs d'entreposage.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pakiranje i prijevoz robe; Skladištenje robe; Iznajmljivanje spremnika [pohrana/prijevoz]; Iznajmljivanje paleta [pohrana/prijevoz]; Zakup broda za prijevoz tereta i putnika; Iznajmljivanje transportnih uređaja i opreme; Skladištenje; Logističke usluge u svezi s prijevozom; Pakiranje i skladištenje logistike; Usluge savjetovanja u vezi logistikom u vezi s transportom; Logističke usluge u vezi s prijevozom; Usluge logistike, koje se sastoje od skladištenja, prijevoza i isporuke robe; Usluge savjetovanja povezanih s prijevozom i skladištenjem robe; Iznajmljivnje skladišnih kontejnera.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Termékek csomagolása és szállítása; Áruk raktározása; Tároló/szállító tartályok bérbeadása; Tároló/szállító raklapok bérbeadása; Szállítmányozás; Eszközök és berendezések bérlése; Áruk raktározása; Szállítási logisztikai szolgáltatások; Logisztikai csomagolás és tárolás; Szállítási logisztikai tanácsadási szolgáltatások; Szállítási logisztikai szolgáltatások; Logisztikai szolgáltatások, javak raktározására, szállítmányozására és kiszállítására vonatkozóan; Áruk szállításával, és raktározásával kapcsolatos tanácsadási szolgáltatások; Tároló tartályok kölcsönzése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Imballaggio e trasporto di prodotti; Deposito di merci; Noleggio di contenitori [immagazzinamento/trasporto]; Noleggio di pallet [immagazzinamento/trasporto]; Noleggio [di una nave]; Noleggio di dispositivi ed apparecchiature di trasporto; Immagazzinamento; Organizzazione di trasporti; Imballaggio e immagazzinamento per logistica; Servizi di consulenza riguardanti la logistica in materia di trasporti; Servizi logistici per il trasporto; Servizi logistici, costituiti dall'immagazzinamento, dal trasporto e dalla consegna di merci; Servizi di consulenza inerenti il trasporto e l'immagazzinamento di merci; Noleggio di container di deposito.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Prekių pakavimas ir gabenimas; Prekių saugojimas; Taros nuoma [laikymo / vežimo]; Padėklų nuoma [laikymo / vežimo]; Frachtavimas; Transportavimo įrenginių ir įrangos nuoma; Sandėliavimas; Transporto logistika; Logistikos pakavimas ir sandėliavimas; Patarimai transporto logistikos klausimais; Gabenimo logistikos paslaugos; Logistikos paslaugos, kurias sudaro krovinių sandėliavimas, gabenimas ir pristatymas; Konsultacinės paslaugos, susijusios su prekių vežimu ir sandėliavimu; Sandėlių konteinerių nuoma.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Preču iepakošana un pārvadāšana; Preču uzglabāšana; Konteineru noma [uzglabāšanas/transportēšanas]; Plātņu noma [uzglabāšanas/transportēšanas]; Kuģu vai tā daļu noma kravu pārvadāšanai; Transporta iekārtu un aprīkojuma noma; Preču uzglabāšana; Transporta loģistika; Loģistikas iepakošana un uzglabāšana; Konsultāciju pakalpojumi attiecībā uz loģistiku pārvadājumu jomā; Transportēšanas loģistika; Loģistikas pakalpojumi, proti, preču uzglabāšana, transportēšana un izsniegšana; Konsultāciju pakalpojumi saistībā ar preču transportēšanu un uzglabāšanu; Uzglabāšanas konteineru noma.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">L-ippakkjar u l-ġarr ta' oġġetti; Ħażna ta' merkanzija; Kiri ta' kontenituri [ħażna/trasport]; Kiri ta' pelits [ħażna/trasport]; Trasport ta' merkanzija b'massa; Kiri ta' strumenti u tagħmir tat-trasport; Servizzi tal-ħażna; Loġistika tat-trasportazzjoni; Ippakkjar u ħażna ta' loġistika; Servizzi ta' pariri dwar il-loġistika tat-trasport; Servizzi ta' loġistika dwar it-trasport; Servizzi ta' loġistika, li jikkonsistu mill-ħażna, it-trasport u l-kunsinna ta' merkanzija; Servizzi ta' konsulenza relatata mat-trasport u ħżin ta' oġġetti; Il-kiri ta' kontenituri tal-ħżin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verpakking en transport van goederen; Opslag van goederen; Verhuur van containers [opslag/transport]; Verhuur van pallets [opslag/transport]; Charterdiensten; Verhuur van transportinrichtingen en -uitrustingen; Opslag; Logisiteke diensten op het gebied van transport; Verpakking en opslag (logistiek); Advisering op het gebied van vervoerslogistiek; Transportlogistiek; Logistieke diensten, bestaande uit de opslag, het vervoer en de levering van goederen; Adviesdiensten met betrekking tot transport en opslag van goederen; Verhuur van opslagcontainers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pakowanie i transport towarów; Składowanie towarów; Wynajmowanie pojemników [magazynowych/transportowych]; Wynajmowanie palet [magazynowych/transportowych]; Fracht; Wypożyczanie urządzeń i sprzętu do transportu; Składowanie towarów; Logistyka transportu; Pakowanie i składowanie w zakresie logistyki; Usługi doradztwa dotyczące logistyki w zakresie transportu; Transportowe usługi logistyczne; Usługi logistyczne obejmujące składowanie, transport i dostawę towarów; Usługi doradztwa w zakresie transportu i składowania towarów; Wypożyczanie kontenerów magazynowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Embalagem e transporte de produtos; Armazenamento de mercadorias; Aluguer de contentores [para armazenamento/transporte]; Aluguer de paletes [para armazenamento/transporte]; Fretamento; Aluguer de dispositivos e equipamentos de transporte; Armazenamento; Logística de transporte; Logística de embalagem e de armazenamento; Serviços de consultadoria relacionados com a logística em matéria de transporte; Serviços de logística de transportes; Serviços de logística, constituídos pelo armazenamento, transporte e entrega de mercadorias; Serviços de consultadoria relacionados com o transporte e armazenamento de produtos; Aluguer de contentores de armazenamento.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ambalare şi transport de produse; Depozitarea mărfurilor; Închiriere de containere [depozitare/transport]; Închiriere de paleţi [depozitare/transport]; Transportare de mărfuri; Închiriere de dispozitive şi echipamente de transport; Depozitarea mărfurilor; Logistică de transport; Ambalare şi depozitare pentru logistică; Servicii de consiliere cu privire la logistică în materie de transport; Servicii de logistică constând în transport; Servicii logistice constând din depozitarea, transportul şi livrarea de bunuri; Consultanţă cu privire la transportul şi depozitarea produselor; Închiriere de containere de depozitare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Balenie a preprava tovaru; Skladovanie tovarov (úschova); Prenájom [prepravných a skladovacích] kontajnerov; Prenájom [prepravných a skladovacích] paliet; Prenájom dopravných prostriedkov; Prenájom dopravných zariadení a vybavenia; Skladovanie; Logistické služby v doprave; Logistika v oblasti balenia a skladovania; Poradenské služby týkajúce sa logistických služieb v preprave; Dopravné logistické služby; Logistické služby, pozostávajúce zo skladovania, prepravy a doručovania výrobkov; Poradenské služby vo vzťahu k transportu a skladovaniu tovarov; Prenájom skladovacích kontajnerov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pakiranje in prevoz blaga; Skladiščenje blaga; Dajanje zabojnikov v najem [shranjevanje/prevoz]; Dajanje palet v najem [shranjevanje/prevoz]; Natovarjanje; Najem naprav za prevoz ter opreme; Skladiščenje blaga; Transportna logistika; Pakiranje in skladiščenje logistike; Svetovalne storitve glede logistike na področju transporta; Transportne logistične storitve; Logistične storitve, sestavljene iz skladiščenja, prevoza in dostave blaga; Svetovalne storitve v zvezi s transportom in skladiščenjem blaga; Najem skladiščnih kontejnerjev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Emballering och transport av varor; Godsmagasinering; Uthyrning av containrar [förvaring/transport]; Uthyrning av lastpallar [förvaring/transport]; Befraktning; Uthyrning av transportanordningar och -utrustningar; Godsmagasinering; Transportlogistik; Förpackning och logistiklagring; Rådgivning avseende transportlogistik; Transportlogistiktjänster; Logistiktjänster, bestående av lagring, transport och leverans av gods; Rådgivningstjänster relaterade till transport och lagring; Uthyrning av förvaringscontainrar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/078</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-27</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/211</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-11-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>703590</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>11578</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003126694</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-07-24</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>FR</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>1742907</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>1990-01-08</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>1742907</RegistrationNumber>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>COMBIPASS</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>FR</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>3000425</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2000-01-07</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>3000425</RegistrationNumber>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>COMBIPASS</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>WO</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<DesignatedCountryDetails>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>AT</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>BG</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>BX</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>CY</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>CZ</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>DE</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>DK</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>EE</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>EM</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>ES</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>FI</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>FR</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>GB</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>GR</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>HR</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>HU</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>IE</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>IT</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>LT</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>LV</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>MT</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>PL</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>PT</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>RO</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>SE</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>SI</DesignatedCountryCode>
           <DesignatedCountryCode>SK</DesignatedCountryCode>
          </DesignatedCountryDetails>
<ApplicationNumber>744384</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2000-06-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>744384</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2000-06-23</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>COMBIPASS</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>48340</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>11212</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
