<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-28T12:49:01</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226486</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226486</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-25</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-28</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>KINTO</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>8</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Прибори за маса, а именно ножове, вилици и лъжици; Ножарски изделия и прибори за хранене.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Stolní náčiní, jmenovitě nože, vidličky a lžíce; Nože, vidličky a lžíce.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Bestik, nemlig knive, gafler og skeer; Knivsmedevarer, gafler og skeer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Tafelgeschirr, nämlich Messer, Gabeln und Löffel; Messerschmiedewaren, Gabeln und Löffel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Επιτραπέζια σκεύη, συγκεκριμένα μαχαίρια, πιρούνια και κουτάλια· Όργανα κοπής, Μαχαιροπήρουνα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Tableware, namely knives, forks and spoons; cutlery.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cuberterías, en concreto, cuchillos, tenedores y cucharas; Artículos de cuchillería, tenedores y cucharas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Söögiriistad, nimelt noad, kahvlid ja lusikad; Noad, kahvlid, lusikad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ruokailuvälineet, nimittäin veitset, haarukat ja lusikat; Aterimet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vaisselle, à savoir, couteaux, fourchettes et cuillères; Coutellerie, fourchettes et cuillers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Stolni pribor, odnosno noževi, vilice i žlice; Pribor za jelo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Evőeszközök, név szerint kések, villák és kanalak; Evőeszközök.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Posate, ovvero coltelli, forchette e cucchiai; Coltelleria, forchette e cucchiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Valgomieji įrankiai, būtent šakutės, peiliai ir šaukštai; Peiliai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Galda piederumi, proti, naži, dakšiņas un karotes; Galda piederumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pożati, jiġifieri, skieken, frieket u mgħaref; Pożati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Tafelgerei, te weten messen, vorken en lepels; Messenmakerswaren, vorken en lepels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Zastawa stołowa, mianowicie noże, widelce i łyżki; Wyroby nożownicze.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Artigos de mesa, nomeadamente facas, garfos e colheres; Cuteleria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole de masa, si anume cutite, furculite si linguri; Cuţite, furculiţe şi linguri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kuchynský riad, menovite vidličky, lyžice a nožíky; Nožiarsky tovar a príbory.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Jedilni pribor, in sicer noži, vilice, žlice; Noži, vilice in žlice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bordsserviser, nämligen knivar, gafflar och skedar; Knivsmidesvaror, bestick.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Книжни филтри за кафе.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Papírové filtry na přípravu kávy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kaffefiltre af papir.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kaffeefilter aus Papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Φίλτρα για καφέ από χαρτί.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Paper coffee filters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Filtros de papel para café.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Paberist kohvifiltrid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kahvisuodatinpaperit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Filtres à café en papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Filtri za kavu, papirnati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Papír kávéfilterek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Filtri per il caffè in carta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Filtrai (Popieriniai kavos -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kafijas filtri (papīra).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Filtri tal-karti għall-kafè.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Koffiefilters van papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Filtry do kawy papierowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Filtros de papel para café.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Filtre de cafea din hârtie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Papierové filtre na kávu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Papirnati filtri za kavo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kaffefilter av papper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Чаши (за вода); Керамични чаши; Уреди за варене на ориз за употреба в микровълнови фурни; Сервизи за чай, не от благороден метал; Кутийки за съхранение на чай; Чаени чаши; Стъклария; Стъклени чаши (съдове); Цилиндрични чаши с дръжка; Чаши; Кани, не от благороден метал; Гарафи; Стъклени гарафи; Свистящи чайници; Котли, неелектрически; Чинии; Купи; Кабаретни подноси, не от благороден метал; Подноси за храна; Подложки (прибори за маса); Вази за цветя; Преносими готварски комплекти за използване на открито; Неелектрически, филтри за наливане на кафе, не от хартия, за варене на кафе; Съдове за сервиране на кафе, неелектрически; Стъклени чаши за пиене; Стъклени купи; Кухненски съдове, не от благороден метал; Кухненски прибори; Тенджери с капак; Цедки за чай, не от благороден метал; Чайници; Подноси за домакински цели; Грънчарски изделия, А именно, Пръстени тенджери, Чаши, направени от керамика, Глинени чинии, Керамични купички; Термоси; Термоси; Котли, неелектрически; Вази; Кани, не от благороден метал; Чаши (за вода); Чинийки за чаши; Подложки за маса, не от хартия или текстил; Подложки за хранене, не от хартия или текстил; Хаванчета и чукала за кухненска употреба; Кутии за сапун; Дозатори за сапун; Стойки за четки за тоалети чинии; Поставки за четки за бръснене; Поставки за четки за зъби; Комплекти метални кутии; Поставки за клечки за хранене; Керамика, А именно, Пръстени тенджери, Чаши, направени от керамика; Неелектрически глинени филтърни кафемашини за приготвяне на кафе; Глинени контейнери за домакинска или кухненска употреба; Глинени чаши и чинийки; Глинени чинии; Керамични купички; Глинени вази за цветя.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Poháry bez nožky; Keramické džbánky; Nádoby na vaření rýže pro použití v mikrovlnné troubě; Čajové servisy [stolní nádobí]; Krabičky na čaj; Šálky na čaj; Skleněné zboží; Sklenice [nádoby]; Hrnky; Šálky; Džbány; Dekantéry; Skleněné dekantéry; Pískací konvice; Konvice na vaření vody, ne elektrické; Stolní talíře; Misky; Kabarety [dělené misky]; Jídelní podnosy; Podtácky; Vázy na květiny; Přenosné kuchyňské soupravy k venkovnímu použití; Neelektrické, kávové filtry nevyrobené z papíru na vaření kávy; Konvice na kávu, ne elektrické; Sklenice na pití; Skleněné mísy; Kuchyňské dózy a krabičky; Kuchyňské náčiní; Kastroly; Sítka na slévání čaje; Čajové konvice; Podnosy pro použití v domácnosti; Nádobí z kameniny, Jmenovitě, Kameninové nádoby, Keramické hrnky, Talíře z majoliky, Kameninové mísy; Izolované lahve; Izolované lahve; Konvice na vaření vody, ne elektrické; Vázy; Džbány; Poháry bez nožky; Podšálky; Podtácky, ne papírové nebo textilní; Prostírání, ne papírové nebo textilní; Hmoždíře a paličky ke kuchyňskému použití; Držáky na mýdlo; Dávkovače mýdla; Stojany na záchodové štětky; Stojánky na štětky na holení; Držáky na zubní kartáčky; Sady dóz; Opěrky na jídelní hůlky; Hrnčířské výrobky, Jmenovitě, Kameninové nádoby, Keramické hrnky; Neelektrické keramické překapávače na vaření kávy; Keramické nádoby pro domácnost nebo kuchyň; Keramické šálky a podšálky; Talíře z majoliky; Kameninové mísy; Keramické vázy na květiny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Vandglas; Kopper af lertøj; Riskogere til brug i mikrobølgeovne; Teservicer [bordservice]; Tedåser; Tekopper; Glasvarer; Glas [beholdere]; Krus; Kopper; Krukker; Karafler; Glaskarafler; Fløjtekedel; Kedler, ikke elektriske; Tallerkner; Spølkum; Kabaret [serveringsbakke]; Madbakker; Bordskånere (bordservice); Knopvaser; Transportabelt madlavningsgrej til udendørs brug; Kaffefiltre til overhældning, ikke elektriske, ikke fremstillet af papir, til brygning af kaffe; Kaffekander, ikke elektriske; Drikkeglas; Glasbowler; Køkkenbeholdere; Køkkenredskaber; Kasseroller; Tesier; Tepotter; Bakker til husholdningsbrug; Lertøj, Nemlig, Lergryder, Krus af lertøj, Tallerkner af lertøj, Fade af stentøj; Termoflasker; Termoflasker; Kedler, ikke elektriske; Vaser; Krukker; Vandglas; Underkopper; Bordskånere, ikke af papir eller tekstil; Dækkeservietter, ikke af papir eller tekstiler; Mortere og stødere til køkkenbrug; Sæbeholdere; Sæbedispensere; Toiletbørsteholdere; Holdere til barberkoste; Tandbørsteholdere; Dåsesæt; Genstande til at lægge spisepinde på; Pottemagervarer, Nemlig, Lergryder, Krus af lertøj; Kaffetragte af ler, ikke elektriske, til kaffebrygning; Beholdere af ler til husholdnings- eller til køkkenbrug; Kopper og underkopper af ler; Tallerkner af lertøj; Fade af stentøj; Blomstervaser af ler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bechergläser; Becher aus Ton; Reiskocher zur Verwendung in Mikrowellenherden; Teeservice [Tafelgeschirr]; Teedosen; Teetassen; Glaswaren; Gläser [Gefäße]; Becher; Tassen; Kannen und Krüge; Karaffen; Dekantiergefäße aus Glas; Pfeifkessel; Wasserkessel, nicht elektrisch; Geschirr; Schalen; Kabaretts [Servierplatten]; Tabletts; Untersetzer [Tafelgeschirr]; Blumenvasen; Transportable Küchengeschirrsets zur Verwendung im Freien; Nicht elektrische, Aufguss-Kaffeefiltergeräte, nicht aus Papier, zum Aufbrühen von Kaffee; Nicht elektrische Kaffeekocher; Glaswaren für Getränke; Glaskugeln; Küchengefäße; Küchengeräte; Kasserollen; Teesiebe; Teekannen; Tabletts für den Haushalt; Steingutware, Nämlich, Tontöpfe, Steingut-Krüge, Steingutplatten, Schüsseln aus Steingut; Isolierflaschen; Isolierflaschen; Wasserkessel, nicht elektrisch; Vasen; Kannen und Krüge; Bechergläser; Untertassen; Nicht aus Papier oder Stoff bestehende Untersetzer; Nicht aus Papier oder Stoff bestehende Platzdeckchen [Sets]; Mörser und Stößel für Küchenzwecke; Seifenhalter, -schalen; Seifenspender; Toilettenbürstenhalter; Rasierpinselhalter; Zahnbürstenhalter; Behälter-Sets; Ablagen für Essstäbchen; Töpferwaren, Nämlich, Tontöpfe, Steingut-Krüge; Nicht elektrische Kaffeetropffilter aus Ton zum Aufbrühen von Kaffee; Tonbehälter für Haushalt oder Küche; Tontassen und -untertassen; Steingutplatten; Schüsseln aus Steingut; Blumenvasen aus Ton.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κύπελλα· Φλιτζάνια από πηλό· Σκεύη για το μαγείρεμα ρυζιού σε φούρνο μικροκυμάτων· Σερβίτσια τσαγιού [επιτραπέζια σκεύη]· Κουτιά τσαγιού· Φλυτζάνια τσαγιού· Υαλικά είδη· Ποτήρια· Κούπες· Κύπελλα (όχι από πολύτιμα μέταλλα)· Κανάτες, όχι από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Καράφες· Γυάλινες καράφες· Τσαγιέρες που σφυρίζουν· Βραστήρες μη ηλεκτρικοί· Πιατέλες· Γαβάθες· Δίσκοι σερβιρίσματος· Δίσκοι φαγητού· Επιτραπέζιες προστατευτικές βάσεις για ποτήρια -σου-βέρ (επιτραπέζια σκεύη)· Βάζα για μπουμπούκια λουλουδιών· Φορητά σετ μαγειρικής για υπαίθρια χρήση· Φίλτρα για μη ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες περίχυσης (pour-over), μη αποτελούμενα από χαρτί για την προετοιμασία καφέ· Καφετιέρες σερβιρίσματος, μη ηλεκτρικές· Γυαλικά είδη για ποτά· Γαβάθες γυάλινες· Δοχεία μαγειρικής χρήσης· Σκεύη μαγειρικής χρήσης· Κατσαρόλες μεσαίου μεγέθους· Σουρωτήρια τσαγιού· Τσαγιέρες· Δίσκοι για οικιακή χρήση· Επιτραπέζια σκεύη, Συγκεκριμένα, Πήλινες κατσαρόλες, Φλιτζάνια από φαγεντιανά, Πιάτα από φαγεντιανή, Γαβάθες φαγεντιανής· Φιάλες ισοθερμικές· Φιάλες ισοθερμικές· Βραστήρες μη ηλεκτρικοί· Βάζα· Κανάτες, όχι από πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Κύπελλα· Πιατάκια φλυτζανιών· Βάσεις για ποτήρια (σουβέρ), όχι από χαρτί ή ύφασμα· Επιτραπέζιες προστατευτικές βάσεις σερβίτσιων, όχι από χαρτί ή ύφασμα· Γουδιά και γουδοχέρια για μαγειρική χρήση· Σαπουνοθήκες [διακοσμητικά μπάνιου]· Σαπουνιού διανεμητές· Θήκες βούρτσας για αποχωρητήρια· Βάσεις πινέλων ξυρίσματος· Υποδοχές για οδοντόβουρτσες· Σετ δοχείων· Βάσεις στήριξης για ξυλάκια φαγητού· Κεραμικά, Συγκεκριμένα, Πήλινες κατσαρόλες, Φλιτζάνια από φαγεντιανά· Μη ηλεκτρικές καφετιέρες αργής εκχύλισης από πηλό για προετοιμασία καφέ· Πήλινα δοχεία οικιακής ή μαγειρικής χρήσης· Πήλινα κύπελλα και πιατάκια· Πιάτα από φαγεντιανή· Γαβάθες φαγεντιανής· Πήλινα βάζα για άνθη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Tumblers; ceramic mugs; rice cookers for use in microwave ovens; tea sets; tea canisters; tea cups; glassware; glass containers; mugs; cups; jugs; carafes; glass carafes; Whistling kettles; Kettles [non-electric]; plates; bowls; serving trays; meal trays; coasters (tableware); flower vases; portable cooking kits for outdoor use; non-electric, pour-over coffee filters not of paper for brewing coffee; coffee pots, non-electric; drinking glasses; glass bowls; kitchen containers; Kitchen utensils; saucepans; tea strainers; tea pots; trays for domestic purposes; earthenware, namely, earthenware pots, earthenware mugs, earthenware plates, earthenware bowls; insulated flasks; insulating flasks; kettles, non-electric; vases; pitchers; Tumblers for use as drinking glasses; saucers; coasters, not of paper or textile; place mats, not of paper or textile; mortars and pestles for kitchen use; soap dishes; soap dispensers; Lavatory brush stands; Shaving brush stands; Stands for tooth brushes; canister sets; chopstick rests; Pottery, namely, clay pots, clay mugs; non-electric clay coffee dripper for brewing coffee; clay containers for household or kitchen use; clay cup and saucers; clay plates; clay bowls; clay flower vases.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Vasos altos; Tazas de cerámica; Recipientes para cocer arroz, para su uso en hornos microondas; Servicios de té [vajilla]; Cajas para té; Tazas para té; Cristalería que no se incluya en otras clases; Vasos [recipientes]; Tazones; Tazas; Jarras; Decantadores; Decantadores de cristal; Hervidores que silban; Hervidores no eléctricos; Platos; Tazones (cuencos); Licoreras [bandejas]; Bandejas para la comida; Posavasos (vajilla); Floreros; Juegos de cocina portátiles para exteriores; Filtros de café por goteo no eléctricos, que no sean de papel, para hacer café; Cafeteras no eléctricas; Cristalería para bebidas; Bolas de vidrio; Recipientes de cocina; Utensilios de cocina; Cazos; Coladores de té; Teteras; Bandejas para uso doméstico; Artículos de loza, En concreto, Cazuelas, Tazones de loza, Platos de loza, Fuentes de gres; Termos; Termos; Hervidores no eléctricos; Jarrones; Jarras; Vasos altos; Platillos [platos pequeños]; Posabotellas y posavasos que no sean de papel ni de materias textiles; Manteles individuales que no sean de papel ni de materias textiles; Morteros y manos de mortero para la cocina; Portajabones [jaboneras]; Dispensadores de jabón; Escobilleros de cuarto de baño; Portabrochas de afeitar; Soportes para cepillos de dientes; Juegos de botes para cocina; Apoya palillos chinos; Artículos de alfarería, En concreto, Cazuelas, Tazones de loza; Cafetera por goteo de arcilla, no eléctrica, para hacer café; Recipientes de arcilla para el menaje o la cocina; Tazas y platillos de arcilla; Platos de loza; Fuentes de gres; Jarrones floreros de arcilla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Veeklaasid, õlleklaasid; Keraamilised kruusid; Mikrolaineahju riisikeetjad; Teeserviisid [lauanõud]; Teetoosid; Teetassid; Klaasnõud; Klaasmahutid; Kruusid; Tassid; Kannud; Karahvinid; Klaaskarahvinid; Vilega teekannud; Veekeedukannud, v.a elektrilised; Taldrikud; Kausid, vaagnad; Serveerimiskandikud; Toidukandikud; Jooginõude alused (lauanõud); Lillevaasid; Kaasaskantavad toiduvalmistuskomplektid väljas kasutamiseks; Mitteelektrilised pealevalatavad kohvifiltrid (v.a paberist) kohvi valmistamiseks; Kohvikeedukannud, v.a elektrilised; Joogiklaasid; Klaaskausid; Köögimahutid; Köögitarbed; Haudepotid; Teesõelad; Teekannud; Majapidamiskandikud; Savinõud, Nimelt, Savipotid, Savikruusid, Saviplaadid, Kivikausid; Termospudelid; Termospudelid; Veekeedukannud, v.a elektrilised; Vaasid; Kannud; Veeklaasid, õlleklaasid; Alustassid; Jooginõualused, v.a paberist või tekstiilist; Sööginõude alusmatid, v.a paberist või tekstiilist; Uhmrid ja uhmrinuiad [köögitarbed]; Seebialused; Seebijaoturid; Tualetiharja hoidikud; Habemeajamispintslite hoidlid; Hambaharjahoidjad; Kuivainepurgid; Söögipulkade toed; Pottsepatooted, Nimelt, Savipotid, Savikruusid; Mitteelektriline savist kohvitilguti kohvi valmistamiseks; Savist majapidamis- või köögimahutid; Savitassid ja -alustassid; Saviplaadid; Kivikausid; Savist lillevaasid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Jalattomat juomalasit; Savesta tehdyt kupit; Riisinkeittoastiat käytettäviksi mikroaaltouuneissa; Teeserviisit [astiastot]; Teetölkit; Teekupit; Lasitavarat; Lasit [astiat]; Mukit; Kupit; Kannut; Viinikarahvit; Lasikannut; Viheltävät kattilat; Vesipannut, ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Lautaset; Vadit [astiat]; Tarjottimet; Ateriatarjottimet; Juomalasin alustat (astiat); Kukkavaasit; Siirrettävät retkikeitinsarjat; Muut kuin sähkötoimiset ja muusta kuin paperista tehdyt kahvinsuodattimet; Kahvipannut, ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Lasiset juoma-astiat; Lasikulhot; Keittiön säilytysastiat; Keittokattilasarjat; Kasarit; Teesiivilät; Teepannut; Tarjottimet kotitalouskäyttöön; Savitavara, Nimittäin, Savipadat, Keramiikasta tehdyt mukit, Savilautaset, Savikulhot; Termospullot; Termospullot; Vesipannut, ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Maljakot; Kannut; Jalattomat juomalasit; Teevadit; Lasinaluset, muut kuin paperiset tai kankaiset; Ruokailualustat, ei paperia eikä tekstiiliä; Huhmareet ja petkeleet keittiökäyttöön; Saippuarasiat; Saippuanjakelulaitteet; WC-harjatelineet; Partasutitelineet; Hammasharjatelineet; Purkkisarjat; Syömäpuikkojen tuet; Keramiikka-astiat, Nimittäin, Savipadat, Keramiikasta tehdyt mukit; Muut kuin sähkökäyttöiset savesta tehdyt kahvinsuodattimet; Savesta tehdyt säilytysastiat kotitalous- tai keittiökäyttöön; Savesta tehdyt kupit ja aluslautaset; Savilautaset; Savikulhot; Savesta tehdyt maljakot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Verres droits [récipients pour boissons]; Tasses en poterie; Cuiseurs de riz destinés à la cuisson au four à micro-ondes; Services à thé; Boîtes à thé; Tasses à thé; Verrerie; Verres [récipients]; Mugs; Tasses; Cruchons; Carafes; Carafes en verre; Bouilloires à sifflet; Bouilloires non électriques; Assiettes; Bols; Cabarets [plateaux à servir]; Plateaux-repas (vaisselle); Dessous de verres (vaisselle); Vases à fleurs; Ustensiles de cuisson portables en kit à usage extérieur; Filtres à café non électriques pour infusion par versement d'eau non en papier pour infuser du café; Cafetières non électriques; Verrerie pour boissons; Boules de verre; Récipients de cuisine; Ustensiles de cuisine; Casseroles; Passe-thé; Théières; Plateaux à usage domestique; Faïence, À savoir, Poêlons, Tasses [mugs] en faïence, Assiettes en faïence, Plats en grès; Bouteilles isolantes; Bouteilles isolantes; Bouilloires non électriques; Vases; Cruchons; Verres droits [récipients pour boissons]; Soucoupes; Dessous de carafes, ni en papier ni en matières textiles; Sets de table, ni en papier ni en matières textiles; Mortiers et pilons pour la cuisine; Porte-savon; Distributeurs de savon; Porte-brosses de toilette; Porte-blaireaux; Supports pour brosses à dents; Assortissements de boîtes de cuisine; Porte-baguettes; Poteries, À savoir, Poêlons, Tasses [mugs] en faïence; Percolateurs en argile non électriques pour infuser le café; Récipients en argile pour le ménage ou la cuisine; Tasses et soucoupes en argile; Assiettes en faïence; Plats en grès; Vases en argile pour fleurs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Čaše bez drška; Keramičke šalice; Kuhala za rižu za namjenu u mirkovalnim pećnicama; Čaj [servisi za čaj]; Kutije za čaj; Šalice za čaj; Staklarija; Staklene posude; Šalice; Šalice; Pehari (bokali) za piće; Dekanteri; Stakleni dekanteri; Čajnici koji zvižde; Neelektrični čajnici; Tanjuri; Plitice [zdjelice]; Porculanski poslužavnici; Poslužavnici za jelo; Podmetači (stolni pribor); Vaze za cvijeće; Prijenosni pribor za kuhanje za uporabu na otvorenom; Neelektrični, filtri za kavu, nepapirnati, za kuhanje kave; Neelektrične posude za kuhanje kave; Stakleno posuđe za pića; Staklene zdjele; Kuhinjske posude; Kuhinjski pribor; Lonci za pirjanje; Filtri za čaj; Čajnici; Polsužavnici za kućanstvo; Zemljano posuđe, I to, Zemljane posude, Glinene šalice, Tanjuri od pečene gline, Zdjele od pečene gline; Izolacijske boce; Izolacijske boce; Neelektrični čajnici; Vaze; Pehari (bokali) za piće; Čaše bez drška; Tanjurići; Podmetači za čaše, nepapirnati i netekstilni; Podmetači za stolove, osim od tekstila i papira; Kuhinjski mužar i tučak; Kutije za sapun; Držači sapuna [naprave za izdavanje sapuna]; Držači za zahodske četke; Držači za četke za brijanje; Držači za četkice za zube; Set kuhinjskih posuda; Podmetači za štapiće za jelo; Zemljano posuđe, I to, Zemljane posude, Glinene šalice; Neelektrične kapaljke od gline za kavu za kuhanje kave; Glinene posude za kućansku ili kuhinjsku uporabu; Glinene šalice i tanjuri; Tanjuri od pečene gline; Zdjele od pečene gline; Glinene vaze za cvijeće.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vizespoharak, ivópoharak; Kerámiabögrék, csészék; Mikrohullámú sütőben használható rizsfőző edények; Teáskészletek [terítékek]; Teásdobozok; Teáscsészék; Üvegáru; Üvegek [tárolóedények]; Bögrék, korsók; Csészék; Kancsók; Dekantálók; Üveg dekantálók; Fütyülős teáskannák; Üstök, nem elektromos; Tányérok; Mosdótálak, lavórok; Porcelán tálcák; Étkező tálcák; Poháralátétek [asztalnemű]; Virágvázák; Hordozható főzőkészletek kültéri használatra; Nem elektromos, nem papírból készült, átönthető kávészűrők kávéfőzéshez; Kávéskannák, nem elektromos; Üvegáru italokhoz; Üvegtálak; Konyhai dobozok, tárolók; Konyhai eszközök, kis méretű; Nyeles lábasok; Teaszűrők; Teáskannák; Tálcák háztartási használatra; Agyagedények, Nevezetesen, Agyagedények, Agyagbögrék, Kerámiatányérok, Cseréptálak; Termoszok; Termoszok; Üstök, nem elektromos; Vázák; Kancsók; Vizespoharak, ivópoharak; Csészealjak; Poháralátétek, nem papírból vagy textilből; Tányéralátétek, nem papírból vagy textilből; Mozsarak és zúzók konyhai használatra; Szappantartók; Szappanadagolók; WC-kefe tartók; Borotvapamacs tartók; Fogkefetartók; Konyhai tároló készlet; Evőpálcika-tartók; Fazekasáruk, Nevezetesen, Agyagedények, Agyagbögrék; Nem elektromos agyag kávéfőző kávéfőzéshez; Agyag edények háztartási vagy konyhai használatra; Agyag csészék és csészealjak; Kerámiatányérok; Cseréptálak; Agyag virágvázák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Bicchieri per bere; Tazze in ceramica; Recipienti per cuocere il riso da utilizzare nei forni a microonde; Servizi da tè; Scatole per il tè; Tazze da tè; Articoli di vetro; Vetri [recipienti]; Tazzoni; Tazze; Brocchette; Decanter; Brocche di vetro; Bollitori con fischio; Cuccume non elettriche; Piatti; Bacinelle; Vassoi [piatti per servire]; Vassoi; Sottobicchieri (stoviglie); Vasi decorativi per fiori; Kit portatili per cucinare all'aperto; Filtri non elettrici di tipo "pour over", non di carta, per la preparazione del caffè per infusione; Caffettiere non elettriche; Vetreria [bicchieri]; Bocce di vetro; Recipienti per la cucina; Utensili da cucina; Casseruole; Filtri per il tè; Teiere; Guantiere per uso domestico; Faenza [ceramica], Ovvero, Tegamini, Tazze alte in terracotta, Piatti in maiolica, Vassoi di ceramica; Bottiglie isolanti; Bottiglie isolanti; Cuccume non elettriche; Vasi; Brocchette; Bicchieri per bere; Piattini; Sottocaraffe, non di carta o di tessuto; Tovagliette, non di carta o di tessuto; Mortai e pestelli da cucina; Porta-sapone; Distributori di sapone; Portascopini per gabinetti; Porta-pennelli per la barba; Portaspazzolini da denti; Set di contenitori; Poggia-bastoncini cinesi; Vasellame [di terracotta], Ovvero, Tegamini, Tazze alte in terracotta; Gocciolatore per caffè non elettrico in argilla per la preparazione del caffè; Contenitori in argilla per la casa o la cucina; Tazza e piattini in argilla; Piatti in maiolica; Vassoi di ceramica; Vasi da fiori in argilla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Gilios stiklinės; Keraminiai puodeliai; Mikrobangų krosnelėse naudojami ryžių virimo indai; Arbatos servizai [valgomieji reikmenys]; Arbatos dėžutės; Arbatos puodeliai; Stiklo gaminiai; Stikliniai indai [tara]; Bokalai; Puodukai; Ąsočiai; Ropinės [grafinai]; Stikliniai grafinai; Arbatiniai su švilpuku; Ne elektriniai virduliai; Lėkštės; Katiliukai; Padėklai; Valgių padėklai; Padėkliukai (valgomieji reikmenys); Gėlių vazos; Nešiojamieji maisto ruošimo rinkiniai, skirti naudoti lauke; Neelektriniai kavos filtrai, ne iš popieriaus, skirti kavai virti; Kavinukai (Ne elektriniai -); Stiklinės; Stiklinės taurės; Virtuviniai konteineriai; Virtuviniai indai; Puodai (žemi); Arbatos koštuvėliai; Arbatinukai; Padėklai (buities reikmėms); Keraminiai indai, Būtent,, Moliniai puodai, Moliniai puodeliai, Keramikinės plokštelės, Moliniai dubenys; Termosai; Termosai; Ne elektriniai virduliai; Vazos; Ąsočiai; Gilios stiklinės; Lėkštelės; Ropinių [grafinų] padėkliukai (ne popieriniai ar ne tekstiliniai); Ne popieriniai ir ne tekstiliniai patiesalai; Piestos ir grūstuvės virtuvės reikmėms; Muilinės; Muilo dalytuvai; Klozeto šepečių stovai; Skutimosi šepetėlių laikikliai; Dantų šepetėlių laikikliai; Dėžučių (indų) rinkiniai; Valgomųjų lazdelių padėklai; Keramikos dirbiniai, Būtent,, Moliniai puodai, Moliniai puodeliai; Neelektrinis molinis kavos lašintuvas kavai gaminti; Molio indai buities ar virtuvės reikmėms; Molio puodelis ir lėkštės; Keramikinės plokštelės; Moliniai dubenys; Molinės gėlių vazos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Glāzes [dzērienu trauki]; Māla tases; Rīsu gatavošanas trauki izmantošanai mikroviļņu krāsnīs; Tējas servīzes [galda piederumi]; Tējas kārbiņas; Tējas krūzes; Stikla trauki; Stikla trauki; Krūzes; Tases; Krūzes ar osu; Karafes; Stikla karafes; Tējkannas ar svilpi; Neelektriskas tējkannas; Šķīvji; Bļodas [tvertnes]; Paplātes; Ēdienu paplātes; Paliktņi (galda piederumi); Puķu vāzes; Pārnēsājami kulinārijas komplekti izmantošanai ārpus telpām; Neelektriski kafijas filtri, kam uzlej karstu ūdeni, no papīra kafijas pagatavošanai; Neelektriskas kafijas kannas; Dzērienu glāzes; Stikla bļodas; Virtuves kārbas; Virtuves trauki; Kastroļi; Tējas sietiņi; Tējkannas; Paplātes mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Māla trauki, Proti, Putras katli, Krūzes, kas izgatavotas no keramikas, Māla šķīvji, Koka bļodas; Vakuuma pudeles; Vakuuma pudeles; Neelektriskas tējkannas; Vāzes; Krūzes ar osu; Glāzes [dzērienu trauki]; Apakštases; Glāžu paliktņi, kas nav no papīra vai auduma; Individuālie galda paliktņi, kas nav no papīra vai auduma; Piestas izmantošanai virtuvē; Ziepju trauki (ar vāku); Ziepju dozatori; Tualetes birstes turētāji; Skūšanās otiņu statīvi; Zobu suku turētāji; Kārbu komplekti; Ēšanas irbuļu turētāji; Podniecības izstrādājumi, Proti, Putras katli, Krūzes, kas izgatavotas no keramikas; Neelektrisks māla kafijas pilinātājs kafijas pagatavošanai; Māla tvertnes mājsaimniecības vai virtuves vajadzībām; Māla krūze un apakštases; Māla šķīvji; Koka bļodas; Māla ziedu vāzes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tazzi mingħajr manku jew sieq; Kikkri tal-fuħħar; Tagħmir tat-tisjir tar-ross għall-użu fi fran tal-majkrowejv; Servizzi tat-tè [oġġetti tal-mejda]; Kaxxetti tat-te; Kikkri tat-te; Prodotti tal-ħġieġ; Ħġieġ [reċipjenti]; Maggijiet; Kikkri; Ġarra; Karaffi; Karaffi tal-ħġieġ; Ktieli li jsaffru; Kittli, mhux tal-elettriku; Platti li fihom jisserva l-ikel; Friskaturi [skutelli]; Gabarrejiet [trejs]; Trejs tal-ikel; Kowsters [metts żgħar tondi jew kwadri għal taħt it-tazzi] (oġġetti ta' fuq il-mejda); Vażuni għal fjuri; Settijiet tat-tisjir portabbli għall-użu fil-beraħ; Filtri tal-kafè li tferra' fuqhom mhux tal-elettriku mhux magħmula mill-karti għat-tisjir tal-kafè; Kafettieri, mhux tal-elettriku; Tazzi tal-ħġieġ; Skutelli tal-ħġieġ; Reċipjenti tal-kċina; Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir; Kazzoli; Passaturi tat-te; Tettieri; Gabarrès għal skopijiet domestiċi; Reċipjenti tax-xaqquf, Jiġifieri, Borom tat-tafal, Kikkri magħmula mill-fuħħar, Platti tal-fuħħar, Skutelli tal-fuħħar; Termos; Termos; Kittli, mhux tal-elettriku; Vażuni; Ġarra; Tazzi mingħajr manku jew sieq; Plattini; Gabarrejiet żgħar għal użu taħt it-tazzi, mhux tal-karta u jew tat-tessut; Matts ta' taħt il-platti, mhux tal-karta jew tat-tessut; Mhiereż u lidl għall-użu fil-kċina; Kontenituri tas-sapun; Dispenser tas-sapun; Stends għall-ixkupilja tal-loki; Sostenn għall-pinzell tal-leħja; Ħowlders għall-ixkupilji tas-snien; Settijiet ta' kaxxi; Bażi għaż-żamma taċ-ċopstiks; Fuħħar, Jiġifieri, Borom tat-tafal, Kikkri magħmula mill-fuħħar; Drippers tal-kafè tat-tafal mhux elettriċi għat-tisjir tal-kafè; Kontenituri tal-fuħħar għall-użu domestiku jew fil-kċina; Kikkri u plattini tal-fuħħar; Platti tal-fuħħar; Skutelli tal-fuħħar; Vażuni tat-tafal għall-fjuri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Tuimelbekers; Kopjes van pottenbakkerswaren; Rijstkokers voor gebruik in de magnetron; Theeserviezen; Theedozen; Theekopjes; Glaswerk; Glazen [houders]; Drinkbekers; Kopjes; Drinkkruiken; Karaffen; Glazen decanteerflessen; Fluitketels; Waterketels, niet elektrisch; Borden; Kommen; Presenteerbladen; Dienbladen voor maaltijden; Onderleggers (voor gebruik aan tafel); Vaasjes (Kleine, smalle -); Draagbare kooksets voor buitengebruik; Niet-elektrische koffiefilters, niet van papier, voor het koffiezetten; Koffiepotten, niet elektrisch; Drinkglazen; Glazen bollen; Houders voor de keuken; Keukengerei; Stoofpannen; Theezeefjes; Theepotten; Dienbladen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Aardewerk, Te weten, Sauspannen, Bekers vervaardigd uit aardewerk, Borden van aardewerk, Schalen van steen; Thermosflessen; Thermosflessen; Waterketels, niet elektrisch; Vazen; Drinkkruiken; Tuimelbekers; Schoteltjes; Onderzetters, niet van papier of linnen, voor karaffen; Placemats, niet van papier of textiel; Vijzels en stampers voor gebruik in de keuken; Zeephouders; Zeepdispensers; Houders voor toiletborstels; Scheerkwasthouders; Houders voor tandenborstels; Bussensets; Stokjesleggers; Pottenbakkerswaren, Te weten, Sauspannen, Bekers vervaardigd uit aardewerk; Niet-elektrische koffiefilterhouders van aardewerk of steengoed voor het koffiezetten; Vaatwerk van aardewerk of steengoed voor de huishouding of de keuken; Kop en schotels van aardewerk of steengoed; Borden van aardewerk; Schalen van steen; Bloemenvazen van aardewerk of steengoed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Szklanki bez uchwytów; Kubki z gliny garncarskiej; Parowniki do ryżu do stosowania w mikrofalówkach; Serwisy do herbaty; Pudełka na herbatę; Filiżanki na herbatę; Wyroby szklane; Szklane naczynia do picia; Kubki; Filiżanki; Dzbanki; Karafki [na alkohol]; Karafki ze szkła; Czajniki z gwizdkiem; Czajniki nieelektryczne; Talerze; Miseczki; Półmiski [tace]; Tace na posiłki; Podstawki stołowe pod naczynia; Wazony na kwiaty; Przenośne zestawy do gotowania do użytku na wolnym powietrzu; Nieelektryczne przelewowe filtry do kawy, niepapierowe, do parzenia kawy; Dzbanki do kawy, nieelektryczne; Naczynia szklane do napojów; Miski ze szkła; Pojemniki kuchenne; Przybory kuchenne; Rondle; Sitka do herbaty; Czajniczki do herbaty; Tace do użytku domowego; Naczynia ceramiczne, Zn, Garnki gliniane, Kubki gliniane, Talerze ceramiczne, Misy kamionkowe; Termosy; Termosy; Czajniki nieelektryczne; Wazony; Dzbanki; Szklanki bez uchwytów; Spodeczki; Podkładki pod szklanki, nie z papieru i nie z materiałów tekstylnych; Maty na stół, nie z papieru ani materiałów tekstylnych; Moździerze do użytku kuchennego; Mydelniczki; Dozowniki mydła; Uchwyty do szczotek toaletowych; Stojaki na pędzle do golenia; Uchwyty na szczoteczki do zębów; Komplety puszek kuchennych; Podpórki na pałeczki do jedzenia; Wyroby garncarskie, Zn, Garnki gliniane, Kubki gliniane; Nieelektryczne filtry [dripy] gliniane do parzenia kawy; Pojemniki gliniane do użytku domowego lub kuchennego; Gliniane filiżanki i spodki; Talerze ceramiczne; Misy kamionkowe; Donice gliniane.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Copos sem pé; Taças em cerâmica; Recipientes de cozer arroz para uso em fornos microondas; Serviços de chá [louça de mesa]; Caixas para chá; Chávenas de chá; Artigos de vidro; Recipientes em vidro; Canecas; Taças; Jarros; Decantadores; Decantadores de vidro; Chaleiras com apito; Chaleiras, não elétricas; Louça; Bacias [pias]; Bandejas [tabuleiros]; Bandejas para refeições; Bases para copos; Vasos para flores; Kits de cozinha portáteis para uso ao ar livre; Filtros de café não elétricos, não em papel, para fazer café de filtro; Cafeteiras, não elétricas; Copos para bebidas; Tijelas em vidro; Recipientes para cozinha; Utensílios para cozinha; Caçarolas; Coadores de chá; Chaleiras [bules para chá]; Tabuleiros para uso doméstico; Cerâmica em barro, Nomeadamente, Tachos de barro, Canecas de faiança, Pratos em faiança, Taças em grés; Garrafas térmicas; Garrafas térmicas; Chaleiras, não elétricas; Vasos; Jarros; Copos sem pé; Pires; Bases para copos, não sendo em papel ou têxteis; Individuais de mesa, não sendo em papel ou têxteis; Almofarizes e pilões para a cozinha; Saboneteiras; Dispensadores de sabonete; Suportes para escovas de piaçaba; Porta-pincéis para barbear; Suportes para escovas de dentes; Conjuntos de latas de armazenamento para cozinha; Apoios para pauzinhos chineses; Cerâmica, Nomeadamente, Tachos de barro, Canecas de faiança; Gotejadores de café em barro, não elétricos, para fazer café; Recipientes de barro para uso doméstico ou na cozinha; Chávenas e pires em barro; Pratos em faiança; Taças em grés; Vasos para flores em barro.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Pahare fără picior; Căni din ceramică; Vase de fiert orez pentru cuptor cu microunde; Servicii de ceai [veselă]; Ceai (Cutii pentru -); Ceşti de ceai; Articole de sticlărie; Sticle [recipiente]; Căni; Ceşti; Stacane; Carafe; Carafe din sticlă; Ceainice cu fluier; Fierbătoare neelectrice; Farfurii; Chiuvete; Tăvi [platouri de servit]; Tăvi pentru servit masă; Suporturi pentru pahare (articole de masă); Vaze pentru flori; Seturi portabile de bucătărie pentru excursii; Filtre de cafea neelectrice, cu picurare, nu din hârtie, pentru preparat cafea; Cafetiere neelectrice; Articole din sticlă pentru băuturi; Boluri de sticlă; Bucătărie (Recipiente pentru -); Ustensile de bucătărie; Cratiţe; Strecurători de ceai; Ceainice; Tăvi de uz casnic; Faianţă (Obiecte din -), Şi anume, Tăvi din lut, Căni confecţionate din ceramică, Farfurii din ceramică, Vase din gresie ceramică; Termosuri; Termosuri; Fierbătoare neelectrice; Vaze; Stacane; Pahare fără picior; Farfurioare; Suporturi pentru pahare, nu din hârtie sau material textil; Individualuri de masă, nu din hârtie sau material textil; Mojare şi pisăloage pentru bucătărie; Savoniere; Dozatoare de săpun; Suporturi pentru periile de WC; Suporturi pentru pămătufuri de bărbierit; Suporturi pentru periuţe de dinţi; Set recipiente de bucătărie; Suporturi pentru beţişoare chinezeşti; Produse de olărie, Şi anume, Tăvi din lut, Căni confecţionate din ceramică; Ibric neelectric din lut pentru preparat cafea; Recipiente din lut pentru menaj sau bucătărie; Căniși farfurioare din lut; Farfurii din ceramică; Vase din gresie ceramică; Vaze din lut pentru flori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Poháre; Šálky z hlinenej keramiky; Nádoby na varenie ryže na použitie v mikrovlnnej rúre; Čajové súpravy (stolový riad); Dózy na čaj; Čajové šálky; Sklenený tovar; Poháre [nádoby]; Hrnčeky; Šálky; Džbány; Karafy; Sklené dekantačné karafy; Pískajúce kanvice; Kanvice (nie elektrické); Taniere; Misy; Podnosy (tácne); Podnosy na jedlo; Podložky pod poháre (stolový riad); Vázy na kvetiny; Prenosné kuchynské súpravy na použitie v exteriéri; Neelektrické nalievacie kávové filtre okrem papierových, určené na varenie kávy; Kanvice na kávu (nie elektrické); Sklené poháre; Sklené gule; Kuchynské nádoby; Kuchynský riad; Kastróly; Cedidlá na čaj; Čajníky; Podnosy na použitie v domácnosti; Hrnčiarske výrobky, T.z, Hlinené hrnce, Hrnčeky z keramiky (kameniny), Keramické taniere, Kameninové misy; Termosky; Termosky; Kanvice (nie elektrické); Vázy; Džbány; Poháre; Tanieriky pod šálky; Tanieriky pod fľaše (nie papierové, nie textilné); Prestieranie na stolovanie okrem textilného a papierového; Mažiare a paličky na kuchynské účely; Obaly na mydlá; Dávkovače mydla; Držiaky na záchodové kefy; Stojany na štetky na holenie; Stojany na zubné kefky; Sady kuchynských nádob s vekom; Podpierky na čínske paličky; Hrnčiarsky tovar, T.z, Hlinené hrnce, Hrnčeky z keramiky (kameniny); Neelektrické keramické kávové prekvapkávadlá na varenie kávy; Keramické nádoby do domácnosti alebo kuchyne; Keramické šálky a tanieriky; Keramické taniere; Kameninové misy; Keramické vázy na kvetiny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kozarci za vodo; Skodelice iz keramike; Kuhalniki za riž za uporabo v mikrovalovni pečici; Čajni servisi; Škatle za čaj; Skodelice za čaj; Steklovina; Kozarci; Vrčki; Skodelice; Vrči; Karafe; Steklene karafe; Čajniki s piskanjem; Kotlički, neelektrični; Krožniki; Umivalniki (sklede); Servirni pladnji; Kovinski pladnji; Namizni podstavki; Cvetlične vaze; Prenosni kompleti za kuhanje na prostem; Neelektrični, nepapirni filtri za kavo za prelivanje, za kuhanje kave; Aparati za kavo (neelektrični); Kozarci za pijačo; Steklene sklede; Kuhinjske posode; Kuharski pripomočki; Ponve; Cedila za čaj; Čajniki; Pladnji za gospodinjske namene; Lončenina, Sicer, Glinasti lonci, Lončeni skodelice, Krožniki iz fajanse, Lončene sklede; Termovke; Termovke; Kotlički, neelektrični; Vaze; Vrči; Kozarci za vodo; Krožnički za pod skodelice; Podstavki, ne iz papirja ali blaga; Pogrinjki, ne iz papirja ali blaga; Terilniki za kuhinjsko uporabo; Posodice za milo; Dozirniki mila; Držala za straniščne ščetke; Stojala za čopiče za britje; Držala za zobne ščetke; Seti kuhinjskih posod; Držala za jedilne paličice; Lončene posode, Sicer, Glinasti lonci, Lončeni skodelice; Neelektrični lončeni kapljalniki za kuhanje kave; Lončene posode za shranjevanje za uporabo v gospodinjstvu ali kuhinji; Lončene čajne skodelice in krožnički; Krožniki iz fajanse; Lončene sklede; Lončene vaze za cvetje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tumlare; Koppar gjorda av keramik; Riskokare för användning i mikrovågsugnar; Teserviser [bordsserviser]; Teburkar; Tekoppar; Glasvaror; Glas [förvaringskärl]; Muggar; Bägare; Krus; Karaffer; Glaskaraffer; Visselpannor; Icke-elektriska vattenkokare; Fat; Bunkar [skålar]; Likörbrickor; Måltidsbrickor; Underlägg (bordsservis); Knoppvaser; Bärbara matlagningsset för utomhusbruk; Icke-elektriska pourover-kaffefilter, ej av papper, för pourover-bryggning av kaffe; Icke-elektriska kaffekannor; Glasvaror för drycker; Glasskålar; Köksbehållare; Köksgeråd; Kastruller; Tesilar; Tekannor; Brickor för hushållsändamål; Bordsporslin, Nämligen, Lergrytor, Muggar tillverkade av lergods, Tallrikar av lergods, Skålar av stengods; Termosflaskor; Termosflaskor; Icke-elektriska vattenkokare; Vaser; Krus; Tumlare; Tefat för koppar; Underlägg, inte av papper eller textil; Bordstabletter, inte av papper eller textil; Mortlar och mortelstötar för köksanvändning; Tvålkoppar; Tvålautomater; Borsthållare för vattenklosetter; Ställ för rakborstar; Tandborsthållare; Uppsättningar av köksbehållare; Ätpinnsstöd; Keramikvaror, Nämligen, Lergrytor, Muggar tillverkade av lergods; Icke-elektriska kaffebryggare av lera för bryggning av kaffe; Lerbehållare för hushålls- eller köksanvändning; Lerkopp med fat; Tallrikar av lergods; Skålar av stengods; Blomvaser av lera.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/091</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-15</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/163</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-27</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080369</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>60996</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
