<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-07T00:14:39</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226270</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226270</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>it</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-20</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>NUTRIEVO</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162306633</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226270/000162306633.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>02.01.95</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.11</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.13</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.14</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Диетични хранителни препарати за лечебни цели; Здравословно хранително блокче заместител на хранене за стимулиране на енергията; Хранителни добавки за медицински цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Dietetické potravinové přípravky upravené k léčebným účelům; Energetické tyčinky nahrazující jídlo jakožto doplňky stravy; Výživové doplňky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Diætetiske fødevarepræparater til medicinsk brug; Energistænger som kosttilskud og måltidserstatning; Næringstilskud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Diätetische Nahrungsmittelpräparate für medizinische Zwecke; Nährstoff-Energieriegel als Nahrungsergänzungsmittel; Nahrungsergänzungsmittel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαιτητικά παρασκευάσματα διατροφής προσαρμοσμένα για ιατρική χρήση· Υποκατάστατα θρεπτικά γεύματος σε μορφή ράβδου για τόνωση της ενέργειας· Συμπληρώματα διατροφής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Dietetic food preparations adapted for medical use; Nutritional supplement meal replacement bars for boosting energy; Nutritional supplements.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Preparaciones dietéticas alimenticias para uso médico; Barritas de sustitución de comidas como complemento nutritivo para potenciar la energía; Complementos nutricionales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meditsiiniliseks kasutuseks kohandatud dieettoidupreparaadid; Energiat suurendavad toitu asendavad toidulisandibatoonid; Toidulisandid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Dieettiruokavalmisteet lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Ravintolisää sisältävät aterian korvaavat patukat; Lisäravintoaineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Préparations alimentaires diététiques à usage médical; Substituts de repas sous forme de barres nutritionnelles pour donner de l'énergie; Compléments nutritionnels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Dijetetski prehrambeni pripravci prilagođeni za medicinske potrebe; Pločice za podizanje energije kao zamjena za obrok; Hranjivi dodaci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Diétás ételkészítmények gyógyászati használatra; Étkezést helyettesítő, táplálékkiegésztő, energianövelő szeletek; Táplálékkiegészítők.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Prodotti alimentari dietetici per uso medico; Barrette sostitutive di pasti energetiche; Integratori alimentari per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Dietiniai maisto preparatai medicinos reikmėms; Maisto papildų batonėliai kaip valgio pakaitalas skirti energijai didinti; Mitybos papildai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Diētiskā pārtika medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Maltīšu aizstāšanas batoniņi enerģijas rezervju atjaunošanai; Uztura bagātinātāji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Preparazzjonijiet ta' ikel djetetiku adattati għal skopijiet mediċi; Ċangaturi ta' ikel nutrittiv bħala sostituti għall-ibbustjar tal-enerġija; Supplimenti ta' nutrizzjoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diëtische voedingsmiddelen voor medische doeleinden; Energierepen met voedingssupplementen als maaltijdvervanger; Voedingssupplementen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dietetyczne preparaty żywnościowe przystosowane do celów medycznych; Batony energetyzujące stanowiące zamienniki posiłków zawierające dodatki odżywcze; Odżywcze suplementy diety.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Preparações alimentares dietéticas para uso medicinal; Barras nutricionais para substituição de refeições para aumentar os níveis de energia; Suplementos nutricionais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Preparate alimentare dietetice de uz medical; Batoane care înlocuiesc o masă, ca supliment nutritiv, pentru sporirea energiei; Suplimente nutritive.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Dietetické potravinové prípravky upravené na lekárske použitie; Energetické tyčinky nahradzujúce jedlo ako doplnok stravy; Výživové doplnky na lekárske použitie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Dietetični prehrambeni pripravki, prirejeni za medicinske namene; Prehranske ploščice za nadomeščanje obrokov za povečanje energije; Hranilni dodatki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Dietiska näringspreparat anpassade för medicinska ändamål; Måltidsersättningar som bars med näringstillskott för att höja energin; Näringstillskott.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>29</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Месни екстракти; Екстракти от риба; Зеленчукови екстракти за храни; Екстракти за супа; Концентрирани бульони; Предварително приготвени супи; Сухи смеси за супа; Крем супи; Желета, конфитюри, компоти, плодови и зеленчукови пастети; Гъби, консервирани; Консервирани домати; Артишок, консервиран; Грах, консервиран; Зеленчуци, консервирани; Зеленчукови консерви; Сметана на растителна основа; Консервирани чушки; Соеви зърна, консервирани, за хранителни цели; Осолено месо; Обработени плодове, гъби, зеленчуци, ядки и варива; Спанак, замразен; Замразени мезета, състоящи се предимно от пилешко месо; Замразени мезета, съставени предимно от морски дарове; Замразени, предварително опаковани предястия, състоящи се предимно от меса; Хамбургери; Вегетариански бургери; Птичи яйца и яйчни продукти; Мляко; Лецитин за кулинарни цели; Маргарин; Сметана [млечни произведения]; Бита сметана; Кисело мляко; Семена за ядене; Хранителни масла и мазнини; Месо; Фъстъчено масло; Супи и бульони, месни екстракти; Бульони; Бульон (Препарати за приготвяне на -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Masové výtažky; Rybí výtažky; Zeleninové výtažky do potravin; Výtažky do polévek; Polévkové koncentráty; Polévky v konzervách; Polévky v prášku; Základy k přípravě polévek; Želé, džemy, kompoty, ovocné a zeleninové pomazánky; Konzervované houby; Konzervovaná rajčata; Artyčoky, konzervované; Konzervovaný hrášek; Konzervovaná zelenina; Zeleninové konzervy; Krémy se zeleninovým základem; Konzervovaná paprika; Konzervované sojové boby pro potravinářské účely; Nasolená masa; Zpracované ovoce, houby a zelenina, ořechy a luštěniny; Špenát, zmrazený; Zmrazené předkrmy převážně z kuřecího masa; Zmrazené předkrmy převážně z mořských plodů; Mražené balené předkrmy převážně z plodů moře; Hamburgery; Zeleninové hamburgery; Ptačí vejce a vaječné výrobky; Mléko; Lecitin pro kulinářské použití; Margarín; Smetana [mléčný výrobek]; Šlehačka; Jogurt; Jedlá semena; Jedlé oleje a tuky; Maso; Arašídové máslo; Polévky a vývary, masové výtažky; Bujóny; Bujónové přípravky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kødekstrakter; Fiskeekstrakter; Grøntsagsekstrakter til næringsmidler; Suppeekstrakter; Suppekoncentrat; Supper på dåse; Suppepulvere; Suppepasta (puréer); Geléer, syltetøj, kompotter, frugt- og grøntsagssmørepålæg; Svampe, konserverede; Konserverede tomater; Konserverede artiskokker; Ærter, konserverede; Grøntsager, konserverede; Grøntsagskonserves; Vegetabilsk fløde; Konserverede peberfrugter; Sojabønner, konserverede [næringsmiddel]; Saltet kød; Forarbejdede frugt, svampe, grøntsager, nødder og bælgfrugter; Frossen spinat; Frosne forretter hovedsagelig bestående af kylling; Frosne forretter hovedsagelig bestående af fisk og skaldyr; Frosne, færdigpakkede hovedretter hovedsageligt bestående af fisk og skaldyr; Hamburgerbøffer; Grøntsagsburgere; Fugleæg og æggeprodukter; Mælk; Lecitin til brug som næringsmiddel; Margarine; Fløde; Flødeskum; Yoghurt; Spiselige frø; Spiselige olier og fedtstoffer; Kød; Jordnøddesmør; Supper og fonder, kødekstrakter; Bouillon; Præparater til fremstilling af bouillon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Fleischextrakte; Fischextrakte; Gemüseextrakte für Nahrungszwecke; Suppenextrakte; Suppenkonzentrate; Suppen in Dosen; Suppenpulver; Suppenpasten; Gallerten und Gelees, Konfitüren, Kompotte, Frucht- und Gemüseaufstriche; Konservierte Pilze; Konservierte Tomaten; Konservierte Artischocken; Konservierte Erbsen; Konserviertes Gemüse; Gemüsekonserven [Dosen]; Sahne auf Gemüsebasis; Konservierte Paprika; Konservierte Sojabohnen für Speisezwecke; Eingesalzene Fleischwaren [Pökelfleisch]; Verarbeitete Früchte, Pilze, Gemüse, Nüsse und Hülsenfrüchte; Tiefgekühlter Spinat; Tiefgefrorene Vorspeisen, hauptsächlich bestehend aus Huhn; Tiefgefrorene Vorspeisen, hauptsächlich bestehend aus Meeresfrüchten; Gefrorene vorverpackte Hauptgerichte, hauptsächlich bestehend aus Meeresfrüchten; Hacksteak; Vegetarische Bratlinge; Vogeleier und Eierprodukte; Milch; Lezithin für Speisezwecke; Margarine; Sahne [Rahm]; Schlagsahne, Schlagobers; Joghurt; Essbare Samenkörner; Speiseöle und -fette; Fleisch; Erdnussbutter; Suppen und Brühen, Fleischextrakte; Bouillon; Zubereitungen für die Herstellung von Bouillon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εκχυλίσματα κρέατος· Εκχυλίσματα από ψάρια· Εκχυλίσματα λαχανικών για τρόφιμα· Εκχυλίσματα για σούπες· Συμπυκνωμένες σούπες· Σούπες σε κονσέρβα· Σούπες σε σκόνη· Πολτοί για σούπες· Ζελέ, μαρμελάδες, κομπόστα, φρούτα και λαχανικά σε μορφή κρέμας· Μανιτάρια συντηρημένα· Διατηρημένες ντομάτες· Αγκινάρες, διατηρημένες· Αρακάς κονσερβοποιημένος· Λαχανικά κονσερβοποιημένα· Κονσέρβες λαχανικών· Κρέμα με βάση λαχανικά· Πιπεριές, διατηρημένες· Σπόροι σόγιας διατηρημένοι για διατροφή· Παστά κρέατα· Επεξεργασμένα φρούτα, μανιτάρια, λαχανικά, ξηροί καρποί και όσπρια· Κατεψυγμένο σπανάκι· Κατεψυγμένα ορεκτικά κυρίως από κοτόπουλο· Κατεψυγμένα ορεκτικά κυρίως από θαλασσινά· Κατεψυγμένα προσυσκευασμένα ορεκτικά αποτελούμενα κυρίως από θαλασσινά· Χάμπουργκερ· Μπιφτέκια από λαχανικά· Αυγά πουλιών και προϊόντα αυγών· Γάλα· Λεκιθίνη για μαγειρική χρήση· Βούτυρο, μαργαρίνη· Κρέμα (γάλακτος) [γαλακτοκομικά προϊόντα]· Σαντιγύ (κρέμα χτυπημένη)· Γιαούρτι· Βρώσιμοι σπόροι· Έλαια και λίπη βρώσιμα· Κρέατα· Φυστικοβούτυρο· Σούπες και ζωμοί, εκχυλίσματα κρέατος· Ζωμοί· Ζωμών (Προϊόντα για την παρασκευή -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Meat extracts; Fish extracts; Vegetable extracts for food; Extracts for soups; Soup concentrates; Canned soups; Soup powders; Soup pastes; Jellies, jams, compotes, fruit and vegetable spreads; Mushrooms, preserved; Tomato preserves; Artichokes, preserved; Peas, preserved; Vegetables, preserved; Vegetables, tinned; Vegetable-based cream; Preserved peppers; Soya beans, preserved, for food; Salted meats; Processed fruits, fungi, vegetables, nuts and pulses; Frozen spinach; Frozen appetizers consisting primarily of chicken; Frozen appetizers consisting primarily of seafood; Frozen pre-packaged entrees consisting primarily of seafood; Hamburgers; Vegetable burgers; Birds eggs and egg products; Milk; Lecithin for culinary purposes; Margarine; Cream [dairy products]; Whipped cream; Yoghurt; Edible seeds; Edible oils and fats; Meat; Peanut butter; Soups and stocks, meat extracts; Broth; Preparations for making bouillon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Extractos de carne; Extractos de pescado; Productos vegetales para uso alimenticio; Extractos para sopas; Concentrados para sopas; Sopas en lata; Polvos para sopas; Pastas para hacer sopa; Jaleas, mermeladas, compotas, frutas y verduras para untar; Champiñones en conserva; Conservas de tomate; Alcachofas en conserva; Guisantes en conserva; Verduras, hortalizas y legumbres en conserva; Verduras, hortalizas y legumbres enlatadas [conservas]; Crema a base de verduras, hortalizas y legumbres; Pimientos en conserva; Granos de soja en conserva para uso alimenticio; Salazones; Frutos, hongos, verduras, frutos secos y legumbres procesados; Espinacas congeladas; Aperitivos congelados compuestos principalmente de pollo; Aperitivos congelados compuestos principalmente de mariscos; Platos principales congelados y preenvasados compuestos principalmente de mariscos; Hamburguesas; Hamburguesas vegetales; Huevos y ovoproductos; Leche; Lecitina para uso culinario; Margarina; Nata; Nata montada; Yogur; Semillas comestibles; Aceites y grasas comestibles; Carne; Mantequilla de cacahuete; Sopas y caldos, extractos de carne; Caldos; Preparaciones para hacer caldo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Lihaekstraktid; Kalaekstraktid; Toiduks kasutatavad köögiviljaekstraktid; Supiekstraktid; Supikontsentraadid; Konservsupid; Supipulbrid; Supipastad; Tarrendid, moosid, kompotid, puu- ja köögiviljamäärded; Seenekonservid, konservitud seened; Tomatikonservid/ Konservitud tomatid; Konserveeritud artišokid; Hernekonservid, konservitud herned; Köögiviljakonservid, konservitud köögiviljad; Konservitud köögiviljad; Taimne koor; Konservpiprad; Sojaoakonservid, konservitud sojaoad; Soolaliha; Töödeldud puuviljad, seened, köögiviljad, pähklid ja kaunviljad; Sügavkülmutatud spinat; Peamiselt kanaliha sisaldavad sügavkülmutatud suupisted; Peamiselt mereande sisaldavad sügavkülmutatud suupisted; Peamiselt mereandidest koosnevad sügavkülmutatud pakendatud eelroad; Pihvid; Köögiviljaburgerid; Linnumunad ja munatooted; Piim; Kulinaarne letsitiin; Margariin; Koor [piimatoode]; Vahukoor; Jogurt; Söödavad seemned; Toiduõlid ja toidurasvad; Liha; Maapähklivõi; Supid ja puljongid, lihaekstraktid; Puljongid, rammuleemed; Puljongivalmistusained, puljongiained.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lihauutteet; Kalauutteet; Kasvisuutteet elintarvikekäyttöön; Keittouutteet; Keittotiivisteet; Purkkikeitot; Keittojauheet; Keittotahnat; Hyytelöt, hillot, hillokkeet, hedelmä- ja vihanneslevitteet; Sienet, säilötyt; Säilötyt tomaatit; Säilötyt artisokat; Herneet, säilötyt; Vihannekset, säilötyt; Säilykevihannekset; Kasvispohjainen kerma; Paprikat, säilötyt; Soijapavut (säilötyt), ravinnoksi; Suolaliha; Käsitellyt hedelmät, sienet, vihannekset, pähkinät ja palkokasvit; Pinaatti pakastettuna; Pääosin kanasta koostuvat pakastetut alkupalat; Pääosin äyriäisistä koostuvat pakastetut alkupalat; Pääasiassa merenelävistä koostuvat valmiiksi pakatut pakastetut pääruoat; Hampurilaispihvit; Kasvispihvit; Linnunmunat ja munatuotteet; Maito; Lesitiini ruoanlaittoon; Margariini; Kerma [maitotuotteista]; Kermavaahto; Jogurtti; Siemenet, syötävät; Ravintoöljyt ja -rasvat; Liha; Pähkinävoi; Keitot ja liemet, lihauutteet; Liemet; Lihaliemivalmisteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Extraits de viande; Extraits de poisson; Extraits de légumes à usage alimentaire; Extraits pour potages; Concentrés de soupe; Soupes en boîte; Soupes en poudre; Pâtes pour potages; Gelées, confitures, compotes, pâtes à tartiner de fruits et de légumes; Champignons conservés; Tomates en conserve; Artichauts conservés; Pois conservés; Légumes conservés; Conserves de légumes; Crème à base de légumes; Poivrons conservés; Graines de soja conservées à usage alimentaire; Salaisons; Fruits, champignons, légumes, fruits à coque et légumineuses transformés; Épinards congelés; Amuse-gueule congelés composés principalement de poulet; Amuse-gueule congelés composés principalement de fruits de mer; Plats principaux congelés pré-emballés composés principalement de fruits de mer; Steaks hachés; Steaks végétaux; Œufs de volaille et ovoproduits; Lait; Lécithine à usage culinaire; Margarine; Crème [produit laitier]; Crème fouettée; Yaourt; Graines comestibles; Huiles et graisses comestibles; Viandes; Beurre d'arachides; Potages et bouillons, extraits de viande; Bouillons; Préparations pour faire des bouillons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Mesni ekstrakti; Riblji ekstrakti; Ekstrakti povrća za prehranu; Ekstrakti za juhe; Koncentrati za juhu; Juhe u konzervi; Juhe u vrećici; Paste za pripremanje juhe; Želei, džemovi, kompoti, voćni i povrtni namazi; Konzervirane gljive; Konzervirane rajčice; Konzervirane artičoke; Konzervirani grašak; Povrće, konzervirano; Konzerve od povrća; Vrhnje na biljnoj bazi; Konzervirane paprike; Konzervirana soja u zrnu za prehranu; Usoljeno meso; Prerađeno voće, gljive, povrće, orašasti plodovi i mahunarke; Smrznuti špinat; Smrznuta predjela koja se uglavnom sastoje od piletine; Smrznuta predjela koja se uglavnom sastoje od morskih plodova; Smrznuta pakirana predjela koja se uglavnom sastoje od morskih plodova; Hamburgeri; Burgeri od povrća; Ptičja jaja i proizvodi od jaja; Mlijeko; Lecitin za upotrebu u kulinarstvu; Margarin; Vrhnje [mliječni proizvodi]; Tučeno vrhnje; Jogurt; Jestive sjemenke; Jestiva ulja i masti; Meso; Maslac od arašida; Juhe i temeljci, mesni ekstrakti; Bujon; Sastojci za pripremanje bujona.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Húskivonatok; Halkivonatok; Növénykivonatok étkezési célokra; Leveskivonatok; Leves koncentrátum; Leveskonzervek; Levesporok; Levespaszta; Kocsonyák, dzsemek, kompótok, gyümölcs- és zöldségkrémek; Gomba, tartósított; Tartósított paradicsom; Articsóka, tartósított; Borsó, tartósított; Zöldségek, tartósított; Zöldségkonzervek; Növényi alapú tejszín; Tartósított paprika; Szójabab, tartósított, táplálkozási használatra; Sózott hús; Feldolgozott gyümölcsök, gombák, zöldségek, diófélék és hüvelyesek; Spenót, fagyasztva; Elsősorban csirkehúst tartalmazó fagyasztott előételek; Elsősorban tenger gyümölcseit tartalmazó fagyasztott előételek; Elsősorban tengeri ételeket tartalmazó előre csomagolt fagyasztott főételek; Hamburgerek, húspogácsák; Zöldségpogácsák; Tojások és tojástermékek; Tej; Lecitin étkezési célokra; Margarin; Tejszín [tejtermékek]; Tejszínhab; Joghurt; Ehető magvak; Étkezési olajok és zsírok; Húsok; Mogyoróvaj; Levesek és csontlevesek, húskivonatok; Csontleves, húsleves; Készítmények húsleveshez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">estratti di carne; Estratti di pesce; Estratti vegetali per uso alimentare; Estratti per minestre; Minestre concentrate; Minestre in scatola; Polveri per minestre; Paste per minestre; Gelatine, marmellate, composte, frutta e verdura spalmabili; Funghi conservati; Pomodori (conservati); Carciofi, conservati; Piselli conservati; Legumi conservati; Conserve di legumi; Crema a base di legumi; Peperoni conservati; Fagioli di soia conservati; Alimenti salati [cibi conservati sotto sale]; Frutta, funghi ed ortaggi lavorati (inclusi frutta a guscio e legumi); Spinaci congelati; Antipasti congelati principalmente a base di pollo; Antipasti congelati composti principalmente da frutti di mare; Piatti principali congelati preconfezionati che principalmente a base di frutti di mare; Hamburger; Hamburger alle verdure; Uova e prodotti a base di uova; Latte; lecticina per uso culinario; margarina; panna [prodotto lattiero]; panna montata; yogurt; Semi commestibili; olii e grassi commestibili; Prodotti di salumeria; burro di arachidi; Zuppe e brodi, estratti di carne; Brodi; Preparati per fare i brodi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Mėsos ekstraktai; Žuvų ekstraktai; Daržovių ekstraktai maistui; Sriubų ekstraktai; Sriubų koncentratai; Konservuotos sriubos [skardinėse]; Sriubų sausieji ruošiniai; Sriubų pastos; Drebučiai, uogienės, kompotai, vaisių ir daržovių užtepai; Konservuoti grybai; Konservuoti pomidorai; Konservuoti artišokai; Konservuoti žirneliai; Konservuotos daržovės; Konservuotos daržovės [skardinėse]; Daržovių tyrė; Konservuotos paprikos; Konservuotos sojų pupelės (maistui); Sūdyti mėsos produktai; Apdoroti vaisiai, grybai, daržovės, riešutai ir ankštinės daržovės; Šaldyti špinatai; Šaldyti užkandžiai vištienos pagrindu; Šaldyti užkandžiai jūros gėrybių pagrindu; Šaldyti fasuoti pirmieji patiekalai, daugiausia iš jūrų gėrybių; Mėsos paplotėliai suvožtiniams; Daržovių paplotėliai suvožtiniams; Kiaušiniai ir kiaušinių produktai; Pienas; Lecitinas (kulinarijos reikmėms); Margarinas; Grietinėlė [pieno produktas]; Plakta grietinėlė; Jogurtas; Valgomos sėklos; Valgomieji aliejai ir riebalai; Mėsa; Žemės riešutų sviestas; Sriubos ir sultiniai, mėsos ekstraktai; Sultiniai; Sultinių ruošiniai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Gaļas ekstrakti; Zivju ekstrakti; Pārtikai paredzēti dārzeņu ekstrakti; Zupu ekstrakti; Zupu koncentrāti; Zupu konservi; Pulverveida zupu maisījumi; Pastas zupu pagatavošanai; Želejas, ievārījumi, kompoti, augļu un dārzeņu pastas; Konservētas sēnes; Tomāti (konservēti); Konservēti artišoki; Konservēti zirņi; Konservēti dārzeņi; Dārzeņu konservi; Dārzeņu krēmi; Konservētie pipari; Konservētas sojas pupiņas pārtikai; Sālīta gaļa; Apstrādāti augļi, sēnes, dārzeņi, rieksti un pākšaugi; Saldēti spināti; Saldētās uzkodas, kas galvenokārt sastāv no vistas gaļas; Saldētas uzkodas, kas galvenokārt sastāv no jūras veltēm; Saldētas, fasētas uzkodas, kas galvenokārt sastāv no jūras veltēm; Burgeru gaļa; Dārzeņu burgeri; Putnu olas un olu produkti; Piens; Lecitīns kulinārijas nolūkiem; Margarīns; Krējums [piena produkti]; Putukrējums; Jogurts; Ēdamas sēklas; Pārtikas eļlas un tauki; Gaļas izstrādājumi; Zemesriekstu sviests; Zupas un buljoni, gaļas ekstrakti; Buljoni; Buljona sagataves.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Estratti tal-laħam; Estratti tal-ħut; Estratti tal-ħxejjex għall-ikel; Estratti tas-sopop; Konċentrati tas-soppa; Sopop fil-laned; Trab tas-soppa; Pejsts tas-sopop; Ġeli, ġammijiet, frott frisk jew niexef mgħolli biz-zokkor, spreds tal-frott jew tal-ħxejjex; Faqqiegħ (ippreservat); Tadam ippreservat; Qaqoċċ, ippreservat; Piżelli preservati; Ħxejjex ippreservati; Ħxejjex tal-landa; Krema bbażata fuq il-ħaxix; Bżarijiet ippreservati; Fażola tas-soja (preservata) għall-ikel; Laħam immellaħ; Frott proċessat, fungi, ħxejjex ġewż u legumi; Spinaċi, iffriżati; Tnaqqir iffriżat magħmul l-aktar mit-tiġieġ; Tnaqqir iffriżat magħmul l-aktar mill-frott tal-baħar; L-ewwel platti ffriżati ppakkjati minn qabel magħmula l-aktar minn frott il-baħar; Ħambergers; Pulpetti tal-ħaxix; Bajd jew prodotti tal-bajd tal-għasafar; Ħalib; Leċitina għal skopijiet kulinarji; Marġerina; Krema [prodotti tal-ħalib]; Panna mħabbta; Jogurt; Żerriegħa li tittiekel; Żjut u xaħmijiet li jittieklu; Laħmijiet; Butir tal-karawett; Sopop u stokkijiet, estratti tal-laħam; Stokk; Brodu ħafif (Preparazzjonijiet għall-għamla ta' -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Vleesextracten; Visextracten; Groetenextracten voor voedingsdoeleinden; Extracten voor soepen; Soepconcentraten; Soepen (Ingeblikte -); Soeppoeder; Pasta voor soep; Geleien, jams, compotes en fruit- en groentesmeersels,; Champignons, geconserveerd; Geconserveerde tomaten; Artisjokken, geconserveerd; Erwten, geconserveerd; Geconserveerde groenten; Groenteconserven; Room op groentebasis; Geconserveerde paprika's; Sojabonen, geconserveerd, voor voedingsdoeleinden; Ingezouten voedingsmiddelen; Bewerkte vruchten, paddenstoelen, groenten, noten en peulvruchten; Spinazie, bevroren; Bevroren hapjes hoofdzakelijk op basis van kip; Bevroren hapjes hoofdzakelijk op basis van zeevruchten; Bevroren voorverpakte voorgerechten hoofdzakelijk op basis van zeevruchten; Hamburgers; Groenteburgers; Eieren en eierproducten; Melk; Lecithine voor gebruik tijdens het koken; Margarine; Room; Slagroom; Yoghurt; Eetbare zaden; Eetbare oliën en vetten; Vlees; Pindakaas; Soepen en bouillons, vleesextracten; Bouillon; Bouillonpreparaten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Ekstrakty mięsne; Ekstrakty z ryb; Ekstrakty z warzyw do konsumpcji; Ekstrakty do zup; Koncentraty zup; Zupy w puszkach; Zupy w proszku; Pasty do zup; Galaretki, dżemy, kompoty, pasty owocowe i warzywne; Grzyby konserwowane; Pomidory konserwowane; Karczochy konserwowe; Groszek konserwowy; Konserwowane warzywa; Warzywa w puszkach; Śmietana na bazie warzyw; Papryka konserwowana; Soja konserwowana spożywcza; Mięso solone; Przetworzone owoce, grzyby, warzywa, orzechy i nasiona roślin strączkowych; Szpinak, mrożony; Przystawki mrożone składające się głównie z kurczaka; Przystawki mrożone składające się głównie z owoców morza; Mrożone pakowane przystawki składające się głównie z owoców morza; Hamburgery; Burgery warzywne; Jaja ptasie i produkty z jaj; Mleko; Lecytyna do celów kulinarnych; Margaryna; Śmietana [produkty mleczarskie]; Bita śmietana; Jogurt; Nasiona jadalne; Oleje i tłuszcze jadalne; Mięso i wędliny; Masło arachidowe; Zupy i wywary, ekstrakty mięsne; Wywar, bulion; Bulion (Preparaty do produkcji -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Extratos de carne; Extratos de peixe; Extratos vegetais para uso alimentar; Extratos para sopas; Concentrados de sopas; Sopas em lata; Sopas em pó; Pastas para fazer sopa; Geleias, compotas, doces de frutos e legumes para barrar; Cogumelos em conserva; Conservas de tomate; Alcachofras em conserva; Ervilhas em conserva; Legumes em conserva; Legumes enlatados; Nata à base de vegetais; Pimentos conservados; Grãos de soja, em conserva, para a alimentação; Carnes salgadas; Frutos, fungos e vegetais processados (incluindo oleaginosas e leguminosas); Espinafres, congelados; Aperitivos congelados compostos principalmente de frango; Aperitivos congelados compostos principalmente de marisco; Pratos principais congelados pré-embalados compostos principalmente de marisco; Hambúrgueres; Hambúrgueres de legumes; Ovos de aves e produtos à base de ovo; Leite; Lecitina para fins culinários; Margarina; Nata [láctea]; Nata batida; Iogurte; Sementes comestíveis; Óleos e gorduras alimentares; Carnes; Manteiga de amendoim; Sopas e caldos, extratos de carne; Caldos; Preparações para fazer caldos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Extracte din carne; Extracte de peste; Extracte vegetale pentru alimente; Extracte pentru supe; Concentrate pentru supă; Supe la conservă; Prafuri pentru supe; Paste pentru supă; Jeleuri, dulcețuri, compoturi, paste de fructe și legume; Ciuperci conservate; Roșii conservate; Anghinare, conservate; Mazăre conservată; Conserve cu legume; Conserve de legume; Frișcă vegetală; Ardei conservati; Boabe de soia conservate, de uz alimentar; Carne sărată; Fructe, ciuperci, legume, nuci și leguminoase prelucrate; Spanac, congelat; Aperitive congelate constând în principal din carne de pui; Aperitive congelate constând în principal din fructe de mare; Aperitive congelate preambalate constând în principal din fructe de mare; Hamburgeri; Burgeri din legume; Ouă și produse din ouă; Lapte; Lecitină pentru uz culinar; Margarină; Smântână [produse lactate]; Frișcă; Iaurt; Semințe comestibile; Uleiuri și grăsimi comestibile; Carne; Unt de arahide; Supe și baze de supă, extracte din carne; Supe, bulion; Bulion (preparate pentru obținerea -lui).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Mäsové výťažky; Výťažky z rýb; Jedlé zeleninové výťažky; Výťažky na použitie do polievok; Polievkové koncentráty; Konzervované polievky; Instantná polievka; Polievkové pasty; Ovocné želatíny, lekváre, kompóty, ovocné a zeleninové nátierky; Konzervované šampiňóny; Konzervované paradajky; Konzervované artičoky; Konzervovaný hrach; Konzervovaná zelenina; Konzervy so zeleninou; Rastlinná smotana; Konzervovaná paprika; Konzervované sójové bôby (potraviny); Solené potraviny; Spracované ovocie, huby, zelenina, orechy a strukoviny; Špenát, mrazený; Mrazené predjedlá obsahujúce prevažne kuracie mäso; Mrazené predjedlá obsahujúce prevažne morské plody; Mrazené vopred balené predjedlá pozostávajúce predovšetkým z morských plodov; Hamburgery; Zeleninové fašírky; Konzumné vtáčie vajcia a výrobky z nich; Mlieko; Lecitín na prípravu jedál; Margarín; Smotana (mliečne výrobky); Šľahačka; Jogurt; Jedlé semená; Jedlé oleje a tuky; Mäso; Arašidové maslo; Polievky, vývary, bujóny, mäsové výťažky; Vývary (bujóny); Prípravky na vývary (bujóny).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Mesni ekstrakti; Ribji ekstrakti; Rastlinski izvlečki za prehrano; Jušni ekstrakti; Jušni koncentrati; Juhe v konzervi; Mešanice v prahu za juho; Pripravki za juho; Želeji, džemi, kompoti, sadni in zelenjavni namazi; Konzervirane gobe; Konzerviran paradižnik; Artičoke, konzervirane; Grah, konzerviran; Zelenjava, konzervirana; Zelenjava v konzervah; Rastlinske smetane; Konzervirane paprike; Konzervirana sojina zrna za prehrano; Meso v razsolu; Predelano sadje, gobe, zelenjava, oreščki in stročnice; Zamrznjena špinača; Zamrznjene predjedi, ki so sestavljene predvsem iz piščanca; Zamrznjene predjedi, ki so sestavljene predvsem iz morskih sadežev; Zamrznjene pakirane predjedi, ki so sestavljene predvsem iz morskih sadežev; Hamburgerji; Zelenjavni burgerji; Ptičja jajca in jajčni proizvodi; Mleko; Lecitin za kuhanje; Margarina; Smetana [mlečni proizvodi]; Stepena smetana; Jogurt; Jedilna semena; Jedilno olje in maščoba; Meso; Arašidovo (kikirikijevo) maslo; Juhe in jušne osnove, mesni ekstrakti; Jušna osnova; Preparati za pripravo mesne juhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Köttextrakt; Fiskextrakt; Grönsaksextrakt för livsmedelsändamål; Extrakt för soppor; Soppkoncentrat; Konserverade soppor; Soppulver; Pastor för soppor; Geléer, sylter, kompotter, bredbara pålägg av frukter och grönsaker; Konserverad svamp; Konserverade tomater; Kronärtskockor, konserverade; Konserverade ärter; Konserverade grönsaker; Grönsakskonserver; Vegetabilisk grädde; Konserverade paprikor; Sojabönor som livsmedelskonserver; Saltat kött; Behandlade frukter, svampar, grönsaker, nötter och baljfrukter; Spenat, frusen; Frusna aptitretare huvudsakligen bestående av kyckling; Frusna aptitretare huvudsakligen bestående av fisk och skaldjur; Frusna förpaketerade förrätter i huvudsak bestående av fisk och skaldjur; Hamburgare (biffar); Grönsaksburgare; Fågelägg och äggprodukter; Mjölk; Lektin (matlagning); Margarin; Grädde; Vispad grädde; Surmjölk; Ätliga frön; Ätliga oljor och fetter; Kött; Jordnötssmör; Soppor och buljonger, köttextrakt; Buljonger; Buljongpreparat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>30</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Кафе, чай и какао и техни заместители; Ориз; Тапиока; Саго; Брашно; Зеленчуково брашно; Брашно от зърнени култури; Прясна паста; Сушени тестени изделия; Преподготвени продукти от зърнени растения; Готови ястия на основата на ориз; Смес от зърнени продукти, ядки, сухи плодове [мюсли]; Снаксови храни на зърнена основа; Крекери [тънки, сухи бисквити]; Оризови бисквити; Хляб; Петифури [пасти, торти, кексове и др.]; Овкусени сладки; Таблетки (сладкарски изделия); Бонбони; Сладолед; Захар; Мед; Меласи; Мая и закваски; Сол; Горчица; Оцет; Сосове [подправки за ястия]; Сосове за използване с макаронени изделия; Препарати за приготвяне на сосове; Пикантни подправки; Лед [замразена вода].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Káva, čaj, kakao a jejich náhražky; Rýže; Tapioka; Ságo; Mouka; Rostlinná mouka; Obilná mouka; Čerstvé těstoviny; Sušené těstoviny; Přípravky vyrobené z obilnin; Hotová jídla na bázi rýže; Müsli; Svačinové občerstvení na bázi cereálií; Krekry; Rýžové sušenky; Chléb; Minizákusky [dortíky]; Slané pečivo; Tablet (skotská cukrovinka); Cukrovinky; Zmrzlina; Cukr; Med; Zlatý sirup; Droždí a přípravky na kynutí potravin; Sůl; Hořčice; Ocet; Omáčky [dochucovadla]; Omáčky na těstoviny; Přípravky k výrobě omáček; Koření; Led [zmrazená voda].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kaffe, te, kakao og erstatninger herfor; Ris; Tapioka; Sago; Mel; Grøntsagsmel; Mel af korn; Frisk pasta (makaroni og lignende); Tørret pasta; Præparater lavet af kornsorter; Færdigretter fremstillet på basis af ris; Müsli; Kornbaserede snacks; Kiks; Riskiks; Brød; Petits-four; Konditorivarer med krydret smag; Tablet (skotske konfekturevarer); Konfekturevarer; Iscreme; Sukker; Honning; Lys sirup; Gær og hævemidler; Salt; Sennep; Eddike; Kryddersaucer; Pasta sauce; Præparater til fremstilling af saucer; Urter [tørrede krydderier]; Råis [frossen vand].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kaffee, Tee, Kakao und Ersatzstoffe hierfür; Reis; Tapioka; Sago; Mehl; Gemüsemehl; Getreidemehl; Frische Teigwaren; Getrocknete Nudeln; Getreidezubereitungen; Fertiggerichte auf Reisbasis; Müsli; Getreidesnacks; Kräcker [Gebäck]; Reisplätzchen; Brot; Petits Fours; Pikantes Gebäck; Lutschtabletten [Süßwaren]; Zuckerwaren, Konfekt; Eiscreme; Zucker; Honig; Sirup; Hefe und Treibmittel; Salz; Senf; Essig; Soßen [Würzen]; Pastasauce; Präparate für die Zubereitung von Bratensoßen; Gewürze; Eis [gefrorenes Wasser].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καφές, τσάι και κακάο και υποκατάστατα αυτών· Ρύζι· Ταπιόκα· Σαγού· Αλεύρι· Άλευρα λαχανικών· Αλεύρι δημητριακών· Νωπά ζυμαρικά· Αποξηραμένα ζυμαρικά· Παρασκευάσματα φτιαγμένα από δημητριακά· Έτοιμα γεύματα με βάση το ρύζι· Μούσλι· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) με βάση τα δημητριακά· Κράκερ· Ρυζιού κέικ· Άρτος· Πτιφούρ [είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής]· Αλμυρά πιτοειδή· Ημίσκληρα γλυκίσματα από καραμελωμένη ζάχαρη, γάλα και βούτυρο (τάμπλετ)· Ζαχαρώδη· Παγωτά και κρέμα παγωτό· Ζάχαρη· Μέλι· Σιρόπια και μελάσες· Μαγιά και προζύμι· Αλάτι· Μουστάρδα [σινάπι]· Ξύδι· Σάλτσες [καρυκεύματα]· Σάλτσες για ζυμαρικά· Παρασκευάσματα για σάλτσες γκρέιβι· Μαγειρικά βότανα, μπαχαρικά· Πάγος [παγωμένο νερό].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Coffee, teas and cocoa and substitutes therefor; Rice; Tapioca; Sago; Flour; Vegetable flour; Cereal flour; Fresh pasta; Dried pasta; Preparations made from cereals; Rice-based prepared meals; Muesli; Cereal-based snack food; Crackers; Rice biscuits; Bread; Petits fours [cakes]; Savory pastries; Tablet (confectionary); Confectionery; Ice cream; Sugar; Honey; Treacle; Yeast and leavening agents; Salt; Mustard; Vinegar; Sauces [condiments]; Pasta sauce; Preparations for making up into sauces; Spices; Ice [frozen water].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Café, té, cacao y sucedáneos de los mismos; Arroz; Tapioca; Sagú; Harinas; Harina de verduras; Harina de cereales; Pasta fresca; Pasta seca; Preparados a base de cereales; Comidas preparadas a base de arroz; Muesli; Refrigerios a base de cereales; Galletas saladas [crackers]; Galletas de arroz; Pan; Pastelitos dulces y salados [productos de pastelería]; Pasteles salados; Tabletas (confitería); Productos de confitería; Helados cremosos; Azúcar; Miel; Jarabe de melaza; Levadura y otros agentes fermentadores; Sal; Mostaza; Vinagres; Salsas [condimentos]; Salsas para pastas alimenticias; Preparados para hacer salsas; Especias; Hielo [agua congelada].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kohv, tee ja kakao ning nende aseained; Riis; Tapiokk, maniokitärklis; Saago, saagotangud; Jahu; Aedviljajahu; Teraviljajahu; Värsked makarontooted; Kuivatatud makarontooted; Teraviljadest valmissegud; Riisipõhised valmistoidud; Müsli; Teraviljast valmistatud suupisted; Küpsised, kuivikud; Riisiküpsised; Leib, sai; Väikesed kondiitrikoogid; Soolased kondiitritooted; Šoti iiris (tablet); Maiustused; Koore- või piimajäätis; Suhkur; Mesi; Kuldsiirup, melass; Pärm ja teised kergitusained; Sool; Sinep; Äädikas; Maitsekastmed; Pastakastmed; Kastmevalmistusained; Vürtsid; Jää [külmutatud vesi].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kahvi, tee ja kaakao ja niiden korvikkeet; Riisi; Tapioka; Saagosuurimot; Jauhot; Kasvisjauho; Viljasta jauhetut jauhot; Tuorepastat; Kuivatut pastaruoat; Viljoista valmistetut tuotteet; Riisipohjaiset valmisateriat; Mysli; Viljapohjainen pikaruoka; Voileipäkeksit; Riisikeksit; Leipä; Leivät (Pikku -); Suolaiset leivonnaiset; Tabletit (makeiset); Sokerimakeiset; Jäätelöt; Sokeri; Hunaja; Siirapit ja melassit; Hiiva ja nostatusaineet; Suola; Sinappi; Etikka; Kastikkeet (Mauste -); Pastakastikkeet; Kastikkeiden valmistusaineet; Maustesekoitukset; Jää [jäädytetty vesi].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Café, thés, cacao et leurs succédanés; Riz; Tapioca; Sagou; Farine; Farine de légumes; Farine de céréales; Pâtes fraîches; Pâtes sèches; Préparations à base de céréales; Repas préparés à base de riz; Muesli; En-cas à base de céréales; Crackers; Biscuits de riz; Pain; Petits fours [pâtisserie]; Pâtisseries salées; Confiseries écossaises à base de fondant et de beurre [tablets]; Confiserie; Crèmes glacées; Sucre; Miel; Sirop de mélasse; Levures et agents levants; Sel; Moutarde; Vinaigres; Sauces [condiments]; Sauces pour pâtes alimentaires; Préparations pour faire des sauces; Épices; Glace à rafraîchir [eau congelée].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kava, čajevi, kakao i njihovi nadomjesci; Riža; Tapioka; Sago [škrob iz jezgre palme sago]; Brašno; Biljno brašno; Brašno od žitarica; Svježa tjestenina; Sušena tjestenina; Pripravci od žitarica; Gotova jela s rižom; Musli; Grickalice na bazi žitarica; Krekeri; Keksi od riže; Kruh; Minjoni; Slani pekarski proizvodi; Škotske slastice [u obliku tablica]; Slastice; Sladoledi i mliječni sladoledi; Šećer; Med; Sirupi i melase; Kvasac i tvari za dizanje tijesta; Sol; Slačica [senf]; Ocat; Umaci (začinski); Umaci za tjesteninu; Pripravci za pravljenje umaka; Mirodije; Led [smrznuta voda].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kávé, tea, kakaó és helyettesítőik; Rizs; Tápióka; Szágó; Liszt; Zöldségliszt; Gabonaliszt; Friss tészta; Száraztészták; Gabonafélékből előállított készítmények; Rizsalapú előkészített ételek; Müzli; Snack ételek (Gabona alapú -); Kekszek, rágcsálnivalók; Puffasztott rizs szelet; Kenyér; Petits fours [sütemény]; Sós sütemények; Táblás édességek; Kandiscukor; Fagylaltok és jégkrémek; Cukor; Méz; Melaszszirup; Élesztő, élesztőszerek; Só; Mustár; Ecet; Szószok [ízesítőszerek, fűszeres mártások]; Tésztaöntetek; Készítmények mártások előállításához; Fűszerek; Jég [fagyott víz].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Caffè, tè e cacao e loro succedanei; riso; Tapioca; sago; Farine alimentari; Farine vegetali; Farina di cereali; Pasta fresca; Pasta secca; Preparati a base di cereali; Pasti preparati a base di riso; muesli; Snack a base di cereali; Crackers; Biscotti di riso; Pane; Pasticcini [pasticceria]; Pasticceria salata; Tavolette [pasticceria]; confetteria; gelati; zucchero; miele; sciroppo di melassa; Lievito e agenti lievitanti; sale; senape; aceto; salse [condimenti]; Sughi per pasta; Preparati per sughi; spezie; ghiaccio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kava, arbata ir kakava bei jų pakaitalai; Ryžiai; Tapijoka; Sago kruopos; Miltai; Daržovių miltai; Javų miltai; Švieži makaronai; Džiovinti makaronai; Grūdų ruošiniai; Paruošti patiekalai ryžių pagrindu; Javainiai (dribsniai su priedais); Javiniai užkandžiai; Krekeriai [užkandžių sausainiai]; Ryžių sausainiai; Duona; Pyragaičiai su įdaru; Sūrūs kepiniai; Škotiški saldumynai (tablet); Konditerijos gaminiai; Ledai; Cukrus; Medus; Melasos sirupas; Mielės, raugai ir fermentavimo medžiagos; Druska; Garstyčios; Actas; Padažai [uždarai]; Makaronų gaminių padažas; Ruošiniai padažų gamybai; Prieskoniai [aštrieji]; Ledas [užšaldytas vanduo].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kafija, tēja, kakao un to aizstājēji; Rīsi; Tapioka; Sāgo; Milti; Dārzeņu milti; Labības milti; Svaigi makaroni; Kaltētu makaronu izstrādājumi; Graudaugu izstrādājumi; No rīsiem pagatavoti ēdieni; Musli; Uzkodas, kas pamatā sastāv no graudaugiem; Krekeri; Rīsu cepumi; Maize; Mazās kūciņas (petits fours); Sāļie maizes konditorejas izstrādājumi; Tabletes (konditorejas izstrādājumi); Konditorejas izstrādājumi; Saldējums; Cukurs; Medus; Melase; Raugs un ieraugi; Sāls; Sinepes; Etiķis; Garšvielu mērces; Pastas (makaronu izstrādājumu vai ēdienu) mērces; Mērču sagataves; Aromātiskās garšvielas; Ledus (sasaldēts ūdens).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kafè, te u kawkaw u sostituti tagħhom; Ross; Tapjoka; Sagu; Dqiq; Dqiq tal-ħaxix; Dqiq taċ-ċereali; Għaġin frisk; Għaġin imnixxef; Preparazzjonijiet magħmulin minn ċereali; Ikliet lesti bbażati fuq ir-ross; Muesli [Taħlita ta ċereali mhux misjura ma' ġewż u frott niexef]; Ikel ħafif magħmul miċ-ċereali; Kràkers; Gallettini tar-ross; Ħobż; Petits fours (kejkijiet żgħar); Ikel tal-għaġina [mhux tal-ħelu]; Ħelu Skoċċiż ibbażat fuq butir u ħalib [tablet]; Ħelu; Ġelati; Zokkor; Għasel; Xiropp u għasel iswed; Ħmira u materjal tat-teħmir; Melħ; Mustarda; Ħall; Zlazi [kondimenti]; Zlazi għall-użu mal-għaġin; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tħejjija tal-grejvi; Ħwawar; Silġ [ilma ffriżat].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Koffie, thee en cacao en vervangingsmiddelen hiervoor; Rijst; Tapioca; Sago; Meel; Groentemeel; Granenbloem; Deegwaren (Verse -); Deegwaren (Gedroogde -); Producten gemaakt van granen; Bereide maaltijden op basis van rijst; Muesli; Versnaperingen op basis van granen; Crackers; Rijstkoekjes; Brood; Petit-fours; Hartig gebak; Reep (zoetwaren); Suikergoed; Roomijs; Suiker; Honing; Melassestroop; Gist en rijsmiddelen; Zout; Mosterd; Azijn; Kruidensausen; Pastasaus; Preparaten voor het bereiden van jus; Specerijen; IJs [bevroren water].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kawa, herbata, kakao i namiastki tych towarów; Ryż; Tapioka; Sago; Mąka; Mąka roślinna; Mąka zbożowe; Świeży makaron; Suszony makaron; Preparaty zbożowe; Gotowe potrawy na bazie ryżu; Muesli; Przekąski na bazie zbóż; Krakersy; Ciasteczka ryżowe; Chleb; Ptifurki [ciasteczka]; Solone wyroby piekarnicze; Tabletki [wyroby cukiernicze]; Wyroby cukiernicze; Lody; Cukier; Miód; Melasa; Drożdze i zaczyny; Sól; Musztarda; Ocet; Sosy [przyprawy]; Sosy do makaronów; Preparaty do sporządzania sosów; Przyprawy korzenne; Lód [zamarznięta woda].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Café, chás e cacau e substitutos dos mesmos; Arroz; Tapioca; Sagú; Farinhas alimentares; Farinha vegetal; Farinha de cereais; Massa fresca; Massa alimentar seca; Preparações à base de cereais; Refeições preparadas à base de arroz; Muesli; Snacks à base de cereais; Bolachas de água e sal; Bolachas de arroz; Pão; Petits four [pastelaria]; Pastelaria salgada; Tabletes (produtos de confeitaria); Confeitaria; Gelados [sorvetes]; Açúcar; Mel; Xarope de melaço; Fermento e agentes de levedura; Sal; Mostarda; Vinagres; Molhos [condimentos]; Molhos para massas alimentícias; Preparações para a confeção de molhos; Especiarias; Gelo [água congelada].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cafea, ceaiuri, cacao și înlocuitori ai acestora; Orez; Tapioca; Sago; Făină; Făină vegetală; Făină de cereale; Paste alimentare proaspete; Paste uscate; Preparate pe bază de cereale; Mâncăruri preparate pe bază de orez; Müsli; Gustări pe bază de cereale; Biscuiți sărați; Biscuiți de orez; Pâine; Prăjiturici uscate [patiserie]; Produse de patiserie aromate; Tablete (dulciuri); Dulciuri; Înghețată; Zahăr; Miere; Siropuri și melasă; Drojdie și agenți de dospire; Sare; Muștar; Oțet; Sosuri [condimente]; Sos pentru paste; Preparate pentru obținerea sosurilor; Mirodenii; Gheață [apă congelată].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Káva, čaj, kakao a ich náhradky; Ryža; Tapioka; Ságo; Múka; Rastlinná múka; Obilná múka; Čerstvé cestoviny; Sušené cestoviny; Prípravky vyrobené z obilnín; Hotové jedlá z ryže; Müsli; Obilninové chuťovky; Slané pečivo (krekery); Ryžové sušienky; Chlieb; Keksy; Lahôdkové pečivo; Tablet [polotvrdá škótska cukrovinka]; Cukrovinky; Smotanové zmrzliny; Cukor; Med; Melasový sirup; Droždie a kypriace prípravky; Soľ; Horčica; Ocot; Omáčky (chuťové prísady); Omáčky na cestoviny; Prípravky na prípravu omáčok; Korenie; Ľad [zmrazená voda].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kava, čaji in kakav ter nadomestki naštetega; Riž; Tapioka; Sago (škrobna moka iz stržena sagove palme); Moka; Rastlinska moka; Žitna moka; Sveže testenine; Sušene testenine; Pripravki, narejeni iz žitaric; Jedi na osnovi riža, pripravljene na uživanje; Müsli; Prigrizki iz žitaric; Krekerji; Riževi piškoti; Kruh; Slaščice [tortni kolački]; Pikantno pecivo; Slaščice v obliki rezin; Slaščice; Mlečni sladoled; Sladkor; Med; Sirupi, melasni sirupi; Kvas in sredstva za vzhajanje; Sol; Gorčica; Kis; Omake [začimbe]; Omake za testenine; Pripravki za pripravo omak; Dišave, začimbe (rastlinskega izvora, največkrat v prahu); Led [zamrznjena voda].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kaffe, te och kakao och ersättningar därtill; Ris; Tapioka; Sagogryn; Mjöl; Vegetabiliskt mjöl; Mjöl av brödsäd; Färsk pasta; Torkad pasta; Preparat tillverkade av säd; Risbaserade tillagade måltider; Müsli; Sädesbaserade tilltugg; Crackers (smörgåskex); Kakor av ris; Bröd; Petits fours [bakverk]; Kryddade bakverk; Tablett [konfektyrer]; Konfektyrer; Glass; Socker; Honung; Sirap; Jäst och jäsningsmedel; Salt; Senap; Vinäger; Såser [smaktillsatser]; Såser för användning med pasta; Tillredningar för framställning av såser; Kryddor; Is [fruset vatten].</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Търговия на храни на дребно; Услуги за търговия на дребно чрез поръчки по пощата във връзка с хранителни продукти; Услуги за каталожна търговия на дребно във връзка с храни; Услуги за бизнес управление, свързани с електронна търговия; Рекламиране на стоки и услуги на други чрез интернет; Съдействие при представяне на нови продукти в рамките на договор за франчайзинг.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Maloobchodní služby vztahující se k potravinám; Maloobchodní zásilkové služby týkající se potravin; Maloobchodní služby týkající se potravin poskytované prostřednictvím katalogů; Služby řízení obchodní činnosti v oblasti elektronického obchodování; Propagace zboží a služeb pro třetí osoby prostřednictvím internetu; Pomoc při komercializaci zboží v rámci frančízových smluv.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Detailhandel i forbindelse med fødevarer; Detailhandel via postordre med fødevarer; Detailhandel via kataloger med fødevarer; Forretningsledelse i forbindelse med elektronisk handel; Markedsføring af produkter og tjenesteydelser for andre på internettet; Bistand ved produktkommercialisering inden for rammerne af en franchisekontrakt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Lebensmittel; Versandhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Lebensmittel; Katalogversandhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Lebensmittel; Geschäftsführung in Bezug auf elektronischen Handel; Werbepräsentation von Waren und Dienstleistungen anderer im Internet; Hilfe bei der Verkaufsförderung [Merchandising] für Produkte im Rahmen eines Franchisevertrags.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με τρόφιμα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης μέσω ταχυδρομικών παραγγελιών σε σχέση με τρόφιμα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης μέσω καταλόγων σε σχέση με τρόφιμα· Υπηρεσίες διοίκησης επιχειρήσεων σε σχέση με το ηλεκτρονικό εμπόριο· Προώθηση των αγαθών και υπηρεσιών άλλων μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Παροχή βοήθειας στον τομέα της εμπορίας προϊόντων, στο πλαίσιο μιας σύμβασης δικαιόχρησης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Retail services relating to food; Mail order retail services related to foodstuffs; Retail services via catalogues related to foodstuffs; Business management services relating to electronic commerce; Promoting the goods and services of others over the Internet; Assistance in product commercialization, within the framework of a franchise contract.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de ventas al por menor relacionados con alimentos; Servicios de venta minorista mediante pedidos por correo relacionados con productos alimentarios; Servicios de venta minorista mediante catálogos relacionados con productos alimentarios; Servicios de gestión comercial relacionados con el comercio electrónico; Promoción de productos y servicios de terceros por Internet; Asistencia de comercialización de productos en el marco de un contrato de franquicia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Toiduainete jaemüügiteenused; Toiduainete postimüügiteenused; Jaemüügiteenused toiduainekataloogide vahendusel; Elektronkaubanduse ärijuhtimisteenused; Kolmandate isikute kaupade ja teenuste müügiedendus Interneti kaudu; Toodete turustamise teenused frantsiisilepingu alusel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Elintarvikkeiden vähittäismyyntipalvelut; Elintarvikkeisiin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut postimyynnin välityksellä; Elintarvikkeiden vähittäismyyntipalvelut luetteloiden avulla; Elektroniseen kaupankäyntiin liittyvät liiketoiminnalliset hallintapalvelut; Muiden tarjoamien tavaroiden ja palveluiden myynninedistäminen Internetissä; Tuotteen kaupallistamisessa avustaminen franchising-sopimuksella.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de vente au détail d'aliments; Services de commande au détail par correspondance concernant des produits alimenaires; Services de vente au détail par le biais de catalogues liés aux produits alimentaires; Services de gestion commerciale liés au commerce électronique; Services de promotion des produits et services de tiers par Internet; Assistance en commercialisation de produits dans le cadre d'un contrat de franchise.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Maloprodajne usluge u svezi hrane; Maloprodajne usluge putem naručivanja poštom u vezi s prehrambenim proizvodima; Maloprodajne usluge putem kataloga u vezi s prehrambenim proizvodima; Usluge poslovnog upravljanja u vezi s elektroničkom trgovinom; Promocija robe i usluga drugih putem Interneta; Podrška za komercijalizaciju proizvoda unutar okvira ugovora o franšizingu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Élelmiszerekkel kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Élelmiszerek postai rendelésével kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Katalógusokon keresztül nyújtott, élelmiszerekkel kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Üzletvezetési szolgáltatások az elektronikus kereskedelemmel kapcsolatban; Harmadik személyek termékeinek és szolgáltatásainak Interneten való reklámozása; Termékek forgalmazásával kapcsolatos segítségnyújtás, franchise-szerződés keretein belül.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di vendita al dettaglio di prodotti alimentari; Vendita al dettaglio per corrispondenza di prodotti alimentari; Vendita al dettaglio tramite catalogo di prodotti alimentari; Gestione aziendale in materia di commercio elettronico; Promozione di prodotti e servizi per conto terzi tramite internet; Assistenza nella commercializzazione di prodotti nell'ambito di un contratto di franchising.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Mažmeninė prekyba maisto prekėmis; Mažmeninė prekyba maisto produktais, užsakant paštu; Mažmeninė prekyba maisto produktais per katalogus; Elektroninės prekybos verslo vadyba; Kitų tiekėjų prekių ir paslaugų reklamavimas internete; Produkto komercializacijos pagalba pagal franšizės sutartį.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pārtikas mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi; Mazumtirdzniecības paklapojumi, izmantojot pasta sūtījumus, saistībā ar pārtikas produktiem; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, izmantojot katalogu, saistībā ar pārtikas produktiem; Uzņēmējdarbības vadības pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar elektronisko tirdzniecību; Preču un pakalpojumu veicināšana internetā citiem; Palīdzība produktu tirdzniecībā franšīzes līguma ietvaros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' bejgħ relatat mal-ikel; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut ta' ordnijiet bil-posta relatati ma' oġġetti tal-ikel; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut permezz ta' katalgi relatati ma' prodotti tal-ikel; Servizzi ta' ġestjoni tan-negozju relatati mal-kummerċ elettroniku; Il-promozzjoni ta' oġġetti u servizzi ta' oħrajn fuq l-Internet; Għajnuna fil-kummerċjalizzazzjoni ta' prodotti, fil-qafas ta' kuntratt ta' frankiġja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Detailhandel op het gebied van voedingsmiddelen; Detailhandel met behulp van postorderdiensten op het gebied van voedingsmiddelen; Detailhandelsdiensten met behulp van catalogi op het gebied van voedingsmiddelen; Commercieel-zakelijk beheer met betrekking tot e-commerce; Promoten van goederen en diensten van anderen op het internet; Ondersteuning bij productcommercialisering in het kader van een franchisecontract.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi handlu detalicznego w zakresie żywności; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej za zamówieniem pocztowym związane z artykułami spożywczymi; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej za pomocą katalogów w związku z artykułami spożywczymi; Usługi zarządzania działalnością gospodarczą dotyczące handlu elektronicznego; Promowanie towarów i usług osób trzecich w Internecie; Pomoc w komercjalizacji produktu w ramach kontraktu franczyzowego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de venda a retalho relacionados com alimentos; Serviços de venda retalhista através de encomenda por correspondência relacionados com produtos alimentares; Serviços de venda retalhista por catálogo relacionados com produtos alimentares; Serviços de gestão de negócios comerciais relacionados com comércio eletrónico; Promoção de produtos e serviços de terceiros através da Internet; Assistência na comercialização de produtos, no âmbito de um contrato de franchising.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul în domeniul alimentației; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul prin corespondență în legătură cu produse alimentare; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul prin catalog în legătură cu produse alimentare; Servicii de gestionare a afacerilor în legătură cu comerțul electronic; Promovarea produselor și serviciilor altor persoane prin internet; Asistență privind comercializarea produselor, în cadrul unui contract de franciză.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Maloobchodné služby spojené s predajom potravín; Maloobchodné zásielkové služby týkajúce sa potravín; Služby maloobchodného predaja potravín prostredníctvom katalógov; Služby podnikového manažmentu týkajúce sa elektronického obchodu; Propagovanie tovaru a služieb klientov prostredníctvom internetu; Pomoc pri komercializácii výrobku v rámci franšíznej zmluvy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Maloprodajne storitve v zvezi s hrano; Maloprodajne storitve z naročilom po pošti, povezane s prehrambenimi izdelki; Maloprodajne storitve prek katalogov v zvezi s prehrambenimi proizvodi; Storitve poslovnega vodenja v zvezi z elektronskim poslovanjem; Promocija blaga in storitev drugih na internetu; Pomoč pri komercializaciji izdelkov v okviru franšiznih pogodb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Återförsäljning avseende mat; Återförsäljning via postorder avseende livsmedel; Detaljhandel via kataloger avseende livsmedel; Företagsledningstjänster avseende e-handel; Reklam för varor och tjänster via internet åt andra; Assistans vid kommersialisering av produkter inom ramen för ett franchisekontrakt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080347</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>75342</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003126391</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-07-20</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>it</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>IT</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>2011901985407</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2011-10-07</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>0001486663</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2012-04-19</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Other</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>NUTRIVA</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>486486</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>14805</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
