<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-05T16:31:38</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226504</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226504</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-31</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>WEGOLIMME</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162314838</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226504/000162314838.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>02.01.91</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.03.02</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Гимнастически и спортни артикули; Уреди за фитнес упражнения; Играчки за домашни любимци; Скейтборд; Стягащи слипове за спортисти [спортни артикули]; Алпинистки колани, ремъци; Жироскопи и стабилизатори за модели на летателни апарати; Въжета за скачане; Машини за степ аеробика; Батути; Ролери; Спортна оборудване; Предпазители за тялото за спортни цели; Рибарско оборудване; Въдичарски пръти; Уреди за трениране на тялото; Главоблъсканици [игри]; Електронни играчки; Украшения за коледни елхи; Играчки маски; Батути.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Gymnastické a sportovní zboží; Přístroje na tělesná cvičení; Hračky pro domácí zvířata; Skateboardy; Sportovní suspenzory pro muže [sportovní výstroj]; Horolezecké úvazky; Gyroskopy a stabilizátory letu do modelů letadel; Švihadla; Steppery na aerobik; Trampolíny; In-line kolečkové brusle; Sportovní vybavení; Chrániče těla pro sportovní účely; Rybářské náčiní; Rybářské pruty; Posilovací stroje; Skládačky; Elektronické hračky; Vánoční ozdoby; Masky [na hraní]; Mini trampolíny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Gymnastik- og sportsartikler; Maskiner til legemsøvelser; Legetøj til kæledyr; Skateboards; Skridtbind til mænd [sportsartikler]; Klatreseler til bjergbestigning; Gyroskoper og flystabilisatorer til modelfly; Sjippetov; Aerobic-stepmaskiner; Trampoliner; In-line rulleskøjter; Sportsudstyr; Kropsbeskyttere til sportsbrug; Fiskegrej; Fiskestænger; Apparater til bodybuilding; Puslespil; Elektronisk legetøj; Juletræspynt; Masker [lejetøj]; Minitrampoliner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Turn- und Sportartikel; Geräte für Körperübungen; Spielzeug für Haustiere; Skateboards; Tiefschutz-Suspensorien [Sportartikel]; Klettergurte [Sportartikel]; Gyroskope und Flugstabilisatoren für Modellflugzeuge; Springseile; Aerobic-Stepper; Trampoline; Rollschuhe, In-line Skates; Sportgeräte; Körperschutzausstattung für Sportler; Angelgeräte; Angeln; Bodybuilding-Geräte; Puzzles; Elektronisches Spielzeug; Christbaumschmuck; Masken [Spielzeug]; Minitrampoline.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Είδη γυμναστικής και αθλητισμού· Συσκευές άσκησης και γυμναστικής· Παιχνίδια για κατοικίδια ζώα· Σανίδες του σκέιτμπορντ· Προστατευτικές περισκελίδες για άνδρες αθλητές [αθλητικά είδη]· Αναρρίχησης αορτήρες· Γυροσκόπια και σταθεροποιητές πτήσης για μοντέλα αεροσκαφών· Σχοινάκια για υπερπηδήσεις· Συσκευές στεπ για ασκήσεις αεροβικής· Τραμπολίνα· Πατίνια με ροδάκια γραμμής· Αθλητικός εξοπλισμός· Προστατευτικά σώματος για αθλητική χρήση· Είδη ψαρέματος· Καλάμια αλιείας· Αποκατάστασης σώματος συσκευές· Παζλ· Ηλεκτρονικά ατομικά παιχνίδια· Διακοσμητικά χριστουγεννιάτικων δέντρων· Μάσκες παιχνιδιού· Μίνι τραμπολίνα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Gymnastic and sporting articles; machines for physical exercises; toys for pets; skateboards; men's athletic supporters [sports articles]; climbers' harness; gyroscopes and flight stabilizers for model aircraft; skipping ropes; aerobic step machines; trampolines; in-line roller skates; sports equipment; body protectors for sports use; fishing tackle; rods for fishing; body-building apparatus; puzzles; electronic toys; decorations for Christmas trees; masks [playthings]; Trampettes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Artículos de deporte y gimnasia; Aparatos para ejercicios físicos; Juguetes para animales de compañía; Monopatines; Suspensorios para deportistas; Arneses de escalada; Giroscopios y estabilizadores de vuelo para modelos a escala de aeronaves; Cuerdas para saltar a la comba; Aparatos de aeróbic con escalones; Camas elásticas; Patines en línea; Equipamientos deportivos; Equipos de protección corporal para deportes; Aparejos de pesca; Cañas de pescar; Aparatos de culturismo; Juegos de ingenio; Juguetes electrónicos; Adornos para árboles de Navidad; Máscaras [juguetes]; Minitrampolines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Võimlemis- ja sportimistarbed; Jõuharjutuste seadmed; Lemmikloomade mänguasjad; Rulad; Meeste kehakaitsmed [sporditarbed]; Mägironijate rihmad; Mudelõhusõidukite güroskoobid ja lennustabilisaatorid; Hüppenöörid; Aeroobikas kasutatavad astumisseadmed; Batuudid; Ühe rattareaga rulluisud; Spordiriistad; Kehakaitsmed spordis kasutamiseks; Kalastustarbed; Õngeridvad; Füüsilise vormi parandamise/taastamise seadmed; Pusled; Elektroonilised mänguasjad; Jõulukuuseehted; Maskid (mänguasjad); Väiksed trampliinid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Voimistelu- ja urheiluvälineet; Kuntosalilaitteet; Lelut lemmikkieläimille; Rullalaudat; Miesten intiimisuojukset [urheilutarvikkeina]; Kiipeilyvaljaat; Lentokoneiden pienoismallien gyroskoopit ja lennonvakaimet; Hyppynarut; Aerobic-askelluskoneet; Trampoliinit; In-line-rullaluistimet; Urheiluvarusteet; Vartalosuojukset urheilukäyttöön; Kalastusvälineet; Onkivavat; Kehonrakennusvälineet; Pulmapelit; Elektroniset lelut; Joulukuusenkoristeet; Leikkinaamarit; Minitrampoliinit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Articles de gymnastique et de sport; Engins pour exercices corporels; Jouets pour animaux de compagnie; Planches à roulettes; Slips de soutien pour sportifs [articles de sport]; Baudriers d'escalade; Gyroscopes et stabilisateurs de vol pour modèles réduits d'aéronefs; Cordes à sauter; Appareils d'aérobic avec marches [step]; Trampolines; Patins à roulettes en ligne; Équipements de sport; Équipements de protection corporelle pour le sport; Attirail de pêche; Cannes à pêche; Appareils pour le culturisme; Casse-tête [jeux]; Jouets électroniques; Décorations pour sapins de Noël; Masques [jouets]; Petits trampolines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Gimnastička i sportska oprema; Aparati za tjelovježbu; Igračke za ljubimce; Daska za koturanje; Muški atletski štitnici [sportska oprema]; Remeni za penjanje; Žiroskopi i stabilizatori za makete zrakoplova; Užad za preskakanje; Steperi za aerobni trening; Trampolini; Koturaljke s kotačićima u nizu; Sportska oprema; Sportski štitnici za tijelo; Ribička oprema; Ribički štapovi; Sprave za body building; Puzzle; Elektroničke igračke; Ukrasi za božićna drvca; Karnevalske maske; Mali trampolini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Torna- és sporttermékek; Fitnesz gépek; Játékok kisállatoknak; Gördeszkák; Férfi szuszpenzorok, altestvédők [sportcikkek]; Hegymászó hevederek; Giroszkópok és repülésstabilizálók repülőgépmodellekhez; Ugrálókötelek; Step-aerobic gépek; Trambulinok; Soros görkorcsolyák; Sportfelszerelés; Testvédők sportoláshoz; Horgászfelszerelések; Horgászbotok; Testedző berendezések; Kirakós játékok [puzzle]; Elektronikus játékszerek; Karácsonyfadíszek; Játékálarcok; Kis trambulinok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Articoli per la ginnastica e lo sport; Attrezzi per esercizi fisici; Giocattoli per animali da compagnia; Skate boards; Slip sospensori per sportivi [articoli sportivi]; Imbracature per scalate; Giroscopi e stabilizzatori di volo per aeromodelli; Corde per fare saltelli; Macchine step per aerobica; Trampolini; Pattini a rotelle in linea; Attrezzature sportive; Protezioni corporali per lo sport; Arnesi da pesca; Canne da pesca; Apparecchi per il culturismo; Giocattoli in forma di puzzle; Giocattoli elettronici; Decorazioni per alberi di Natale; Maschere [giocattoli]; Trampolini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Gimnastikos ir sporto reikmenys; Fizinių pratimų prietaisai; Kambarinių gyvūnėlių žaislai; Riedlentės; Sportinės apsaugos vyrams [sporto reikmenys]; Alpinistų reikmenys; Giroskopai ir skrydžio stabilizatoriai orlaivių modeliams; Šokdynės; Aerobikos žingsniavimo treniruokliai; Batutai; Vienakrypčiai riedučiai; Sportinė įranga; Kūno apsaugos sporto reikmėms; Žvejybos reikmenys; Meškerykočiai; Fizinių pratimų prietaisai [kūnui treniruoti]; Galvosūkiai; Elektroniniai žaislai; Kalėdų eglučių papuošalai; Žaidimų kaukės; Mini batutai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vingrošanas un sporta preces; Trenažieri; Mājas (istabas) dzīvnieku rotaļlietas; Skrituļdēļi; Cirkšņus sargājošas vīriešu sporta bikses; Alpīnistu drošības jostas; Žiroskopi un lidojuma stabilizatori lidmodeļiem; Lecamauklas; Aerobikas kāpšanas trenažieri; Batuti; Skrituļslidas ar vienā līnijā izkārtotiem skrituļiem; Sporta piederumi; Ķermeņa aizsargi izmantošanai sportā; Makšķerēšanas piederumi; Makšķeres; Atlētiskās vingrošanas ierīces; Puzles; Elektroniskās rotaļlietas; Eglīšu rotājumi; Rotaļu maskas; Maza izmēra tramplīni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Artikli tal-ġinnastika u ta' l-isports; Eżerċizzju fiżiku (Magni għall- -); Ġugarelli għal annimali domestiċi; Bords tal-iskejzjar; Ilbies protettiv għall-irġiel fl-atletika [oġġetti sportivi]; Ċineg tal-alpinisti; Ġiroskopji u stabbilizzaturi ta' titjira għal mudelli ta' ajruplani; Ħbula tal-qbiż; Magni aerobiċi forma ta' tarġa; Trampolini; Pattini b'roti dritti waħda wara l-oħra; Tagħmir tal-isports; Protetturi tal-ġisem għall-użu sportiv; Tagħmir tas-sajd; Qasab tas-sajd; Apparat għat-taħriġ tal-muskoli; Logħob tat-taħbil il-moħħ; Ġugarelli elettroniċi; Dekorazzjonijiet għas-siġar tal-Milied; Maskri tal-logħob; Trampolini żgħar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Gymnastiek- en sportartikelen; Toestellen voor lichaamsoefeningen; Speelgoed voor huisdieren; Skateboards; Toques [sportartikelen]; Klimtuigage; Gyroscopen en vluchtstabilisatoren voor modelvliegtuigen; Springtouwen; Stepapparaten voor aerobics; Trampolines; Skeelers; Sportuitrusting; Lichaamsbeschermers voor sportgebruik; Materiaal voor de hengelsport; Vishengels; Fitnesstoestellen; Puzzels; Speelgoed (Elektronisch -); Versierselen voor kerstbomen; Maskers [speelgoed]; Mini-trampolines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Artykuły gimnastyczne i sportowe; Maszyny do ćwiczeń sprawnościowych; Zabawki dla zwierząt domowych; Deskorolki; Suspensoria dla sportowców; Uprząż wspinaczkowa; Żyroskopy i stabilizatory lotu do modeli samolotów w pomniejszonej skali; Skakanki; Steppery [urządzenia] do ćwiczeń aerobowych; Trampoliny; Łyżworolki; Sprzęt sportowy; Ochraniacze ciała do użytku sportowego; Sprzęt wędkarski; Wędki; Przyrządy stosowane do ćwiczeń fizycznych; Puzzle; Zabawki elektroniczne; Ozdoby choinkowe; Maski zabawkowe; Małe trampoliny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Artigos de ginástica e desporto; Máquinas para exercício físico; Brinquedos para animais de estimação; Pranchas de skate; Suspensórios para desporto; Arneses para alpinistas; Giroscópios e estabilizadores de voo para modelos de aeronaves; Cordas de saltar; Máquinas de exercícios aeróbicos com degraus; Trampolins; Patins em linha; Aparelhos de desporto; Protetores corporais para uso desportivo; Aparelhos para a pesca; Canas de pesca; Aparelhos para o culturismo; Puzzles; Brinquedos eletrónicos; Decorações para árvores de Natal; Máscaras [artigos de brincar]; Minitrampolins.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole de gimnastică și de sport; Aparate pentru exerciții fizice; Jucării pentru animale de companie; Skateboarduri; Protecții inghinale pentru sportivi [articole sportive]; Centuri de cățărare; Giroscoape și stabilizatoare de zbor pentru aeromodele; Coarde de sărit; Aparate cu pedale pentru aerobic; Trambuline; Patine cu role în linie; Echipamente pentru sport; Protecții de corp pentru sport; Accesorii de pescuit; Vergi de undițe pentru pescuit; Aparate pentru culturism; Jucării sub formă de puzzle-uri; Jucării electronice; Decorațiuni (ornamente) pentru pomul de Crăciun; Măști de carnaval; Minitrambuline.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Gymnastické a športové predmety; Stroje na telesné cvičenia; Hračky pre zvieratá chované v domácnosti; Skejtbordy; Suspenzory pre športovcov (športové potreby); Upínacie pásy pre horolezcov; Gyroskopy a letové stabilizátory do modelov lietadiel; Švihadlá; Stepery na aerobné cvičenie; Trampolíny; Kolieskové korčule (jednoradové); Športové vybavenie; Chrániče tela používané pri športe; Rybárske náradie; Rybárske udice; Posilňovacie stroje; Puzzle; Elektronické hračky; Ozdoby na vianočný stromček; Masky (hračky); Minitrampolíny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Gimnastične in športne potrebščine; Naprave za telesno vadbo; Igrače za hišne ljubljence; Rolke; Moške podporne hlače za šport [športni izdelki]; Plezalne vrvi; Giroskopi in stabilizatorji leta za modele zrakoplovov; Kolebnice; Steperji za aerobiko; Trampolini; Rolerji; Športna oprema; Ščitniki za telo za uporabo pri športu; Ribiška oprema; Ribiške palice; Naprave za telovadbo; Igrače v obliki sestavljank; Elektronske igrače; Dekoracije za božična drevesa; Maske (igrače); Mini trampolini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Gymnastik- och sportartiklar; Maskiner för fysisk träning; Leksaker för husdjur; Skateboards; Suspensoarer [sportartiklar]; Bergsklättrarselar; Gyroskop och flygstabilisatorer för modellflygplan; Hopprep; Aerobiska trappmaskiner; Studsmattor; In-line rullskridskor; Sportutrustning; Kroppsskydd för sportbruk; Fiskeredskap; Spön för fiske; Träningsapparater; Pussel; Elektroniska leksaker; Prydnader för julgranen; Masker [leksaker]; Trampetter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/146</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>85806</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
