<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-02T09:04:25</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226146</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226146</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="1">Application published</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-02</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>WILD WORLD</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162308054</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226146/000162308054.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>24.11.07</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>18</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ученически чанти; Джобни портфейли; Презраменни торби за носене на бебета (кенгуру); Чанти, кутии за инструменти [празни]; Раници; Джобни портфейли; Пазарски чанти; Дипломатически куфарчета за книжа; Чанти за алпинисти; Чанти за къмпинг; Плажни чанти; Ръчни дамски чанти; Джобни портфейли; Пътни чанти, куфари; Куфари с колелца; Чанти; Чанти с презрамки за носене на деца; Чанти за спорт; Малки пътни чанти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Školní tašky; Cestovní kufry (velké lodní); Závěsná nosítka na nošení dětí; Brašny na nářadí, prázdné; Batohy; Náprsní tašky; Nákupní tašky; Aktovky; Batohy pro horolezce; Turistické batohy; Plážové tašky; Kabelky; Cestovní tašky; Kufry; Kufry na kolečkách; Tašky; Vaky na nošení dětí; Sportovní tašky; Malá cestovní zavazadla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Skoletasker; Rejsekister [store kufferter]; Bæreseler til spædbørn; Værktøjstasker, tomme; Rygsække; Tegnebøger; Indkøbstasker; Dokumentmapper; Tasker til bjergbestigere; Tasker til campister; Strandtasker; Håndtasker; Rejsetasker; Kufferter; Kufferter med hjul; Tasker; Bæreseler til babyer; Sportstasker; Håndkufferter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Schultaschen; Reisekoffer; Babytragetücher zum Umhängen; Leere Werkzeugtaschen; Rucksäcke; Brieftaschen; Einkaufstaschen; Aktentaschen, Dokumentenmappen; Rucksäcke für Bergsteiger; Campingtaschen; Badetaschen; Handtaschen; Reisetaschen; Handkoffer; Koffer mit Rollen; Taschen; Babytragebeutel; Sporttaschen; Kleine Handkoffer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Σχολικές σάκες· Βαλίτσες· Μάρσιποι για τη μεταφορά νηπίων· Τσάντες μεταφοράς εργαλείων (κενές)· Σακίδια πλάτης· Βαλίτσες· Ψώνια (Τσάντες για -)· Χαρτοφύλακες· Ορειβατικά (Σακκίδια -)· Κατασκηνωτικοί σάκκοι· Παραλία (τσάντες -ας)· Τσάντες· Βαλίτσες· Βαλίτσες· Βαλίτσες με ρόδες· Τσάντες για ανεπίσημο ντύσιμο· Μάρσιποι για τη μεταφορά νηπίων· Τσάντες γυμναστηρίου· Βαλίτσες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">School bags; Travelling trunks; Sling bags for carrying infants; Tool bags, empty; Backpacks; Pocket wallets; Shopping bags; Document cases; Bags for climbers; Bags for campers; Beach bags; Handbags; Travelling bags; Suitcases; Suitcases with wheels; Bags; Pouch baby carriers; Bags for sports; Valises.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Mochilas escolares; Baúles de viaje; Bandoleras portabebés de cuero; Bolsas de herramientas vacías; Mochilas; Billeteras; Bolsas para la compra; Portafolios [artículos de marroquinería]; Bolsas de montañismo; Bolsas de campamento; Bolsas de playa; Bolsos de mano; Bolsas de viaje; Maletas; Maletas con ruedas; Bolsas; Canguros portabebés; Bolsas de deporte; Maletas de mano.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Koolikotid; Reisikirstud; Kotid väikelaste kandmiseks; Täitmata tööriistakotid; Seljakotid; Rahataskud; Ostukotid, turukotid; Portfellid; Alpinistikotid; Matkakotid; Rannakotid; Käekotid; Reisikotid; Kohvrid; Ratastega kohvrid; Kotid; Kandelinad; Spordikotid; Reisikotid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Koululaisten olkalaukut; Matka-arkut; Vauvareput vauvojen kantamiseen; Työkalulaukut (tyhjät); Reput; Lompakot; Ostoslaukut; Salkut; Laukut kiipeilijöille; Laukut retkeilijöille; Rantalaukut; Laukut (Käsi -); Matkakassit; Matkalaukut; Pyörälliset matkalaukut; Vapaa-ajanlaukut; Vauvareput vauvojen kantamiseen; Voimistelukassit; Pienet kädessä kannettavat matkalaukut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Serviettes d'écoliers; Coffres de voyage; Porte-bébés hamac; Sacoches à outils vides; Sacs à dos; Portefeuilles; Sacs à provisions; Serviettes [maroquinerie]; Sacs d'alpinistes; Sacs de campeurs; Sacs de plage; Sacs à main; Sacs de voyage; Valises; Valises à roulettes; Sacs; Sacs kangourou [porte-bébés]; Sacs de sport; Mallettes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Torbe na rame; Prtljažni artikli; Marame za bebu; Prazne torbe za alat; Naprtnjače; Prtljažni artikli; Torbe za namirnice; Torbe za spise [aktovke]; Planinarske torbe; Torbe za kampiranje; Torbe za plažu; Ručne torbe; Prtljažni artikli; Putni koferi; Putne torbe s kotačima; Torbe; Marame za bebu; Sportske torbe; Male putne torbe ili koferi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Satchel táskák; Poggyász; Oldalhordozó táskák csecsemők hordozására; Szerszámtáskák, üresen; Hátizsákok, hátitáskák; Poggyász; Bevásárlótáskák; Irattáskák, aktatáskák; Hátizsákok, táskák hegymászóknak; Táskák, hátizsákok táborozóknak; Strandtáskák; Kézitáskák; Poggyász; Bőröndök; Kerekes bőröndök; Hétköznapi, utcai táskák; Oldalhordozó táskák csecsemők hordozására; Sporttáskák, tornazsákok; Útitáskák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cartelle scolastiche; Bauli da viaggio; Imbracatura a tracolla per portare neonati; Borse vuote per i ferri; Zaini; Portafogli; Borse della spesa; Cartelle, buste [articoli di pelle]; Sacchi per alpinisti; Sacchi da campeggiatori; Borse da spiaggia; Borsette; Sacchi da viaggio; Valigie; Valigie con rotelle; Borse; Marsupi porta-bebè; Borse da sport; Valigie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Mokyklinės kuprinės; Kelioninės skrynelės; Vaikjuostės; Įrankių krepšiai (tušti); Kuprinės; Kišeninės piniginės; Krepšeliai (maišeliai) pirkiniams; Portfeliai; Alpinistų krepšiai; Turistų krepšiai; Paplūdimio krepšeliai; Rankinukai; Kelionmaišiai; Maži lagaminai; Lagaminai su ratukais; Krepšiai; Kūdikių nešynės; Sportiniai krepšiai; Sakvojažai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Skolēnu somas; Ceļojumu lādes; Ķengursomas zīdaiņu nēsāšanai; Tukšas darbarīku somas; Mugursomas; Kabatas portfeļi; Iepirkumu somas; Portfeļi; Alpīnistu somas; Tūristu somas; Pludmales somas; Rokassomas; Ceļasomas; Čemodāni; Čemodāni ar ritenīšiem; Somas; Slingu apsēji mazu bērnu nēsāšanai; Sporta somas; Mazas ceļojumu somas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Basktijiet tal-iskola [satchels]; Valiġġi; Ċrienen b'ċineg mal-ispallejn għall-ġarr tat-tfal żgħar; Boroż għall-ġarr tal-istrumenti (vojta); Barżakki ta' fuq id-dahar; Valiġġi; Basktijiet għax-xiri; Kartieri tad-dokumenti; Basktijiet għall-alpinisti; Basktijiet għal min jikkampeġġja; Basktijiet tal-baħar; Basktijiet tal-id; Valiġġi; Bagalji [suitcases]; Valiġġi bir-roti; Basktijiet ta' kuljum; Ċrienen b'ċineg mal-ispallejn għall-ġarr tat-tfal żgħar; Basktijiet għall-affarijiet li jintużaw fil-ġinnasju (sport); Valiġġi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Schooltassen; Reiskoffers; Draagzakken voor het dragen van kinderen; Gereedschapstassen, leeg; Rugzakken; Portefeuilles; Boodschappentassen; Aktentassen; Tassen voor bergbeklimmers; Kampeertassen; Strandtassen; Handtassen; Reistassen; Koffers; Koffers op wielen; Tassen; Draagzakken voor baby's; Sporttassen; Attachékoffertjes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Torby szkolne [z paskiem na ramię]; Bagaż; Nosidełka dla niemowląt do noszenia na ciele; Torby na narzędzia (puste); Plecaki; Bagaż; Torby na zakupy; Aktówki; Torby alpinistyczne; Torby turystyczne; Torby plażowe; Torebki; Bagaż; Walizki; Walizki z kółkami; Torby; Nosidełka dla niemowląt do noszenia na ciele; Torby gimnastyczne; Walizki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Pastas para estudantes; Cofres de viagem; Alcofas para transportar crianças; Sacos para ferramentas [vazios]; Mochilas [com duas alças]; Carteiras de bolso; Sacos para compras; Pastas [maletas]; Sacos para alpinistas; Sacos para campistas; Sacos de praia; Sacos de mão; Sacos de viagem; Malas de viagem; Malas de viagem com rodas; Sacos; Bolsas porta-bebés; Sacos de desporto; Malas de mão.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Serviete pentru școlari; Genți; Portbebeuri pentru transportul copiilor; Genți pentru scule, goale; Rucsacuri; Genți; Sacoșe pentru cumpărături; Documente (Mape pentru -); Rucsacuri pentru alpiniști; Rucsacuri pentru camping; Genți de plajă; Poșete; Genți; Geamantane; Geamantane cu rotile; Genți; Portbebeuri pentru transportul copiilor; Genți sportive; Valize.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Školské tašky (aktovky); Cestovné kufre; Tašky na nosenie detí; Tašky na náradie (prázdne); Plecniaky; Náprsné tašky; Nákupné tašky; Aktovky (kožená galantéria); Horolezecké plecniaky; Turistické plecniaky; Plážové tašky; Kabelky; Cestovné tašky; Kufre; Kufre na kolieskach; Tašky; Vaky na nosenie dojčiat; Športové tašky; Kufríky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Šolske torbe z jermenom; Prtljaga; Košare za nošenje dojenčkov; Torbe za orodje, prazne; Nahrbtniki; Prtljaga; Nakupovalne torbe; Aktovke; Torbe za plezalce; Torbe za tabornike; Torbe za plažo; Ročne torbice; Prtljaga; Kovčki; Kovčki s kolesi; Torbe; Košare za nošenje dojenčkov; Telovadne torbe; Ročni kovčki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Skolväskor med axelremmar; Resekoffertar; Bärväskor för att bära spädbarn; Verktygsväskor (tomma); Ryggsäckar; Plånböcker; Shoppingväskor; Portföljer; Väskor för alpinister; Väskor för campare; Strandväskor; Handväskor; Reseväskor; Resväskor; Resväskor med hjul; Fritidsväskor; Bärselar för spädbarn; Bags för sport; Mindre resväskor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/188</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-01</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080363</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15345</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018181233</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15345</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-16</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018063803</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>86428</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Decision to reject (final)</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-29</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
