<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-21T17:09:11</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226535</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226535</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-21</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="12" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-21</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>KINESIS</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Компютърен софтуер за финансови услуги; Компютърен софтуер за финансов мениджмънт; Софтуер за финансова информация, информационен анализ; Софтуер за финансова консултация; Софтуер за търговия на финансовите пазари; Софтуер за търговия с финансови инструменти; Софтуер за услуги за търговия с криптовалута; Софтуер за финансови услуги, свързани с криптовалута; Всички горепосочени стоки са предназначени само за използване във връзка с цифрови валути, както и криптовалути и традиционните (фиат) валути.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Počítačový software pro finanční služby; Počítačový software pro finanční řízení; Software na analýzy finančních informací a údajů; Software na finanční konzultace; Software pro obchodování na finančních trzích; Software pro obchodování s finančními nástroji; Software pro služby v oblasti obchodování s kryptoměnami; Software pro finanční služby vztahující se ke kryptoměnám; Všechny výše uvedené výrobky jsou určené pouze pro použití v souvislosti s digitálními měnami, jakož i kryptoměnami a tradičními měnami (fiat).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Computersoftware til finansiel virksomhed; Computersoftware til finansiel styring; Software til finansiel information, informationsanalyse; Software til finansiel konsulentbistand; Software til handel på finansielle markeder; Software til handel med finansielle instrumenter; Software til handel med kryptovaluta; Software til finansiel virksomhed i forbindelse med kryptovaluta; Alle de førnævnte varer udelukkende til anvendelse i forbindelse med digital valuta samt krypto- og traditionel valuta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Computersoftware für Finanzdienstleistungen; Computersoftware für Finanzmanagement; Software für Finanzinformationen, Informationsanalyse; Software für Finanzberatung; Software für den Handel auf Finanzmärkten; Software für den Handel mit Finanzinstrumenten; Software für den Handel mit Kryptowährungen; Software für Finanzdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Kryptowährungen; Alle vorstehend genannten Waren zur ausschließlichen Verwendung in Verbindung mit digitalen Währungen sowie Krypto- und traditionellen (Fiat-)Währungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Λογισμικό ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για χρηματοοικονομικές υπηρεσίες· Λογισμικό ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για χρηματοπιστωτική διαχείριση· Λογισμικό χρηματοπιστωτικών πληροφοριών, ανάλυση πληροφοριών· Λογισμικό για παροχή χρηματοπιστωτικών συμβουλών· Λογισμικό διαπραγμάτευσης σε χρηματοπιστωτικές αγορές· Λογισμικό για διαπραγμάτευση χρηματοπιστωτικών τίτλων· Λογισμικό για υπηρεσίες διαπραγμάτευσης κρυπτονομισμάτων· Λογισμικό για χρηματοπιστωτικές υπηρεσίες σε σχέση με κρυπτονομίσματα· Τα προαναφερθέντα είδη στο σύνολό τους προοριζόμενα αποκλειστικά για χρήση σε σχέση με ψηφιακά νομίσματα, όπως και με κρυπτονομίσματα και με παραδοσιακά (παραστατικά) νομίσματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Software for financial services; software for financial management; software for financial information, information analysis; software for financial consultancy; Software for trading in financial markets; software for trading in financial instruments; Software for cryptocurrency trading services; Software for financial services relating to cryptocurrency; all the aforesaid goods being only intended to be used in connection with digital currencies, as well as crypto and traditional (fiat) currencies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Software informático para servicios financieros; Software para la gestión financiera; Software para información financiera, análisis de la información; Software para servicios de consultoría financiera; Software para hacer transacciones en mercados financieros; Software para hacer transacciones con instrumentos financieros; Software para servicios de comercio con criptodivisas; Software para servicios financieros relacionados con criptodivisas; Todos los productos mencionados solo están destinados a su uso en relación con monedas digitales, así como criptomonedas y divisas tradicionales (fiduciarias).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Finantsteenuste arvutitarkvara; Finantsjuhtimiseks ette nähtud arvutitarkvara; Finantsteabe, teabe analüüsimise tarkvara; Finantskonsultatsiooni tarkvara; Finantsturgudel kauplemise tarkvara; Finantsvahenditega kauplemise tarkvara; Tarkvara krüptovaluutaga kauplemise teenuste jaoks; Krüptovaluutaga seotud finantsteenuste tarkvara; Kõik eelmainitud kaubad on kasutuseks ainult seoses digivaluutadega, samuti krüpto- ja traditsiooniliste (fiat) valuutadega.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tietokoneohjelmistot rahoituspalveluja varten; Tietokoneohjelmistot rahataloudellista hallintaa varten; Taloudellisiin tietoihin, tietojen analysointiin liittyvät ohjelmistot; Taloudelliseen konsultointiin liittyvät ohjelmistot; Rahoitusmarkkinoilla tapahtuvaan kauppaan liittyvät ohjelmistot; Rahoitusvälineillä tapahtuvaan kauppaan liittyvät ohjelmistot; Ohjelmistot kryptovaluuttakauppapalveluja varten; Kryptovaluuttaan liittyvät ohjelmistot rahoituspalveluja varten; Edellä mainitut tavarat on tarkoitettu käytettäväksi yksinomaan digitaalisten valuuttojen yhteydessä, sekä krypto- ja perinteisten valuuttojen yhteydessä.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Logiciels pour services financiers; Logiciels de gestion financière; Logiciels pour informations financières, analyses financières; Logiciels d'assistance financière; Logiciels de négociation sur les marchés financiers; Logiciels pour la négociation d'instruments financiers; Logiciels pour services de négociation de cryptomonnaies; Logiciels pour services financiers liés à la cryptomonnaie; Tous les produits précités étant uniquement destinés à être utilisés en rapport avec des devises numériques, ainsi que des cryptomonnaies et des devises traditionnelles (fiat).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Računalni softver za financijske usluge; Računalni softver za financijsko upravljanje; Softver za financijske informacije, analizu informacija; Softver za financijsko savjetovanje; Softver za trgovanje na financijskim tržištima; Softver za trgovanje financijskim instrumentima; Softver za usluge trgovanja kriptovalutama; Softver za financijske usluge u vezi s kriptovalutama; Svi prethodno navedeni proizvodi namijenjeni su samo za uporabu u vezi s digitalnim valutama, kao i kriptovalutama te tradicionalnim (fiducijarnim) valutama.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Pénzügyi szolgáltatásokkal kapcsolatos számítógépes szoftver; Számítógépes szoftverek pénzügyi ügyvitelhez; Szoftver pénzügyi információk és elemzések biztosítására; Szoftver pénzügyi tanácsadásra; Szoftver a pénzügyi piacokon való kereskedelemhez; Szoftver a pénzügyi eszközökkel való kereskedelemhez; Kriptodeviza kereskedési szolgáltatások szoftvere; Kriptovalutával kapcsolatos pénzügyi szolgáltatásokhoz kapcsolódó szoftver; Az összes fent említett áru kizárólag digitális valutákkal, valamint kripto- és hagyományos (fiat) valutákkal való összekapcsolásra szolgál.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Software per servizi finanziari; Software per gestione finanziaria; Software per informazioni finanziarie, analisi d'informazioni; Software per consulenza finanziaria; Software per la compravendita in mercati finanziari; Software per la compravendita in strumenti finanziari; Software per servizi di compravendita di cripto-valuta; Software per servizi finanziari in materia di criptovaluta; Tutti i suddetti prodotti sono destinati a essere utilizzati solo in relazione a valute digitali, nonché a valute criptate e tradizionali (fiat).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Finansinė kompiuterių programinė įranga; Finansų vadybos kompiuterių programinė įranga; Programinė įranga, skirta finansinės informacijos ir analizių teikimui; Programinė įranga, skirta finansų konsultacijoms; Programinė įranga, skirta prekybai finansų rinkoje; Programinė įranga, skirta prekybai finansinėmis priemonėmis; Programinė įranga kriptovaliutų prekybos paslaugoms; Programinė įranga finansinėms paslaugoms, susijusioms su kriptovaliuta; Visos minėtos prekės yra skirtos naudoti tik su skaitmeninėmis valiutomis, taip pat su kriptovaliutomis ir tradicinėmis (fiat) valiutomis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Finanšu pakalpojumu datoru programmatūra; Datoru programmatūra finanšu vadībai; Finanšu informācijas, informācijas analīzes programmatūra; Finanšu konsultāciju programmatūra; Programmatūra tirdzniecībai finanšu tirgū; Programmatūra finanšu instrumentu tirdzniecībai; Programmatūra kriptovalūtu tirdzniecības pakalpojumiem; Programmatūra finanšu pakalpojumiem, kas saistīti ar kriptovalūtu; Visas iepriekšminētās preces ir paredzētas lietošanai tikai saistībā ar digitālajām valūtām, kā arī ar kriptovalūtām un tradicionālajām [papīra naudas] valūtām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Softwer tal-kompjuter għas-servizzi finanzjarji; Softwer tal-kompjuter għall-ġestjoni finanzjarja; Softwer għall-informazzjoni finanzjarja, analiżi tal-informazzjoni; Softwer għall-konsulenza finanzjarja; Softwer għan-negozjar fi swieq finanzjarji; Softwer għan-negozjar fi strumenti finanzjarji; Softwer għal servizzi ta' kummerċ ta' muniti kripto; Softwer għal servizzi finanzjarji relatati mal-muniti kripto; L-oġġetti kollha msemmija qabel huma maħsuba biss biex jintużaw f'rabta mal-valuti diġitali, kif ukoll il-kriptovaluti u l-valuti tradizzjonali (fiat).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Software voor gebruik in samenhang met financiële diensten; Software voor financieel beheer; Software voor financiële informatie, informatieanalyse; Software voor financiële advisering; Software voor handel op financiële markten; Software voor handel in financiële instrumenten; Software voor de handel in cryptovaluta; Software voor financiële diensten op het gebied van cryptovaluta; Alle voornoemde goederen zijn uitsluitend voor gebruik met betrekking tot digitale valuta alsmede cryptovaluta en traditionele valuta (vertrouwensmunten).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Oprogramowanie komputerowe w zakresie usług finansowych; Oprogramowanie komputerowe związane z zarządzaniem finansowym; Oprogramowanie do informacji finansowych i analiz informacji; Oprogramowanie do doradztwa finansowego; Oprogramowanie do handlu na rynkach finansowych; Oprogramowanie do handlu instrumentami finansowymi; Oprogramowanie do usług handlu kryptowalutami; Oprogramowanie do usług finansowych związanych z kryptowalutami; Wszystkie wyżej wymienione towary przeznaczone wyłącznie do użytku w związku z cyfrowymi walutami oraz kryptowalutami i walutami tradycyjnymi (fiat).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Software para serviços financeiros; Computer software for financial management; Software para informações financeiras, análise de informações; Software para consultadoria financeira; Software para realização de transações nos mercados financeiros; Software para transação de instrumentos financeiros; Software para serviços de transação de criptomoeda; Software para serviços financeiros relacionados com criptomoeda; Todos os produtos atrás referidos destinados exclusivamente a ser utilizados no domínio das moedas digitais, bem como das criptomoedas e moedas fiduciárias tradicionais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Software de calculator pentru serviciile financiare; Software de calculator pentru administrare financiara; Software pentru informaţii financiare, analiza informaţiilor; Software pentru consultanţă financiară; Software pentru tranzacţionare pe pieţe financiare; Software pentru comerţ cu instrumente financiare; Software pentru servicii de tranzacționare de criptomonedă; Software pentru servicii financiare referitoare la criptomonedă; Toate produsele susmenționate destinate doar pentru a fi folosite în legătură cu monede digitale, precum și criptomonede și monede tradiționale (fiduciare).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Počítačový softvér pre finančné služby; Počítačový softvér v oblasti finančného riadenia; Softvér pre finančné informácie, analýzu informácií; Softvér pre finančné konzultácie; Softvér pre obchodovanie na finančných trhoch; Softvér pre obchodovanie s finančnými nástrojmi; Softvér pre služby obchodovania s kryptomenami; Softvér pre finančné služby v oblasti kryptomien; Všetky vyššie uvedené výrobky súvisia výlučne s digitálnymi menami, ako aj kryptomenami a tradičnými (fiatovými) menami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Računalniška programska oprema za finančne storitve; Računalniška programska oprema za finančno upravljanje; Programska oprema za nudenje finančnih informacij in analize informacij; Programska oprema za finančno svetovanje; Programska oprema za trgovanje na finančnih trgih; Programska oprema za trgovanje s finančnimi instrumenti; Programska oprema za storitve trgovanja s kriptovalutami; Programska oprema za finančne storitve v zvezi s kriptovalutami; Vsi prej navedeni izdelki so namenjeni le za uporabo v zvezi z digitalnimi valutami ter kripto in klasičnimi (fiat) valutami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Programvara för finansiella tjänster; Programvara för finansiell hantering; Programvara för finansiell information, informationsanalys; Programvara för finansiell konsultation; Programvara för handel på finansmarknaden; Programvara för handel med finansiella instrument; Programvara för handel med kryptovaluta; Programvara för finansiella tjänster avseende kryptovaluta; Samtliga nämnda varor är endast avsedda att användas i samband med digitala valutor, såväl som kryptovalutor och traditionella (fiat) valutor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>14</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Скъпоценни метали; Сплави от благородни метали; Злато; Сребро.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Drahé kovy; Slitiny drahých kovů; Zlato; Stříbro.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Ædle metaller; Legeringer af ædle metaller; Guld; Sølv.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Edelmetalle; Legierungen aus Edelmetall; Gold; Silber.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Κράματα πολύτιμων μετάλλων· Χρυσός· Ασήμι.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Precious metals; Alloys of precious metals; Gold; Silver.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Metales preciosos; Aleaciones de metales preciosos; Oro; Plata.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Väärismetallid; Väärismetallisulamid; Kuld; Hõbe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Jalometallit; Jalometalliseokset; Kulta; Hopea.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Métaux précieux; Alliages de métaux précieux; Or; Argent.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Plemeniti metali; Legure plemenitih metala; Zlato; Srebro.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nemesfémek; Nemesfém ötvözetek; Arany; Ezüst.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Metalli preziosi; Leghe di metalli preziosi; Oro; Argento.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Brangieji metalai; Lydiniai (tauriųjų metalų); Auksas; Sidabras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Dārgmetāli; Dārgmetāla sakausējumi; Zelts; Sudrabs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Metalli prezzjużi; Ligi ta' metall prezzjuż; Deheb; Fidda.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Edele metalen; Legeringen van edele metalen; Goud; Zilver.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Metale szlachetne; Stopy metali szlachetnych; Złoto; Srebro.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Metais preciosos; Ligas de metais preciosos; Ouro; Prata.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Metale preţioase; Aliaje din metale preţioase; Aur; Argint.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Drahé kovy; Zliatiny drahých kovov; Zlato; Striebro.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Žlahtne kovine; Zlitine iz plemenitih kovin; Zlato; Srebro.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Ädelmetaller; Legeringar ädelmetall; Guld; Silver.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>36</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Финансови услуги, а именно, Финансови консултации; Услуги за капиталови инвестиции; Финансови услуги за потребители на интернет, А именно, Финансови анализи, Онлайн банкиране и онлайн финансово планиране; Финансови услуги, свързани с търговия с финансови инструменти; Управление на капитали; Финансови консултации от страна на инвеститорите за потребителите на интернет; Финансово управление на онлайн платформа за търговия и обмен на финансови инструменти, А именно, Онлайн търговия на финансови инструменти, участия, опции и други вторични продукти; Финансова информация и анализи; Предоставяне на финансова информация чрез уебсайт; Услуги за инвестиционно брокерство; Финансова информация относно финансови пазари и инструменти; Финансова информация, осигурявана с употребата на приложен програмен интерфейс (API); Финансови консултации; Финансови услуги, а именно, Предоставяне за обмен на чужда валута, акции и финансови деривати чрез глобална комуникационна мрежа; Предоставяне на информация в областите на обмен на чуждестранна валута, стоки за потребление и финансови деривати чрез глобална комуникационна мрежа; Комисионни услуги за благородни метали; Търговия с криптовалута; Финансови услуги, свързани с криптовалути; Всички горепосочени услуги са предназначени само за използване във връзка с цифрови валути, както и криптовалути и традиционни (фиат) валути.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby finanční, jmenovitě, Finanční poradenství; Investice finančních prostředků; Finanční služby pro uživatele internetu, Jmenovitě, Finanční analýza, On-line bankovnictví a on-line finanční plánování; Finanční služby vztahující se k obchodování s finančními nástroji; Finanční řízení; Finanční konzultace poskytované investory uživatelům internetu; Finančně správní on-line platforma pro obchodování a výměnu finančních nástrojů, Jmenovitě, Online obchodování s finančními nástroji, akciemi, opcemi a jinými deriváty; Finanční informace a rozbory; Poskytování finančních informací prostřednictvím webových stránek; Investiční makléřské služby; Finanční informace o finančních trzích a nástrojích; Finanční informace poskytované pomocí rozhraní pro programování aplikací (API); Finanční poradenství; Služby finanční, jmenovitě, Poskytování výměny cizích měn, komodit a finančních derivátů prostřednictvím globální komunikační sítě; Poskytování informací v oboru cizích měn, komodit a finančních derivátů prostřednictvím globální komunikační sítě; Makléřství v oblasti drahých kovů; Služby v oblasti obchodování s kryptoměnami; Finanční služby v oblasti kryptoměn; Všechny výše uvedené výrobky jsou určené pouze pro použití v souvislosti s digitálními měnami, jakož i kryptoměnami a tradičními měnami (fiat).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Finansiel virksomhed, nemlig, Finansiel rådgivning; Kapitalinvestering; Finansiel virksomhed møntet på internetbrugere, Nemlig, Finansielle analyser, Onlinebankvirksomhed og finansiel onlineplanlægning; Finansiel virksomhed vedrørende handel med finansielle instrumenter; Finansiel styring; Finansiel konsulentbistand af investorer til internetbrugere; Finansiel styring af onlineplatforme til handel og udveksling af finansielle instrumenter, Nemlig, Onlinehandel med finansielle instrumenter, aktier, optioner og andre derivater; Finansiel information og finansielle analyser; Stillen finansiel information til rådighed via et websted; Mæglervirksomhed i forbindelse med investering; Finansiel information vedrørende finansielle markeder og instrumenter; Finansiel information udbudt ved hjælp af en grænseflade til programmering af applikationer (API); Finansiel rådgivning; Finansiel virksomhed, nemlig, Handel med valuta, varer og finansielle derivater via globale kommunikationsnetværk; Udbydelse af information inden for veksling af fremmed valuta, varer og afledte finansielle produkter via et globalt kommunikationsnetværk; Mæglervirksomhed inden for ædle metaller; Tjenester inden for handel med kryptovaluta; Finansielle tjenester i forbindelse med kryptovalutaer; Alle de førnævnte tjenesteydelser udelukkende til anvendelse i forbindelse med digital valuta samt krypto- og traditionel valuta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Finanzwesen, nämlich, Finanzielle Beratung; Kapitalanlage-Dienstleistungen; Finanzdienstleistungen für Benutzer des Internets, Nämlich, Finanzanalysen, Online-Bankwesen und Online-Finanzplanung; Finanzdienstleistungen in Bezug auf den Handel mit Finanzinstrumenten; Vermögensverwaltung; Finanzberatung durch Anleger für Benutzer des Internets; Online-Plattform zur Finanzverwaltung für den Handel und Austausch von Finanzinstrumenten, Nämlich, Online-Handel mit Finanzinstrumenten, Aktien, Optionen und anderen Derivaten; Finanzinformationen und Finanzanalysen; Bereitstellung von finanziellen Informationen über eine Website; Dienstleistungen eines Investmentmaklers; Finanzinformationen in Bezug auf Finanzmärkte und -instrumente; Erteilung von Finanzauskünften unter Verwendung einer Anwendungsprogrammierschnittstelle (API); Finanzielle Beratung; Finanzwesen, nämlich, Bereitstellung des Umtauschs von Fremdwährung, Handelsgütern und Finanzderivaten über ein weltweites Kommunikationsnetz; Bereitstellung von Informationen in den Bereichen Devisen, Handelswaren und Finanzderivate über ein weltweites Kommunikationsnetz; Maklerdienste für Edelmetalle; Handel mit Kryptowährungen; Finanzdienste für Kryptowährungen; Alle vorstehend genannten Dienstleistungen zur ausschließlichen Verwendung in Verbindung mit digitalen Währungen sowie Krypto- und traditionellen (Fiat-)Währungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Χρηματοπιστωτικές υπηρεσίες, συγκεκριμένα, Συμβουλευτική χρηματοοικονομική· Υπηρεσίες επενδύσεων κεφαλαίου· Χρηματοπιστωτικές υπηρεσίες για χρήστες του Διαδικτύου, Συγκεκριμένα, Ανάλυση χρηματοοικονομική, Σχεδιασμός τραπεζικών υπηρεσιών και επιγραμμικός χρηματοπιστωτικός σχεδιασμός· Χρηματοπιστωτικές υπηρεσίες σε σχέση με διαπραγμάτευση χρηματοπιστωτικών τίτλων· Χρηματοοικονομική διαχείριση· Υπηρεσίες παροχής χρηματοπιστωτικών συμβουλών από επενδυτές σε χρήστες του Διαδικτύου· Επιγραμμική πλατφόρμα χρηματοπιστωτικής διαχείρισης για εμπορία και ανταλλαγή χρηματοπιστωτικών τίτλων, Συγκεκριμένα, Επιγραμμική διαπραγμάτευση χρηματοπιστωτικών μέσων, μετοχών, δικαιωμάτων προαίρεσης (οψιόν) και άλλων παραγώγων· Πληροφόρηση και ανάλυση σε σχέση με χρηματοπιστωτικά θέματα· Παροχή χρηματοοικονομικών πληροφοριών μέσω δικτυακού τόπου· Υπηρεσίες διαπραγμάτευσης επενδύσεων· Υπηρεσίες παροχής χρηματοπιστωτικών πληροφοριών σε σχέση με χρηματοπιστωτικές αγορές και χρηματοπιστωτικούς τίτλους· Παροχή χρηματοπιστωτικών πληροφοριών με χρήση διεπαφής προγραμματισμού εφαρμογών· Συμβουλευτική χρηματοοικονομική· Χρηματοπιστωτικές υπηρεσίες, συγκεκριμένα, Παροχή υπηρεσιών ανταλλαγής ξένου συναλλάγματος, χρηματιστηριακών εμπορευμάτων και χρηματοπιστωτικών παραγώγων μέσω παγκόσμιου δικτύου επικοινωνίας· Παροχή πληροφοριών στους τομείς του ξένου συναλλάγματος, των εμπορευμάτων και των χρηματοπιστωτικών παραγώγων μέσω παγκόσμιου δικτύου επικοινωνίας· Πρακτόρευση πολύτιμων μετάλλων· Εμπόριο με κρυπτονομίσματα· Χρηματοπιστωτικές υπηρεσίες σε σχέση με τα κρυπτονομίσματα· Οι προαναφερθείσες υπηρεσίες στο σύνολό τους προοριζόμενες αποκλειστικά για χρήση σε σχέση με ψηφιακά νομίσματα, όπως και με κρυπτονομίσματα και με παραδοσιακά (παραστατικά) νομίσματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Financial services, namely, financial consultation services; funds investment services; financial services for users of the internet, namely, financial analysis, online banking and online financial planning; financial services relating to the trading of financial instruments; financial management; financial consultancy by investors to users of the internet; financial management online platform for trading and exchange of financial instruments, namely, on-line trading of financial instruments, shares, options and other derivative products; financial information analysis; providing financial information via a website; investment brokerage services; financial information regarding financial markets and instruments; financial information provided utilizing an application programming interface (API); financial consultancy; Financial services, namely, providing for the exchange of foreign currency, commodities and financial derivatives via a global communications network; providing information in the fields of foreign currency, commodities and financial derivatives via a global communications network; precious metals brokerage; Cryptocurrency trading services; Financial services relating to cryptocurrency; all the aforesaid services being only intended to be used in connection with digital currencies, as well as crypto and traditional (fiat) currencies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios financieros, en concreto, Consultoría financiera; Servicios de inversión de capitales; Servicios financieros para usuarios de Internet, En concreto, Análisis financiero, Banca en línea y planificación financiera en línea; Servicios financieros en relación con transacciones con instrumentos financieros; Gestión financiera; Servicios de consultoría financiera prestada por parte de inversores a usuarios de Internet; Plataforma en línea de gestión financiera para transacciones y para el intercambio de instrumentos financieros, En concreto, Transacciones en línea de instrumentos financieros, acciones, opciones y otros productos derivados; Información y análisis financieros; Suministro de información financiera por sitios web; Servicios de corretaje de inversiones; Información financiera relativa a mercados e instrumentos financieros; Información financiera suministrada mediante el uso de una interfaz de programación de aplicaciones (API); Consultoría financiera; Servicios financieros, en concreto, Suministro de cambio de divisas, materias primas y derivados financieros a través de una red de comunicaciones global; Suministro de información en relación con divisas, materias primas, derivados financieros a través de una red de comunicaciones mundiales; Corretaje de metales preciosos; Servicios de transacciones con criptomonedas; Servicios financieros relacionados con criptomonedas; Todos los servicios mencionados solo están destinados a su uso en relación con monedas digitales, así como criptomonedas y divisas tradicionales (fiduciarias).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Finantsteenused, nimelt, Finantskonsultatsioonid; Kapitaliinvesteeringud; Internetikasutajate finantsteenused, Nimelt, Finants-, rahandusanalüüsid, Internetipangandus ja veebipõhine finantsplaneerimine; Finantsvahenditega kauplemisega seotud finantsteenused; Finantsjuhtimine; Investoritelt internetikasutajatele osutatav finantskonsultatsioon; Finantsvahenditega kauplemise ja nende vahetamise sidusplatvormi finantshaldus, Nimelt, Siduskauplemine finantsinstrumentide, aktsiate, optsioonide ja muude derivaattoodetega; Finantsteave ja -analüüsid; Veebilehe kaudu finantsinfo pakkumine; Kapitaliinvesteeringute alased vahendusteenused; Finantsturgude ja -vahenditega seotud finantsteave; Finantsteave pakutuna rakenduse programmeerimisliidese (API) kasutamise kaudu; Finantskonsultatsioonid; Finantsteenused, nimelt, Välisvaluuta, kaupade ja finantsderivaatide pakkumine vahetamiseks ülemaailmse sidevõrgu kaudu; Teabe pakkumine välisvaluuta, tarbekaupade ja finantsderivaatide valdkonnas ülemaailmse sidevõrgu kaudu; Väärismetallide vahendamine; Krüptovaluutaga kauplemise teenused; Krüptovaluutadega seotud finantsteenused; Kõik eelmainitud teenused on kasutuseks ainult seoses digivaluutadega, samuti krüpto- ja traditsiooniliste (fiat) valuutadega.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Rahoituspalvelut, nimittäin, Rahoituskonsultointi; Sijoitusrahastopalvelut; Internetin käyttäjille tarkoitetut rahoituspalvelut, Nimittäin, Rahoitusanalyysit, Online-pankkitoiminta ja online-rahoitussuunnittelu; Rahoitusvälineillä tapahtuvaa kauppaan liittyvät rahoituspalvelut; Varainhoito; Sijoittajien tarjoama rahoituskonsultointi Internetin käyttäjille; Varainhoitoon liittyvä online-ympäristö rahoitusvälineisiin liittyvää kaupankäyntiä ja vaihtamista varten, Nimittäin, Rahoitusvälineitä, osakkeita, optioita ja muita johdannaistuotteita koskeva kaupankäynti online-periaatteella; Rahoitustiedot ja taloudelliset analyysit; Taloudellisten tietojen tarjoaminen verkkosivuston kautta; Sijoitusvälityspalvelut; Rahoitusmarkkinoihin ja -välineisiin liittyvä taloudellinen tiedotus; Rahataloudellinen tiedotus, joka tarjotaan sovellusohjelmointiliittymää käyttämällä; Rahoituskonsultointi; Rahoituspalvelut, nimittäin, Ulkomaanvaluutan, hyödykkeiden ja rahoitusjohdannaisten vaihtopalvelun tarjoaminen maailmanlaajuisen viestintäverkon välityksellä; Tietojen tarjoaminen ulkomaanvaluutan, hyödykkeiden ja rahoitusjohdannaisten alalla maailmanlaajuisen viestintäverkon välityksellä; Jalometallien välitys; Kryptovaluuttaan liittyvät kauppakäyntipalvelut; Kryptovaluuttoihin liittyvät rahoituspalvelut; Edellä mainitut palvelut on tarkoitettu käytettäväksi yksinomaan digitaalisten valuuttojen yhteydessä, sekä krypto- ja perinteisten valuuttojen yhteydessä.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services financiers, à savoir, Consultation en matière financière; Services d'investissement de fonds de placement; Services financiers pour internautes, À savoir, Analyse financière, Services bancaires en ligne et de planification financière en ligne; Services financiers liés à la négociation d'instruments financiers; Gestion financière; Assistance financière fournie par des investisseurs aux internautes; Plateforme en ligne de gestion financière pour la négociation et l'échange d'instruments financiers, À savoir, Négociation en ligne d'instruments financiers, d'actions, d'options et d'autres produits dérivés; Informations et analyses financières; Informations financières par le biais de sites web; Services de courtage en placement; Informations financières liées aux marchés et instruments financiers; Informations financières fournies par le biais d'une interface de programmation d'applications (API); Consultation en matière financière; Services financiers, à savoir, Fourniture de devises étrangères, marchandises et produits financiers dérivés par le biais d'un réseau mondial de communications; Services d'information dans les domaines des devises, des marchandises et des produits financiers dérivés par un réseau de communication mondial; Courtage de métaux précieux; Services de négociation de cryptomonnaies; Services financiers liés aux crypto-monnaies; Tous les services précités étant uniquement destinés à être utilisés en rapport avec des devises numériques, ainsi que des cryptomonnaies et des devises traditionnelles (fiat).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Financijske usluge, odnosno, Savjetovanje o financijskim pitanjima; Usluge ulaganja kapitala; Financijske usluge za korisnike interneta, Napomena, Financijska analiza, Bankarstvo na mreži i financijsko planiranje na mreži; Financijske usluge u vezi s trgovanjem financijskim instrumentima; Financijsko upravljanje; Financijsko savjetovanje koje pružaju ulagači korisnicima interneta; Online platforma za financijsko upravljanje za trgovanje i razmjenu financijskih instrumenata, Napomena, Online kupoprodaja financijskih instrumenata, dionica, opcija i ostalih derivata; Financijske informacije i analiza; Pružanje informacija o financijama putem web-stranice; Posredništvo u ulaganjima; Financijske informacije u vezi s financijskim tržištima i instrumentima; Financijske informacije pružene korištenjem sučelja za programiranje aplikacija (API); Savjetovanje o financijskim pitanjima; Financijske usluge, odnosno, Pružanje razmjene strane valute, robe i financijskih derivata putem globalne komunikacijske mreže; Pružanje informacija u područjima strane valute, roba i financijskih derivata putem globalne komunikacijske mreže; Posredovanje pri trgovanju plemenitim metalima; Usluge trgovanja kriptovalutama; Financijske usluge u vezi s kriptovalutama; Sve prethodno navedene usluge namijenjene su samo za uporabu u vezi s digitalnim valutama, kao i kriptovalutama te tradicionalnim (fiducijarnim) valutama.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Pénzügyi szolgáltatások, azaz, Pénzügyi tanácsadás; Tőkebefektetés, tőkeberuházás; Pénzügyi szolgáltatások az Internet használói számára, Nevezetesen, Pénzügyi elemzések, Online banki és online pénzügyi tervezés; Pénzügyi szolgáltatások a pénzügyi eszközökkel való kereskedelemmel kapcsolatban; Pénzügyi menedzsment; Pénzügyi tanácsadás a befektetők által az Internet-felhasználóknak; Online platformok pénzügyi menedzsmentje pénzügyi eszközök kereskedelméhez és cseréjéhez, Nevezetesen, Pénzügyi eszközök, részvények, opciók és más származékos termékek online kereskedelme; Pénzügyi tájékoztatás és elemzés; Pénzügyi információk nyújtása weboldalon keresztül; Beruházási ügynöki tevékenység; Pénzügyi piacokra és pénzügyi eszközökre vonatkozó pénzügyi információk; Szolgáltatott pénzügyi információ egy felhasználói program interfész (API) használatához; Pénzügyi tanácsadás; Pénzügyi szolgáltatások, azaz, Külföldi valuta, árucikkek és pénzügyi származékok váltása globális kommunikációs hálózaton keresztül; Információk biztosítása a devizák, árucikkek és pénzügyi származékok területén globális kommunikációs hálózaton keresztül; Nemesfémekkel kapcsolatos bróker szolgáltatások; Internetes valutakereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Kriptovalutákkal kapcsolatos pénzügyi szolgáltatások; Az összes fent említett szolgáltatás kizárólag a digitális valutákkal, valamint a kripto- és a hagyományos (fiat) valutákkal kapcsolatos használatra készült.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi finanziari, ovvero, Consulenza in materia finanziaria; Servizi d'investimento di capitali; Servizi finanziari per utenti di Internet, Ovvero, Analisi finanziaria, Banking online e pianificazione del banking online; Servizi finanziari in materia di compravendita di strumenti finanziari; Amministrazione di patrimoni; Consulenza finanziaria resa da investitori per utenti di Internet; Piattaforme on-line di gestione finanziaria, per la compravendita e scambio di strumenti finanziari, Ovvero, Compravendita on-line di strumenti finanziari, azioni, contratti a premio e altri prodotti derivati; Informazioni e analisi finanziarie; Informazioni finanziarie diffuse tramite siti web; Mediazione in investimenti; Informazioni finanziarie in materia di mercati e strumenti finanziari; Informazioni finanziarie fornite utilizzando un'interfaccia per la programmazione di applicazioni (API); Consulenza in materia finanziaria; Servizi finanziari, ovvero, Offerta del cambio di valuta, merci e derivati finanziari tramite una rete di comunicazione globale; Informazioni in materia di valuta estera, merci, prodotti finanziari derivati tramite una rete di comunicazione globale; Mediazione in metalli preziosi; Servizi di compravendita di criptovaluta; Servizi finanziari relativi alle criptovalute; Tutti i suddetti servizi sono destinati a essere utilizzati solo in relazione a valute digitali, nonché a valute criptate e tradizionali (fiat).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Finansinės paslaugos, būtent, Finansinės konsultacijos; Piniginių lėšų investavimo paslaugos; Finansinės paslaugos interneto vartotojams, Būtent, Finansų analizė, Internetinė bankininkystė ir finansinis planavimas internetu; Finansinės paslaugos, susijusios su prekyba finansinėmis priemonėmis; Finansinės veiklos vadyba; Investuotojų finansinės konsultacijos vartotojams internetu; Internetinė finansų vadybos platforma, skirta finansinių instrumentų prekybai ir mainams, Būtent, Internetinė prekyba finansinėmis priemonėmis, akcijomis, opcionais ir kitomis išvestinėmis priemonėmis; Finansinė informacija ir analizė; Finansinės informacijos teikimas visuotinio kompiuterių tinklo svetainėse; Investicinių sandorių tarpininkavimo paslaugos; Finansinės informacijos teikimas finansinės rinkos ir instrumentų srityse; Finansinė informacija, pateikta naudojant taikomųjų programų sąsają (API); Finansinės konsultacijos; Finansinės paslaugos, būtent, Užsienio valiutos kurso, biržos prekių ir finansinių išvestinių produktų teikimas visuotiniu ryšių tinklu; Informacijos, susijusios su užsienio valiutomis, prekėmis ir išvestinėmis finansinėmis priemonėmis, teikimas visuotiniais ryšių tinklais; Tarpininkavimas prekiaujant brangiaisiais metalais; Prekybos kripto valiuta paslaugos; Finansinės paslaugos, susijusios su kriptovaliuta; Visos minėtos paslaugos yra skirtos naudoti tik su skaitmeninėmis valiutomis, taip pat su kriptovaliutomis ir tradicinėmis (fiat) valiutomis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Finanšu pakalpojumi, proti, Konsultāciju sniegšana finanšu jomā; Fondu investīciju pakalpojumi; Finanšu pakalpojumi interneta lietotājiem, Proti, Finanšu analīzes nodrošināšana, Tiešsaistes banku darbība un tiešsaistes finanšu plānošana; Finanšu pakalpojumi saistībā ar finanšu instrumentu tirdzniecību; Finanšu pārvaldība; Investoru finansiālās konsultācijas interneta lietotāju labā; Tiešsaistes platformas finansiālā pārvaldība finanšu instrumentu tirdzniecībai un apmaiņai, Proti, Finanšu instrumentu, akciju, komerctiesību līgumu un citu atvasinātu produktu tirdzniecība tiešsaistē; Finanšu informācija un analīze; Finanšu informācijas sniegšana tīmekļa vietnēs; Ieguldījumu starpniecības pakalpojumi; Finanšu informācija saistībā ar finanšu tirgu un instrumentiem; Finanšu informācija, kas nodrošināta izmantojot lietotņu programmēšanas saskarni (API); Konsultāciju sniegšana finanšu jomā; Finanšu pakalpojumi, proti, Ārzemju valūtas, patēriņa preču un finanšu atvasinājumu nodrošināšana apmaiņai, izmantojot globālo sakaru tīklu; Informācijas nodrošināšana ārzemju valūtas, patēriņa preču un finanšu atvasinājumu jomā, izmantojot globālo komunikāciju tīklu; Dārgmetālu starpniecības pakalpojumi; Kriptovalūtas tirdzniecības pakalpojumi; Finanšu pakalpojumi ar kriptovalūtām; Visi iepriekšminētie pakalpojumi ir paredzēti izmantošanai tikai saistībā ar digitālajām valūtām, kā arī ar kriptovalūtām un tradicionālajām [papīra naudas] valūtām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi finanzjarji, jiġifieri, Konsulenza finanzjarja; Servizzi ta' investiment ta' fondi; Servizzi finanzjarji għall-utenti tal-Internet, Jiġifieri, Analiżi (Finanzjarja), Servizzi bankarji online u ppjanar finanzjarju online; Servizzi finanzjarji relatati mal-kummerċ ta' strumenti finanzjarji; Ġestjoni tal-finanzi; Konsulenza finanzjarja minn investituri lill-utenti fuq l-Internet; Pjattaforma onlajn tal-ġestjoni finanzjarja għan-negozju u l-iskambju ta' strumenti finanzjarji, Jiġifieri, Negozjar onlajn ta' strumenti finanzjarji, ishma, opzjonijiet u prodotti derivati oħra; Informazzjoni u analiżi finanzjarji; Forniment ta' informazzjoni finanzjarja permezz ta' sit web; Senserija fuq l-investimenti; Informazzjoni finanzjarja dwar swieq u strumenti finanzjarji; Informazzjoni finanzjarja pprovduta li tuża' interfaċċja tal-ipprogrammar ta' applikazzjoni (APIs); Konsulenza finanzjarja; Servizzi finanzjarji, jiġifieri, Provvista għal skambju ta' muniti barranin, komoditajiet u derivattivi finanzjarji permezz ta' netwerk tal-komunikazzjonijiet globali; Il-provvista ta' informazzjoni fl-oqsma ta' muniti barranin, prodotti bażiċi, derivati finanzjarji permezz ta' netwerk ta' komunikazzjoni globali; Senserija fuq metalli prezzjużi; Servizzi ta' negozju b'muniti kriptografiċi; Servizzi finanzjarji b'rabta ma' kripromuniti; Is-servizzi kollha msemmija qabel huma maħsuba biss biex jintużaw f'rabta mal-valuti diġitali, kif ukoll il-kriptovaluti u l-valuti tradizzjonali (fiat).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Financiële diensten, te weten, Advisering op financieel gebied; Kapitaalinvesteringsdiensten; Financiële diensten voor gebruikers van internet, Te weten, Financiële analyse, Onlinebankieren en financiële onlineplanning; Financiële diensten in verband met de handel in financiële instrumenten; Financieel beheer; Financieel advies van beleggers aan gebruikers van internet; Onlineplatform voor financieel beheer voor het verhandelen en uitwisselen van financiële instrumenten, Te weten, Onlinehandel in financiële instrumenten, aandelen, opties en andere derivaten; Financiële informatie en analyse; Verschaffen van financiële informatie via websites; Makelaardij in investeringen; Financiële informatie met betrekking tot financiële markten en instrumenten; Het verstrekken van financiële informatie door middel van een applicatieprogramma-interface (API); Advisering op financieel gebied; Financiële diensten, te weten, Verschaffing van beurzen voor de handel in vreemde valuta, termijngoederen en financiële derivaten via een wereldwijd communicatienetwerk; Verstrekking van informatie op het gebied van valutahandel, handel in financiële instrumenten ter verkleining van het financieringsrisico van goederentransacties en financiële derivaten via een wereldwijd communicatienetwerk; Makelaardij in edele metalen; Handel in cryptovaluta; Financiële diensten met betrekking tot cryptovaluta's; Alle voornoemde diensten zijn uitsluitend voor gebruik met betrekking tot digitale valuta alsmede cryptovaluta en traditionele valuta (vertrouwensmunten).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi finansowe, mianowicie:, Doradztwo w sprawach finansowych; Usługi związane z funduszami inwestycyjnymi; Usługi finansowe dla użytkowników internetu, Mianowicie, Analizy finansowe, Bankowość online i planowanie finansów online; Usługi finansowe w zakresie handlu instrumentami finansowymi; Zarządzanie finansami; Zarządzanie finansowe inwestorów na rzecz użytkowników internetu; Platforma online w zakresie zarządzania finansowego do handlu i wymiany instrumentów finansowych, Mianowicie, Handel online instrumentami finansowymi, udziałami, opcjami i innymi derywatywami; Informacje i analizy finansowe; Udostępnianie informacji finansowych za pośrednictwem strony internetowej; Inwestycyjne usługi brokerskie; Informacje finansowe dotyczące instrumentów i rynków finansowych; Informacje finansowe udostępniane z użyciem interfejsu programowania aplikacji (API); Doradztwo w sprawach finansowych; Usługi finansowe, mianowicie:, Umożliwianie wymiany walut, towarów i finansowych instrumentów pochodnych za pośrednictwem globalnej sieci łącznościowej; Udzielanie informacji w zakresie walut obcych, towarów, derywatyw finansowych przez globalną sieć internetową; Maklerstwo w zakresie metali szlachetnych; Usługi obrotu kryptowalutą; Usługi finansowe związane z kryptowalutami; Wszystkie wyżej wymienione usługi przeznaczone wyłącznie do użytku w związku z cyfrowymi walutami oraz kryptowalutami i walutami tradycyjnymi (fiat).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços financeiros, nomeadamente, Consultadoria financeira; Serviços de investimento de capitais; Serviços financeiros para utilizadores da Internet, Nomeadamente, Análise financeira, Serviços bancários em linha e planeamento financeiro em linha; Serviços financeiros relacionados com a transação de instrumentos financeiros; Administração financeira; Consultadoria financeira prestada por investidores a utilizadores da Internet; Plataformas de gestão financeira em linha para comercialização e transação em bolsa de instrumentos financeiros, Nomeadamente, Transacção em linha de instrumentos financeiros, acções, opções e outros produtos derivados; Informações e análises financeiras; Fornecimento de informações financeiras através de um website; Serviços de corretagem de investimentos; Informações financeiras relacionadas com mercados e instrumentos financeiros; Informações financeiras fornecidas através de uma interface de programação de aplicações (API); Consultadoria financeira; Serviços financeiros, nomeadamente, Serviços de transações de divisas, mercadorias e derivados financeiros através de uma rede mundial de comunicações; Fornecimento de informações nos domínios das divisas, mercadorias e derivados financeiros, através de uma rede de comunicações mundial; Corretagem de metais preciosos; Serviços de transação de criptomoeda; Serviços financeiros relacionados com criptomoedas; Todos os serviços atrás referidos destinados exclusivamente a ser utilizados no domínio das moedas digitais, bem como das criptomoedas e moedas fiduciárias tradicionais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii financiare, şi anume, Consultații în domeniul financiar; Servicii de investiţii de capital; Servicii financiare pentru utilizatorii de internet, Şi anume, Analiză financiară, Operațiuni bancare online și planificare financiară online; Servicii financiare referitoare la tranzacţionare de instrumente financiare; Management financiar; Consultanţă financiară oferită de investitori utilizatorilor de internet; Platformă online pentru administraţie financiară pentru tranzacţionarea şi schimbul instrumentelor financiare, Şi anume, Comercializare on-line de instrumente financiare, acţiuni, opţiuni şi alte produse derivate; Informaţii şi analize financiare; Furnizare de informații financiare prin intermediul unui site; Servicii de brokeraj pentru investiţii; Furnizarea de informaţii cu privire la pieţe şi instrumente financiare; Informaţii financiare furnizate utilizând o interfaţă pentru programarea aplicaţiilor (API); Consultații în domeniul financiar; Servicii financiare, şi anume, Furnizarea de valută pentru schimb, de mărfuri şi de derivative financiare, printr-o reţea globală de comunicaţii; Furnizarea de informaţii în domeniul valutei, mărfurilor şi derivatelor financiare printr-o reţea globală de comunicaţii; Brokeraj de metale prețioase; Servicii de tranzacţionare de criptovalută; Servicii financiare în legătură cu criptovaluta; Toate serviciile susmenționate destinate doar pentru a fi folosite în legătură cu monede digitale, precum și criptomonede și monede tradiționale (fiduciare).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Finančné služby, menovite, Finančné poradenstvo; Služby týkajúce sa fondových investicií; Finančné služby pre internetových používateľov, Menovite, Finančné analýzy, On-line bankovníctvo a on-line finančné plánovanie; Finančné služby v oblasti obchodovania s finančnými nástrojmi; Finančné riadenie; Finančné konzultácie od investorov pre internetových používateľov; Finančná správa on-line platformy pre obchodovanie a výmenu finančných nástrojov, Menovite, On-line obchodovanie s finančnými nástrojmi, akciami, opciami a inými derivovanými produktami; Finančné informácie a analýzy; Poskytovanie finančných informácií prostredníctvom webových stránok; Sprostredkovateľské služby v oblasti investícií; Finančné informácie v oblasti finančných trhov a nástrojov; Finančné informácie poskytované pomocou aplikačného programovacieho rozhrania (API); Finančné poradenstvo; Finančné služby, menovite, Poskytovanie výmeny devíz, komodít a finančných derivátov prostredníctvom globálnej komunikačnej siete; Poskytovanie informácií v oblasti devíz, komodít a finančných derivátov prostredníctvom globálnej komunikačnej siete; Maklérstvo v oblasti drahých kovov; Služby obchodovania s kryptomenami; Finančné služby v súvislosti s kryptomenami; Všetky vyššie uvedené služby súvisia výlučne s digitálnymi menami, ako aj kryptomenami a tradičnými (fiatovými) menami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Finančni posli, in sicer, Finančno svetovanje; Storitve investiranja kapitala; Finančne storitve za uporabnike interneta, In sicer, Finančna analiza, Spletno bančništvo in spletno finančno načrtovanje; Finančne storitve, povezane s trgovanjem s finančnimi instrumenti; Finančno upravljanje; Finančno svetovanje vlagateljev uporabnikom interneta; Spletna platforma finančnega upravljanje za trgovanje in izmenjavo finančnih instrumentov, In sicer, Spletno trgovanje s finančnimi instrumenti, deleži, opcijami in drugimi izvedenimi produkti; Finančne informacije in analiza; Nudenje finančnih informacij preko spletne strani; Storitve investicijskega posredništva; Finančne informacije o finančnih trgih in instrumentih; Finančne informacije, ki so nudene z uporabo programskih vmesnikov (API); Finančno svetovanje; Finančni posli, in sicer, Nudenje menjave tuje valute, blaga in izvedenih finančnih instrumentov preko svetovnega komunikacijskega omrežja; Nudenje informacij s področja tujih valut, borznega blaga in izvedenih finančnih instrumentov preko svetovnega komunikacijskega omrežja; Posredovanje pri trgovanju s plemenitimi kovinami; Storitve trgovanja s kriptovalutami; finančne storitve v zvezi s kripto valutami; Vse prej navedene storitve so namenjene le za uporabo v zvezi z digitalnimi valutami ter kripto in klasičnimi (fiat) valutami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Finansiella tjänster, nämligen, Finansiella konsultationer; Fondinvestering; Finansiella tjänster för Internetanvändare, Nämligen, Finansiella analyser, Direktanslutna banktjänster och direktansluten finansiell planering; Finansiella tjänster i samband med handel med finansiella instrument; Finansiell förvaltning; Finansiell rådgivning av investerare till internetanvändare; Finansiell förvaltning av direktanslutna plattformar för handel och utbyte av finansiella instrument, Nämligen, Direktansluten handel med finansiella instrument, aktier, optioner och andra derivatprodukter; Finansiell information och analys; Upplåtande av finansiell information via en hemsida; Investeringsmäkleritjänster; Finansiell information avseende finansmarknader och -instrument; Ekonomisk information tillhandahållen genom användning av gränssnitt för tillämpningsprogram (API:s); Finansiella konsultationer; Finansiella tjänster, nämligen, Handel med valuta, råvaror och derivat via globalt kommunikationsnät; Upplåtande av information avseende utländsk valuta, råvaror, finansiella derivat via ett globalt kommunikationsnät; Mäkleri avseende ädelmetaller; Handel med kryptovaluta; Finansiella tjänster i samband med kryptovalutor; Samtliga nämnda tjänster är endast avsedda att användas i samband med digitala valutor, såväl som kryptovalutor och traditionella (fiat) valutor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/083</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-05</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080448</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>30737</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
