<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-05T16:31:36</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226176</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226176</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-31</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Eonpam</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Калъфи за смартфони; Калъфи за таблети; Слушалки; Защитни тънкослойни покрития, пригодени за смартфони; Микрофони; Компютърни клавиатури; Безжични компютърни мишки; Компютърни мишки; Слушалки; 3D очила; Слънчеви очила; Фотографски обективи; Видеокамери, приспособени за наблюдаване; Електронни уреди за наблюдение; Смартфони; Кодирани идентификационни гривни, магнитни; Устройства за четене на карти; Аудио апаратура; Антени за радиосигнали; Адаптори за енергия.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pouzdra na chytré telefony (smartphony); Pouzdra na tabletové počítače; Sluchátka; Ochranné fólie na chytré telefony; Mikrofony; Počítačové klávesnice; Bezdrátové počítačové myši; Počítačové myši; Sluchátka; 3D brýle; Sluneční brýle; Fotografické objektivy; Videokamery přizpůsobené pro účely monitorování; Elektronická sledovací zařízení; Chytré telefony (smartphony); Magnetické kódované identifikační náramky; Čtečky karet; Audio přístroje a zařízení; Antény na rozhlasový signál; Adaptéry elektrického proudu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Etuier til smartphones; Etuier til tablet-computere; Hovedtelefoner; Beskyttelsesfilm tilpasset til smartphones; Mikrofoner; Numeriske tastaturer til computere; Trådløse computermus; Computermus; Hovedtelefoner; 3D briller; Solbriller; Fotografiske linser; Videokameraer til overvågningsformål; Elektronisk overvågningsudstyr; Smartphones; Magnetiske indkodede identifikationsarmbånd; Kortlæserudstyr; Audioapparater; Antenner til radiosignaler; Elektrisk strømadaptere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Schalen für Smartphones; Etuis für Tablet-Computer; Kopfhörer; Angepasste Schutzfolien für Smartphones; Mikrofone; Tastaturen für Computer; Drahtlose Computermäuse; Computermaus; Kopfhörer; 3D-Brillen; Sonnenbrillen; Fotografische Linsen; Videokameras für Überwachungszwecke; Elektronische Überwachungsgeräte; Smartphones; Codierte Identifikationsarmbänder, magnetisch; Kartenlesegeräte; Audiogeräte; Funksignalantennen; Stromadapter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Θήκες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Θήκες για φορητούς ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Κάσκες ακουστικών· Προστατευτικές μεμβράνες προσαρμοσμένες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Μικρόφωνα· Πληκτρολόγια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Ασύρματα ποντίκια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Ποντίκια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Ακουστικά κεφαλής με μικρόφωνο· Γυαλιά 3D· Γυαλιά ηλίου· Φωτογραφικοί φακοί· Βιντεοκάμερες προσαρμοσμένες για χρήσεις παρακολούθησης· Ηλεκτρονικές συσκευές παρακολούθησης· Έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Μαγνητικά κωδικοποιημένα περιβραχιόνια αναγνώρισης ταυτότητας· Εξοπλισμός ανάγνωσης καρτών· Συσκευές ήχου· Κεραίες ραδιοσήματος· Μετασχηματιστές ηλεκτρικής ισχύος.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Protective cases for smartphones; protective cases for tablet computers; headphones; protective films adapted for smartphones; microphones; computer keypads; wireless computer mice; computer mice; headsets; 3D spectacles; sunglasses; lenses for photographic apparatus; video surveillance cameras; electronic surveillance apparatus; smartphones; encoded identification bracelets, magnetic; card readers; audio equipment; radio signal antennas; power adapters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Estuches para teléfonos inteligentes; Estuches para ordenadores tipo tablilla; Auriculares; Películas de protección para teléfonos inteligentes [smartphones]; Micrófonos; Teclados numéricos para ordenadores; Ratones de ordenador inalámbricos; Ratones de ordenador; Cascos con micrófono; Gafas 3D; Gafas de sol; Lentes fotográficas; Videocámaras adaptadas para la monitorización; Aparatos electrónicos de vigilancia; Teléfonos inteligentes [smartphones]; Pulseras de identificación codificadas magnéticas; Equipos lectores de tarjetas; Aparatos de audio; Antenas para señales radioeléctricas; Adaptadores de corriente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Nutitelefonide ümbrised; Tahvelarvutite vutlarid; Kõrvaklapid; Nutitelefonide kaitsekiled; Mikrofonid; Arvutiklaviatuurid; Juhtmeta arvutihiired; Arvutihiired; Mikrofoniga kõrvaklapid; 3D-prillid; Päikeseprillid; Fotoobjektiivid; Videokaamerad jälgimise otstarbel; Elektroonilised seireseadmed; Nutitelefonid; Kodeeritud, identifitseerivad magnetkäevõrud; Kaardilugejad; Heliseadmed; Raadiosignaaliantennid; Elektritoiteadapterid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Älypuhelinten kuoret; Taulutietokoneille tarkoitetut kotelot; Kuulokkeet; Älypuhelimille tarkoitetut suojakalvot; Mikrofonit; Tietokoneiden näppäimistöt; Langattomat tietokoneiden hiiret; Tietokonehiiret; Kuulokkeet; 3D-silmälasit; Aurinkolasit; Valokuvausobjektiivit; Videovalvontakamerat; Elektroniset valvontalaitteet; Älypuhelimet; Koodatut tunnistusrannekkeet, magneettiset; Kortinlukijat; Audiolaitteet; Radiosignaaliantennit; Verkkomuuntajat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Étuis pour smartphones; Etuis pour tablettes électroniques; Casques à écouteurs; Films de protection conçus pour ordiphones [smartphones]; Microphones; Pavés numériques d'ordinateurs; Souris sans fil pour ordinateurs; Souris d'ordinateur; Casques d'écoute; Lunettes 3D; Lunettes de soleil; Objectifs photographiques; Caméras de surveillance; Appareils électroniques de surveillance; Ordiphones [smartphones]; Bracelets magnétiques d'identification; Lecteurs de cartes; Appareils audio; Antennes pour signaux radio; Adaptateurs de courant.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Etuiji za pametne telefone; Futrole za tablet računala; Slušalice; Zaštitne folije prilagođene za pametne telefone; Mikrofoni; Računalne tipkovnice; Bežični računalni miševi; Računalni miševi; Slušalice; 3D naočale; Sunčane naočale; Fotografske leće; Kamere za video nadzor; Elektronički nadzorni sustav; Pametni telefoni; Identifikacijske magnetne narukvice; Oprema za čitanje kartica; Audio uređaji; Antene za radijski signal; Strujni adapteri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tokok okostelefonhoz; Tokok táblagépekhez; Fejhallgatók; Védőfóliák okostelefonokhoz; Mikrofonok; Számítógépes billentyűzetek; Vezeték nélküli számítógépes egerek; Számítógépes egerek; Fejhallgatók; Háromdimenziós szemüvegek; Napszemüvegek; Fényképészeti lencsék; Monitorozási, megfigyelési célokra kialakított videokamerák; Elektronikus felügyeleti eszközök; Okostelefonok; Kódolt azonosító karkötők, mágneses; Kártyaolvasó készülékek, berendezések; Audio berendezések; Antennák rádiójel vezérlésű eszközökhöz; Elektromos hálózati adapterek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Custodie per smartphones; Custodie per tablet; Cuffie per la musica; Pellicola protettiva adattata per smartphone; Microfoni; Tastierini per computer; Mouse senza fili; Mouse per computer; Occhiali per 3D; Occhiali da sole; Obiettivi fotografici; Telecamere di sorveglianza; Apparecchi elettronici di sorveglianza; Smartphone; Braccialetti magnetici di identificazione; Apparecchiature per la lettura di schede; Apparecchi audio; Antenne per segnali radio; Adattatori per alimentazioni elettriche; Cuffie per la musica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Išmaniųjų telefonų dėklai; Planšetinių kompiuterių dangteliai; Radijo ausinės; Išmaniųjų telefonų ekranų apsauginės plėvelės; Mikrofonai; Kompiuterių klaviatūros; Belaidės kompiuterių pelės; Kompiuterių pelės; Ausinės; 3D akiniai; Saulės akiniai; Fotografiniai lęšiai; Vaizdo kameros stebėjimo reikmėms; Elektroniniai stebėjimo aparatai; Išmanieji telefonai; Koduotos magnetinės identifikavimo apyrankės; Kortelių skaitymo įranga; Garso aparatūra; Radijo signalų antenos; Elektros galios adapteriai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Viedtālruņu maciņi; Planšetdatoru futrāļi; Austiņas; Aizsargplēves, kas īpaši paredzētas viedtālruņiem; Mikrofoni; Datoru papildtastatūras; Bezvadu datorpeles; Datorpele; Radioaustiņas; Brilles attēlu uztverei trīsdimensiju (3D) formātā; Saulesbrilles; Fotoobjektīvi; Videokameras pielāgotas novērošanas nolūkiem; Elektroniski aparāti uzraudzībai; Viedtālruņi; Kodētas magnētiskās identifikācijas rokassprādzes; Karšu lasīšanas aprīkojums; Audioierīces; Radio signāla antenas; Strāvas adapteri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kaxxi għall-ismartphones; Kaxxetti għal kompjuters stil tablet; Kuffji; Films protettivi adattati għal smartfowns; Mikrofoni; Tastieri tal-kompjuter; Maws tal-kompjuter mingħajr fili; Maws tal-kompjuter; Kuffji; Nuċċalijiet 3D; Nuċċalijiet tax-xemx; Lentijiet tal-fotografija; Vidjowkameras għas-sorveljanza; Apparat elettroniku tas-sorveljanza; Smartfowns; Brazzuletti tal-identifikazzjoni kodifikati, manjetiċi; Apparat għall-qari ta' kards; Apparat tal-awdjo; Antenni tas-sinjali tar-radju; Adapters tal-enerġija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Etuis voor smartphones; Hoezen voor tablets; Hoofdtelefoons; Beschermende folie aangepast aan smartphones; Microfoons; Computer toetsenborden; Computermuizen (Draadloze -); Computermuis; Hoofdtelefoons; 3D-brillen; Zonnebrillen; Objectieven voor de fotografie; Videocamera' s voor bewakingsdoeleinden; Elektronische bewakingsapparaten; Smartphones; Magnetische identiteitspolsbanden; Kaartlezers; Audio-apparatuur; Antennes voor radiosignalen; Stroom adapters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Etui na smartfony; Etui do tabletów; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Folie ochronne dostosowane do smartfonów; Mikrofony; Klawiatury komputerowe; Bezprzewodowe myszy do komputerów; Myszki komputerowe; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Okulary 3D; Okulary przeciwsłoneczne; Obiektywy fotograficzne; Kamery wideo przystosowane do celów monitoringowych; Urządzenia elektroniczne do monitoringu; Smartfony; Kodowane identyfikacyjne bransoletki magnetyczne; Sprzęt do odczytywania kart; Sprzęt audio; Anteny do sygnałów radiowych; Zasilacze sieciowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Capas para smartphones; Malas concebidas para computadores "tablet"; Auriculares; Películas protetoras adaptadas para smartphones; Microfones; Teclados numéricos de computador; Ratos de computador sem fios; Ratos para computador; Auriculares; Óculos 3D; Óculos de sol; Lentes fotográficas; Câmaras de vídeo para fins de monitorização; Aparelhos de vigilância eletrónica; Smartphones; Braceletes de identificação codificadas, magnéticas; Equipamento para leitura de cartões; Aparelhos de áudio; Antenas para sinais de rádio; Adaptadores de corrente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Carcase pentru telefoane inteligente; Huse pentru calculatoare tabletă; Căști audio; Folii de protecție adaptate pentru telefoane inteligente; Microfoane; Tastaturi de calculatoare; Mouse-uri de calculator fără fir; Mouse-uri pentru computer; Căști; Ochelari 3D; Ochelari de soare; Lentile fotografice; Camere video de supraveghere; Aparate electronice de supraveghere; Telefoane inteligente; Brățări de identificare magnetice și codificate; Dispozitive pentru citirea cardurilor; Aparatură audio; Antene pentru semnale radio; Adaptoare de curent.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Puzdrá na smartfóny; Puzdrá na tabletové počítače; Slúchadlá; Ochranné fólie na smartfóny; Mikrofóny; Počítačové klávesnice; Bezdrôtové počítačové myši; Počítačové myši; Slúchadlá s mikrofónom; 3D okuliare; Slnečné okuliare; Fotografické objektívy; Videokamery na prispôsobené na monitorovacie účely; Monitorovacie elektronické zariadenia; Smartfóny; Identifikačné magnetické náramky; Zariadenia na čítanie kariet; Zvukové zariadenia; Antény pre rádiové signály; Elektrické adaptéry.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Etuiji za pametne telefone; Etuiji za tablične računalnike; Slušalke; Zaščitne folije, prilagojene za pametne telefone; Mikrofoni; Računalniške tipkovnice; Brezžične računalniške miške; Računalniške miške; Slušalke; 3D očala; Sončna očala; Fotografske leče; Video kamere, prilagojene za spremljanje; Elektronski nadzorni aparati; Pametni telefoni; Kodirana magnetna identifikacijska zapestnica; Oprema za branje kartic; Avdio aparati; Antene za radijske signale; Adapterji za električno omrežje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Skal för smartphones; Fodral för surfplattor; On-ear hörlurar; Skyddsfilm för smartphones; Mikrofoner; Datortangentbord; Trådlösa datormöss; Datormusar; Headsets; 3D-glasögon; Solglasögon; Fotografiska linser; Videokameror anpassade för övervakningsändamål; Elektroniska övervakningsapparater; Smartphones; Kodade identifieringsarmband, magnetiska; Kortläsningsutrustning; Ljudapparater; Antenner för radiosignaler; Nätadaptrar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Съдове за хранене на домашни любимци; Тоалетни кутии за домашни любимци; Котешки клозети; Гребени за тупиране на коса; Хранилки за малки животни; Немеханизирани хранилки за животни; Електронни хранилки на домашни любимци; Домакински контейнери за съхранение на храна за домашни любимци; Клетки, кафези за домашни любимци; Купички за хранене и пиене за домашни любимци; Четки за домашни любимци; Форми за сладки; Формички за кубчета лед за хладилници; Лъжици за поливане на месо при печене [прибори за готвене]; Тел за разбиване, неелектрическа, за домакински цели; Бъркалки, неелектрически; Кухненски принадлежности, не от благороден метал; Стойки за дрехи [за изсушаване]; Кутии за сапун; Кутии за сапун.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nádoby na potravu pro domácí zvířata; Toalety pro zvířata; Toalety pro kočky; Tupírovací hřebeny; Krmítka pro malá zvířata; Nemechanizovaná zařízení na krmení zvířat; Elektronická krmná zařízení pro domácí zvířata; Nádoby do domácnosti k ukládání krmiva pro domácí zvířata; Klece pro domácí zvířata; Misky na krmení a pití pro domácí zvířata; Kartáče na domácí mazlíčky; Formy na cukrovinky; Formy na ledové kostky do chladniček; Lžíce na polévání [kuchyňské náčiní]; Metličky pro použití v domácnosti, ne elektrické; Šlehače, ne elektrické; Kuchyňské potřeby; Prádelní sušáky; Držáky na mýdlo; Krabičky na mýdlo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Foderskåle til kæledyr; Afføringsbakker til kæledyr; Kattetoiletter; Kamme til at toupere hår; Foderanordninger til små dyr; Dyrefodringsautomater, ikke mekaniske; Elektroniske foderanordninger til kæledyr; Opbevaringsbeholdere til dyrefoder til husholdningsbrug; Bure til husdyr; Mad- og drikkeskåle til kæledyr; Børster til kæledyr; Forme til konditorbrug; Isterningeforme til køleskabe; Dryppeskeer [redskaber til madlavning]; Piskere, ikke elektriske, til husholdningsformål; Piskere, ikke elektriske; Køkkenredskaber; Tørrestativer til tøj; Sæbeholdere; Sæbeæsker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Futternäpfe für Haustiere; Streukästen für Haustiere; Katzenstreuschalen; Toupierkämme; Futtergefäße für Kleintiere; Nichtmechanische Tierfutterspender; Elektronische Futterspender für Haustiere; Haushaltsbehälter zum Aufbewahren von Haustierfutter; Transportkäfige für Haustiere; Wasser- und Futternäpfe für Haustiere; Bürsten für Haustiere; Konditorformen; Eiswürfelformen für Kühlschränke; Gießlöffel [Küchenutensilien]; Nicht elektrische Schneebesen für den Haushalt; Nicht elektrische Rührgeräte; Küchengeräte; Ständer zum Lüften von Bekleidungsstücken; Seifenhalter, -schalen; Seifendosen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Πιάτα ταΐσματος για κατοικίδια· Κάδοι καθαριότητας κατοικίδιων ζώων· Κουτιά για την αφόδευση γατών,· Χτένες για κρεπάρισμα· Ταΐστρες για μικρά ζώα· Μη μηχανικές ταΐστρες ζώων· Ηλεκτρονικές ταΐστρες για κατοικίδια ζώα· Δοχεία οικιακής φύλαξης τροφών για κατοικίδια ζώα· Κλουβιά για ζώα κατοικίδια· Γαβάθες ταΐσματος και πόσης για κατοικίδια ζώα· Βούρτσες για κατοικίδια ζώα· Φόρμες για ζαχαρώδη· Παγοθήκες ψυγείου· Κουτάλες σούπας [μαγειρικά σκεύη]· Σύρμα κτυπήματος μη ηλεκτρικό· Χτυπητήρια μη ηλεκτρικά· Σκεύη μαγειρικής χρήσης· Απλώστρες ρούχων, για στέγνωμα· Σαπουνοθήκες· Σαπουνοθήκες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">pet feeding bowls; litter boxes for pets; cat litter boxes; combs for back-combing hair; small animal feeders; non-mechanized animal feeders; electronic pet feeders; household containers for storing pet food; cages for household pets; pet feeding and drinking bowls; brushes for pets; pastry molds; ice cube molds for refrigerators; basting spoons [cooking utensils]; whisks, non-electric, for household purposes; Non-electric egg beaters; kitchen utensils; clothes drying racks; soap holders; soap boxes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Contenedores de alimentos para animales de compañía; Bandejas higiénicas para animales de compañía; Cajones higiénicos con arena para gatos; Peines para cardar el cabello; Comederos para animales pequeños; Dispositivos alimentadores no mecanizados para animales; Distribuidores electrónicos de alimentos para animales de compañía; Recipientes de almacenamiento doméstico para comida de animales de compañía; Jaulas para animales de compañía; Cuencos de comida y bebida para animales domésticos; Cepillos para animales de compañía; Moldes de confitería; Moldes de cubitos de hielo para refrigeradores; Cucharones [utensilios de cocina]; Batidores no eléctricos para uso doméstico; Batidoras no eléctricas; Utensilios de cocina; Secadores [tendederos] de ropa; Portajabones [jaboneras]; Jaboneras [estuches].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Lemmikloomade toidumahutid; Lemmikloomade käimlakastid; Kassiliivakastid; Tupeerimiskammid; Väikeloomade sööturid; Mittemehaanilised loomasööturid; Lemmikloomade elektroonilised toitmisseadmed; Lemmikloomatoidu hoidmise mahutid kodumajapidamistele; Lemmikloomapuurid; Lemmikloomade söögi- ja joogikausid; Lemmikloomaharjad; Kondiitrivormid; Külmikute jääkuubikuvormid; Kastmelusikad [köögiriistad]; Majapidamisvisplid, v.a elektrilised; Klopitsad, v.a elektrilised; Köögitarbed; Pesukuivatusrestid; Seebialused; Seebikarbid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lemmikkieläinten ruoka-astiat; Lemmikkieläinten kuivikelaatikot; Kissanhiekkalaatikot; Tupeerauskammat; Pieneläinten syöttölaitteet; Mekanisoimattomat eläinten syöttölaitteet; Elektroniset lemmikkieläinten syöttölaitteet; Kotitalouksien säilytysastiat lemmikkieläinten ravinnolle; Lemmikkieläimille tarkoitetut häkit; Lemmikkieläinten ruoka- ja juomakupit; Lemmikkieläinten harjat; Leivonnaisvuoat; Jääpalamuotit jääkaappeihin; Valelulusikat (keittiövälineet); Vispilät kotitalouskäyttöön, ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Vatkaimet, ei sähkökäyttöiset; Keittokattilasarjat; Vaatteiden kuivaustelineet; Saippuarasiat; Saippuatelineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Gamelles pour animaux de compagnie; Bacs à litière pour animaux de compagnie; Bacs à litière pour chats; Peignes pour crêper les cheveux; Distributeurs d'aliments pour petits animaux; Distributeurs non mécanisés d'aliments pour animaux; Distributeurs électroniques d'aliments pour animaux de compagnie; Récipients ménagers pour entreposer des aliments d'animaux domestiques; Cages pour animaux d'intérieur; Écuelles pour la nourriture et la boisson pour animaux domestiques; Brosses pour animaux de compagnie; Moules à pâtisserie; Bacs à glaçons pour réfrigérateurs; Cuillères pour arroser la viande [ustensiles de cuisson]; Fouets non électriques à usage ménager; Batteurs non électriques; Ustensiles de cuisine; Séchoirs à lessive; Porte-savon; Boîtes à savon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Posude za hranjenje kućnih ljubimaca; Kutije s pijeskom za kućne ljubimce; Posude za pijesak za mačke; Češljevi za tapiranje kose; Hranilice za male životinje; Nemehaničke hranilice za životinje; Električne hranilice za kućne ljubimce; Posude za kućanstvo za držanje hrane za kućne ljubimce; Kavezi za kućne ljubimce; Zdjele za hranu i piće za kućne ljubimce; Četke za kućne ljubimce; Slastičarski kalupi; Kalupi za kockice leda za hladnjake; Žlice za polijevanje hrane [kuhinjsko posuđe]; Miješalice za kućanstvo (neelektrične mlatilice za kućanstvo); Mutilice [neelektrične]; Posuđe (kuhinjsko metalno posuđe); Stalci za sušenje odjeće; Kutije za sapun; Kutije za sapun.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ételtartók kedvtelésből tartott kisállatoknak; Alomtálcák házi kedvenceknek; Macskaalom tálcák; Tupírfésűk; Kisállatetetők; Nem gépesített állatetetők; Elektronikus kisállat-etetők; Háztartási tárolóedények kisállatoknak készült eledel tárolására; Ketrecek kedvtelésből tartott állatok részére; Etető- és ivócsészék kisállatok számára; Kefék kedvtelésből tartott állatok, kisállatok ápolására; Cukrász sablonok, formák; Jégkockaformák hűtőszekrényekhez; Spicckanalak [konyhai eszközök]; Kézi habverők, nem elektromos, háztartási használatra; Habverők, nem elektromos; Konyhai eszközök, kis méretű; Ruhaszárító állványok; Szappantartók; Szappantartók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Vaschette per alimenti per animali da compagnia; Cassette igieniche per animali domestici; Vaschette (lettiere) per gatti; Pettini per cotonare i capelli; Articoli per l'alimentazione di piccoli animali; Distributori di cibo per animali non elettrici; Distributori elettronici di cibo per animali domestici; Contenitori per conservare alimenti per animali da compagnia per uso domestico; Gabbiette per animali domestici; Mangimi per animali domestici e ciotole per abbeveratoi; Spazzole per animali domestici; Stampi per confetteria; Stampi per cubetti di ghiaccio per freezer; Cucchiai per bagnare la carne [utensili da cucina]; Frullatori non elettrici per uso familiare; Battitori non elettrici; Utensili da cucina; Stenditoi per bucato; Porta-sapone; Scatole per sapone.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kambarinių gyvūnėlių šėrimo dubenys; Pakratų dėžutės naminiams gyvūnėliams; Kačių kraiko dėžutės; Šukos, skirtos plaukams velti; Smulkių gyvūnų pašaro tiektuvai; Ne mechanizuotos gyvūnų šėryklos; Elektroninės šėryklos; Buitiniai indai kambarinių gyvūnų ėdalui laikyti; Naminių gyvūnėlių narveliai; Naminių gyvūnų šėrimo ir gėrimo dubenys; Šepečiai (Naminių gyvūnų -); Konditerinės formos; Šaldytuvų ledo kubelių formelės; Šaukštai kepsniams laistyti [virtuvės reikmenys]; Ne elektriniai buitiniai plaktuvai; Ne elektriniai plaktuvai; Virtuviniai indai; Drabužių džiovyklos; Muilo padėklai; Muilinės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Bļodas mājas (istabas) dzīvnieku barošanai; Mājas (istabas) dzīvnieku tualetes kastītes; Kaķu tualetes; Ķemmes matu uzkasīšanai; Mazu dzīvnieku barotavas; Nemehanizētas dzīvnieku barotavas; Elektroniskās mājdzīvnieku barošanas ierīces; Mājsaimniecības konteineri mājdzīvnieku pārtikas glabāšanai; Mājas (istabas) dzīvnieku sprosti; Barošanas un dzirdināšanas bļodas mājdzīvniekiem; Sukas mājdzīvniekiem; Konditorejas izstrādājumu veidnes; Ledus kubiciņu veidnes ledusskapjiem; Karotes cepeša apslacīšanai (virtuves piederumi); Neelektriskas putojamās slotiņas mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Neelektriski putotāji; Ēdienu gatavošanas trauku komplekti; Drēbju žāvēšanas statīvi; Ziepju trauki ar vāku; Ziepju trauki ar vāku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kontenituri tal-ikel, għat-tmigħ tal-annimali domestiċi; Kaxxi tal-ħmieġ għall-annimali domestiċi; Kaxex għall-ħmieġ tal-qtates; Pettnijiet għall-moxt tax-xagħar; Kontenituri żgħar tal-għalf għall-annimali; Alimentatur tal-annimali mhux mekkanizzat; Tagħmir elettroniku li jitma' l-annimali domestiċi; Kontenituri tad-dar fejn jinħażen l-ikel ta' annimali domestiċi; Gaġeġ għall-annimali li jinżammu d-dar; Bwieqi biex tiekol u biex tixrob għall-annimali domestiċi; Xkupilji għall-annimali domestiċi; Forom tad-dulċiera; Forom tal-kubi tas-silġ għar-refriġeraturi; Mgħaref biex troxx il-meraq fuq il-laħam [għodda tal-kċina]; Tagħmir għat-tħabbit tal-krema, eċċ, mhux tal-elettriku, għal użu domestiku; Ħabbata, mhux tal-elettriku; Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir; Xtillieri għall-ħwejjeġ, għat-tnixxif; Kontenituri tas-sapun; Kontenituri tas-sapun.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Voederbakken voor huisdieren; Kattenbakken; Kattenbakken; Kammen voor het achterover kammen van het haar; Voerbakken voor kleine dieren; Niet-gemechaniseerde voedersystemen voor dieren; Elektronische voederapparaten voor huisdieren; Huishoudelijke houders voor het opbergen van dierenvoer; Kooien voor huisdieren; Voedings- en drinkbakken voor huisdieren; Borstels voor huisdieren; Vormen voor suikerbakkerswaren; Vormen voor ijsblokjes, voor ijskasten; Opscheplepels; Gardes, niet elektrisch, voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Kloppers, niet elektrisch; Keukengerei; Rekken voor het luchten van kleding [droogrekken]; Zeephouders; Zeepdozen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pojemniki na żywność dla zwierząt domowych; Kuwety dla zwierząt domowych; Kuwety dla kotów; Grzebienie do tapirowania włosów; Podajniki karmy dla małych zwierząt; Niezmechanizowane podajniki karmy dla zwierząt; Elektroniczne dozowniki pokarmu dla zwierząt domowych; Pojemniki stosowane w gospodarstwie domowym do przechowywania karmy dla zwierząt domowych; Klatki dla zwierząt domowych; Miski na karmę i wodę dla zwierząt domowych; Szczotki dla zwierząt domowych; Formy cukiernicze; Foremki do kostek lodu, do lodówek; Łyżki do polewania pieczeni [utensylia kuchenne]; Ubijaczki nieelektryczne do użytku domowego; Trzepaczki nieelektryczne; Przybory kuchenne; Suszarki do ubrań; Mydelniczki; Mydelniczki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Recipientes para alimentos destinados a animais de estimação; Caixas de areia para animais de estimação; Caixas para asseio de gatos; Pentes para ripar o cabelo; Comedouros para animais pequenos; Distribuidores não mecânicos de alimento para animais; Dispensadores eletrónicos de alimento para animais de estimação; Recipientes domésticos para armazenamento de alimentos para animais; Gaiolas para animais de estimação; Tigelas de comida e bebida para animais de estimação; Escovas para animais de estimação; Formas de confeitaria; Formas para cubos de gelo para frigoríficos; Colheres para regar molho [utensílios de cozinha]; Batedeiras, não elétricas, para uso doméstico; Batedeiras, não elétricas; Utensílios para cozinha; Estendais para a roupa; Saboneteiras [suportes]; Saboneteiras [caixas].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Vase de mâncare pentru animale de casă; Litiere pentru animale de companie; Litiere pentru pisici; Piepteni pentru taparea părului; Biberoane pentru animale mici; Alimentatoare nemecanizate pentru animale; Dispozitive electronice de hrănire pentru animale de companie; Recipiente de uz casnic pentru depozitarea hranei pentru animale de companie; Cuști pentru animale de companie; Boluri pentru hrănirea și adăparea animalelor de companie; Perii pentru animale de companie; Forme pentru cofetărie; Forme pentru cuburi de gheață pentru congelatoare; Linguri pentru gătit și servit [ustensile de bucatarie]; Palete neelectrice de uz casnic; Palete de amestecare neelectrice; Ustensile de bucătărie; Suporturi de uscat haine; Savoniere; Savoniere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nádoby na jedlo pre domáce zvieratá; Odpadové nádoby pre zvieratá chované v domácnosti; Toalety pre mačky; Tupírovacie hrebene; Krmivo pre drobné zvieratá; Nemechanizované kŕmiace zariadenia pre zvieratá; Elektronické kŕmidlá pre domáce zvieratá; Skladovacie nádoby pre domácnosť určené na potravu pre domáce zvieratá; Klietky pre zvieratá chované v domácnosti; Misky na kŕmenie a napájanie domácich zvierat; Kefy pre domáce zvieratá; Formy na cukrovinky; Formy na ľadové kocky do chladničky; Kuchynské naberačky; Šľahače pre domácnosť okrem elektrických; Šľahače (nie elektrické); Kuchynský riad; Sušiaky na sušenie oblečenia; Držiaky na mydlo; Obaly na mydlá.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Posode za hrano za hišne ljubljenčke; Stranišča za hišne ljubljence; Mačja stranišča; Glavniki za česanje las nazaj; Krmilniki za male živali; Nemehanizirani krmilniki za živali; Elektronske naprave za hranjenje hišnih ljubljencev; Posode za gospodinjstvo, za shranjevanje hrane hišnih ljubljenčkov; Kletke za hišne ljubljenčke; Sklede za hrano in pijačo, za hišne ljubljenčke; Krtače za hišne ljubljenčke; Slaščičarski modeli; Posodice za ledene kocke, za hladilnike; Žlice za zalivanje [kuhinjski pripomočki]; Neelektrične metlice za stepanje, za gospodinjsko uporabo; Stepalniki (neelektrični); Kuharski pripomočki; Stojala za sušenje oblačil; Posodice za milo; Posodice za milo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Matbehållare för husdjursmat; Lådor för husdjurströ; Kattsandlådor; Tuperingskammar; Matningsanordningar för små djur; Icke-mekaniska djurmatningsanordningar; Elektroniska matskålar för husdjur; Hushållsbehållare för förvaring av djurfoder; Burar för husdjur; Foder- och dryckesskålar för husdjur; Borstar för husdjur; Formar för konfekttillverkning; Iskubsformar för kylskåp; Össlevar [köksgeråd]; Icke-elektriska vispar för hushållsändamål; Vispar, inte elektriska; Köksgeråd; Torkställningar för kläder; Tvålhållare; Tvålaskar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/146</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080423</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>85806</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
