<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-08T07:36:58</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226742</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226742</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-05</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-08</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>GADONX</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162309805</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226742/000162309805.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.19</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.25</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Мишка (компютърна периферия); Подложки за мишки; Слушалки; Електронни интерактивни бели дъски; Таблетен компютър; Микрофони; Фотоапарати [фотография]; Прожекционни апарати за диапозитиви; Апарати за разпознаване на лицето; Броячи; Подложкиза ръце при работа с компютър; Смарт часовници; Писалки (Електронни -) [визуални индикаторни устройства]; Преносими зарядни устройства; Кантари за баня; Цифрови знаци; Клавиатури за мобилни телефони; Защитни тънкослойни покрития, пригодени за смартфони; Електропроводи (Материали за -) [проводници, кабели]; Клавиатури; Говорители.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Myši [počítačová periferní zařízení]; Podložky pod myš; Sluchátka; Elektronické interaktivní tabule; Tablety (počítače); Mikrofony; Fotoaparáty; Promítačky na diapozitivy, diaprojektory; Zařízení na rozpoznávání obličeje; Počítadla; Opěrky zápěstí pro práci s počítačem; Chytré hodinky; Elektronická pera [vizualizační nástroje]; Přenosné nabíječky; Koupelnové váhy; Digitální panely; Klávesnice pro mobilní telefony; Ochranné fólie na chytré telefony; Materiály pro elektrická vedení [vodiče, kabely]; Klávesnice; Reproduktory.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Mus [perifere enheder til computere]; Musemåtter; Hovedtelefoner; Interaktive elektroniske whiteboards; Tablet-computere; Mikrofoner; Fotografiapparater; Projektorer til diapositiver; Apparater til ansigtsgenkendelse; Tællere; Håndledsstøtter til brug med computere; Smartwatches; Penne, elektroniske [enheder til dataskærme]; Bærbare opladere; Badevægte; Digitale skilte; Tastaturer til mobiltelefoner; Beskyttelsesfilm tilpasset til smartphones; Materiel til elektriske hovedledninger [tråd, kabler]; Tastaturer; Højttalere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Mäuse [Computerzubehör]; Mauspads [Mausmatten]; Kopfhörer; Elektronische interaktive Whiteboards; Tablet-Computer; Mikrofone; Kameras; Diaprojektoren; Geräte zur Gesichtserkennung; Zählwerke; Handgelenkauflagen zur Verwendung mit Computern; Smartwatches; Elektronische Stifte [für Bildschirmgeräte]; Tragbare Ladegeräte; Badezimmerwaagen; Digital Signage; Tastaturen für Mobiltelefone; Angepasste Schutzfolien für Smartphones; Material für elektrische Leitungen [Drahte, Kabel]; Tastaturen; Lautsprecher.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ποντίκια [εξοπλισμός πληροφορικής]· Προστατευτικές βάσεις για ποντίκια (ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών)· Ακουστικά· Ηλεκτρονικοί αλληλεπιδραστικοί λευκοί πίνακες· Φορητοί υπολογιστές (Tablet)· Μικρόφωνα· Φωτογραφικές μηχανές· Συσκευές προβολής διαφανειών· Συσκευές αναγνώρισης προσώπου· Μετρητές· Καρπών στηρίγματα για χρήση με ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Έξυπνα ρολόγια χειρός· Ηλεκτρονικές γραφίδες· Φορητοί φορτιστές· Ζυγοί για την κουζίνα, ατομικοί ζυγοί· Ψηφιακά σήματα· Πληκτρολόγια για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Προστατευτικές μεμβράνες προσαρμοσμένες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Υλικά για δίκτυα ηλεκτρισμού [σύρματα, καλώδια]· Πληκτρολόγια· Ηχεία.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">mouse [computer peripheral]; mouse pads; headphones; electronic interactive whiteboards; tablet computers; microphones; cameras; transparency projection apparatus; Facial recognition apparatus; counters; wrist rests for use with computers; Smart watches; electronic pens [visual display units]; Portable chargers; bathroom scales; digital signs; Keyboards for mobile phones; Protective films adapted for mobile phone screens; materials for electricity mains [wires, cables]; keyboards; loudspeakers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Ratones [periféricos informáticos]; Alfombrillas de ratón; Auriculares; Pizarras interactivas electrónicas; Tabletas electrónicas; Micrófonos; Cámaras fotográficas; Proyectores de diapositivas; Aparatos de reconocimiento facial; Contadores; Reposamuñecas para utilizar con ordenadores; Relojes inteligentes; Lápices electrónicos para unidades de visualización; Cargadores portátiles; Básculas para cuartos de baño; Letreros digitales; Teclados para teléfonos móviles; Películas de protección para teléfonos inteligentes [smartphones]; Material para conducciones eléctricas [hilos, cables]; Teclados; Altavoces.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hiired [arvuti välisseadmed]; Hiirematid; Kõrvaklapid; Elektroonilised interaktiivsed tahvlid; Tahvelarvutid; Mikrofonid; Fotokaamerad, fotoaparaadid; Slaidiprojektorid, diaprojektorid; Näotuvastusseadmed; Loendurid, mõõturid; Randmetoed arvutikasutajatele; Nutikellad; Elektroonilised pliiatsid; Kaasaskantavad laadijad; Vannitoakaalud; Digitaalsildid; Mobiiltelefonide klahvistikud; Nutitelefonide kaitsekiled; Elektriliinimaterjalid [juhtmed, kaablid]; Klaviatuurid, klahvistikud; Kõlarid, valjuhääldid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hiiri [tietokoneen oheislaite]; Hiirimatot; Kuulokkeet; Vuorovaikutteiset elektroniset valkotaulut; Tablettitietokoneet; Mikrofonit; Kamerat; Diaprojektorit; Kasvojentunnistuslaitteet; Mittarit; Rannetuet käytettäviksi tietokoneiden kanssa; Älykellot; Kynät, elektroniset; Kannettavat laturit; Kylpyhuonevaa'at; Digitaaliset opasteet; Matkapuhelinten näppäimistöt; Älypuhelimille tarkoitetut suojakalvot; Sähköjakeluverkkokaapelit; Näppäimistöt; Kaiuttimet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Souris [périphérique d'ordinateur]; Tapis de souris; Casques d'écoute; Tableaux blancs électroniques interactifs; Tablettes électroniques; Microphones; Appareils photo; Appareils de projection de diapositives; Appareils de reconnaissance faciale; Compteurs; Repose-poignets à utiliser avec un ordinateur; Montres intelligentes; Crayons électroniques pour unités d'affichage visuel; Chargeurs portatifs; Balances de salle de bain; Enseignes numériques; Claviers pour téléphones mobiles; Films de protection conçus pour ordiphones [smartphones]; Matériel pour conduites d'électricité [fils, câbles]; Claviers; Enceintes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Miš [računalna oprema]; Podloge za miša; Slušalice; Elektroničke interaktivne bijele ploče; Tablet računalo; Mikrofoni; Fotoaparati; Dijaprojektori; Uređaji za prepoznavanje lica; Mjerni instrumenti; Podlošci za šaku za rad s računalima; Pametni ručni satovi; Svjetlosne olovke; Prijenosni punjači; Osobne vage; Digitalni znakovi; Tipkovnice mobilnih telefona; Zaštitne folije prilagođene za pametne telefone; Materijali za električne mreže [žice, kablovi]; Tipkovnice; Zvučnici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Egér [számítógép-periféria]; Egérpadok; Fejhallgatók; Elektronikus interaktív táblák; Táblagépek; Mikrofonok; Fényképezőgépek, kamerák; Írásvetítő berendezések; Arcfelismerő készülékek; Számlálók, mérőműszerek; Csuklótámaszok számítógépekhez; Okoskarórák; Fényceruzák vizuális kijelzőkhöz, displayekhez; Hordozható töltők; Fürdőszobai mérlegek; Digitális jelek; Billentyűzetek mobiltelefonokhoz; Védőfóliák okostelefonokhoz; Anyagok elektromos hálózatokhoz, fővezetékekhez [huzalok, kábelek]; Billentyűzetek; Hangszórók, hangosbemondók, megafonok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Mouse [informatica]; Tappetini per mouse; Cuffie per la musica; Lavagne bianche elettroniche interattive; Tablet; Microfoni; Macchine fotografiche; Diaproiettori; Apparecchi per il riconoscimento del viso; Contatori; Poggiapolsi per tastiera per l'uso del computer; Orologi intelligenti; Matite elettroniche per unità di visualizzazione; Caricabatterie portatili; Bilance da bagno; Insegne digitali; Tastiere per telefoni cellulari; Pellicola protettiva adattata per smartphone; Materiale per condotte per l'elettricità [fili, cavi]; Griglie per tastiere; Altoparlanti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Pelės [kompiuterio išoriniai įtaisai]; Pelės padėkliukai; Radijo ausinės; Elektroninės interaktyviosios lentos; Planšetiniai kompiuteriai; Mikrofonai; Fotoaparatai; Diaskopai; Veidų atpažinimo įranga; Skaitikliai; Riešų atramos darbui su kompiuteriais; Išmanieji laikrodžiai; Elektroniniai rašikliai; Nešiojamieji įkrovikliai; Vonios svarstyklės; Skaitmeniniai ženklai; Mobiliųjų telefonų klaviatūros; Išmaniųjų telefonų ekranų apsauginės plėvelės; Elektros linijų medžiagos [laidai, kabeliai]; Klaviatūros; Garsiakalbiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pele (datoru perifērijas ierīces); Peļu paliktņi; Austiņas; Elektroniskas interaktīvās baltās tāfeles; Planšetdatori; Mikrofoni; Kameras; Diaprojektori; Sejas atpazīšanas ierīces; Skaitītāji; Plaukstas locītavas balsti datorlietotājiem; Viedie rokaspulksteņi; Elektroniskie zīmuļi videogaliekārtām; Portatīvās uzlādes ierīces; Vannasistabas svari; Digitālās zīmes; Tastatūras mobilajiem telefoniem; Aizsargplēves, pielāgotas viedtālruņiem; Elektrības tīklu materiāli (vadi, kabeļi); Tastatūras; Skaļruņi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Maws [periferal tal-kompjuter]; Mattijiet għall-maws; Kuffji; Wajtbords interattivi elettroniċi; Kompjuter f'forma ta' tablets; Mikrofoni; Kameras; Apparat għall-projezzjoni ta' folji trasparenti; Apparat għar-rikonoxximent tal-uċuħ; Indikaturi tal-kejl; Serħ il-polz għal użu ma' kompjuters; Arloġġi tal-idejn tat-tip smart; Pinen elettroniċi; Ċarġers portabbli; Mwieżen tal-kamra tal-banju; Sinjali diġitali; Tastieri għal telefoni ċellulari; Films protettivi adattati għal smartfowns; Materjali għall-mejns tal-elettriku (linji); Tastieri; Lawdspikers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Computermuizen; Muismatten; Hoofdtelefoons; Elektronische interactieve whiteboards; Elektronische tablets; Microfoons; Camera's; Diaprojectors; Apparatuur voor gezichtsherkenning; Tellers; Polssteunen voor gebruik met computers; Smartwatches; Lichtpennen; Draagbare laders; Personenweegschalen voor badkamers; Digitale borden; Toetsenborden voor mobiele telefoons; Beschermende folie aangepast aan smartphones; Materiaal voor elektrische leidingen [draden, kabels]; Toetsenpanelen; Speakers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Myszy [sprzęt do przetwarzania danych]; Podkładki pod myszy komputerowe; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Interaktywne tablice elektroniczne; Tablety; Mikrofony; Aparaty fotograficzne; Aparaty do projekcji przezroczy; Urządzenia rozpoznające twarz; Liczniki; Podpórki pod nadgarstki do użytku z komputerem; Zegarki inteligentne; Elektroniczne pióra [ekranopisy]; Ładowarki przenośne; Wagi łazienkowe; Znaki cyfrowe; Klawiatury do telefonów komórkowych; Folie ochronne dostosowane do smartfonów; Materiały na przewody instalacji elektrycznych [kable]; Klawiatury; Głośniki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Ratos [periféricos informáticos]; Tapetes para ratos de computador; Auriculares; Quadros interativos eletrónicos; Computadores em forma de tablet; Microfones; Câmaras; Aparelhos de projeção de diapositivos; Aparelhos de reconhecimento facial; Contadores; Apoios de pulsos para utilização com computador; Relógios de pulso inteligentes; Canetas eletrónicas [canetas digitais] para unidades de visualização; Carregadores portáteis; Balanças de casa de banho; Sinalizações digitais; Teclados para telemóveis; Películas protetoras adaptadas para smartphones; Materiais para condução elétrica [fios, cabos]; Teclados; Altifalantes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Mouse [periferice de calculator]; Suporturi de mouse; Căşti audio; Table electronice interactive whiteboard; Tablete; Microfoane; Aparate de fotografiat; Diapozitive (Aparate de proiecţie pentru -); Aparate de recunoaştere facială; Contoare; Suporturi pentru încheietura mâinii, folosite de utilizatorii de calculatoare; Ceasuri inteligente; Creioane electronice [pentru unităţi de afişaj vizual]; Încărcătoare portabile; Cântare de baie; Indicatoare digitale; Tastaturi pentru telefoane mobile; Folii de protecţie adaptate pentru telefoane inteligente; Materiale pentru reţeaua de electricitate [fire, cabluri]; Tastaturi; Difuzoare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Myši (periférne zariadenia počítačov); Podložky pod myš; Slúchadlá; Elektronické interaktívne tabule; Tablety (prenosné počítače); Mikrofóny; Fotoaparáty; Premietacie prístroje na diapozitívy; Prístroje na rozpoznávanie tváre; Počítadlá; Opierky zápästia na prácu s počítačom; Inteligentné hodinky; Elektronické perá (vizuálne zobrazovacie zariadenia); Prenosné nabíjačky; Kúpeľňové váhy; Digitálne tabule; Klávesnice pre mobilné telefóny; Ochranné fólie na smartfóny; Materiály na elektrické vedenie (drôty, káble); Klávesnice; Reproduktory, amplióny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Miška [računalniška periferna enota]; Podloge za miško; Slušalke; Elektronske interaktivne table; Tablični računalnik; Mikrofoni; Fotoaparati; Diaprojektorji; Naprave za prepoznavanje obraza; Merilne naprave (števci); Počivala za zapestje, ki se uporabljajo z računalniki; Pametne zapestne ure; Elektronska pisala; Prenosni polnilniki; Kopalniške tehtnice; Digitalne oznake; Tipkovnice za mobilne telefone; Zaščitne folije, prilagojene za pametne telefone; Materiali za električno napeljavo [žice, kabli]; Tipkovnice; Zvočniki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Möss [datorutrustning]; Musmattor; Hörlurar; Elektroniska interaktiva whiteboardtavlor; Portföljdator; Mikrofoner; Kameror; Diaprojektorer; Apparater för ansiktsigenkänning; Mätare; Handledsstöd för användning vid datorer; Smarta klockor; Ljuspennor; Bärbara laddare; Badrumsvågar; Digitala skyltar; Tangentbord för mobiltelefoner; Skyddsfilm för smartphones; Material för elektriska huvudledningar [tråd, kablar]; Knappsatser; Högtalare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Разпространение на рекламни материали (дипляни, проспекти, Брошури, мостри, каталози, особено за продажби на дълги разстояния) независимо дали трансгранично или не; Търговско управление при лицензиране на стоки и услуги за трети лица; Агенции за внос и износ; Снабдяване за сметка на трети лица [закупуване на стоки или услуги за други предприятия]; Маркетинг на стоки и услуги за трети лица; Трудови борси; Индексиране на съдържанието на уебсайтове за търговски и рекламни цели; Разпространение на мостри; Представяне на стоки; Подреждане на витрини; Реклама в Интернет за трети лица; Разпространение на проспекти и мостри; Рекламиране и рекламни услуги; Насърчаване на продажбите [за трети лица]; Маркетингови услуги; Осигуряване на онлайн пазар за покупко-продажби на стоки и услуги; Търговски справки; Агенции за търговска информация; Рекламни услуги по пощатата; Рекламиране на стоки и услуги за трети лица.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Distribuce reklamních materiálů (letáků, prospektů, brožur, vzorků, zejména pro zásilkové prodeje dle katalogu) zahraniční či nikoliv; Obchodní správa licencí k výrobkům a službám jiných osob; Služby agentury zaměřené na export a import; Zásobovací služby pro jiné osoby [nákup zboží a služeb pro jiné podniky]; Marketing zboží a služeb pro třetí osoby; Zprostředkování zaměstnání; Indexace webových stránek pro obchodní nebo reklamní účely; Šíření vzorků; Předvádění zboží; Aranžování výkladů; Reklama na internetu pro třetí osoby; Distribuce prospektů a vzorků; Propagace; Podpora prodeje jiných osob; Marketing; Provozování online trhu pro kupující a prodejce výrobků a služeb; Poptávky; Zprostředkování obchodních informací; Cílené zasílání reklamních materiálů; Propagace zboží a služeb pro třetí osoby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">National eller international distribution af reklamemateriale i form af løbesedler, prospekter, brochurer og vareprøver, især til kataloger og med henblik på langdistancesalg; Kommerciel administration ved licensering af andres varer og tjenesteydelser; Import- og eksportagenturer; Indkøbsbistand til andre ved køb af varer og tjenesteydelser; Markedsføring af andres varer og tjenesteydelser; Arbejdsformidlingskontorvirksomhed; Webindeksering med kommercielle eller reklamemæssige formål; Distribution af vareprøver; Demonstration af varer; Dekoration af butiksvinduer; Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed på internettet for andre; Distribution af prospekter og vareprøver; Reklamevirksomhed; Salgsfremmende foranstaltninger for andre; Marketing; Tilvejebringelse af en onlinemarkedsplads til købere og sælgere af varer og tjenesteydelser; Indhentning af forretningsoplysninger; Forretningsmæssig oplysningsagenturvirksomhed; Avertering pr. post; Salgsfremmende foranstaltninger for andres varer og tjenesteydelser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Verteilung von Werbematerial [Handzettel, Prospekte, Broschüren, Warenproben, insbesondere für den Versandhandel], grenzüberschreitend oder nicht; Kommerzielle Verwaltung der Lizenzierung von Waren und Dienstleistungen für Dritte; Dienstleistungen einer Im- und Exportagentur; Beschaffungsdienstleistungen für Dritte [Erwerb von Waren und Dienstleistungen für andere Unternehmen]; Marketing für Waren und Dienstleistungen von Dritten; Personal-, Stellenvermittlung; Indexierung von Webseiten für Geschäfts- und Werbezwecke; Verteilung von Warenproben zu Werbezwecken; Vorführung von Waren für Werbezwecke; Dekorieren von Schaufenstern; Werbung im Internet für Dritte; Verteilung von Prospekten und Warenmustern; Werbung; Verkaufsförderung [Sales promotion] [für Dritte]; Marketing; Bereitstellen eines Online-Marktplatzes für Käufer und Verkäufer von Waren und Dienstleistungen; Auskünfte in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Erteilung von Auskünften in Handels- und Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Direktversandwerbung; Verkaufsförderung für Waren und Dienstleistungen Dritter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διανομή διαφημιστικού υλικού (φέιγ-βολάν, ενημερωτικά φυλλάδια, φυλλάδια, δείγματα, ειδικότερα για εξ αποστάσεως πωλήσεις μέσω καταλόγου) εκτός ή εντός συνόρων· Εμπορική διοίκηση αδειών εκμετάλλευσης προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Πρακτορεία εισαγωγών-εξαγωγών· Εφοδιασμού για τρίτους (υπηρεσίες -) [αγορά προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για άλλες επιχειρήσεις]· Εμπορία [μάρκετινγκ] προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για λογαριασμό άλλων· Πρακτορεία εύρεσης εργασίας· Διαδικτυακή ευρετηρίαση για εμπορικούς ή διαφημιστικούς σκοπούς· Διανομή δειγμάτων· Επίδειξη προϊόντων· Διακόσμηση βιτρινών· Διαφήμιση για λογαριασμό τρίτων στο Διαδίκτυο (INTERNET)· Διανομή διαφημιστικών φυλλαδίων και δειγμάτων· Διαφήμιση· Προώθηση πωλήσεων [για τρίτους]· Υπηρεσίες μάρκετινγκ· Παροχή χώρων αγορών επί γραμμής για αγοραστές και πωλητές προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών· Επιχειρηματικές έρευνες· Πρακτορεία εμπορικών πληροφοριών· Υπηρεσίες διαφημιστικού ταχυδρομείου· Υπηρεσίες προώθησης προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για λογαριασμό τρίτων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Distribution of publicity materials, namely, flyers, prospectuses, brochures, samples, particularly for catalogue long distance sales [whether crossborder or not]; commercial administration of the licensing of the goods and services of others; import-export agency services; Procurement services for others [purchasing goods and services for other businesses]; Marketing the goods and services of others; employment agency services; web indexing for commercial or advertising purposes; distribution of samples; demonstration of goods; shop window dressing; Advertisement for others on the Internet; Distribution of prospectuses and samples; publicity; sales promotion for others; marketing; provision of an online marketplace for buyers and sellers of goods and services; business inquiries; commercial information agency services; direct mail advertising; Promotion of goods and services for others.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Distribución de material publicitario (flyers, prospectos, muestras, en particular para ventas por catálogo) transfronteriza o no; Gestión comercial de licencias de productos y servicios de terceros; Servicios de agencias de importación-exportación; Servicios de abastecimiento para terceros [compra de productos y servicios para otras empresas]; Marketing de productos y servicios de terceros; Servicios de oficinas de empleo; Indexación de páginas web con fines comerciales o publicitarios; Distribución de muestras; Demostración de productos; Decoración de escaparates; Publicidad en Internet para terceros; Distribución de prospectos y muestras; Publicidad; Promoción de ventas para terceros; Marketing; Suministro de espacios de venta en línea para vendedores y compradores de productos y servicios; Indagaciones sobre negocios; Servicios de agencias de información comercial; Distribución de material publicitario [folletos, prospectos, impresos, muestras]; Servicios de promoción de productos y servicios de terceros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reklaammaterjalide (lendlehtede, prospektide, brošüüride, näidiste) levitamine riigisiseselt või välismaale eelkõige kataloogi vahendusel kaugmüügi teostamiseks; Teiste omanike kaupade ja teenuste litsentsimise korraldamine äri eesmärgil; Ekspordi- ja impordiagentuuride teenused; Hanketeenused teistele ettevõtetele [kaupade ja teenuste ostmine]; Kolmandate isikute kaupade ja teenuste turundamine; Tööhõivekontoriteenused; Veebi indekseerimine äri või reklaami eesmärgil; Näidiste (proovide) levitamine; Kaupade demonstreerimine; Poeakende (vaateakende) kaunistamine, dekoreerimine; Reklaam internetis teenusena; Reklaamprospektide ja näidiste (proovide) levitamine; Reklaam; Müügikampaaniad, -reklaam teenusena; Turundus; Veebipõhise müügikeskkonna pakkumine kaupade ja teenuste ostjatele ning müüjatele; Ärialased päringud, küsitlused; Kaubandusteabeagentuuride teenused; Posti teel reklaami levitamine; Teiste isikute kaupade ja teenuste reklaamimine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mainontamateriaalin jakelu (lentolehtisten, esittelylehtisten, esitteiden, näytteiden, erityisesti kaukomyyntiluettelojen) joko rajan yli tai ei; Kaupallinen hallinnointi koskien toisten tavaroiden ja palveluiden lisensointia; Tuonti- ja vientiagentuuripalvelut; Hankintapalvelut muille [tavaroiden ja palveluiden osto muille yrityksille]; Muiden tuottamien tavaroiden ja palvelujen markkinointi; Työnvälitys; Verkkoluetteloiden tekeminen kaupan tai mainonnan tarkoituksiin; Tavaranäytteiden jakelu; Tavaroiden esittely; Näyteikkunoiden somistelu; Mainonta kolmansille osapuolille Internetissä; Esitteiden ja näytteiden jakelu; Mainonta; Myynninedistäminen [muille]; Markkinointipalvelut; Online-markkinapaikan tarjoaminen tavaroiden ja palvelujen ostajille ja myyjille; Liikkeenhoitoa koskevat kyselyt; Tietotoimistot, kaupalliset; Suorapostimainonta; Tavaroiden ja palveluiden myynninedistäminen muille.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Distribution de matériel publicitaire tels que tracts, flyers, prospectus, brochures et échantillons, notamment pour la vente à distance sur catalogue, aussi bien au niveau national qu'à l'étranger; Administration commerciale de licences de produits et de services de tiers; Services d'agences d'import-export; Services d'approvisionnement pour des tiers [achat de produits et de services pour d'autres entreprises]; Marketing de produits et services de tiers; Services de bureaux de placement; Référencement de sites web à but commercial ou publicitaire; Diffusion d'échantillons; Démonstration de produits; Décoration de vitrines; Publicité sur Internet pour le compte de tiers; Distribution de prospectus et d'échantillons; Publicité; Promotion des ventes pour des tiers; Services de marketing; Mise à disposition d'espaces de vente en ligne pour acheteurs et vendeurs de produits et services; Fourniture de renseignements d'affaires; Services d'agences d'informations commerciales; Distribution de matériel publicitaire [tracts, prospectus, imprimés, échantillons]; Promotion des produits et des services de tiers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Distribucija promidžbenih materijala (letaka, prospekata, brošura, uzoraka, posebno za katalošku prodaju na veliku udaljenost) izvan granice ili ne; Komercijalno upravljanje u svezi licenci proizvoda i usluga trećih osoba; Agencije za uvoz-izvoz; Nabava za treće osobe [usluge kupnje proizvoda i usluga za druga poduzeća]; Marketing proizvoda i usluga za druge; Uredi za zapošljavanje; Indeksiranje internetskih stranica za komercijalne ili promidžbene potrebe; Podjela [distribucija] uzoraka; Demonstracija proizvoda; Uređenje izloga; Oglašavanje za treće osobe na Internetu; Distribucija prospekata i uzoraka; Oglašavanje; Promicanje prodaje za treće osobe; Marketing; Pružanje internetskog tržišnog prostora za kupce i prodavatelje proizvoda i usluga; Poslovi (obavještenja o poslovima); Agencije za komercijalne obavijesti; Raspačavanje reklamnog materijala [traktata, prospekata, tiskanica, uzoraka]; Promidžba robe i usluga za druge.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Reklámanyagok [szórólapok, prospektusok, brosúrák, termékminták, főként katalóguson keresztüli távértékesítés céljából] akár külföldi, akár belföldi terjesztése; Áruk és szolgáltatások engedélyezésének kereskedelmi ügyintézése; Import-export ügynökségek; Beszerzői szolgáltatások [áruk illetve szolgáltatások beszerzése más cégeknek]; Mások áruinak és szolgáltatásainak marketingje; Állásközvetítő irodák; Webindexelés kereskedelmi vagy reklám célokra; Termékminták, áruminták terjesztése; Árubemutatás; Kirakatrendezés; Internetes reklámozási szolgáltatások; Prospektusok és termékminták terjesztése; Hirdetési- és reklámszolgáltatások; Értékesítési promóciós szolgáltatások; Marketing szolgáltatások; Online piactér biztosítása áruk és szolgáltatások eladói és vásárlói részére; Üzleti tájékoztatás, információnyújtás; Kereskedelmi információs ügynökségek; Reklámanyagok [röplapok, prospektusok, nyomtatványok, áruminták] terjesztése; Mások termékeinek és szolgáltatásainak reklámozása.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Distribuzione di materiale pubblicitario (volantini, prospetti, opuscoli, campioni, in particolare per vendite a distanza mediante cataloghi) sia all'estero che non; Amministrazione commerciale di licenze di prodotti e di servizi di terzi; Servizi di agenzie per l'importazione e l'esportazione; Servizi di approvvigionamento per conto terzi [aquisto di prodotti e di servizi per altre imprese]; Commercializzazione di prodotti e servizi per conto terzi; Collocamento; Indicizzazione sul web per scopi commerciali o pubblicitari; Distribuzione di campioni per scopi pubblicitari; Dimostrazione pratica di prodotti per scopi pubblicitari; Decorazione di vetrine; Pubblicità su Internet per conto terzi; Distribuzione di dépliant e di campioni; Pubblicità; Promozione delle vendite per i terzi; Marketing; Fornitura su mercato on-line di beni e servizi per acquirenti e venditori; Ragguagli d'affari; Servizi di agenzie di informazioni commerciali; Pubblicità diretta per corrispondenza; Promozione di beni e servizi per conto terzi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Reklaminės medžiagos (skrajučių, prospektų, brošiūrų, prekių pavyzdžių) platinimas nuotolinei prekybai pagal katalogus šalies viduje bei užsienyje; Trečiųjų asmenų prekių ir paslaugų licencijavimo komercinis administravimas; Importo ir eksporto agentūrų paslaugos; Tiekimo paslaugos kitiems [prekių ir paslaugų pirkimas kitiems verslams]; Prekių ir paslaugų rinkodara kitiems; Samdos agentūrų paslaugos; Žiniatinklio indeksavimas komercijos ar reklamos reikmėms; Pavyzdžių platinimas; Prekių rodymas; Parduotuvių vitrinų puošimas [tvarkymas]; Reklamavimas kitiems internete; Prospektų ir pavyzdžių platinimas; Reklama; Prekių pardavimo skatinimas [kitiems]; Rinkodara; Interneto prekyviečių teikimas prekių ir paslaugų pardavėjams bei pirkėjams; Verslo patikrinimai; Komercinės informacijos agentūrų paslaugos; Reklama paštu; Prekių ir paslaugų pardavimo skatinimas (kitiems).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reklāmas materiālu izplatīšana (reklāmas lapiņas, prospekti, brošūras, preču paraugi, jo īpaši attālinātajai tirdzniecībai ar katalogu starpniecību) valsts robežās vai ārpus tām; Preču un pakalpojumu licencēšanas komerciālā vadība citu personu labā; Importa-eksporta aģentūru pakalpojumi; Uzņēmumu apgāde [preču un pakalpojumu sagāde trešo personu interesēs]; Preču un pakalpojumu tirgvedība trešām personām; Darbā iekārtošanas biroju pakalpojumi; Atsauču norādīšana tīmekļa lapām komerciālos vai reklāmas nolūkos; Paraugu izplatīšana; Preču demonstrēšanas pakalpojumi; Veikalu skatlogu noformēšana; Trešo personu reklamēšana internetā; Prospektu un paraugu izplatīšana; Reklāma; Preču noieta veicināšana trešajām personām; Tirgvedības pakalpojumi; Tiešsaistes tirgus nodrošināšana preču un pakalpojumu pārdevējiem un pircējiem; Darījumu informācijas vākšana; Komercinformācijas aģentūru pakalpojumi; Tiešā pasta reklāma; Preču un pakalpojumu veicināšana citu vajadzībām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Id-distribuzzjoni ta' materjal pubbliċitarju (volantini, prospektus, opuskuli, kampjuni, partikolarment katalgi ta' bejgħ fuq distanza twila) kemm jekk transkonfinali jew le; Servizzi ta' amministrazzjoni kummerċjali ta' ħaddieħor, għal-liċenzjar ta' oġġetti u servizzi; Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-importazzjoni u esportazzjoni; Servizzi ta' akkwist għal oħrajn [xiri ta' prodotti u servizzi għal negozji oħra]; Marketing ta' prodotti u servizzi ta' oħrajn; Aġenziji tal-impjieg; Indiċjar web għall-finijiet kummerċjali jew ta' reklamar; Distribuzzjoni ta' kampjuni; Dimostrazzjoni ta' prodotti; Arranġament ta' vetrini tal-ħwienet; Reklamar għal terzi persuni permezz tal-Internet; Distribuzzjoni ta' prospetti u kampjuni; Reklamar; Il-promozzjoni tal-bejgħ għal oħrajn; Servizzi ta' kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Forniment ta' suq onlajn għal xerrejja u bejjiegħa ta' prodotti u servizzi; Inkjesti dwar negozju; Aġenziji ta' informazzjoni kummerċjali; Reklamar dirett bil-posta; Il-promozzjoni ta' oġġetti u servizzi ta' oħrajn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verspreiding van reclamemateriaal (vlugschriften, prospectussen, brochures, monsters, met name catalogi voor internationale verkoop) over de grens of niet; Zakelijke administratie van licenties op producten en diensten van derden; Import- en exportagentschappen; Aankoop voor andere bedrijven; Marketing van goederen en diensten van derden; Diensten van arbeidsbureaus; Web indexering voor commerciële of publicitaire doeleinden; Verspreiding van monsters; Demonstratie van producten; Decoratie van etalages; Reclame voor anderen op het internet; Verspreiding van prospectussen, monsters; Publiciteit; Verkooppromotie [voor derden]; Marketing; Ter beschikking stellen van online verkoopplaats voor kopers en verkopers van goederen en diensten; Inlichtingen over zaken; Agentschappen voor handelsinlichtingen; Reclame via direct mail; Promoten van waren en diensten van anderen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dystrybucja materiałów reklamowych (ulotek, prospektów, broszur, próbek, w szczególności do sprzedaży katalogowej dalekodystansowej) w kraju lub poza nim; Zarządzanie handlowe w zakresie koncesjonowania dóbr i usług na rzecz osób trzecich; Usługi agencji importowo-eksportowych; Usługi w zakresie nabywania dla osób trzecich [zakupy produktów i usług dla innych przedsiębiorstw]; Marketing towarów i usług na rzecz innych; Biura pośrednictwa pracy; Indeksowanie stron internetowych w celach handlowych lub reklamowych; Kolportaż próbek; Pokazy towarów; Dekoracja wystaw sklepowych; Reklama w Internecie dla osób trzecich; Dystrybucja prospektów i próbek; Reklama; Promocja sprzedaży dla osób trzecich; Usługi marketingowe; Zapewnianie platformy internetowej dla nabywców i sprzedawców towarów i usług; Badania dotyczące działalności gospodarczej; Agencje informacji handlowej; Bezpośrednia reklama pocztowa; Promowanie towarów i usług osób trzecich.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Distribuição de material publicitário (flyers, prospetos, brochuras, amostras, em especial para vendas de longa distância por catálogo), tanto internacionais como nacionais; Administração comercial do licenciamento de produtos e serviços para terceiros [serviços de]; Agências de importação-exportação; Serviços de fornecimento para terceiros [compra de produtos e serviços para outras empresas]; Marketing de produtos e serviços de terceiros; Agências de emprego; Indexação Web para fins comerciais ou publicitários; Distribuição de amostras; Demonstração de produtos; Decoração de montras; Publicidade para terceiros na Internet; Distribuição de prospetos e de amostras; Serviços publicitários; Promoção de vendas [para terceiros]; Serviços de marketing; Disponibilização de um espaço de mercado on-line para compradores e vendedores de produtos e serviços; Inquéritos de negócios comerciais; Agências de informações comerciais; Publicidade direta por correio; Promoção dos bens e serviços de terceiros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Distribuire de materiale publicitare (pliante, prospecte, broşuri, mostre, în special pentru vânzările la distanţă pe bază de catalog) indiferent dacă sunt transfrontaliere sau nu; Administrarea comercială a licenţelor produselor şi a serviciilor pentru terţi; Agenţii de import-export; Servicii de aprovizionare pentru terţi [achiziţii de bunuri şi servicii pentru alte întreprinderi]; Marketing de produse şi servicii pentru alte persoane; Agenţii de plasare; Indexare web în scop comercial sau publicitar; Distribuţie de mostre; Prezentare de produse; Decorarea vitrinelor; Publicitate pentru terţi pe internet; Distribuţie de prospecte şi de mostre; Publicitate; Promovarea vânzărilor pentru terţi; Servicii de marketing; Furnizarea unei pieţe online pentru cumpărătorii şi vânzătorii de bunuri şi servicii; Date referitoare la afaceri; Agenţii de informaţii comerciale; Publicitate directă prin poştă; Promovare de produse şi servicii pentru terţi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Rozširovanie reklamných materiálov (letákov, prospektov, brožúr, vzoriek, najmä na účely katalógového predaja) aj do zahraničia; Obchodná správa licencií výrobkov a služieb (pre tretie osoby); Kancelárie zaoberajúce sa dovozom a vývozom; Zásobovacie služby pre tretie osoby (nákup tovarov a služieb pre iné podniky); Marketing výrobkov a služieb tretích osôb; Sprostredkovateľne práce; Indexovanie webových stránok na obchodné alebo reklamné účely; Rozširovanie vzoriek tovarov; Predvádzanie tovaru; Aranžovanie výkladov; Reklama na internete pre tretie osoby; Rozširovanie (distribúcia) prospektov a vzoriek; Reklama; Podpora predaja (pre tretie osoby); Marketing; Online poskytovanie obchodného priestoru pre nákupcov a predajcov tovarov a služieb; Poskytovanie obchodných alebo podnikateľských informácií; Komerčné informačné kancelárie; Rozširovanie reklamných materiálov zákazníkom (letáky, prospekty, tlačoviny, vzorky); Propagovanie tovarov a služieb pre tretie osoby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Distribucija reklamnih materialov (letakov, prospektov, brošur, vzorcev, zlasti za kataloško prodajo na daljavo) bodisi čezmejno ali ne; Poslovna administracija licenciranja blaga in storitev drugih; Uvozno - izvozne agencije; Prokuratorske storitve [nabava blaga in storitev za druga podjetja]; Trženje blaga in storitev drugih; Zaposlovalne agencije; Spletno indeksiranje za komercialne ali oglaševalske namene; Distribucija vzorcev; Predstavitev izdelkov; Aranžiranje izložb; Internetno oglaševanje za tretje osebe; Distribucija prospektov in vzorcev; Oglaševanje in oglaševalske storitve; Pospeševanje prodaje (za druge); Storitve trženja; Zagotavljanje spletnega trga za kupce in prodajalce blaga in storitev; Poslovne poizvedbe; Agencije za poslovne informacije; Neposredno oglaševanje po pošti; Promocija blaga in storitev drugih.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Distribution av reklammaterial (flygblad, prospekt, broschyrer, prover, särskilt kataloger för långdistans försäljning) över gränserna eller inte; Kommersiell administration av licensiering av varor och tjänster för andra; Import-exportagenturer; Inköp av varor och tjänster för annans räkning; Marknadsföring av andras varor och tjänster; Arbetsförmedlingar; Webbindexering för kommersiella eller reklamändamål; Utdelning av varuprover; Varudemonstrationer; Skyltning av skyltfönster; Reklam för andra på internet; Distribution av prospekt och varuprover; Reklam; Sales promotiontjänster; Marknadsföringstjänster; Tillhandahållande av en marknadsplats on-line för köpare och säljare av varor och tjänster; Undersökningar avseende företags- eller affärsverksamhet; Byråer för kommersiell information; Direktreklam; Marknadsföring av varor och tjänster för annans räkning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/100</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/171</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-08</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>956</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
