<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-09T15:51:20</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226505</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226505</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-11-09</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Washing Tower</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>7</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Миялни машини за порцелан; Електрическа прахосмукачка; Маркучи за прахосмукачки; Торбички за прахосмукачки; Стик прахосмукачки; Електрически ротационни вентилатори; Роботи [машини]; Помпи, работещи със сгъстен въздух; Електрически ротационни компресори; Компресори за хладилници; Електрически миксери за домакински цели; Автоматизирани прахосмукачки; Кухненски роботи; Паропочистващи машини за домакински цели; Електрически ръчни прахосмукачки; Електрически прахосмукачки за спални артикули; Домакински роботи за домакински цели; Роботи за персонална употреба; А именно; Роботи за почистване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Myčky nádobí; Elektrické vysavače; Hadice k vysavačům; Sáčky do vysavačů; Tyčové vysavače; Elektrická rotační dmychadla; Roboty [stroje]; Čerpadla na stlačený vzduch; Elektrické rotační kompresory; Kompresory pro ledničky; Mísicí kuchyňské stroje elektrické; Robotické vysavače; Elektrické kuchyňské roboty; Parní čističe pro domácnost; Elektrické ruční vysavače; Elektrické vysavače na lůžkoviny; Roboti na úklid pro použití v domácnosti; Roboty pro osobní použití; Jmenovitě; Roboty na úklid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Opvaskemaskiner; Elektriske støvsugere; Støvsugerslanger; Støvsugerposer; Skaftstøvsugere; Roterende elektriske blæsere; Robotter [maskiner]; Trykluftpumper; Elektriske roterende kompressorer; Kompressorer til køleskabe; Elektriske miksere til husholdningsbrug; Robotstøvsugere; Food processorer, elektriske; Damprensere til husholdningsformål; Elektriske håndholdte støvsugere; Elektriske støvsugere til sengetøj; Husholdningsrobotter til brug i hjemmet; Robotter til personlig brug; Nemlig; Robotter til rengøring.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Geschirrspülmaschinen; Elektrische Staubsauger; Staubsaugerschläuche; Staubsaugerbeutel; Stabstaubsauger; Elektrische Drehkolbengebläse; Roboter [Maschinen]; Druckluftpumpen; Elektrische Rotationskompressoren; Kompressoren für Kühlanlagen; Elektrische Mixer für den Haushalt; Staubsaugerroboter; Elektrische Universal-Küchenmaschinen; Dampfreiniger für Haushaltszwecke; Elektrische Handstaubsauger; Elektrische Staubsauger für Bettzeug; Haushaltsroboter für Haushaltszwecke; Roboter für den persönlichen Gebrauch; Nämlich; Reinigungsroboter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Πλυντήρια για πήλινα σκεύη· Ηλεκτρικές σκούπες· Ηλεκτρικές σκούπες (Σωλήνες για -)· Σακκούλες για ηλεκτρικές σκούπες· Ηλεκτρικές σκούπες τύπου ράβδου· Ηλεκτρικοί περιστροφικοί φυσητήρες· Ρομπότ [μηχανές]· Αέρα πεπιεσμένου (Αντλίες -)· Ηλεκτρικοί περιστροφικoί συμπιεστές· Συμπιεστές για ψυγεία· Ηλεκτρικοί αναμίκτες [μίξερ] για οικιακή χρήση· Ρομποτικές ηλεκτρικές σκούπες· Κουζίνας ηλεκτρικές συσκευές· Ατμοκαθαριστές οικιακής χρήσης· Ηλεκτρικές σκούπες χειρός· Ηλεκτρικές σκούπες για κλινοστρωμνή· Ρομποτ οικιακών εργασιών για οικιακή χρήση· Ρομπότ για προσωπική χρήση; Συγκεκριμένα; Ρομπότ καθαριότητος.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Automatic dishwashers; Electric vacuum cleaners; Hoses for electric vacuum cleaners; Bags for electric vacuum cleaners; Stick type vacuum cleaners; Electric rotary blowers; Robots (machines); Compressed air pumps; Electric rotary compressors; Compressors for refrigerators; Electric mixers for household purposes; Robotic vacuum cleaners; Electric food processors; Steam cleaners for household purposes; Hand-held vacuum cleaners; Electric vacuum cleaners for bedding; Housekeeping robots for household purpose; Robots for personal use, namely, robots for cleaning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Lavaplatos [máquinas]; Aspiradores eléctricos; Tubos de aspiradoras; Bolsas para aspiradoras; Aspiradoras de tipo bastón; Soplantes eléctricos giratorios; Robots industriales; Bombas de aire comprimido; Compresores rotativos eléctricos; Compresores para refrigeradores; Batidoras eléctricas de uso doméstico; Aspiradoras robotizadas; Robots de cocina eléctricos; Limpiadores a vapor para uso doméstico; Aspiradoras de mano eléctricas; Aspiradoras eléctricas para camas; Robots de limpieza para fines domésticos; Robots para uso personal; En concreto; Robots para limpiar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Nõudepesumasinad; Elektrilised tolmuimejad; Tolmuimeja voolikud; Tolmuimeja kotid; Kepitüüpi tolmuimejad; Elektrilised rootorpuhurid; Tööstusrobotid; Suruõhupumbad, pneumopumbad; Elektrilised pöördkompressorid; Külmutusseadmete kompressorid; Elektrimikserid majapidamisotstarbeks; Robottolmuimejad; Elektrilised toidutöötlusmasinad; Majapidamises kasutatavad aurpuhastid; Käsitolmuimejad (elektrilised); Voodikatete elektrilised tolmuimejad; Majapidamises kasutatavad majapidamisrobotid; Isiklikult kasutatavad robotid; Nimelt; Puhastusrobotid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Astianpesukoneet; Sähkökäyttöiset pölynimurit; Pölynimuriletkut; Pölynimureissa käytettävät pussit; Varsityyppiset pölynimurit; Sähkökäyttöiset pyörivät puhaltimet; Robotit [koneina]; Paineilmapumput; Sähkökäyttöiset kiertomäntäkompressorit; Kompressorit jääkaappeihin; Mikserit (Sähkö -), keittiökäyttöön; Robottipölynimurit; Keittiökoneet, sähkökäyttöiset; Höyrypesurit kotitalouskäyttöön; Kädessä pidettävät pölynimurit (sähkökäyttöiset); Sähköimurit vuodevaatteita varten; Kotitalouskäyttöön tarkoitetut kodinhoitorobotit; Robotit henkilökohtaiseen käyttöön; Nimittäin; Puhdistusrobotit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Machines à laver la vaisselle; Aspirateurs électriques; Tuyaux d'aspirateurs de poussière; Sacs pour aspirateurs; Aspirateurs sous forme de balais; Souffleuses rotatives électriques; Robots [machines]; Pompes à air comprimé; Compresseurs rotatifs électriques; Compresseurs pour réfrigérateurs; Mixeurs électriques à usage ménager; Aspirateurs robotisés; Robots de cuisine électriques; Appareils de nettoyage à la vapeur à usage ménager; Aspirateurs électriques à main; Aspirateurs électriques pour la literie; Robots ménagers à usage domestique; Robots à usage personnel; À savoir; Robots pour le nettoyage.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Perilice za posuđe; Električni usisavači; Cijevi za usisavače prašine; Vrećice za usisavače; Štapni usisivači; Električna rotacijska puhala; Roboti [strojevi]; Zračne crpke; Električni rotacijski kompresori; Kompresori za hladnjake; Električni mikseri za kućanstvo; Robotizirani usisavači; Kuhinjski,elektriučni strojevi; Parni čistači za kućanstvo; Ručni usisavači (Električni -); Električni usisavači za krevetninu; Kućanski roboti za upotrebu u domaćinstvu; Roboti za osobnu uporabu; Odnosno; Roboti za čišćenje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Mosogatógépek cserépedényekhez; Elektromos porszívók; Csövek porszívókhoz; Zsákok porszívókhoz; Nyeles porszívók; Elektromos forgódugattyús fúvók; Robotok [gépek]; Sűrített levegős szivattyúk; Elektromos forgó kompresszorok; Kompresszorok hűtőgépekhez; Keverőgépek háztartási használatra [elektromos]; Robotizált porszívók; Elektromos keverőgépek; Háztartási gőztisztító berendezések; Elektromos kézi porszívók; Elektromos porszívók ágyneműhöz; Háztartási robotok háztartási célra; Robotok személyi használatra; Nevezetesen; Takarító robotok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Lavastoviglie; Aspirapolvere elettrici; Tubi per aspirapolvere; Sacchi per aspirapolvere; Scopa elettrica; Soffianti rotanti elettrici; Robot [macchine]; Pompe ad aria compressa; Compressori rotativi elettrici; Compressori per frigoriferi; Mixer da cucina per uso domestico [elettrici]; Aspirapolvere robotizzati; Robots da cucina elettrici; Apparecchi per la pulizia a vapore per uso domestico; Aspiratori manuali (Elettrici -); Aspiratori elettrici per biancheria da letto; Robot per la pulizia della casa per uso domestico; Robot per uso personale; Ovvero; Robot per la pulizia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Indaplovės; Elektriniai dulkių siurbliai; Dulkių siurblių žarnos; Dulkių siurblių maišeliai; Lazdos formos dulkių siurbliai; Elektriniai rotaciniai ventiliatoriai; Robotai [mašinos]; Pneumatiniai siurbliai; Elektriniai rotaciniai kompresoriai; Šaldytuvų kompresoriai; Elektriniai buitiniai maisto maišytuvai; Robotizuoti dulkių siurbliai; Elektrinė maisto pramonės įranga; Buitiniai garinio valymo prietaisai; Rankiniai dulkių siurbliai (Elektriniai -); Elektriniai dulkių siurbliai patalynei; Namų ūkio tvarkymo robotai; Robotai, skirti asmeninėms reikmėms; Būtent,; Valymo robotai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Trauku mazgājamās mašīnas; Elektriskie putekļu sūcēji; Putekļsūcēju caurules; Putekļsūcēju maisiņi; Nūjveida putekļsūcēji; Elektriski rotējošie pūtēji; Roboti [iekārtas]; Saspiesta gaisa sūkņi; Elektriski rotācijas kompresori; Kompresori ledusskapjiem; Elektriskie mikseri izmantošanai mājsaimniecībā; Robotizēti putekļu sūcēji; Elektriski universālie virtuves kombaini; Tvaika tīrīšanas ierīces izmantošanai mājsaimniecībā; Rokas elektriskie putekļsūcēji; Elektriski putekļsūcēji gultasveļai; Roboti mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Roboti personīgai lietošanai; Proti; Roboti tīrīšanas mērķiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Magni tal-ħasil għall-affarijiet li tiekol fihom jew isservi l-ikel bihom; Naddafa tal-vakwu elettriċi; Pajpijiet tan-naddafa bil-vakwu; Boroż għal vacuum cleaners; Apparat tat-tindif bil-vakwu stick-type; Blowers rotatorji elettriċi; Robots [magni]; Pompi tal-arja kompressata; Kumpressuri rotatorji elettriċi; Kumpressuri għall-friġġijiet; Apparat elettriku li jħallat għal skopijiet domestiċi; Vacuum cleaners robotiċi; Magni tal-kċina, ta' l-elettriku; Apparat li jnaddaf bil-fwar għall-użu fid-djar; Apparat ta' tindif bil-vakum li jinżamm fl-idejn (elettriċi); Vacuum cleaners elettriċi għall-friex; Robots li jinżammu d-dar għall-użu domestiku; Robots għall-użu personali; Jiġifieri; Robots għat-tindif.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Vaatwassers; Stofzuigers (Elektrische -); Stofzuigerslangen; Stofzuigerzakken; Steelstofzuigers; Elektrische roterende blazers; Robots [machines]; Luchtdrukpompen; Elektrische roterende compressoren; Compressoren voor koelkasten; Elektrische mixers voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Stofzuigers (Robot -); Elektrische keukenmachines [food processors]; Stoomreinigers voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Handstofzuigers (elektriscn); Elektrische stofzuigers voor beddengoed; Huishoudelijke robots voor huishoudelijke doeleinden; Robots voor persoonlijk gebruik; Te weten; Schoonmaakrobots.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia do mycia naczyń stołowych; Odkurzacze elektryczne; Węże do odkurzaczy; Torby do odkurzaczy; Odkurzacze na drążku; Elektryczne dmuchawy rotacyjne; Roboty przemysłowe; Pompy na sprężone powietrze; Elektryczne sprężarki rotacyjne; Sprężarki do lodówek; Miksery elektryczne do celów domowych; Odkurzacze roboty; Maszyny kuchenne, elektryczne; Urządzenia do czyszczenia parą, przeznaczone do użytku domowego; Elektryczne odkurzacze ręczne; Odkurzacze elektryczne do pościeli; Roboty sprzątające na potrzeby gospodarstwa domowego; Roboty do użytku osobistego; Zn; Roboty sprzątające.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máquinas de lavar loiça; Aspiradores elétricos; Tubos de aspiradores; Sacos para aspiradores; Aspiradores de pó verticais; Sopradores rotativos elétricos; Robôs [máquinas]; Bombas de ar comprimido; Compressores rotativos elétricos; Compressores para frigoríficos; Liquidificadores elétricos de uso doméstico; Aspiradores robóticos; Robôs de cozinha, elétricos; Aparelhos de limpeza a vapor para uso doméstico; Aspiradores de mão elétricos; Aspiradores de pó elétricos para roupa de cama; Robôs domésticos para fins domésticos; Robôs para uso pessoal; Nomeadamente; Robôs para limpeza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Vesela (Mașini pentru spălat -); Aspiratoare electrice; Tuburi pentru aspiratoare de praf; Saci pentru aspiratoare; Aspiratoare verticale; Suflante rotative electrice; Roboţi [maşini]; Pompe de aer comprimat; Compresoare rotative electrice; Compresoare pentru frigidere; Mixere electrice de uz casnic; Aspiratoare automate; Bucătărie (Mașini electrice de -); Aparate de curățat cu aburi de uz casnic; Aspiratoare cu mâner electrice; Aspiratoare electrice pentru așternuturi; Roboți pentru menaj de uz casnic; Roboţi pentru uz personal; Şi anume; Roboți pentru curățenie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Umývačky riadu; Elektrické vysávače; Hadice vysávačov prachu; Vrecká do vysávačov; Tyčové vysávače; Elektrické rotačné dúchadlá; Roboty (stroje); Čerpadlá na stlačený vzduch; Elektrické rotačné kompresory; Kompresory chladiacich zariadení; Ručné mixéry a šľahače do domácnosti [elektrické]; Robotické vysávače; Elektrické kuchynské roboty; Prístroje na čistenie parou do domácnosti; Elektrické ručné vysávače; Elektrické vysávače na posteľnú bielizeň; Upratovacie roboty pre domácnosť; Roboty na osobné účely; T.z; Upratovacie roboty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pralni stroji za lončeno posodo; Električni sesalniki; Cevi za sesalce za prah; Vrečke za vakuumske sesalce; Pokončni sesalniki; Električni rotacijski pihalniki; Roboti [stroji]; Črpalke na stisnjen zrak; Električni rotacijski kompresorji; Kompresorji za hladilnike; Električni stepalniki za gospodinjske namene; Robotski vakuumski sesalniki; Električni mešalniki; Parni čistilniki za gospodinjske namene; Električni ročni sesalniki; Električni sesalniki za posteljnino; Gospodinjski roboti za gospodinjske namene; Roboti za osebno uporabo; Sicer; Roboti za čiščenje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Diskmaskiner för porslin; Elektriska dammsugare; Dammsugarslangar; Dammsugarpåsar; Dammsugare av skafttyp; Elektriska roterande blåsmaskiner; Robotar [maskiner]; Tryckluftspumpar; Elektriska roterande kompressorer; Kompressorer för kylskåp; Elektriska mixers för hushållsändamål; Robotdammsugare; Matberedare, elektriska; Ångrengöringsmaskiner för hushållsbruk; Handdammsugare (elektriska); Elektriska dammsugare för sängkläder; Robotar för hushållsskötsel för hemmet; Robotar för personligt bruk; Nämligen; Robotar för rengöring.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Климатични апарати; Апарати за горещ въздух, а именно, отоплителни апарати с горещ въздух за пространствено отопление; Овлажнители на въздуха; Обезвлажнители за домакинска употреба; Електрически печки; Уреди за пречистване на вода за домакински цели; Водни йонизатори [за домакински цели]; Мембрани за филтриране на вода; Слънчеви колектори [за отопление]; Въздухопречистватели; Вентилационни апарати (климатици) за отопление; Светодиодни [LED] лампи; Газови готварски печки; Електрически готварски фурни; Готварски уреди и инсталации; Електрически хладилници; Вентилационни капаци; Вентилаторни отводи за пещи.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Klimatizační přístroje; Teplovzdušná zařízení, jmenovitě horkovzdušná topná tělesa; Zvlhčovače vzduchu; Odvlhčovače k domácímu použití; Elektrická kamna; Čističky vody pro použití v domácnosti; Ionizátory vody pro domácnost; Membrány k filtraci vody; Solární termální kolektory [vytápění]; Čističe vzduchu; Ventilační [klimatizační] přístroje na topení; Lampy LED; Plynové sporáky; Elektrické trouby na přípravu jídel; Přístroje a zařízení na vaření; Elektrické ledničky; Digestoře; Digestoře nad trouby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Luftkonditioneringsapparater; Varmluftsapparater, nemlig varmluftapparater til opvarmning af rum; Luftfugtere; Affugtere til husholdningsbrug; Elektriske komfurer; Vandrensningsapparater til husholdningsformål; Vandioniseringsapparater [til husholdningsbrug]; Membraner til filtrering af vand; Termiske solfangere [opvarmning]; Luftrensere; Apparater til opvarmning, ventilation og luftkonditionering; LED-lamper; Gasdrevne kogeapparater; Elektriske ovne til madlavning; Apparater og installationer til kogning; Elektriske køleskabe; Ventilationshætter; Udsugningshætter [kapper] til ovne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Klimageräte; Heißluftapparate, nämlich Heißluftraumheizgeräte; Luftbefeuchter; Entfeuchter für Haushaltszwecke; Elektroherde; Wasserreinigungsgeräte für Haushaltszwecke; Wasserionisatoren [für Haushaltszwecke]; Membranen zur Wasserfilterung; Thermische Sonnenkollektoren [Heizung]; Luftreiniger; Lüftungsgeräte [Klimatisierung] zum Heizen; LED-Lampen; Gasherde; Elektroküchenherde; Kochapparate und -anlagen; Elektrische Kühlschränke; Belüftungshauben; Abzugshauben für Öfen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές κλιματισμού· Συσκευές θερμού αέρα, συγκεκριμένα, συσκευές θέρμανσης χώρου με θερμό αέρα· Συσκευές ύγρανσης, συσκευές αφύγρανσης· Αφυγραντήρες για οικιακή χρήση· Ηλεκτρικές κουζίνες· Συσκευές καθαρισμού ύδατος για οικιακή χρήση· Ιονιστές ύδατος για οικιακή χρήση· Μεμβράνες για τη διήθηση νερού· Θερμικοί ηλιακοί συλλέκτες [θέρμανσης]· Απολυμαντές του αέρα [συσκευές απολύμανσης του αέρα]· Συσκευές αερισμού [κλιματιστικά] για θέρμανση· Λυχνίες φωτοδιόδων (LED)· Κουζίνες αερίου· Φούρνοι ηλεκτρικοί· Ψησίματος (Συσκευές και εγκαταστάσεις -)· Ηλεκτρικά ψυγεία· Απορροφητήρες εξαερισμού· Ανοικτοί απορροφητήρες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Air conditioners; Hot air apparatus, namely, hot-air space heating apparatus; Humidifiers; Electric dehumidifier for household use; Electric ranges; Water purifiers for household purposes; Water ionizers for household purposes; Membrane apparatus in the nature of filters for purifying water; Solar thermal collectors (heating); Air purifiers; Ventilation (air-conditioning) apparatus for heating; LED lamps; Gas ranges; Electric kitchen ovens; Apparatus or installations for cooking; Electric refrigerators; Ventilation hoods; Ventilation hoods for oven.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de aire acondicionado; Aparatos de aire caliente, en concreto aparatos de calefacción de aire caliente; Saturadores; Deshumidificadores para uso doméstico; Cocinas eléctricas; Purificadores de agua para uso doméstico; Ionizadores de agua [para uso doméstico]; Membranas para filtrar agua; Colectores solares térmicos [calefacción]; Purificadores de aire; Aparatos de ventilación [aire acondicionado] de calefacción; Lámparas LED; Cocinas (fogones) de gas; Hornos de cocina eléctricos; Aparatos e instalaciones de cocción; Frigoríficos eléctricos; Campanas de ventilación; Campanas de ventilación de hornos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kliimaseadmed, klimaatorid; Kuumaõhuseadmed, nimelt kuumaõhu-ruumikütteseadmed; Õhuniisutajad; Niiskuse-eemaldajad majapidamises kasutamiseks; Elektripliidid; Veepuhastid majapidamises kasutamiseks; Veeionisaatorid [majapidamises kasutamiseks]; Membraanid vee filtrimiseks; Päikesekollektorid [küte]; Õhupuhastid; Kütte-ventilatsiooniseadmed [kliimaseadmed]; Valgusdioodlambid, LED-lambid; Gaasipliidid, gaasiga töötavad pliidid; Elektriküpsetusahjud, elektrilised küpsetusahjud; Toiduainete kuumtöötlemise seadmed; Elektrikülmikud; Tõmbekapid; Ahjude tõmbekapid, ventilaatorkapid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ilmastointilaitteet; Kuumailmalaitteet, nimittäin kuumalla ilmalla toimivat sisätilojen lämmityslaitteet; Ilmankostuttimet; Kosteudenpoistimet kotitalouskäyttöön; Sähköliedet; Vedenpuhdistimet kotikäyttöön; Veden ionisointiin tarkoitetut laitteet (kotitaloustarkoituksiin); Kalvot veden suodatukseen; Aurinkolämpöenergian kerääjät [lämmitykseen]; Ilmanpuhdistimet; Ilmanvaihtolaitteet (ilmastointi) lämmitykseen; LED-lamput; Kaasukeittimet; Sähkökäyttöiset uunit ruoanlaittoon; Keittolaitteet; Sähköjääkaapit; Ilmanvaihtokuvut; Liesituulettimet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils de climatisation; Appareils à air chaud, à savoir, appareils de chauffage des locaux à air chaud; Humidificateurs d'air; Déshumidificateurs à usage ménager; Cuisinières électriques; Épurateurs d'eau à usage domestique; Ioniseurs d'eau à usage ménager; Membranes pour la filtration de l'eau [parties d'installations sanitaires]; Capteurs solaires à conversion thermique [chauffage]; Purificateurs d'air; Appareils de ventilation [climatisation] pour chauffage; Ampoules DEL; Cuisinières à gaz; Fours de cuisson électriques; Appareils et installations de cuisson; Réfrigérateurs électriques; Hottes d'aération; Hottes de ventilation pour fours.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Klimatizacijiski uređaji; Uređaji koji proizvode vrući zrak, odnosno uređaji koji proizvode vrući zrak za zagrijavanje prostora; Ovlaživači; Odvlaživači za kućanstvo; Električni štednjaci; Uređaji za pročišćavanje vode za kućanstvo; Ionizatori vode [za kućanstvo]; Membrane za filtriranje vode; Paneli za solarno grijanje; Pročišćivači zraka; Ventilacijski [klimatizacijski] uređaji za grijanje; Svjetiljke LED; Plinska kuhala; Električne kuhinjske pećnice; Uređaji i instalacije za kuhanje; Električni hladnjaci; Nape (Ekstrator -) za kuhinje; Ventilatorske nape za peći.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Légkondicionálók; Forrólevegős készülékek, nevezetesen forrólevegős fűtőberendezések; Légnedvesítők; Párátlanítók háztartási használatra; Elektromos tűzhelyek; Víztisztítók háztartási célokra; Vízionizálók [háztartási célokra]; Vízszűrésre szolgáló membránok; Napkollektorok [fűtés]; Légtisztítók; Szellőző- [légkondicionáló] berendezés fűtéshez; LED-lámpák; Gáztűzhelyek; Elektromos sütők; Főző berendezések és készülékek; Elektromos hűtőgépek, hűtőszekrények; Elszívóernyők; Páraelszívó ernyők.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi per climatizzazione dell'aria; Apparecchi ad aria calda, ovvero riscaldatori d'aria per ambienti; Saturatori; Deumidificatori per uso domestico; Fornelli elettrici; Depuratori d'acqua per uso domestico; Ionizzatori d'acqua [per uso domestico]; Membrane per la filtrazione dell'acqua; Collettori solari [riscaldamento]; Depuratori d'aria; Apparecchi di ventilazione [condizionamento d'aria] per il riscaldamento; Lampade a LED; Cucine a gas; Forni elettrici da cucina; Apparecchi ed impianti per la cottura; Frigoriferi elettrici; Cappe di aerazione; Cappe di ventilazione per forni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Oro kondicionavimo aparatai; Karšto oro aparatai, būtent, karšto oro patalpų šildymo aparatai; Oro drėkintuvai; Drėgmės surinkėjai namų ūkio reikmėms; Elektrinės viryklės; Vandens valymo įrenginiai buities reikmėms; Vandens jonizatoriai [namų apyvokos reikmėms]; Vandens filtravimo membranos; Saulės kolektoriai [šildymas]; Oro gryninimo mašinos; Vėdinimo [oro kondicionavimo] aparatai šildymo reikmėms; Šviesolaidžio (LED) lempos; Dujinės viryklės; Elektrinės valgio gaminimo orkaitės; Maisto gaminimo [virimo, kepimo] aparatai ir įrenginiai; Elektriniai šaldytuvai; Traukos gaubtai; Orkaitės ventiliatoriaus gaubtai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Gaisa kondicionēšanas ierīces; Karstā gaisa ierīces, proti, karstā gaisa telpas sildierīces; Ierīces gaisa mitrināšanai; Mitruma regulatori mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Elektriskas plītis; Ūdens attīrītāji mājsaimniecībām; Ūdens jonizatori [mājsaimniecības vajadzībām]; Ūdens filtrēšanas membrānas; Saules kolektori apkures nolūkiem; Gaisa attīrīšanas ierīces; Ventilācijas [gaisa kondicionēšana] iekārtas apkurei; LED lampas; Gāzes plītis; Elektriskas cepeškrāsnis; Ēdienu termiskās apstrādes ierīces un to sistēmu daļas; Elektriski ledusskapji; Ventilācijas sistēmu nosūcēji; Krāsns tvaika nosūcēji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat tal-ikkondizzjonar tal-arja; Apparat li jaħdem b'arja sħuna, jiġifieri, apparat għat-tisħin tal-ispazju bl-arja sħuna; Tagħmir għas-saturazzjoni; Apparat li jneħħi l-umdita għall-użu domestiku; Kukers elettriċi għat-tisjir; Purifikaturi tal-ilma għall-użu domestiku; Jonizzaturi tal-ilma [għal skopijiet domestiċi]; Membrani għall-filtrazzjoni tal-ilma; Apparat għall-ġbir tas-sħana mix-xemx [għat-tisħin]; Purifikaturi tal-arja; Apparat ta' ċirkolazzjoni tal-arja [ikkondizzjonar tal-arja] għat-tisħin; Lampi LED; Kukers tal-gass; Fran tat-tisjir elettriċi; Apparat u tagħmir tat-tisjir; Refriġeraturi tal-elettriku; Għata għall-ventilazzjoni; Koperti għall-ventilaturi tal-fran.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Airconditioning-apparaten; Heteluchtapparaten, te weten voor ruimteverwarming; Bevochtigers; Ontvochtigers [voor huishoudelijke doeleinden]; Elektrische fornuizen; Waterzuivereraars voor huishoudelijke doeleinden; Waterionisatie-inrichtingen [voor huishoudelijke doeleinden]; Membranen voor het filtreren van water; Zonnecollectoren voor warmteconversie; Luchtzuiveraars; Ventilatie- [klimaatregelings-] apparaten voor verwarming; Led-lampen; Gasfornuizen; Elektrische kookfornuizen; Kooktoestellen en -installaties; Koelkasten (Elektrische -); Luchtafzuigkappen; Afzuigkappen voor ovens.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia klimatyzacyjne; Urządzenia generujące gorące powietrze, mianowicie urządzenia do ogrzewania przestrzeni gorącym powietrzem; Nawilżacze powietrza; Osuszacze do zastosowania w gospodarstwie domowym; Kuchenki elektryczne; Urządzenia do oczyszczania wody do użytku domowego; Jonizatory wody do celów domowych; Membrany do filtrowania wody; Termiczne kolektory słoneczne [ogrzewanie]; Oczyszczacze powietrza; Urządzenia wentylacyjne [klimatyzacji] do ogrzewania; Lampy LED; Kuchenki gazowe; Piekarniki elektryczne; Urządzenia i instalacje do gotowania; Lodówki elektryczne; Wyciągi wentylacyjne; Okapy wentylacyjne do piekarników.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos de ar condicionado; Aparelhos de ar quente, nomeadamente, aparelhos de ar quente para aquecimento de espaços interiores; Saturadores; Desumidificadores para uso doméstico; Fogões elétricos de cozinha; Purificadores de água para uso doméstico; Ionizadores de água [para uso doméstico]; Membranas para a filtragem de água; Coletores solares [aquecimento]; Purificadores do ar; Aparelhos de ventilação [ar condicionado] para aquecimento; Lâmpadas LED; Fogões a gás; Fornos elétricos para cozinhar; Aparelhos e instalações de cozinhar; Refrigeradores elétricos; Tabiques de ventilação; Exaustores de fumos para fornos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate de climatizare; Aparate cu aer cald, şi anume, aparate de încălzirea a spaţiilor cu aer cald; Umidificatoare; Dezumidificatoare de uz casnic; Mașini electrice de gătit; Aparate pentru purificarea apei, de uz casnic; Aparate pentru ionizarea apei [de uz casnic]; Membrane pentru filtrarea apei; Colectoare termice solare [încălzire]; Purificatoare de aer; Aparate pentru încălzire, ventilare [aer condiţionat]; Lămpi cu LED; Mașini de gătit pe gaz; Cuptoare electrice de gătit; Aparate și instalații de gătit; Frigidere electrice; Hote de aerisire; Hote cu ventilator pentru cuptor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Klimatizačné prístroje; Teplovzdušné zariadenia, menovite teplovzdušné vykurovacie zariadenia do miestností; Sýtiace zariadenia; Odvlhčovače do domácnosti; Elektrické sporáky; Čističky vody pre domácnosť; Ionizátory vody pre domáce použitie; Membrány na filtrovanie vody; Solárne kolektory na ohrev vody a vykurovanie; Čističe vzduchu; Ventilačné [klimatizačné] prístroje na vykurovanie; LED lampy; Plynové sporáky; Elektrické rúry na pečenie; Varné prístroje a zariadenia; Elektrické chladničky; Dymníky; Digestory pre rúry.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Klimatske naprave; Naprave na vroči zrak, in sicer naprave za ogrevanje prostorov z vročim zrakom; Saturatorji; Razvlažilci za uporabo v gospodinjstvu; Električni štedilniki; Čistilne naprave za vodo, za gospodinjske namene; Vodni ionizatorji [za gospodinjsko uporabo]; Membrane za filtriranje vode; Sončni termalni kolektorji [ogrevanje]; Prečiščevalci zraka; Naprave za prezračevanje [klimatizacija] za ogrevanje; LED svetilke; Kuhalniki na plin; Električne pečice za kuhinjo; Naprave in napeljave za kuhanje; Električni hladilniki; Prezračevalne nape; Prezračevalne nape za peči.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Luftkonditioneringsapparater; Varmluftsapparater, nämligen varmluftsapparater för uppvärmning av utrymmen; Saturatorer; Avfuktningsapparat för hushållsändamål; Elektriska spisar; Vattenrenare för hushållsändamål; Vattenjoniserare [för hushållsändamål]; Membran för filtrering av vatten; Solvärmesfångare [uppvärmning]; Luftrenare; Ventilations- [luftkonditionerings-] apparater för uppvärmning; LED-lampor; Brännare för gas; Elektriska matlagningsugnar; Apparater och installationer för kokning; Elektriska kylskåp; Ventilationskåpor; Ugnsventilationshuvar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/194</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-09</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>144734</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>10014</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003134473</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-11-09</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018046865</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2019-04-03</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>018046865</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2019-09-14</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>WASHTOWER</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018193675</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-02-07</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>018193675</RegistrationNumber>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>WASHTOWER</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>1101541</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>43640</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
