<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-05T16:31:39</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226516</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226516</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-31</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>sv</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>FIRST AID KIT</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Звукозаписи; Видеозаписи; Аудио- и видеозаписи; Софтуер; Електронни публикации, които могат да бъдат прехвърляни върху друг носител; Звукозаписни апарати; Апарати за записване на изображения; Звукопредавателни апарати; Устройства за предаване на видеосигнал; Звуковъзпроизвеждащи апарати; Апарати за възпроизвеждане на образи; Магнитни носители на данни; Грамофонни плочи; Дигитална музика предлагана в интернет с възможност за сваляне; Компакт-дискове; DVD; Видеокасети; Рамки за пенснета; Слънчеви очила.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Audio nahrávky; Videozáznamy; Audio a video záznamy; Počítačový software; Stahovatelné elektronické publikace; Přístroje pro záznam zvuku; Přístroje na záznam obrazu; Zařízení pro přenos zvuku; Přístroje na reprodukci zvuku; Přístroje pro reprodukci zvuku; Přístroje na reprodukci obrazu; Magnetická datová média; Gramofonové desky; Digitální stahovatelná hudba dodávána z internetu; Kompaktní disky; DVD; Videopásky; Brýlové obroučky; Sluneční brýle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Indspilninger af lyd; Videooptagelser; Audiovisuelle optagelser; Software; Elektroniske publikationer, downloadable; Lydoptageapparater; Apparater til billedoptagelse; Lydtransmitterende apparater; Apparater til billedtransmission; Lydgengiveapparater; Apparater til gengivelse af billeder; Magnetiske databærere; Lydplader; Digital musik til download fra internettet; CDer; Dvd'er; Videobånd; Brillestel; Solbriller.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Tonaufnahmen; Videoaufzeichnungen; Ton- und Videoaufzeichnungen; Software; Herunterladbare elektronische Publikationen; Tonaufzeichnungsgeräte; Bildaufzeichnungsgeräte; Tonübertragungsgeräte; Bildübertragungsgeräte; Tonwiedergabegeräte; Bildwiedergabegeräte; Magnetdatenträger; Schallplatten; Aus dem Internet herunterladbare digitale Musik; CDs; DVDs; Videobänder; Brillenfassungen, -gestelle; Sonnenbrillen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ηχητικές εγγραφές· Βιντεοεγγραφές· Οπτικοακουστικές εγγραφές· Λογισμικό· Ηλεκτρονικές εκδόσεις, με δυνατότητα μεταφόρτωσης· Εγγραφή ήχου (Όργανα για τη -)· Συσκευές εγγραφής εικόνων· Ήχου (Συσκευές και μηχανήματα μετάδοσης -)· Συσκευές μετάδοσης εικόνων· Αναπαραγωγής ήχου (Συσκευές -)· Συσκευές αναπαραγωγής εικόνων· Μαγνητικοί φορείς δεδομένων· Ηχογραφήσεων δίσκοι· Ψηφιακή μουσική με δυνατότητα μεταφόρτωσης, παρεχόμενη από το Διαδίκτυο· Σύμπυκνοι δίσκοι· Ψηφιακοί βιντεοδίσκοι (DVD)· Κασέτες βίντεο· Σκελετοί γυαλιών· Γυαλιά ηλίου.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Audio recordings; Video recordings; Audio visual recordings; Computer software; Electronic publications, downloadable; Sound recording apparatus; Apparatus for recording images; Sound transmitting apparatus; Apparatus for the transmission of images; Sound reproduction apparatus; Apparatus for the reproduction of images; Magnetic data media; Phonograph records; Digital music downloadable provided from the internet; Compact discs; DVDs; Videotapes; Spectacle frames; Sunglasses.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Grabaciones de audio; Grabaciones de vídeo; Grabaciones audiovisuales; Software informático; Publicaciones electrónicas descargables; Aparatos de grabación de sonido; Aparatos para el registro de imágenes; Aparatos de transmisión de sonido; Aparatos para la transmisión de imágenes; Aparatos de reproducción de sonido; Aparatos para la reproducción de imágenes; Soportes magnéticos de datos; Discos acústicos; Música digital (descargable) facilitada desde Internet; Discos compactos; DVD; Cintas de vídeo; Monturas de gafas; Gafas de sol.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Helisalvestised; Videosalvestised; Audiovisuaalsed salvestised; Arvutitarkvara; Elektroonilised allalaaditavad publikatsioonid; Helisalvestusaparaadid, helisalvestusseadmed; Seadmed piltide salvestamiseks; Heliedastusseadmed; Seadmed piltide edastamiseks; Helitaasestusaparaadid, helitaasesitusseadmed; Seadmed piltide kopeerimiseks, taasesituseks; Magnetandmekandjad; Heliplaadid, grammofoniplaadid; Internetist allalaaditav digitaalne muusika; Laserplaadid; DVD-d; Videolindid; Prilliraamid; Päikeseprillid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Audiotallenteet; Videotallenteet; Audiovisuaaliset tallenteet; Ohjelmistot; Elektroniset julkaisut [järjestelmästä toiseen poimittavat]; Äänityslaitteet; Kuvantallennuslaitteet; Äänensiirtolaitteet; Kuvien lähetyslaitteet; Äänentoistolaitteet; Kuvantoistolaitteet; Magneettiset tietovälineet; Äänilevyt; Internetin kautta tarjottava (ladattava) digitaalinen musiikki; Cd-levyt; DVD-levyt; Videokasetit; Silmälasinkehykset; Aurinkolasit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Enregistrements audio; Enregistrements vidéo; Enregistrements audiovisuels; Logiciels pour ordinateurs; Publications électroniques téléchargeables; Appareils pour l'enregistrement du son; Appareils d'enregistrement d'images; Appareils pour la transmission du son; Appareils de transmission d'images; Appareils pour la reproduction du son; Appareils de reproduction d'images; Supports de données magnétiques; Disques acoustiques; Musique numérique téléchargeable hébergée sur Internet; Disques compacts [CD]; DVD; Bandes vidéo; Montures de lunettes; Lunettes de soleil.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Audio snimke; Video snimke; Audio vizualne snimke; Softver; Elektronske publikacije koje se mogu preuzeti s Interneta; Uređaji za snimanje zvuka; Uređaji za snimanje slika; Uređaji za prijenos zvuka; Uređaji za prijenos slika; Uređaji za reprodukciju zvuka; Uređaji za reprodukciju slika; Podloge magnetne za podatke; Akustične ploče; Digitalna glazba koja se može preuzeti s Interneta; Kompaktni diskovi; DVD-ovi; Videokasete; Okviri za naočale; Sunčane naočale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Audio felvételek; Videofelvételek; Audiovizuális felvételek; Szoftverek; Letölthető elektronikus kiadványok, publikációk; Hangrögzítő, hangfelvevő készülékek; Képrögzítő készülékek; Hangátvitelre szolgáló készülékek; Képátvitelre szolgáló készülékek; Hangreprodukáló készülékek; Képreprodukáló készülékek; Mágneses adathordozók; Hanglemezek; Internetről letölthető digitális zene; Kompaktlemezek, CD-k; DVD-k; Videokazetták; Szemüvegkeretek; Napszemüvegek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Registrazioni audio; Registrazioni video; Registrazioni audiovisive; Software; Pubblicazioni elettroniche [scaricabili]; Apparecchi per la registrazione del suono; Apparecchi per la registrazione di immagini; Apparecchi per la trasmissione del suono; Apparecchi per la trasmissione di immagini; Apparecchi per la riproduzione del suono; Apparecchi per la riproduzione di immagini; Supporti magnetici per dati; Dischi acustici; Musica digitale scaricabile fornita da Internet; CD; DVD; Nastri video; Montature di occhiali; Occhiali da sole.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Garso įrašai; Vaizdo įrašai; Garso ir vaizdo įrašai; Programinė įranga; Elektroniniai leidiniai [parsisiunčiamieji]; Garso įrašymo aparatai; Vaizdų įrašymo aparatai; Garso perdavimo aparatai; Vaizdų perdavimo aparatūra; Garso atkūrimo aparatai; Vaizdo reprodukcijos aparatai; Magnetinės duomenų laikmenos; Garso įrašai; Skaitmeninė muzika (parsisiųsdinama) iš interneto; Kompaktiniai diskai; Skaitmeniniai vaizdo diskai (DVD); Vaizdajuostės [videojuostos]; Akinių rėmai; Saulės akiniai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Audioieraksti; Videoieraksti; Audiovizuālie ieraksti; Datoru programmatūra; Lejupielādējamas elektroniskās publikācijas; Skaņu ieraksta ierīces; Attēlu ierakstīšanas ierīces; Skaņu pārraides ierīces; Attēlu pārraides iekārtas; Skaņu reproducēšanas ierīces; Attēlu pavairošanas iekārtas; Magnētiskie datu nesēji; Skaņuplates un skaņu ieraksta diski; Digitālā mūzika (lejupielādējama), kas iegūstama no Interneta; Kompaktdiski; Digitālie videodiski; Videoieraksta lentes; Briļļu rāmji; Saulesbrilles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reġistrazzjonijiet tal-awdjo; Reġistrazzjonijiet tal-vidjo; Reġistrazzjonijiet awdjoviżivi; Softwer; Pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi, li jistgħu jitniżżlu; Tagħmir għar-reġistrazzjoni tal-ħoss; Apparat li jirreġistra l-immaġni; Apparat li jittrasmetti l-ħsejjes; Apparat għat-trasmissjoni tal-immaġni; Apparat li jirriproduċi l-ħsejjes; Apparat għar-riproduzzjoni ta' immaġni; Medja ta' data manjetika; Rekords tal-fonografu; Mużika diġitali li tista' titniżżel provduta mill-internet; Diski kumpatti; DVDs; Kasetts tal-vidjo; Frejms għan-nuċċalijiet; Nuċċalijiet tax-xemx.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Audio-opnamen; Video-opnamen; Audiovisuele opnamen; Software; Elektronische publicaties [te downloaden]; Geluidsopname-apparaten; Beeldopname-apparatuur; Apparaten voor het overbrengen van geluid; Beeldoverdracht-apparatuur; Geluidsweergave-apparaten; Beeldweergave-apparatuur; Magnetische gegevensdragers; Schijfvormige geluidsdragers; Digitale muziek (downloadbaar) geleverd vanaf het Internet; Compactdiscs; Dvd's; Videobanden; Brilmonturen; Zonnebrillen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Nagrania audio; Nagrania wideo; Nagrania audio i wideo; Oprogramowanie; Publikacje elektroniczne, do pobrania; Urządzenia do rejestrowania dźwięku; Urządzenia do nagrywania obrazów; Urządzenia do transmisji dźwięku; Urządzenia do przesyłania obrazów; Urządzenia do odtwarzania dźwięku; Urządzenia do odtwarzania obrazów; Magnetyczne nośniki danych; Płyty gramofonowe; Muzyka cyfrowa do pobrania dostarczona z Internetu; Płyty kompaktowe; Płyty DVD; Kasety wideo; Oprawki do okularów; Okulary przeciwsłoneczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Gravações de áudio; Gravações de vídeo; Gravações audiovisuais; Software; Publicações eletrónicas descarregáveis; Aparelhos para a gravação de som; Aparelhos para gravação de imagens; Aparelhos para a transmissão de som; Aparelhos de transmissão de imagens; Aparelhos para a reprodução de som; Aparelhos para a reprodução de imagens; Suportes de dados magnéticos; Discos acústicos; Música digital descarregável fornecida a partir da internet; Discos compactos; DVDs; Fitas de vídeo; Armações de óculos; Óculos de sol.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Înregistrări audio; Înregistrări video; Aparate pentru înregistrări audio-video; Software; Publicații electronice descărcabile; Înregistrarea sunetelor (Aparate pentru -); Aparate pentru înregistrarea imaginilor; Aparate pentru transmiterea sunetului; Aparate de transmitere de imagini; Reproducerea sunetului (Aparate pentru -); Aparate pentru reproducerea imaginilor; Suporturi de date magnetice; Discuri de picup; Muzică digitală care poate fi descărcată de pe internet; Compact discuri; DVD-uri; Casete video; Rame de ochelari fără brațe; Ochelari de soare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Audionahrávky; Video nahrávky; Audiovizuálne nahrávky; Softvér; Elektronické publikácie (sťahovateľné); Zvukové nahrávacie zariadenia; Prístroje na záznam obrazu; Zariadenia na prenos zvuku; Zariadenia na prenos obrazov; Zvukové prehrávacie zariadenia, prehrávače; Prístroje na reprodukciu obrazu; Magnetické nosiče údajov; Gramofónové platne; Stiahnuteľná digitálna hudba z internetu; Kompaktné disky; DVD; Videopásky; Rámy na okuliare; Slnečné okuliare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Avdio posnetki; Video posnetki; Avdiovizualni posnetki; Programska oprema; Naložljive elektronske publikacije; Aparati za snemanje zvoka; Aparati za snemanje slik; Aparati za prenos zvoka; Aparati za prenos slik; Aparati za reprodukcijo zvoka; Aparati za reprodukcijo slik; Magnetni nosilci podatkov; Gramofonske plošče; Naložljiva digitalna glasba, nudena na internetu; Kompaktni diski [zgoščenke]; DVD-ji; Videokasete; Okvirji za očala; Sončna očala.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Ljudinspelningar; Videoinspelningar; Audiovisuella inspelningar; Datormjukvaror; Tidskrifter (elektroniska), nedladdningsbara; Ljudupptagningsapparater; Bildupptagningsapparater; Apparater för ljudöverföring; Bildöverföringsapparater; Ljudåtergivningsapparater; Bildreproduceringsapparater; Magnetiska datamedia; Skivor för ljudinspelningar; Digital musik nedladdningsbar från internet; Cd-skivor; Dvd-skivor; Videoband; Glasögonbågar; Solglasögon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Облекло; Украшения за глава, шапки; Обувки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Oděvy; Pokrývky hlavy; Obuv.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beklædningsgenstande; Hovedbeklædning; Fodtøj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bekleidungsstücke; Kopfbedeckungen; Schuhwaren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ενδύματα· Είδη πιλοποιίας· Υποδήματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Clothing; Headgear; Footwear.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Prendas de vestir; Artículos de sombrerería; Calzado.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rõivad; Peakatted; Jalatsid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatteet; Päähineet; Jalkineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vêtements; Chapellerie; Chaussures.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Odjeća; Pokrivala za glavu; Obuća.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ruházati cikkek; Kalapáruk; Lábbelik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Abbigliamento; Cappelleria; Calzature.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Drabužiai, apranga; Galvos apdangalai; Apavas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apģērbi; Galvassegas; Apavi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ilbies; Xedd ir-ras; Xedd is-saqajn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kleding; Hoofddeksels; Schoeisel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odzież; Nakrycia głowy; Obuwie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vestuário; Chapelaria; Calçado.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole de îmbrăcăminte; Articole pentru acoperirea capului; Articole de încălțăminte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Odevy; Pokrývky hlavy; Obuv.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oblačila; Pokrivala; Obutev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kläder; Huvudbonader; Fotbeklädnader.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Развлекателни услуги; Услуги за образование и обучение; Услуги за електронни игри; Услуги за записи; Производство на радио- и телевизионни програми; Продукция на кинематографични филми; Спортна и културна дейност; Предоставяне на онлайн музика, без възможност за сваляне; Предоставяне на видео онлайн, без възможност за сваляне.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zábava; Vzdělávací a školicí služby; Služby v oblasti elektronických her; Nahrávací služby; Výroba rozhlasových a televizních programů; Výroba kinematografických filmů; Sportovní a kulturní aktivity; Poskytování hudby online bez možnosti stažení; Poskytování videí online bez možnosti stažení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Underholdningsvirksomhed; Uddannelses- og undervisningsvirksomhed; Elektronisk spilvirksomhed; Udførelse af lydoptagelser; Produktion af radio- og fjernsynsprogrammer; Produktion af kinematografiske film; Sportsarrangementer og kulturelle arrangementer; Stillen online musik til rådighed, ikke-downloadable; Stillen online videoer til rådighed, ikke-downloadable.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Unterhaltungsdienstleistungen; Bildung, Erziehung und Unterricht; Durchführung elektronischer Spiele; Aufzeichnungsdienste; Produktion von Rundfunk- und Fernsehprogrammen; Produktion von Filmen; Kulturelle und sportliche Aktivitäten; Bereitstellung von nicht herunterladbarer Online-Musik; Bereitstellung von nicht herunterladbaren Online-Videos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες ψυχαγωγικού περιεχομένου· Υπηρεσίες εκπαίδευσης και διδασκαλίας· Υπηρεσίες ηλεκτρονικών παιχνιδιών· Υπηρεσίες εγγραφής· Παραγωγή ραδιοφωνικών και τηλεοπτικών προγραμμάτων· Παραγωγή ταινιών για τον κινηματογράφο· Αθλητικές και πολιτιστικές δραστηριότητες· Ψηφιακή μουσική (μη τηλεφορτώσιμη) διαθέσιμη στο Διαδίκτυο· Παροχή διαδικτυακών βίντεο, μη μεταφορτώσιμων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Entertainment services; Education and instruction services; Electronic games services; Recording services; Production of radio and television programmes; Production of cinematographic films; Sporting and cultural activities; Providing online music, not downloadable; Providing online videos, not downloadable.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de entretenimiento; Servicios de educación e instrucción; Servicios de juegos electrónicos; Servicios de grabación; Producción de programas de radio y televisión; Producción de películas de cinematografía; Actividades deportivas y culturales; Suministro en línea de música no descargable; Suministro en línea de vídeos no descargables.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meelelahutusteenused; Haridus- ja õpetusteenused; Elektroonilised mänguteenused; Salvestusteenused; Raadio- ja teleprogrammide lavastamine, produtseerimine; Kinofilmide tootmine; Spordi- ja kultuurialane tegevus; On-line-muusika (v.a allalaaditava) pakkumine; On-line-videote (v.a allalaaditavate) pakkumine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Huvipalvelut; Koulutus- ja opetuspalvelut; Elektronisiin peleihin liittyvät palvelut; Äänityspalvelut; Radio- ja televisio-ohjelmien tuotanto; Elokuvafilmien tuotanto; Urheilu- ja kulttuuritoiminnat; Digitaalisen musiikin [ei ladattavan] tarjoaminen Internetistä; Muiden kuin ladattavien online-videoiden tarjoaminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de divertissement; Services d’éducation et d’instruction; Services de jeux électroniques; Services d'enregistrement vidéo; Production d'émissions de radio et de télévision; Production de films cinématographiques; Activités sportives et culturelles; Mise à disposition en ligne de musique non téléchargeable; Mise à disposition en ligne de vidéos non téléchargeables.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Zabavne usluge; Usluge obrazovanja i podučavanja; Usluge elektroničkih igara; Usluge snimanja; Montaža radijskih i televizijskih programa; Produkcija kinematografskih filmova; Kulturne i sportske aktivnosti; Pružanje on-line glazbe, koja nije za preuzimanje; Pružanje on-line video snimaka, koji nisu za preuzimanje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szórakoztatási szolgáltatások; Oktatási és képzési szolgáltatások; Elektronikus játék szolgáltatások; Felvételkészítő szolgáltatások; Rádió- és televízióműsorok készítése; Mozifilmek gyártása; Sport- és kulturális tevékenységek; Digitális zene szolgáltatása az interneten [nem letölthető]; Online, nem letölthető videók biztosítása.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di divertimento; Servizi relativi a educazione e istruzione; Giochi elettronici; Servizi di registrazione; Montaggio di programmi radiofonici e televisivi; Produzione cinematografica; Attività sportive e culturali; Fornitura di musica online, non scaricabile; Fornitura di video online, non scaricabili.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Pramogų paslaugos; Švietimo ir instruktavimo paslaugos; Elektroninių žaidimų paslaugos; Įrašymo paslaugos; Radijo ir televizijos programų rengimas; Kino filmų kūrimas; Sportinė ir kultūrinė veikla; Tiesioginis muzikos pateikimas per kompiuterių tinklą (ne parsisiunčiamosios); Tiesioginis vaizdo įrašų pateikimas per kompiuterių tinklą (ne parsisiunčiamųjų).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Izklaides pakalpojumi; Izglītības un instruēšanas pakalpojumi; Elektronisko spēļu pakalpojumi; Ierakstīšanas pakalpojumi; Radio un televīzijas programmu veidošana; Kinofilmu sagatavošana; Sporta un kultūras pasākumi; Nelejupielādējamu digitālās mūzikas ierakstu nodrošināšana tiešsaistē; Nelejupielādējamu videomateriālu nodrošināšana tiešsaistē.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' divertiment; Servizzi ta' edukazzjoni u ta' tagħlim; Servizzi ta' logħob elettroniku; Servizzi ta' reġistrazzjoni; Il-produzzjoni ta' programmi għar-radju u t-televiżjoni; Il-produzzjoni ta' films ċinematografiċi; Attivitajiet kulturali u sportivi; Provvista ta' mużika diġitali (li ma tistax titniżżel) mill-internet; Forniment ta' vidjows online, li ma jitniżżlux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Amusementsdiensten; Diensten met betrekking tot opvoeding en opleiding; Elektronische speldiensten; Opnamediensten; Samenstelling van radio- en televisieprogramma's; Productie van cinematografische films; Sportieve en culturele activiteiten; Ter beschikking stellen van online niet-downloadbare muziek; Ter beschikking stellen van online niet-downloadbare video's.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi rozrywkowe; Usługi edukacyjne i instruktażowe; Usługi w zakresie gier elektronicznych; Usługi w zakresie nagrań; Produkcja programów radiowych i telewizyjnych; Realizacja filmów kinematograficznych; Zajęcia sportowe i kulturalne; Udostępnianie muzyki cyfrowej [nie do pobrania] w Internecie; Udostępnianie filmów online nie do pobrania.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de divertimento; Serviços de educação e formação; Serviços de jogos eletrónicos; Serviços de gravação; Produção de programas de rádio e televisão; Produção de filmes de cinema; Atividades desportivas e culturais; Disponibilização de música online, não descarregável; Disponibilização de vídeos online, não descarregáveis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de divertisment; Servicii educative și de instruire; Servicii in domeniul jocurilor electronice; Servicii de înregistrare; Producție de programe radiofonice și de televiziune; Producția de filme cinematografice; Activități sportive și culturale; Punerea la dispoziție de muzică digitală [fără posibilitatea de descărcare] pe internet; Furnizare de materiale video on-line, nedescărcabile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zábava; Výchovné a vzdelávacie služby; Služby v oblasti elektronických hier; Nahrávacie služby; Tvorba rozhlasových a televíznych programov; Tvorba kinematografických filmov; Športové a kultúrne činnosti; Online poskytovanie digitálnej hudby (bez možnosti kopírovania); Online poskytovanie videozáznamov (bez možnosti kopírovania).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Razvedrilne storitve; Storitve izobraževanja in poučevanja; Storitve elektronskih iger; Snemalne storitve; Produkcija televizijskih in radijskih programov; Produkcija kinematografskih filmov; Športne in kulturne dejavnosti; Nudenje digitalne glasbe [ki se je ne da naložiti] iz interneta; Nudenje spletnih videoposnetkov, ki se jih ne da naložiti preko računalniške mreže.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Underhållningstjänster; Utbildnings- och undervisningstjänster; elektroniska speltjänster; Inspelningstjänster; Produktion av radio- och televisionsprogram; Produktion av filmer för bio; Sport- och idrottsaktiviteter, kulturverksamhet; Upplåtande av musik online, inte nedladdningsbar; Upplåtande av filmer online, inte nedladdningsbara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<SeniorityDetails>
<Seniority>
<SeniorityCountryCode>GB</SeniorityCountryCode>
<SeniorityApplicationNumber>UK00002552228</SeniorityApplicationNumber>
<SeniorityFilingDate>2010-07-06</SeniorityFilingDate>
<SeniorityRegistrationNumber>UK00002552228</SeniorityRegistrationNumber>
<SeniorityRegistrationDate>2010-10-08</SeniorityRegistrationDate>
<InternationalTradeMarkCode>EU</InternationalTradeMarkCode>
<SeniorityPartialIndicator>false</SeniorityPartialIndicator>
<SeniorityStatusCode>Accepted</SeniorityStatusCode>
</Seniority>
</SeniorityDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/146</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080436</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>26169</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
