<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-02T10:33:00</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226498</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226498</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-19</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>buruberi</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">3D очила; Джойстици за компютри, различни от тези за видеоигри; Слушалки за поставяне в ушите; Хуманоидни роботи с изкуствен интелект; Слушалки; Кутии за високоговорители; Цифрови органайзери; Входящи устройства за компютри; Компютърни клавиатури; Компютърни мишки; Подложки за китки при работа с компютърни мишки; Портативни устройства за измерване на спортна активност; Слушалки; Периферни устройства, пригодени за използване с компютри; Лаптопи; Подложки за мишки; Смарт часовници; Видео записващи устройства за кола; USB адаптори; Стереоуредби за коли; Радиоприемници за превозни средства.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">3D brýle; Joysticky pro počítače, jiné než pro videohry; Sluchátka do uší; Humanoidní roboti vybavení umělou inteligencí; Sluchátka; Reproduktorové skříně; Digitální organizéry; Vstupní zařízení pro počítače; Počítačové klávesnice; Počítačové myši; Opěrky zápěstí pro uživatele počítačových myší; Monitorovací zařízení nošená na těle; Sluchátka; Periferní zařízení počítačů; Počítače; Podložky pod myš; Chytré hodinky; Videorekordéry do automobilů; USB adaptéry; Autorádia stereo; Autorádia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">3D briller; Joysticks til brug med computere, andre end til videospil; Øretelefoner; Humanoide robotter med kunstig intelligens; Hovedtelefoner; Højttalerkabinetter; Digitale kalendere; Anordninger til input til PCer; Tastaturer til computere; Computermus; Håndledsstøtter til brugere af computermus; Wearable aktivitetstrackere; Hovedtelefoner; Perifere enheder til computere; Computere; Musemåtter; Smartwatches; Videobåndoptagere til biler; USB-adaptere; Autostereoer; Radioer til befordringsmidler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">3D-Brillen; Joysticks für Computer, ausgenommen für Videospiele; In-Ear-Kopfhörer; Humanoide Roboter mit künstlicher Intelligenz; Kopfhörer; Lautsprecherboxen; Digitale Agenden; Computereingabegeräte; Computertastaturen; Computermaus; Handgelenkauflagen für Computermausbenutzer; Tragbare Activity Tracker; Kopfhörer; An Computer angepasste Peripheriegeräte; Laptops [Computer]; Mauspads [Mausmatten]; Smartwatches; Videorekorder für Autos; USB-Adapter; Autostereoanlagen; Radios für Fahrzeuge.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Γυαλιά 3D· Χειριστήρια τύπου μοχλού για ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές, εκτός αυτών για χρήση με βιντεοπαιχνίδια· Κεφαλόφωνα [ακουστικά] για τοποθέτηση εντός του αυτιού· Ανθρωποειδή ρομπότ με τεχνητή νοημοσύνη· Κάσκες ακουστικών· Κουτιά ηχείων· Ψηφιακοί οργανωτές· Διατάξεις εισόδου για ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Πληκτρολόγια ηλεκτρονικού υπολογιστή· Ποντίκια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Στηρίγματα καρπού για χρήστες ποντικιού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Φορετοί ανιχνευτές δραστηριότητας· Ακουστικά κεφαλής με μικρόφωνο· Περιφερειακός εξοπλισμός προσαρμοσμένος για χρήση σε ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Ηλεκτρονικοί υπολογιστές· Προστατευτικές βάσεις για ποντίκια (ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών)· Έξυπνα ρολόγια χειρός· Συσκευές εγγραφής βίντεο για αυτοκίνητα· Προσαρμογείς USB (ενιαίος σειριακός δίαυλος)· Στερεοφωνικά συστήματα αυτοκινήτων· Οχημάτων ραδιόφωνα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">3D spectacles; joysticks for use with computers, other than for video games; in-ear headphones; humanoid robots with artificial intelligence; headphones; cabinets for loudspeakers; digital organizers; input devices for computers; computer keyboards; computer mice; wrist rests for computer mouse users; wearable activity trackers; headsets; computer peripheral devices; computer apparatus; mouse pads; smartwatches; Car video recorders; USB adapters; Car stereos; Vehicle radios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Gafas 3D; Palancas de mando [joysticks] de ordenador, que no sean para videojuegos; Auriculares internos; Robots humanoides dotados de inteligencia artificial; Auriculares; Cajas de altavoces; Organizadores digitales; Dispositivos de entrada para ordenadores; Teclados de ordenador; Ratones de ordenador; Apoyamuñecas para usuarios de ratón de ordenador; Monitores de actividad física ponibles; Cascos con micrófono; Dispositivos periféricos utilizados con ordenadores; Ordenadores; Alfombrillas de ratón; Relojes inteligentes; Grabadoras de vídeo para coche; Adaptadores de USB; Equipos de música (estéreos) para coches; Aparatos de radio para vehículos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">3D-prillid; Arvutijuhtkangid, v.a videomängudele; Kõrvasisesed kuularid; Tehisintellektiga humanoidrobotid; Kõrvaklapid; Kõlarikastid; Digitaalsed kalendrid; Arvutite sisendseadmed; Arvutite klaviatuurid, klahvistikud; Arvutihiired; Randmetoed arvutihiire kasutajaile; Kantavad aktiivsusmonitorid; Mikrofoniga kõrvaklapid; Arvutite välisseadmed; Arvutid, raalid; Hiirematid; Nutikellad; Autovideosalvestid; USB-adapterid; Autostereod; Autoraadiod, sõidukiraadiod.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">3D-silmälasit; Tietokoneiden kanssa käytettävät ohjainsauvat muuta kuin videopelejä varten; Korvakuulokkeet; Tekoälyllä varustetut humanoidirobotit; Kuulokkeet; Kaiutinkotelot; Digitaaliset päivyrit; Tietokoneiden syöttölaitteet; Tietokoneen näppäimistöt; Tietokonehiiret; Rannetuet tietokonehiiren käyttäjille; Puettavat aktiivisuusmittarit; Kuulokkeet; Tietokoneiden oheislaitteet; Sylimikrot; Hiirimatot; Älykellot; Autojen videonauhurit; USB-sovittimet; Autostereot; Ajoneuvoradiot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Lunettes 3D; Leviers de commande à utiliser avec un ordinateur autres que pour jeux vidéo; Écouteurs intra-auriculaires; Robots humanoïdes dotés d'une intelligence artificielle; Casques à écouteurs; Boîtiers de haut-parleurs; Organiseurs numériques; Dispositifs d'entrée pour ordinateurs; Claviers d'ordinateur; Souris d'ordinateur; Repose-poignet pour utilisateurs de souris d'ordinateur; Capteurs d'activité à porter sur soi; Casques d'écoute; Périphériques adaptés pour utilisation avec des ordinateurs; Ordinateurs; Tapis de souris; Montres intelligentes; Magnétoscopes pour voitures; Adaptateurs USB; Autoradios; Appareils de radio pour véhicules.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">3D naočale; Džojstik za uporabu s računalima, osim za videoigre; In-ear slušalice; Humanoidni roboti s umjetnom inteligencijom; Slušalice; Kućišta razglasa; Digitalni rokovnici; Ulazni sklopovi za računala; Tipkovnice računala; Računalni miševi; Odmorišta za ručni zglob za korisnike računalnog miša; Uređaji za praćenje aktivnosti koji se nose; Slušalice; Periferni uređaji prilagođeni za uporabu s računalima; Računala; Podloge za miša; Pametni ručni satovi; Video kamere za automobile; USB adapteri; Automobilski radio uređaji; Radioaparati za automobile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Háromdimenziós szemüvegek; Botkormányok számítógépekhez, nem videojátékokhoz; Fülbe helyezhető fejhallgatók; Humanoid robotok mesterséges intelligenciával; Fejhallgatók; Hangszórószekrények, hangszóródobozok; Digitális szervező készülékek; Beviteli eszközök számítógépekhez; Számítógép billentyűzetek; Számítógépes egerek; Csuklótámaszok számítógépes egerek használatához; Viselhető aktivitásészlelők; Fejhallgatók; Számítógéphez kialakított perifériák; Számítógépek; Egérpadok; Okoskarórák; Autós videokamerák; USB adapterek; Sztereó autórádiók; Autórádiók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Occhiali per 3D; Barre di comando da utilizzare con computer, non per video-giochi; Auricolari interni; Robots umanoidi dotati di intelligenza artificiale; Cuffie per la musica; Casse acustiche; Agende digitali; Periferiche di input per computer; Tastiere del computer; Mouse per computer; Poggia-polsi per l'uso del mouse; Tracciatori di attività fisica indossabili; Periferiche concepite per essere utilizzate con i computer; Elaboratori elettronici; Tappetini per mouse; Orologi intelligenti [smartwatch]; Videoregistratori per automobili; Adattatori USB; Radio per veicoli; Cuffie per la musica; Radio per veicoli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">3D akiniai; Kompiuterių vairasvirtės (ne vaizdo žaidimams); Į ausis kišamosios ausinės; Dirbtinio intelekto humanoidiniai robotai; Radijo ausinės; Garsiakalbių korpusai; Skaitmeninės tvarkytuvės; Kompiuterių įvesties įrenginiai; Kompiuterių klaviatūros; Kompiuterių pelės; Kompiuterio pelės naudotojų riešų atramos; Dėvimieji fizinio aktyvumo įrašymo įrenginiai; Ausinės; Kompiuterių išoriniai įrenginiai; Kompiuteriai; Pelės padėkliukai; Išmanieji laikrodžiai; Automobiliniai vaizdo magnetofonai; USB adapteriai; Automobilinė stereoaparatūra; Transporto priemonių radijo imtuvai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Brilles attēlu uztverei trīsdimensiju (3D) formātā; Kursorsviras datoriem, izņemot videospēlēm paredzētās kursorsviras; Ausīs liekamas austiņas; Cilvēkveidīgie roboti ar mākslīgo intelektu; Austiņas; Skandu korpusi; Digitālie dienas plānotāji; Datoru ievadierīces; Datoru tastatūras; Datorpele; Plaukstas locītavu balsti datoru peļu lietotājiem; Valkājamas ierīces fiziskās aktivitātes izsekošanai; Radioaustiņas; Datoru perifērijas ierīces; Datori; Peļu (datoru perifērijas ierīču) paliktņi; Viedie rokaspulksteņi; Videoierakstītāji automašīnām; USB adapteri; Transportlīdzekļu audio sistēmas; Radiouztvērēji transportlīdzekļiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Nuċċalijiet 3D; Ġojstikks għall-użu ma' kompjuters, għajr għall-vidjowgejms; Kuffji ta' ġol-widna; Robots umanojdi b'intelliġenza artifiċjali; Kuffji; Kabinetti għall-amplifikaturi tal-ħoss; Organizzaturi diġitali; Tagħmir ta' input għal kompjuters; Tastieri tal-kompjuters; Maws tal-kompjuter; Tagħmir għas-serħan tal-polz għall-utenti tal-maws tal-kompjuters; Apparat li jirreġistra l-attività li jista' jinġarr; Kuffji; Periferali addattati għall-użu mal-kompjuters; Kompjuters; Mattijiet għall-maws; Arloġġi tal-idejn tat-tip smart; Reġistraturi tal-vidjos tal-karozzi; Adatturi ta' l-USB; Sterjos tal-karozzi; Radjijiet tal-vetturi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">3D-brillen; Joysticks voor gebruik met computers, anders dan voor videospellen; Oortjes; Hominoïde robots met kunstmatige intelligentie; Hoofdtelefoons; Luidsprekerkasten; Digitale organizers; Computerinvoerinstrumenten; Toetsenborden voor computers; Computermuis; Polssteunen voor muisgebruikers; Draagbare activiteitsmeters; Hoofdtelefoons; Computerrandapparatuur; Computers; Muismatten; Smartwatches; Videorecorders voor auto's; USB-adapters; Stereo-apparatuur voor auto's; Autoradio's.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Okulary 3D; Dżojstiki do użytku z komputerami, inne niż do gier wideo; Słuchawki dokanałowe; Roboty humanoidalne wyposażone w sztuczną inteligencję; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Obudowy głośników; Organizery cyfrowe; Urządzenia wejściowe do komputerów; Klawiatury komputerowe; Myszki komputerowe; Podpórki pod nadgarstki dla użytkowników myszy komputerowych; Przyrządy do śledzenia aktywności do noszenia na sobie; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Sprzęt peryferyjny do komputerów; Komputery; Podkładki pod myszy komputerowe; Zegarki inteligentne; Magnetowidy samochodowe; Adaptery USB; Samochodowe zestawy stereo; Radia samochodowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Óculos 3D; Joysticks para uso com computadores, sem ser para videojogos; Fones para ouvidos; Robôs humanóides com inteligência artificial; Auriculares; Caixas de altifalantes; Agendas digitais; Dispositivos de entrada para computadores; Teclados de computador; Ratos para computador; Apoios para os pulsos para utilizadores de ratos de computador; Dispositivos de uso corporal para registo de atividade física; Auriculares; Periféricos adaptados para uso com computadores; Computadores; Tapetes de rato; Relógios inteligentes; Gravadores de vídeo para automóveis; Adaptadores USB; Aparelhos de estéreo para veículos; Aparelhos de rádio para veículos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ochelari 3D; Joystick-uri pentru calculatoare, nu pentru jocuri video; Căști in-ear; Roboți umanoizi cu inteligență artificială; Căști audio; Cutii pentru difuzoare; Agende electronice; Dispozitive de intrare pentru calculatoare; Tastaturi de calculator; Mouse-uri pentru computer; Dispozitive de sprijin pentru încheietura mâinii folosite de utilizatorii de mouse-uri de calculator; Dispozitive portabile de urmărire a activității; Căști; Periferice adaptate pentru a fi folosite la calculatoare; Computere; Suporturi de mouse; Ceasuri inteligente; Aparate de înregistrare video pentru mașină; Adaptoare USB; Difuzoare stereo pentru automobile; Radio (Aparate de -) pentru vehicule.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">3D okuliare; Ovládače k počítačom (džojstiky), nie na počítačové hry; Slúchadlá do uší; Humanoidné roboty s umelou inteligenciou; Slúchadlá; Reproduktorové skrinky; Digitálne organizéry; Vstupné zariadenia pre počítače; Počítačové klávesnice; Počítačové myši; Opierky zápästia pre používateľov počítačových myší; Zariadenia na sledovanie fyzickej aktivity nosené na tele; Slúchadlá s mikrofónom; Periférne zariadenia počítačov; Počítače; Podložky pod myš; Inteligentné hodinky; Automobilové videorekordéry; USB adaptéry; Stereo autorádiá; Autorádiá.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">3D očala; Kontrolne ročice za uporabo z računalniki razen za video igre; Slušalke za v uho; Humanoidni roboti z umetno inteligenco; Slušalke; Ohišja zvočnikov; Digitalni organizatorji; Vhodne naprave za računalnike; Računalniške tipkovnice; Računalniške miške; Počivala za zapestje za uporabnike računalniških mišk; Nosljive naprave za spremljanje aktivnosti; Slušalke; Zunanje enote, prilagojene za uporabo z računalniki; Računalniki; Podloge za miško; Pametne zapestne ure; Videorekorderji za avtomobile; Adapterji USB; Avtomobilski radijski aparati; Radioaparati za vozila.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">3D-glasögon; Joysticks för användning med datorer, inte för videospel; In-ear hörlurar; Människoliknande robotar med artificiell intelligens; On-ear hörlurar; Högtalarlådor; Digitala anteckningsböcker; Inmatningsanordningar för datorer; Tangentbord för datorer; Datormusar; Handledsstöd för datormusanvändare; Bärbara aktivitetsband; Headsets; Kringutrustning anpassade för användning med datorer; Datorer; Musmattor; Smarta klockor; Videoinspelningapparater för bilar; USB-adaptrar; Stereo för bilar; Fordonsradior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>26</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Изкуствени коледни гирлянди; Изкуствени цветя от пластмаса; Изкуствена зеленина; Изкуствени плодове; Изкуствени цветя от текстил; Изкуствени цветя; Изкуствени гирлянди, венци; Коса за удължаване; Украшения за коса от рода на ленти за глава; Средства за усукване на коса [аксесоари за коса]; Украшения, орнаменти за коса; Дребни украшения [не бижутерия или не за ключове, халки или верижки]; Вълнени галони, ширити; Ресни, пискюли; Пера [аксесоари за дрехи]; Пасмантерия; Закопчалки за облекло; Украшения, гарнитури за дрехи; Златна бродерия; Копчета.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Umělé girlandy na vánoční stromky; Umělé květiny z plastu; Umělé listnaté rostliny; Umělé ovoce; Textilní umělé květiny; Umělé květiny; Umělé girlandy; Umělé vlasy; Vlasové ozdoby ve formě ozdob, které se vmotávají do vlasů; Twistery [vlasové doplňky na stočení vlasů]; Ozdoby do vlasů; Přívěsky [nikoli klenoty nebo přívěsky na klíče, prstýnky nebo řetízky]; Vlněné šňůrky; Třásně; Pera [oděvní doplňky]; Lemovací krajky; Uzávěry, spony na oděvy; Ozdobné lemy na oděvy; Zlaté výšivky; Knoflíky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kunstige juleguirlander; Kunstige blomster af plastic; Kunstig løv; Kunstige frugter; Stofblomster; Kunstige blomster; Kunstige blomsterkranse; Kunstigt hår; Hårpynt i form af hårsvøb; Hårtilbehør til at flette i hår; Pyntegenstande til håret; Charms [ikke smykker eller til nøgler, ringe eller kæder); Snore af uld; Frynser; Fjer, som tilbehør til beklædning; Possementmagerarbejder; Spænder til beklædningsgenstande; Borter til beklædning; Guldbroderier; Knapper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Künstliche Weihnachtsgirlanden; Unechte Blumen aus Kunststoff; Künstliche Blätter; Künstliche Früchte; Künstliche Blumen aus textilem Material; Künstliche Blumen; Künstliche Girlanden; Perücken [Haarteile]; Haarschmuck in Form von Hairwraps; Haaraccessoire zum Eindrehen der Haare; Haarschmuck; Anhänger, ausgenommen für Schmuck, Schlüsselringe oder Schlüsselanhänger; Wollschnüre; Fransen; Federn [Kleideraccessoires]; Posamenten [Besatzwaren]; Kleiderverschlüsse; Besatzwaren [Posamenten]; Goldstickereien; Knöpfe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Τεχνητές χριστουγεννιάτικες γιρλάντες· Τεχνητά άνθη από πλαστικό· Τεχνητές φυλλωσιές· Φρούτα τεχνητά· Τεχνητά άνθη από ύφασμα· Άνθη τεχνητά· Γιρλάντες τεχνητές· Περουκίνια· Στολίδια για τα μαλλιά με τη μορφή καλυμμάτων για τα μαλλιά· Διακοσμητικά και εξαρτήματα πλέξης ή συγκράτησης πλεξούδων [αξεσουάρ μαλλιών]· Διακοσμητικά είδη για τα μαλλιά· Φυλαχτά (γούρια) [όχι κοσμήματα ή για κλειδιά, δακτυλίδια ή αλυσίδες]· Κορδόνια από μαλλί· Κρόσσια· Φτερά [είδη ένδυσης]· Είδη ταινιοπλεκτικής· Πόρπες για ενδύματα· Τσαντόρ [καλύπτρες](ψιλικά)· Χρυσός (Κεντήματα με -)· Κουμπιά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Artificial Christmas garlands; artificial flowers of plastics; artificial foliage; artificial fruit; artificial flowers of textile; artificial flowers; artificial garlands; false hair; hair ornaments in the nature of hair wraps; hair twisters [hair accessories]; decorative articles for the hair; Charms [not jewellery or for keys, rings or chains]; woollen laces; fringes; feathers [clothing accessories]; lace trimmings; clasps for clothing; trimmings for clothing; gold embroidery; buttons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Guirnaldas de Navidad artificiales; Flores artificiales de plástico; Follaje artificial; Frutas artificiales; Flores artificiales de tela; Flores artificiales; Guirnaldas artificiales; Cabello postizo; Adornos para envolver mechas de cabello; Coleteros para el cabello [accesorios]; Artículos de adorno para el cabello; Dijes [no de joyería o para llaves, anillos o cadenas]; Cordones de lana; Flecos; Plumas [complementos de vestir]; Pasamanería; Broches para prendas de vestir; Orlas [pasamanería]; Bordados de hilos de oro; Botones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tehisjõuluvanikud; Plastist kunstlilled; Kunstlehestik; Kunstpuuviljad, tehispuuviljad; Tekstiilist tehislilled; Kunstlilled; Kunstvanikud; Valejuuksed; Juuksekaunistused juuksesidumisrättidena; Juuksepunumisvahendid [juuksetarvikud]; Juukseehted; Ripatsid, v.a juveeltooted või võtme-, rõnga- või ketiripatsid; Villased paelad; Narmad; Suled [rõivamanused]; Tressipaelad; Rõivakinnised; Rõivaposamendid; Kuldtikandid; Nööbid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Keinotekoiset jouluköynnökset; Muoviset tekokukat; Tekolehvästöt; Tekohedelmät; Kankaiset tekokukat; Tekokukat; Tekokukkaköynnökset; Tupeet; Hiuskoristeet punosten muodossa; Hiusspiraalit [hiustarvikkeet]; Hiuskoristeet; Riipukset [eivät koruja eivätkä avaimia, renkaita tai ketjuja varten]; Villanauhat; Hapsut [reunukset], vaatteisiin; Sulat (Linnun -) vaatetukseen; Pitsinauhat; Hakaset vaatteisiin; Koristeet vaatteisiin; Kultakoruompeleet; Napit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Guirlandes de Noël artificielles; Fleurs artificielles en matières plastiques; Feuillage artificiel; Fruits artificiels; Fleurs artificielles en matières textiles; Fleurs artificielles; Guirlandes artificielles; Cheveux postiches; Ornements capillaires servant à enrouler des mèches de cheveux; Attaches torsadées pour les cheveux; Articles décoratifs pour la chevelure; Breloques sauf joaillerie, porte-clés, anneaux ou chaînes; Cordons en laine; Franges; Plumes [accessoires d'habillement]; Passementerie; Fermoirs pour vêtements; Guimperie [passementerie]; Broderies en or; Boutons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Umjetne božićne girlande; Umjetno cvijeće od plastike; Umjetno lišće; Umjetno voće; Umjetno cvijeće od tekstila; Cvijeće, umjetno; Vijenci od umjetnog cvijeća [girlande]; Umjetna kosa; Ukrasi za kosu u obliku pramenova opletenih koncem; Uvijači [dodaci za kosu]; Ukrasni predmeti za kosu; Privjesci [ne nakit ili za ključeve, prstene ili lančiće]; Vunene vezice [gajtani]; Rese; Perje [odjevni pribor]; Čipka [pozamanterijska roba]; Kopče za odjeću; Pozamanterijski detalji za odjeću; Vez od zlatnih niti; Dugmad [puceta].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Karácsonyi mű girlandok; Művirágok műanyagból; Műlomb; Műgyümölcs; Textilből készült művirágok; Művirágok; Mesterséges girlandok; Hajhosszabbítások; Hajdíszek indián tincsek formájában; Hajcsavarók [hajtincs díszítő kiegészítők]; Hajdíszek; Amulettek [nem ékszerek vagy kulcsokhoz, gyűrűkhöz vagy láncokhoz]; Gyapjú csipke; Rojtok, bojtok; Tollak [ruházati kellékek]; Csipke paszományok; Ruhakapcsok; Díszszegők ruhához [paszományáru]; Aranyhímzés; Gombok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Ghirlande natalizie artifiiciali; Fiori artificiali di plastica; Fogliame artificiale; Frutta artificiale; Fiori artificiali in stoffa; Fiori artificiali; Ghirlande artificiali; Capelli posticci; Decorazioni per acconciature sotto forma di treccine colorate; Fermagli a spirale per capelli [accessori per capelli]; Articoli d'ornamento per la capigliatura; Amuleti [non gioielli o per chiavi, anelli o catene]; Cordoni di lana; Frange; Piume [accessori di abbigliamento]; Passamaneria; Fermagli per abbigliamento; Soggoli di monache [passamaneria]; Ricami in oro; Bottoni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Dirbtinės Kalėdų girliandos; Dirbtinės gėlės iš plastiko; Dirbtinė augalija; Dirbtiniai vaisiai; Tekstilinės dirbtinės gėlės; Dirbtinės gėlės; Dirbtinės girliandos; Netikri plaukai; Plaukų surišimo aksesuarai plaukams papuošti; Plaukų suktukai [plaukų aksesuarai]; Plaukų papuošalai; Karuliai (ne juvelyriniams dirbiniams, raktų žiedams ar raktų grandinėlėms); Vilnoniai raišteliai; Spurgai, kutai; Plunksnos [drabužiams puošti]; Galionai; Drabužių užsegimai; Drabužių apvadai [puošmenos]; Auksu siuvinėti gaminiai; Sagos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mākslīgas Ziemassvētku vītnes; Mākslīgie ziedi no plastmasas; Mākslīgās lapotnes; Mākslīgie augļi; Mākslīgie ziedi no auduma; Mākslīgie ziedi; Mākslīgo augu vītnes; Mākslīgie mati; Matu dekori matu gumiju veidā; Matu šķipsnas satinēji [matu rotas]; Dekoratīvas matu rotas; Amuletu piekariņi [kas nav juvelierizstrādājumi vai atslēgu piekariņi, gredzeni vai ķēdītes]; Vilnas mežģīnes; Bārkstis; Spalvas (apģērbu aksesuāri); Mežģīņu rotājumi; Aizdares apģērbiem; Apģērbu rotājumi; Zelta izšuvumi; Pogas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Girlandi tal-Milied artifiċjali; Fjuri artifiċjali tal-plastik; Weraq artifiċjali; Frott artifiċjali; Fjuri artifiċjali magħmula mit-tessut; Fjuri artifiċjali; Girlandi artifiċjali; Estensjonijiet tax-xagħar; Ornamenti tax-xagħar f'għamla ta' tgeżwir tax-xagħar; Twisters tax-xagħar [aċċessorji għax-xagħar]; Oġġetti dekorattivi għax-xagħar; Amuleti [mhux ġojjellerija jew għaċ-ċwievet, ħoloq jew ktajjen]; Lazzijiet tas-suf; Frenżi; Rix [aċċessorji tal-ilbies]; Dekorazzjonijiet tal-bizzilla; Klipps għall-ħwejjeġ; Orlaturi għall-ilbies; Rakkmu tad-deheb; Buttuni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kunstkerstslingers; Kunstbloemen van plastic; Kunstbladeren; Kunstfruit; Kunstbloemen van textiel; Kunstbloemen; Slingers van kunstbloemen; Vals haar; Haarversieringen om in het haar te wikkelen; Gedraaide haarklemmen; Versiersels voor het haar; Bedeltjes [geen juwelierswaren of niet voor sleutels, ringen of kettingen]; Wolkoorden; Franjes; Veren [kledingtoebehoren]; Passementwerk; Gespen voor kleding; Passementwerk voor sluiers; Goudborduursel; Knopen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Sztuczne girlandy bożonarodzeniowe; Sztuczne kwiaty z tworzyw sztucznych; Sztuczne listowie; Sztuczne owoce; Sztuczne kwiaty z tkanin; Kwiaty sztuczne; Girlandy sztuczne; Włosy do przedłużania; Ozdoby do włosów w postaci opasek do zawijania włosów; Sprężynki do włosów [akcesoria do włosów]; Dekoracyjne akcesoria do włosów; Zawieszki [nie biżuteria ani nie do kluczy, kółek lub łańcuszków]; Koronki wełniane; Frędzle; Pióra [dodatki do ubrań]; Koronkowe ozdoby; Zatrzaski do ubrań; Ozdoby do ubrań; Złote hafty; Guziki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Guirnaldas artificiais de Natal; Flores artificiais em plástico; Folhagem artificial; Fruta artificial; Flores artificiais em matérias têxteis; Flores artificiais; Grinaldas artificiais; Cabelo postiço; Enfeites capilares para enrolar cabelo; Roscas para o cabelo [acessórios para o cabelo]; Artigos decorativos para o cabelo; Berloques [sem ser de joalharia ou para chaves, argolas ou correntes]; Cordões de lã; Franjas; Plumas [acessórios de vestuário]; Passamanaria; Grampos para vestuário; Guarnições [passamanaria]; Bordados em ouro; Botões.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ghirlande artificiale de Crăciun; Flori artificiale din materiale plastice; Frunze artificiale; Fructe artificiale; Flori artificiale din materiale textile; Flori artificiale; Ghirlande artificiale; Meșe (de păr); Ornamente de păr sub formă de împletituri în păr; Ace de prins părul [accesorii pentru păr]; Articole decorative pentru păr; Brelocuri [nu ca bijuterii sau pentru chei, inele sau lanțuri]; Cordoane din lână; Franjuri; Pene [accesorii vestimentare]; Dantele; Copci pentru îmbrăcăminte; Ceaprazuri [pasmanterie]; Broderii în aur; Nasturi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Umelé vianočné girlandy; Umelé kvety z plastu; Umelé lístie; Umelé ovocie; Umelé kvety z textilu; Umelé kvety; Umelé girlandy; Umelé vlasy; Vlasové ozdoby v podobe bavlniek do vlasov; Vlasový twister [vlasové doplnky]; Ozdoby do vlasov; Prívesky [nie ako šperky, ani na kľúče, krúžky alebo retiazky]; Vlnené šnúrky; Strapce; Perie (odevné doplnky); Čipkársky tovar; Spony a pracky; Čipky, krajky; Zlaté výšivky (galantéria); Gombíky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Umetne božične girlande; Umetne rože iz plastike; Umetno listje; Umetno sadje; Umetne rože iz tkanine; Umetne rože; Umetne girlande; Lasni podaljški; Okraski za lase v obliki pletenih pramenov; Pripomoček za spletanje las [dodatki za lase]; Dekorativni izdelki za lase; Obeski [ne nakit ali za ključe, obročke in verižice]; Volnene vrvice; Resice; Peresa [dodatki za oblačila]; Čipkaste obrobe; Sponke za oblačila; Okrasne obrobe za oblačila; Zlate vezenine; Gumbi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Konstgjorda julgirlanger; Konstgjorda blommor av plast; Konstgjorda lövverk; Konstgjorda frukter; Konstgjorda blommor av tyg; Konstgjorda blommor; Konstgjorda girlanger; Löshår; Hårprydnader i form av håromslag; Hårsnoddar [håraccessoarer]; Dekorativa artiklar för håret; Berlocker [inte smycken eller avsedda för nycklar, ringar eller kedjor]; Ullsnoddar; Fransbårder; Fjädrar [beklädnadstillbehör]; Snörmakeriarbeten; Knäppen till kläder; Snörmakerier för kläder; Guldbroderier; Knappar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>85806</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003124476</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-06-19</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion
Unfair advantage /detriment to distinctiveness or repute</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>003930971</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2004-07-13</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>003930971</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2005-09-27</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>BURBERRY</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>014439814</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2015-08-03</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>014439814</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2015-10-14</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>BURBERRY</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>IT</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>2014902255077</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2014-04-22</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>0001591532</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2014-05-06</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Other</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>BURBERRY</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>IT</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>2014902255077</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2014-04-22</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>0001591532</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2014-05-06</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Other</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>BURBERRY</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>GB</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>UK00002225986</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2000-03-15</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>UK00002225986</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2000-08-25</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>BURBERRY</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>GB</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>UK00002225986</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2000-03-15</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>UK00002225986</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2000-08-25</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>BURBERRY</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>GB</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>UK00003106644</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2015-04-30</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>UK00003106644</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2018-04-20</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>BURBERRY</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>18441</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15475</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
