<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-05T16:31:37</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226128</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226128</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-01</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>feelbaby</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Аудиовизуални приемници; Безжични телефони; Софтуер за игри; Компютърен софтуер за системи за глобално позициониране [GPS]; Смартфони; Бебефони; Бебешки видеомонитори; Клетъчни телефони; Електронни нашийници за дресиране на животни; Измервателни уреди за бебета; Безжични телефони; Софтуер за игри.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Audio a video přijímače; Bezdrátové telefony; Software pro počítačové hry; Počítačový software pro globální polohovací systémy[GPS]; Chytré telefony (smartphony); Chůvičky; Video chůvičky; Buňkové telefony; Elektronické obojky pro výcvik zvířat; Váhy pro kojence; Bezdrátové telefony; Software pro počítačové hry.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Audio-video-modtagere; Trådløse telefoner; Software til spil; Computersoftware til globale positioneringssystemer [GPS]; Smartphones; Babyalarmer; Babyalarmer med video; Mobiltelefoner; Elektroniske halsbånd til træning af hunde; Vægte til spædbørn; Trådløse telefoner; Software til spil.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Ton- und Bildempfangsgeräte; Schnurlose Telefone; Spielsoftware; Computersoftware für globale Positionierungssysteme [GPS]; Smartphones; Babyüberwachungsgeräte; Video-Babyüberwachungsgeräte; Mobiltelefone; Elektronische Halsbänder für die Dressur von Tieren; Babywaagen; Radiotelefone; Spielsoftware.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Οπτικοακουστικοί δέκτες· Ασύρματα τηλέφωνα· Λογισµικό ηλεκτρονικών παιχνιδιών· Λογισμικό ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για παγκόσμια συστήματα προσδιορισμού θέσης [GPS]· Έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Μέσα παρακολούθησης βρεφών· Οθόνες παρακολούθησης βρεφών· Κινητά τηλέφωνα· Ηλεκτρονικά περιλαίμια για την εκπαίδευση ζώων· Ζυγαριές βρεφών· Ασύρματα τηλέφωνα· Λογισµικό ηλεκτρονικών παιχνιδιών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">audio- and video-receivers; cordless telephones; computer game software; computer software for global positioning systems (gps); smartphones; baby monitors; video baby monitors; mobile telephones; electronic collars to train animals; baby scales; Radiotelephones; Computer gaming software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Receptores [audio y vídeo]; Teléfonos inalámbricos; Software de juegos; Software informático para sistemas de localización por satélite; Teléfonos inteligentes [smartphones]; Dispositivos de audio y vídeo para la vigilancia de bebés; Monitores de vídeo para la vigilancia de bebés; Teléfonos celulares; Collares electrónicos para el adiestramiento de animales; Pesabebés; Radioteléfonos móviles; Software de juegos con apuestas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Heli ja kujutise vastuvõtjad; Juhtmeta telefonid; Mängude tarkvara; GPS-arvutitarkvara; Nutitelefonid; Beebimonitorid; Videosaatjaga beebimonitorid; Mobiiltelefonid; Elektroonilised kaelarihmad loomade treenimiseks; Imikukaalud; Juhtmeta telefonid; Arvutitarkvara hasartmängude mängimiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Äänen-/kuvanvastaanottimet; Langattomat puhelimet; Peliohjelmistot; Maailmanlaajuisten paikannusjärjestelmien tietokoneohjelmistot; Älypuhelimet; Vauvamonitorit; Videoivat vauvamonitorit; Matkapuhelimet; Elektroniset opetuskaulapannat eläimille; Vauvojen vaa'at; Langattomat puhelimet; Peliohjelmistot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Récepteurs [audio, vidéo]; Téléphones sans fil; Logiciels de jeux enregistrés; Logiciels informatiques pour systèmes de localisation mondiaux; Ordiphones [smartphones]; Dispositifs audio et vidéo pour la surveillance de bébés; Dispositifs vidéo pour la surveillance de bébés; Téléphones mobiles; Colliers électroniques pour le dressage d'animaux; Pèse-bébés; Téléphones sans fil; Logiciels de jeux enregistrés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Audiovizualni prijemnici; Bežični telefoni; Softver za igrice; Računalni softver za sustave za globalno pozicioniranje [GPS]; Pametni telefoni; Monitori za bebe; Video monitori za bebe; Mobiteli; Elektroničke ogrlice za dresuru životinja; Vage za bebe; Bežični telefoni; Softver za igrice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Audiovizuális vevőkészülékek; Vezeték nélküli telefonok; Játékszoftverek; Számítógépes szoftverek globális helymeghatározó rendszerekhez [GPS]; Okostelefonok; Bébiőrök; Kamerás bébiőrök; Mobiltelefonok; Elektronikus nyakörvek állatok idomításához; Csecsemőmérlegek; Vezeték nélküli telefonok; Játékszoftverek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Ricevitori [audio, video]; Telefoni senza fili; Software per giochi; Software per sistemi di posizionamento globale [GPS]; Smartphone; Dispositivi audio e video per la sorveglianza dei neonati; Dispositivi video per la sorveglianza dei neonati; Telefoni portatili; Collari elettronici per l'addestramento degli animali; Bilance elettriche pesa bebè; Telefoni senza fili; Software per giochi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Garso ir vaizdo imtuvai; Belaidžiai telefonai; Kompiuterinių žaidimų programinė įranga; Globalinių padėties nustatymo sistemų [GPS] kompiuterinė programinė įranga; Išmanieji telefonai; Prietaisai kūdikiams stebėti; Videoprietaisai kūdikiams stebėti; Mobilieji telefonai; Elektroniniai gyvūnų dresavimo antkakliai; Kūdikių svarstyklės; Radiotelefonai; Žaidimų programinė įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Audio un video signālu uztvērēji; Bezvadu tālruņi; Spēļu programmatūra; Globālās pozicionēšanas sistēmu [GPS] datoru programmatūra; Viedtālruņi; Elektroniskas ierīces zīdaiņu uzraudzībai; Videoierīces zīdaiņu uzraudzībai; Mobilie tālruņi; Elektroniskas kaklasiksnas dzīvnieku apmācībai; Zīdaiņu svari; Radiotelefoni; Datorspēļu programmatūra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Riċevituri awdjoviżivi; Telefons mingħajr fili; Softwer tal-logħbiet; Softwer tal-kompjuter għal Sistemi tal-Ippożizzjonar Globali [GPS]; Smartfowns; Moniters tat-trabi; Moniters tat-trabi bil-vidjow; Mowbajls; Kullari elettroniċi għat-taħriġ tal-annimali; Mwieżen tat-trabi; Telefons ċellulari; Softwer tal-logħbiet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Ontvangers [audio, video]; Mobiele telefoons; Spelsoftware; Computersoftware voor global positioning systems [GPS]; Smartphones; Babyfoons; Babyfoons met beeldscherm; Mobiele telefoons; Elektronische trainingshalsbanden voor dieren; Babyweegschalen; Mobiele telefoons; Spelsoftware.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odbiorniki audiowizualne; Telefony bezprzewodowe; Oprogramowanie gier; Oprogramowanie komputerowe do globalnych systemów pozycyjnych [GPS]; Smartfony; Urządzenia do monitorowania niemowląt; Urządzenia wideo do monitorowania niemowląt; Telefony komórkowe; Elektroniczne obroże treningowe dla zwierząt; Wagi dla niemowląt; Radiotelefony; Oprogramowanie gier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Recetores [áudio, vídeo]; Telefones sem fios; Software de jogos; Software para Sistemas de Posicionamento Global [GPS]; Smartphones; Dispositivos para vigilância de bebés; Dispositivos para videovigilância de bebés; Telefones celulares; Coleiras eletrónicas para treino de animais; Balanças para bebés; Telefones sem fios; Software de jogos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Receptoare audiovizuale; Telefoane fără fir; Software pentru jocuri; Software informatic pentru sisteme de poziționare globală [GPS]; Telefoane inteligente; Dispozitive de monitorizare a bebelușilor; Dispozitive video de monitorizare a bebelușilor; Telefoane mobile; Zgărzi electronice de dresaj pentru animale; Cântare pentru bebeluși; Telefoane fără fir; Software pentru jocuri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Audiovizuálne prijímače; Bezdrôtové telefóny; Počítačové hry (softvér); Počítačový softvér pre GPS systémy [GPS]; Smartfóny; Audiovizuálne prístroje na monitorovanie bábätiek; Videoprístroje na monitorovanie bábätiek; Mobilné telefóny; Elektronické obojky na výcvik zvierat; Detské váhy; Bezdrôtové telefóny; Programy na hry (softvér).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Avdiovizualni sprejemniki; Brezžični telefoni; Programska oprema za igrice; Računalniška programska oprema za sisteme globalnega pozicioniranja [GPS]; Pametni telefoni; Otroške varuške; Video otroške varuške; Mobilni telefoni; Elektronski ovratniki za urjenje živali; Tehtnice za dojenčke; Brezžični telefoni; Programska oprema za igrice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Audiovisuella mottagare; Sladdlösa telefoner; Programvara för spel; Programvara för globala positioneringssystem [GPS]; Smartphones; Övervakningsapparater för spädbarn; Videoövervakningsapparater för spädbarn; Mobiltelefoner; Elektroniska halsband för att träna djur; Babyvågar; Radiotelefoner; Spelprogramvara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Агенции за внос и износ; Консултации в областта на търговското ръководство и организация; Рекламиране и рекламни услуги; Насърчаване на продажбите [за трети лица]; Онлайн реклама в компютърна мрежа; Снабдяване за сметка на трети лица [закупуване на стоки или услуги за други предприятия]; Представяне на стоки с цел продажаба на дребно чрез всички средства за комуникация; Маркетингови услуги; Телемаркетингови услуги; Осигуряване на онлайн пазар за покупко-продажби на стоки и услуги.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zprostředkování dovozu a vývozu; Poradenství v oblasti řízení a organizace podniku; Propagace; Podpora prodeje jiných osob; Online inzerce v počítačové síti; Zásobovací služby pro jiné osoby [nákup zboží a služeb pro jiné podniky]; Prezentace výrobků v komunikačních médiích pro účely maloobchodu; Marketing; Telemarketing; Provozování online trhu pro kupující a prodejce výrobků a služeb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Import- og eksportagenturer; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsledelse og organisation; Reklamevirksomhed; Salgsfremmende foranstaltninger for andre; Online-annoncering på et computernetværk; Indkøbsbistand til andre ved køb af varer og tjenesteydelser; Præsentation af varer på kommunikationsmedier til detailhandelsmæssige formål; Marketing; Telemarketing; Tilvejebringelse af en onlinemarkedsplads til købere og sælgere af varer og tjenesteydelser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Dienstleistungen einer Im- und Exportagentur; Beratung bei der Organisation und Führung von Unternehmen; Werbung; Verkaufsförderung [Sales promotion] für Dritte; Online-Werbung in einem Computernetzwerk; Beschaffungsdienstleistungen für Dritte [Erwerb von Waren und Dienstleistungen für andere Unternehmen]; Präsentation von Waren in Kommunikations-Medien für den Einzelhandel; Marketing; Telemarketing; Bereitstellen eines Online-Marktplatzes für Käufer und Verkäufer von Waren und Dienstleistungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Πρακτορεία εισαγωγών-εξαγωγών· Επιχειρήσεων (Συμβουλές για οργάνωση και διεύθυνση -)· Διαφήμιση· Προώθηση πωλήσεων [για τρίτους]· Διαφήμιση on line σε δίκτυο πληροφορικής· Εφοδιασμού για τρίτους (υπηρεσίες -) [αγορά προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για άλλες επιχειρήσεις]· Παρουσίαση αγαθών σε μέσα επικοινωνίας με σκοπό τη λιανική πώληση· Υπηρεσίες μάρκετινγκ· Υπηρεσίες τηλεμπορίας (τηλεμάρκετινγκ)· Παροχή χώρων αγορών επί γραμμής για αγοραστές και πωλητές προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">import-export agency services; business management and organization consultancy; advertising; sales promotion for others; Online advertising on a computer network; procurement services for others [purchasing goods and services for other businesses]; presentation of goods on communication media, for retail purposes; marketing; telemarketing services; provision of an on-line marketplace for buyers and sellers of goods and services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de agencias de importación-exportación; Consultoría sobre organización y dirección de negocios; Publicidad; Promoción de ventas para terceros; Publicidad en línea por una red informática; Servicios de abastecimiento para terceros [compra de productos y servicios para otras empresas]; Presentación de productos en cualquier medio de comunicación para su venta minorista; Marketing; Servicios de telemarketing; Suministro de espacios de venta en línea para vendedores y compradores de productos y servicios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ekspordi- ja impordiagentuuride teenused; Äritegevuse juhtimise ja korraldamise konsultatsioonid; Reklaam; Müügikampaaniad, -reklaam teenusena; Arvutivõrgureklaam; Hanketeenused teistele ettevõtetele [kaupade ja teenuste ostmine]; Kaupade jaemüügi reklaam meediakanalites; Turundus; Telemarketingiteenused; Veebipõhise müügikeskkonna pakkumine kaupade ja teenuste ostjatele ning müüjatele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tuonti- ja vientiagentuuripalvelut; Liikkeenhoitoon ja organisaatioon liittyvä konsultointi; Mainonta; Myynninedistäminen [muille]; Online-mainonta tietoverkoissa; Hankintapalvelut muille [tavaroiden ja palveluiden osto muille yrityksille]; Tavaraesittely tiedotusvälineissä vähittäismyyntiä varten; Markkinointipalvelut; Puhelinmyyntipalvelut; Online-markkinapaikan tarjoaminen tavaroiden ja palvelujen ostajille ja myyjille.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d'agences d'import-export; Conseils en organisation et direction des affaires; Publicité; Promotion des ventes pour des tiers; Publicité en ligne sur un réseau informatique; Services d'approvisionnement pour des tiers [achat de produits et de services pour d'autres entreprises]; Présentation de produits sur tout moyen de communication pour la vente au détail; Marketing; Services de télémarketing; Mise à disposition d'espaces de vente en ligne pour acheteurs et vendeurs de produits et services.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Agencije za uvoz-izvoz; Savjeti o organizaciji i vođenju poslova; Oglašavanje; Promicanje prodaje za treće osobe; Online oglašavanje na računalnim mrežama; Nabava za treće osobe [usluge kupnje proizvoda i usluga za druga poduzeća]; Prezentacija robe putem komunikacijskih medija, u maloprodajne svrhe; Marketing; Usluge telemarketinga; Pružanje internetskog tržišnog prostora za kupce i prodavatelje proizvoda i usluga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Import-export ügynökségek; Üzletszervezési és üzletvezetési tanácsadás; Hirdetési- és reklámszolgáltatások; Értékesítési promóciós szolgáltatások; On-line hirdetői tevékenység számítógépes hálózaton; Beszerzői szolgáltatások [áruk illetve szolgáltatások beszerzése más cégeknek]; Áruk bemutatása kommunikációs médiában, kiskereskedelmi célokból; Marketing szolgáltatások; Telemarketing szolgáltatások; Online piactér biztosítása áruk és szolgáltatások eladói és vásárlói részére.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di agenzie per l'importazione e l'esportazione; Servizi di consulenza per l'organizzazione e la gestione degli affari; Pubblicità; Promozione delle vendite per i terzi; Pubblicità online su rete informatica; Servizi di approvvigionamento per conto terzi [acquisto di prodotti e di servizi per altre imprese]; Presentazione di prodotti con mezzi di comunicazione per la vendita al dettaglio; Marketing; Servizi di telemarketing; Fornitura di un mercato online per acquirenti e venditori di beni e servizi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Importo ir eksporto agentūrų paslaugos; Verslo vadybos ir organizavimo konsultacijos; Reklama; Prekių pardavimo skatinimas [kitiems]; Viešasis elektroninis reklamavimas kompiuterių tinkle; Tiekimo paslaugos kitiems [prekių ir paslaugų pirkimas kitiems verslams]; Prekių pateikimas žiniasklaidoje pardavimo reikmėms; Rinkodara; Telerinkodaros paslaugos; Interneto prekyviečių teikimas prekių ir paslaugų pardavėjams bei pirkėjams.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Importa-eksporta aģentūru pakalpojumi; Konsultāciju sniegšana darījumu vadīšanā un organizēšanā; Reklāma; Preču noieta veicināšana; Reklāma tiešsaistē ar datortīklu starpniecību; Uzņēmumu apgāde (preču un pakalpojumu sagāde trešo personu interesēs); Preču demonstrēšana komunikācijas līdzekļos mazumtirdzniecības nolūkiem; Mārketinga pakalpojumi; Telemārketinga pakalpojumi; Tiešsaistes tirgus nodrošināšana preču un pakalpojumu pārdevējiem un pircējiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-importazzjoni u esportazzjoni; Konsulenza dwar il-ġestjoni u l-organizzazzjoni ta' negozju; Reklamar; Il-promozzjoni tal-bejgħ għal oħrajn; Reklamar onlajn fuq netwerk tal-kompjuters; Servizzi ta' akkwist għal oħrajn [xiri ta' prodotti u servizzi għal negozji oħra]; Il-preżentazzjoni ta' oġġetti fuq mezzi tal-komunikazzjoni, għal skopijiet ta' bejgħ bl-imnut; Servizzi ta' kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Servizzi ta' telepromozzjoni; Forniment ta' suq onlajn għal xerrejja u bejjiegħa ta' prodotti u servizzi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diensten van import- en exportagentschappen; Bedrijfsorganisatorische en -bestuurlijke advisering; Publiciteit; Verkooppromotie [voor derden]; Online reclame op een computernetwerk; Aankoop voor andere bedrijven; Presentatie van goederen op communicatiemedia, voor verkoopdoeleinden; Marketing; Telemarketing; Ter beschikking stellen van online verkoopplaats voor kopers en verkopers van goederen en diensten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi agencji importowo-eksportowych; Doradztwo w zakresie organizowania i prowadzenia działalności gospodarczej; Reklama; Promocja sprzedaży dla osób trzecich; Reklama online za pośrednictwem sieci komputerowej; Usługi w zakresie nabywania dla osób trzecich [zakupy produktów i usług dla innych przedsiębiorstw]; Prezentowanie produktów w mediach dla celów sprzedaży detalicznej; Usługi marketingowe; Telemarketing; Zapewnianie platformy internetowej dla nabywców i sprzedawców towarów i usług.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de agências de importação-exportação; Consultadoria em organização e direção de negócios comerciais; Publicidade; Promoção de vendas [prestada a terceiros]; Publicidade online numa rede informática; Serviços de fornecimento para terceiros [compra de produtos e serviços para outras empresas]; Apresentação de produtos nos meios de comunicação, para fins de venda a retalho; Marketing; Serviços de telemarketing; Disponibilização de um espaço de mercado online para compradores e vendedores de produtos e serviços.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Agenții de import-export; Consultanță în managementul și organizarea afacerilor; Publicitate; Promovarea vânzărilor pentru terți; Publicitate on-line într-o rețea informatizată; Servicii de aprovizionare pentru terți [achiziții de bunuri și servicii pentru alte întreprinderi]; Prezentarea produselor prin toate mijloacele de comunicare pentru vânzarea cu amănuntul; Servicii de marketing; Servicii de telemarketing; Furnizarea unei piețe online pentru cumpărătorii și vânzătorii de bunuri și servicii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kancelárie zaoberajúce sa dovozom a vývozom; Poradenstvo pri organizovaní a riadení obchodnej činnosti; Reklama; Podpora predaja (pre tretie osoby); Online reklama na počítačovej komunikačnej sieti; Zásobovacie služby pre tretie osoby (nákup tovarov a služieb pre iné podniky); Prezentácia výrobkov v komunikačných médiách pre maloobchod; Marketing; Telemarketingové služby; Online poskytovanie obchodného priestoru pre nákupcov a predajcov tovarov a služieb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Uvozno - izvozne agencije; Poslovodno in organizacijsko svetovanje; Oglaševanje in oglaševalske storitve; Pospeševanje prodaje (za druge); Spletno oglaševanje preko računalniškega omrežja; Prokuratorske storitve [nabava blaga in storitev za druga podjetja]; Predstavitev blaga v komunikacijskih medijih (prodaja na drobno); Storitve trženja; Storitve telemarketinga; Zagotavljanje spletnega trga za kupce in prodajalce blaga in storitev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Import-exportagenturer; Konsultationer avseende företagsledning och -organisation; Reklam; Sales promotiontjänster; Annonsering online via datanätverk; Inköp av varor och tjänster för annans räkning; Presentation av varor på kommersiella media, för försäljningsändamål; Marketing; Telemarketingtjänster; Tillhandahållande av en marknadsplats online för köpare och säljare av varor och tjänster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/077</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-24</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/146</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080321</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>38810</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
