<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-19T10:29:41</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226147</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226147</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-15</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-19</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Bairi</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162308058</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226147/000162308058.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>26.99.06</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.99.24</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.07</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.25</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Светодиодни лампи за външно осветление; Електрическо фенерче; Тръби за флуоресцентни лампи; Светлини на автомобили; Лампи; Лампени стъкла; Осветителни уреди и инсталации; Фенерчета за четене на книги; Спот лампи; Таванно осветление; Противобактерийни лампи за пречистване на въздух; Ултравиолетови лампи, не за медицински цели; Настолни лампи; Крушки за осветление тип LED; Слънчеви лампи; Улични лампи; Лампиони; Фенери за глава; Фенери със свещи; Светлини за монтиране на стени; Прожектори за светлина.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">LED lampy na venkovní osvětlení; Vyhledávací světlomety; Fluorescenční zářivkové trubice; Světla pro automobily; Svítidla; Punčošky do lamp; Osvětlovací přístroje a zařízení; Čtecí lampičky k uchycení na knihu; Bodové reflektory; Stropní svítidla; Germicidní lampy na čištění vzduchu; UV lampy, ne pro léčebné účely; Stolní lampy; LED žárovky; Solární lampy; Pouliční lampy; Světelné řetězy pro slavnostní dekorace; Čelové svítilny; Svíčkové lucerny; Nástěnná světla; Světelné projektory.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">LED-lys til udendørs belysning; Lyskastere; Lysstofrør til belysning; Lygter til automobiler; Lamper; Lamperør; Belysningsapparater og installationer; Boglamper; Spotlamper; Loftsbelysning; Bakteriedræbende lamper til rensning af luft; Lamper til ultraviolet bestråling, ikke til medicinske formål; Bordlamper; LED-pærer til belysning; Sollamper; Gadelamper; Kulørte lamper til festdekoration; Pandelygter; Lyslanterner; Væglamper; Spotlamper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">LED-Landschaftsbeleuchtungen; Suchscheinwerfer; Fluoreszierende Leuchtstoffröhren; Leuchten für Kraftfahrzeuge; Beleuchtungslampen; Lampenglühstrümpfe; Beleuchtungsapparate und -anlagen; Buchleuchten; Strahler; Deckenlampen; Luftreinigungslampen mit keimtötender Wirkung; Ultraviolettlampen, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Tischlampen; LED-Glühlampen; Solarlampen; Stehlampen, Straßenlampen; Lichterketten für die Festtagsdekoration; Stirnlampen; Kerzenlaternen; Wandleuchten für Beleuchtungszwecke; Lichtprojektoren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Φώτα εξωτερικών χώρων με φωτοδιόδους· Προβολείς εντοπισμού· Σωλήνες φθορισμού· Οχημάτων φανάρια· Φωτισμός (λαμπτήρες -ού)· Πλαίσια, περιβλήματα και καλύμματα φωτισμού· Φωτισμός (μηχανισμοί και εγκαταστάσεις -ού)· Λάμπες χειρός για ανάγνωση· Σποτάκια· Οροφής φωτισμοί· Μικροβιοκτόνες (- λυχνίες) για το καθαρισμό του αέρα· Λαμπτήρες υπεριωδών ακτίνων για μη ιατρική χρήση· Επιτραπέζιες λάμπες· Λυχνίες λαμπτήρων LED· Ηλιακοί λαμπτήρες· Λάμπες για οδικό φωτισμό· Λαμπιόνια χρωματιστά διακοσμητικά για γιορτινές διακοσμήσεις· Φακοί για τοποθέτηση στο κεφάλι· Φανάρια για κεριά· Λαμπτήρες τοίχου· Προβολείς φωτισμού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">LED landscape lights; searchlights; Fluorescent tubes; automobile lights; lamps; lamp mantles; Lighting apparatus and installations; Book lights; Spotlights; ceiling lights; germicidal lamps for purifying air; ultraviolet ray lamps, not for medical purposes; Table lamps; LED light bulbs; Solar lights; street lamps; fairy lights for festive decoration; head torches; candle lanterns; Wall lamps; Light projectors.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Luces LED de paisajismo; Proyectores de luz; Tubos de lámparas fluorescentes; Luces para automóviles; Lámparas [aparatos de iluminación]; Manguitos de lámparas; Aparatos e instalaciones de alumbrado; Linternas de lectura; Focos de luz directa; Plafones [lámparas]; Lámparas germicidas para purificar el aire; Lámparas de rayos ultravioleta que no sean para uso médico; Lámparas de mesa; Bombillas de iluminación LED; Lámparas solares; Farolas; Guirnaldas de luces decorativas para fiestas; Linternas frontales; Faroles de vela; Lámparas de pared; Proyectores de luz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">LED-maastikuvalgustid; Taskulambid [valgustusseadmed], helgiheitjad, prožektorid; Luminofoortorud; Autolaternad; Lambid [valgustid]; Lambi-hõõgsukad; Valgustusaparaadid ja -seadised; Lugemislambid; Kohtvalgustid; Laevalgustid; Bakterihävituslambid, bakteritsiidlambid õhupuhastuseks; Ultraviolettlambid, v.a meditsiinilised; Laualambid; LED-lambipirnid; Päikeselambid; Tänavalaternad; Dekoreertuled, ehistuled, ilutuled pidulikuks kaunistamiseks; Pealambid; Küünlalaternad; Seinavalgustid; Valgusprožektorid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ledimaisemavalot; Soihdut valaistukseen; Loisteputket; Ajoneuvojen valaisimet; Lamput; Lampunkuoret; Valaistuslaitteet; Kirjavalaisimet; Kohdelamput; Kattovalaisimet; Itiöitä ja mikro-organismeja tuhoavat lamput ilmanpuhdistukseen; Ultraviolettisäteilylamput, ei-lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Pöytävalaisin; LED-valolamput; Aurinkovalot; Jalkalamput; Värilliset lamput koristeluun; Otsalamput; Kynttilälyhdyt; Seinälamput; Valoprojektorit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Lampes à LED pour espaces verts; Projecteurs d'éclairage; Tubes de lampes fluorescentes; Feux pour automobiles; Lampes d'éclairage; Manchons de lampes; Appareils et installations d'éclairage; Mini-lampes de lecture; Spots; Plafonniers; Lampes germicides pour la purification de l'air; Lampes à rayons ultraviolets autres qu'à usage médical; Lampes de table; Ampoules LED; Lampes solaires; Lampadaires; Guirlandes lumineuses pour décoration de fête; Lampes frontales; Lanternes à bougie; Appareils d'éclairage fixés au mur; Projecteurs de lumière.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">LED svjetla za krajolik; Džepne svjetiljke za rasvjetu; Fluorescentne cijevi; Svjetla za automobile; Rasvjetne svjetiljke; Cijevi [tuljci] za svjetiljke; Rasvjetni uređaji i instalacije; Svjetiljke za čitanje [koje se zakače za knjigu]; Svjetiljke za usmjerenu rasvjetu [spot svjetiljke]; Stropna svjetla; Svjetiljke za uništavanje klica radi pročišćavanja zraka; Ultraljubičaste lampe, nisu za medicinske potrebe; Stolne svjetiljke; LED žarulje za svjetiljke; Solarna lampe; Stajaće svjetiljke; Lampioni za svečane dekoracije; Čeone svjetiljke; Lanterne za svijeće; Zidna rasvjeta; Svjetlosni projektori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kerti, kültéri LED lámpák; Keresőlámpák, zseblámpák; Fénycsöves világítótestek; Lámpák járművekhez; Lámpák; Lámpaüvegek; Világító berendezések és készülékek; Könyvlámpák; Spotlámpák; Mennyezetvilágítások, mennyezeti lámpák; Csíraölő lámpák a levegő tisztításához; Ultraviola lámpák nem gyógyászati használatra; Asztali lámpák; LED-izzók; Napelemes lámpák; Beltéri állólámpák; Lámpák, égők ünnepi díszkivilágításhoz; Fejlámpák; Gyertyás lámpások; Fali világítás; Fényprojektorok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Luci a LED per uso paesaggistico; Proiettori; Tubi per lampade fluorescenti; Fanali per automobili; Lampade per illuminazione; Reticelle per lampade; Apparecchi ed impianti di illuminazione; Lampade da lettura; Riflettori; Plafoniere; Lampade germicide per la depurazione dell'aria; Lampade a raggi ultravioletti non per uso medico; Lampade da tavolo; Lampadine LED; Lampade ad energia solare; Lampade a stelo; Ghirlande luninose decorative per le feste; Torce da testa; Lanterne con candele; Lampade da parete; Lampade lenticolari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Šviesos diodų lauko lempos; Prožektoriai; Apšvietimo vamzdeliai; Automobilių žibintai; Lempos; Lempų dangčiai; Apšvietimo prietaisai ir įrenginiai; Knygų skaitymo šviesos; Prožektoriai; Lubų šviestuvai; Oro valymo baktericidinės lempos; Ultravioletinės lempos (ne medicinos reikmėms); Stalo šviestuvai; Šviesos diodų lemputės; Saulės energijos lempos; Gatvių šviestuvai; Šventinių lempučių girliandos; Žibintuvėliai dedami ant galvos; Žvakių žibintai; Sieniniai šviestuvai; Šviesos prožektoriai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Gaismas diožu lampas āra apgaismojumam; Kabatas baterijas; Luminiscences spuldzes; Transporta līdzekļu gaismas; Lampas; Lampu kupoli; Apgaismošanas ierīces un aparāti; Lampas grāmatu lasīšanai; Prožektori; Griestu lampas; Baktericīdas lampas gaisa attīrīšanai; Ultravioleto staru lampas nemedicīniskiem nolūkiem; Galda lampas; Gaismas diožu spuldzes (LED); Saules enerģijas gaismekļi; Stāvlampas; Lampiņu virtenes svētku dekorācijām; Galvas lukturīši; Sveču lukturi; Sienas gaismekļi; Prožektori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Dwal LED għall-pajsaġġi; Torċ għad-dawl; Tubi fluworexxenti; Dwal għall-vetturi; Lampi; Ċumniji tal-lampi; Apparat u sistemi tad-dawl; Dwal għall-kotba; Lampi li jarmu raġġ ta' dawl qawwi għax-xenarji [spotlights]; Dwal tas-soqfa; Lampi li jnaddfu l-arja u li joqtlu l-imnibbta; Lampi tar-raġġi ultravjola, mhux għal skopijiet mediċi; Lampi ta' fuq il-mejda; Bozoz tad-dawl tal-LED; Lampi solari; Lampi stàndard; Lampi żgħar tat-tiżjin għad-dekorazzjoni festivi; Torċi tar-ras; Lanterni tax-xemgħa; Dwal tal-ħajt; Projetturi tad-dawl.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Led-landschapsverlichting; Toortsen voor verlichting; Buizen voor fluorescerende lampen; Lichten voor automobielen; Lampen voor verlichting; Behuizingen voor lampen; Verlichtingsapparaten en -installaties; Leeslampjes; Schijnwerperlichten; Plafondlampen; Kiemdodende lampen voor het zuiveren van lucht; Ultravioletlampen, niet voor medisch gebruik; Tafellampen; LED-lichtpeertjes; Lampen op zonne-energie; Lantaarnpalen; Lichtstrengen voor decoratieve doeleinden; Hoofdlampen; Kaarslantaarns; Wandverlichting; Lichtprojectoren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Oświetlenie typu LED zewnętrzne [ogrody, krajobrazy]; Latarki; Lampy fluorescencyjne rurowe do oświetlania; Światła do pojazdów; Lampy oświetleniowe; Klosze do lamp [kominki]; Urządzenia i instalacje oświetleniowe; Lampki przyczepiane do książki; Reflektory punktowe; Oświetlenie sufitowe; Lampy bakteriobójcze do oczyszczania powietrza; Lampy ultrafioletowe, nie do celów medycznych; Lampy stołowe; Żarówki oświetleniowe LED; Lampy słoneczne; Lampy stojące; Kolorowe światełka do dekoracji świątecznych; Czołówki; Lampiony na świece; Oświetlenie ścienne; Rzutniki światła.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Luzes paisagísticas LED; Tochas [archotes] para a iluminação; Tubos de lâmpadas fluorescentes; Luzes para automóveis; Lâmpadas; Camisas de candeeiros; Aparelhos e instalações de iluminação; Luzes de leitura; Focos spot; Candeeiros de teto; Lâmpadas germicidas para a purificação do ar; Lâmpadas para raios ultravioletas não para uso medicinal; Candeeiros de mesa; Lâmpadas de iluminação LED; Unidades de lâmpadas solares; Lampadários; Fios de luzes para decorações festivas; Tochas [cabeça] para a iluminação; Lanternas de vela; Lâmpadas de murais; Projetores de luz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Lumini LED pentru iluminatul public; Lanterne pentru iluminat; Tuburi fluorescente; Aparate de iluminat pentru vehicule; Lămpi de iluminat; Sticle de lampă; Aparate şi instalaţii de iluminat; Lumini pentru citit; Reflectoare de scenă; Plafoniere; Lămpi germicide pentru purificarea aerului; Lămpi cu raze ultraviolete (care nu sunt de uz medical); Lămpi de masă; Becuri cu LED; Lămpi solare; Lampadare; Ghirlande luminoase pentru decoraţiuni festive; Lanterne pentru cap; Felinare cu lumânări; Aplice de perete; Proiectoare de lumină.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">LED svetlá používané na dekoráciu v exteriéri; Baterky (svietidlá); Žiarivkové trubicové svietidlá; Osvetľovacie zariadenia na dopravné prostriedky; Lampy; Objímky na svietidlá; Osvetľovacie prístroje a zariadenia; Lampičky na čítanie s možnosťou uchytenia na knihu; Bodové svetlá; Stropné svetlá; Lampy na čistenie vzduchu od baktérií (germicídne); UV-lampy nie na lekárske použitie; Stolové lampy; LED žiarovky; Solárne lampy; Pouličné lampy; Dekoračné svetelné reťaze; Čelové lampy; Lampáše na sviečky; Svetlá na priedeloch; Svetlomet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">LED svetilke za pokrajino; Žepne svetilke za razsvetljavo; Fluorescentne cevne žarnice; Naprave za osvetlitev za vozila; Svetilke; Okvir za luči; Naprave in napeljave za razsvetljavo; Luči za branje knjig; Žarometi; Stropne luči; Germicidne svetilke za prečiščevanje zraka; Svetilke u ultravijoličnimi žarki, ne za medicinske namene; Namizne svetilke; LED žarnice; Sončne svetilke; Stoječe svetilke; Lučke za praznično okrasitev; Naglavne svetilke; Laterne za svečo; Stenske svetilke; Projektorji svetlobe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">LED-lampor för utomhusbelysning; Handlyktor; Lysrör för lampor; Billyktor; Lampor; Lamphus; Belysningsapparater och -installationer; Boklampor; Spotlights; Innertaksbelysningar; Bakteriedödande lampor för luftrening; Lampor för ultraviolettstrålning, inte för medicinska ändamål; Bordslampor; LED-glödlampor; Sollampenheter; Golvlampor; Ljusslingor för dekoration; Pannlampor; Ljuslanternor; Lampor för väggprydnad; Ljusprojektorer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/085</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-07</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/156</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-18</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080364</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>22326</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018229982</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Change of name and professional address</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>22326</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-30</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
