<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-07T08:34:35</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226159</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226159</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-05</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-07</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>CREABEST</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Уреди за отчитане; Геодезични апарати и инструменти; Апарати за изследване, не за медицински цели; Термометри, с изключение на такива за медицински цели; Детектори с инфрачервени лъчи; Измервателни устройства, електрически; Защитни устройства за лично ползване за защита при злополуки; Противозаслепяващи козирки; Предпазни средства за глава; Дихателни маски [с изключение на такива за изкуствено дишане]; Респиратори за филтриране на въздух; Защитни очила; Предпазно облекло срещу злополуки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Měřící nástroje a zařízení; Geodetické přístroje a nástroje; Testovací přístroje, ne lékařské; Teploměry, ne lékařské; Infračervené detektory; Elektrické měřicí přístroje; Osobní ochranné prostředky k prevenci nehod; Stínítka (clony) proti oslnění; Ochranné přílby; Dýchací masky, ne pro umělé dýchání; Respirátory na filtraci vzduchu; Bezpečnostní brýle; Oděvy na ochranu před úrazy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Måleapparater; Geodætiske apparater og instrumenter; Testapparater, ikke til medicinske formål; Termometre [ikke til medicinsk brug]; Infrarøde detektorer; Måleapparater, elektriske; Beskyttelsesindretninger til personlig brug mod ulykker; Visirer til hjelme; Hovedbeskyttelse; Åndedrætsmasker, undtagen til kunstigt åndedræt; Respiratorer til filtrering af luft; Beskyttelsesbriller; Beklædning til beskyttelse mod ulykker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Messgeräte; Vermessungsapparate und -instrumente; Analysegeräte, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Thermometer, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Infrarotdetektoren; Elektrische Messgeräte; Unfallschutzvorrichtungen für den persönlichen Gebrauch; Helmvisiere; Kopfschutz; Atemmasken, ausgenommen für künstliche Beatmung; Atemschutzgeräte mit Luftfilter; Korbbrille; Unfallschutz-Bekleidungsstücke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μέτρηση (όργανα -ης)· Τοπογραφικές (- συσκευές και όργανα)· Ανάλυσης (Συσκευές -) για χρήση μη ιατρική· Θερμόμετρα όχι ιατρικά· Ανιχνευτές υπερύθρων· Μέτρηση (ηλεκτρικές συσκευές -ης)· Ατυχημάτων (Μηχανισμοί ατομικής προστασίας κατά των -)· Αντιθαμβωτικά γείσα· Προστατευτικά κεφαλής· Αναπνευστικές μάσκες, εκτός αυτών που προορίζονται για τεχνητή αναπνοή· Απορροφητήρες για το φιλτράρισμα του αέρα· Προστατευτικά γυαλιά· Ενδύματα για προστασία από ατυχήματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Measuring apparatus; surveying apparatus and instruments; testing apparatus not for medical purposes; thermometers, not for medical purposes; infrared detectors; measuring devices, electric; protection devices for personal use against accidents; visors for helmets; protective helmets; respiratory masks, other than for artificial respiration; respirators for filtering air; protective goggles; clothing for protection against accidents; safety goggles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de medición; Aparatos e instrumentos geodésicos; Aparatos de análisis que no sean para uso médico; Termómetros que no sean para uso médico; Detectores de infrarrojos; Aparatos eléctricos de medición; Dispositivos de protección personal contra accidentes; Viseras para cascos; Cascos de protección; Máscaras respiratorias que no sean para la respiración artificial; Respiradores para filtrar el aire; Gafas protectoras; Ropa de protección contra accidentes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Mõõteaparaadid, mõõteseadmed; Geodeesiaaparaadid ja -seadmed; Analüsaatorid, analüüsiseadmed, v.a meditsiinilised; Termomeetrid, v.a meditsiinilised; Infrapunadetektorid; Elektrilised mõõteseadmed; Individuaalkaitsevahendid; Kiivrite näoekraanid; Peakaitsmed; Respiraatormaskid, respiraatorid, v.a kunstliku hingamise seadmed; Respiraatorid õhu filtreerimiseks; Ohutusprillid; Õnnetuste eest kaitsvad kaitserõivad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mittalaitteet; Geodeettiset laitteet; Koestuslaitteet, ei-lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Lämpömittarit, ei-lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Infrapunailmaisimet; Mittalaitteet, sähkötoimiset; Suojalaitteet onnettomuuksien varalta, henkilökohtaiset; Kypärävisiirit; Päänsuojaimet; Hengityssuojaimet [paitsi tekohengitykseen]; Hengityssuojaimet ilman suodatukseen; Turvasuojalasit; Vaatteet tapaturmilta suojautumiseen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Mesureurs; Appareils et instruments géodésiques; Appareils pour l'analyse non à usage médical; Thermomètres, non à usage médical; Détecteurs à infrarouges; Appareils électriques de mesure; Dispositifs de protection personnelle contre les accidents; Visières pour casques; Casques de protection; Masques respiratoires autres que pour la respiration artificielle; Respirateurs pour le filtrage de l'air; Lunettes de protection; Vêtements de protection contre les accidents.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Mjerni instrumenti; Geodetski uređaji i instrumenti; Uređaji za testiranje [nisu za medicinske potrebe]; Toplomjeri nisu za medicinsku uporabu; Infracrveni detektori; Električne naprave za mjerenje; Nesreće na radu (uređaji za osobnu zaštitu na radu); Protuzasljepljujuća sjenila; Zaštitna oprema za glavu; Maske za disanje,osim za umjetno disanje; Respiratori za filtriranje zraka; Zaštitne naočale; Odjeća za zaštitu od nezgoda.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Mérőműszerek; Földmérő berendezések és eszközök; Tesztelő készülékek nem gyógyászati használatra; Hőmérők, nem gyógyászati használatra; Infravörös érzékelő berendezések; Mérőkészülékek, elektromos; Védőeszközök személyek balesetvédelmére; Vakításgátló ellenzők; Fejvédő eszközök; Légzőmaszkok nem mesterséges lélegeztetéshez; Légzőkészülékek légszűrésre; Védőszemüvegek; Ruházat balesetek megelőzésére.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Misuratori; Apparecchi e strumenti geodesici; Apparecchi per l'analisi non per uso medico; Termometri non per uso medico; Rilevatori a infrarossi; Apparecchi elettrici di misura; Dispositivi di protezione personale contro gli infortuni; Visiere per caschi; Protezioni per la testa; Maschere respiratorie non per la respirazione artificiale; Respiratori per il filtraggio dell'aria; Occhiali di protezione; Indumenti di protezione contro gli infortuni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Matavimo aparatai; Geodezijos aparatai ir prietaisai; Bandymų aparatai (išskyrus naudojamus medicinoje); Termometrai (išskyrus medicininius); Infraraudonųjų spindulių detektoriai; Elektriniai matavimo prietaisai; Asmeninės apsaugos priemonės nuo nelaimingų atsitikimų; Kepurių snapeliai nuo akinimo; Apsauginiai šalmai; Respiratorių kaukės [ne dirbtinio kvėpavimo]; Oro filtravimo respiratoriai; Apsauginiai akiniai; Apsauginiai drabužiai nuo nelaimingų atsitikimų.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mēraparatūra; Ģeodēzijas aparatūra un ierīces; Pārbaudes ierīces, izņemot medicīniskiem nolūkiem paredzētās ierīces; Termometri, ne medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Infrasarkanā starojuma detektori; Elektriskie mēraparāti; Ierīces individuālai aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem; Pretapžilbšanas sejsegi; Galvassegas galvas aizsardzībai; Respiratoru maskas, izņemot mākslīgajai elpināšanai paredzētās maskas; Respiratori gaisa filtrēšanai; Brilles acu aizsardzībai; Apģērbs aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Strumenti tal-kejl; Apparat u strumenti għal stħarriġ; Apparat tal-ittestjar mhux għal skopijiet mediċi; Termometri [mhux għal skopijiet mediċi]; Apparat li jidditektja l-infrared; Strumenti tal-kejl elettriċi; Tagħmir ta' protezzjoni għall-użu personali kontra l-inċidenti; Ilqugħ għad-dija; Protezzjoni tar-ras; Apparat tan-nifs, minbarra dak għal nifs artifiċjali; Respiraturi għat-tisfija tal-arja; Nuċċalijiet protettivi; Ħwejjeġ għall-protezzjoni minn inċidenti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Meetapparaten; Geodetische apparatuur en instrumenten; Analysetoestellen, niet voor medisch gebruik; Thermometers, niet voor medisch gebruik; Infrarooddetectie-apparatuur; Elektrische meetapparaten; Inrichtingen voor de bescherming van personen tegen ongevallen; Kleppen voor helmen; Beschermers voor het hoofd; Ademhalingsmaskers, anders dan voor beademing; Respiratoren voor het filtreren van lucht; Beschermende brillen; Kleding voor bescherming tegen ongevallen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przyrządy pomiarowe; Urządzenia i przyrządy geodezyjne; Urządzenia testujące, inne niż do celów medycznych; Termometry nie do celów medycznych; Urządzenia do detekcji podczerwieni; Elektryczne urządzenia pomiarowe; Urządzenia do ochrony osobistej przed wypadkami; Osłony przeciwodblaskowe; Osłony głowy; Maski do oddychania, inne niż do sztucznego oddychania; Respiratory do filtrowania powietrza; Okulary ochronne; Odzież chroniąca przed wypadkami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos de medição; Aparelhos e instrumentos geodésicos; Aparelhos para análise, sem ser para uso medicinal; Termómetros, não sendo para uso médico; Detetores de infravermelhos; Aparelhos elétricos de medida; Dispositivos de proteção pessoal contra os acidentes; Viseiras para capacetes; Proteções para a cabeça; Máscaras respiratórias, sem ser para a respiração artificial; Respiradores para filtragem do ar; Óculos de proteção; Vestuário de proteção contra acidentes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Instrumente de măsurare; Aparate și instrumente topografice; Aparate pentru analize, altele decât cele de uz medical; Termometre, altele decât cele de uz medical; Aparate de detectare cu raze infraroșii; Aparate electrice de măsurare; Dispozitive de protecție, de uz personal, împotriva accidentelor; Apărătoare împotriva orbirii; Protecția capului; Măști respiratorii, altele decât cele pentru respirație artificială; Măști protectoare pentru filtrarea aerului; Ochelari de protecție; Îmbrăcăminte de protecție împotriva accidentelor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Meracie prístroje; Geodetické prístroje a nástroje; Skúšobné prístroje (nie na lekárske použitie); Teplomery (nie na lekárske použitie); Detektory infračerveného žiarenia; Elektrické meracie zariadenia; Osobné ochranné prostriedky proti nehodám; Clony proti oslepeniu svetlom; Chrániče hlavy; Dýchacie masky (nie na umelé dýchanie); Respirátory na filtráciu vzduchu; Bezpečnostné okuliare; Odevy chrániace pred úrazmi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Merilni instrumenti; Geodetski aparati in instrumenti; Testni aparati, ne za medicinske namene; Termometri, ne za medicinske namene; Infrardeči detektorji; Električne merilne naprave; Zaščitne naprave proti poškodbam, za osebno uporabo; Ščitniki proti bleščanju; Proizvodi za zaščito glave; Dihalne maske, razen za umetno dihanje; Respiratorji za filtriranje zraka; Zaščitni naočniki; Oblačila za zaščito pred nezgodami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Mätapparater; Geodetiska apparater och instrument; Testapparater, inte för medicinska ändamål; Termometrar, inte för medicinska ändamål; Infraröda detektorer; Elektriska mätredskap; Skyddsanordningar mot olyckor för personligt bruk; Visir för hjälmar; Huvudskydd; Andningsmasker, inte för konstgjord andning; Respiratorer för luftfiltrering; Skyddsglasögon; Kläder för skydd mot olyckor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Апарати за масаж; Медицински апарати и инструменти; Термометри за медицински цели; Респираторни маски за изкуствено дишане; Терапевтични маски за лице; Ръкавици за медицински цели; Стерилни чаршафи [хирургия]; Облекло специално за операционни зали; Маски за дишане за медицинска употреба; Защитни съоръжения срещу рентгенови лъчи за медицински цели; Маски за медицински персонал; Санитарни маски за медицински цели; Дигитални термометри за медицински цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Masážní přístroje; Lékařské přístroje a nástroje; Teploměry pro lékařské účely; Respirační masky pro umělé dýchání; Terapeutické obličejové masky; Rukavice pro lékařské účely; Chirurgická sterilní prostěradla; Oděvy určené pro operační sály; Respirační masky k lékařskému použití; Ochranná zařízení proti rentgenovým paprskům pro lékařské účely; Roušky pro lékařský personál; Hygienické masky pro lékařské účely; Digitální teploměry k lékařským účelům.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Massageapparater; Medicinske apparater og instrumenter; Termometre til medicinsk brug; Respirationsmasker til kunstig respiration; Terapeutiske ansigtsmasker; Handsker til medicinske formål; Sterile lagner, kirurgiske; Beklædning specielt til operationsstuer; Åndedrætsværn til medicinske formål; Beskyttelsesindretninger mod røntgenstråler til medicinske formål; Masker til brug for medicinsk personel; Sanitære masker til medicinske formål; Digitale termometre til medicinske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Massagegeräte; Medizinische Apparate und Instrumente; Thermometer für medizinische Zwecke; Atemmasken für künstliche Beatmung; Therapeutische Gesichtsmasken; Handschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Sterile Tücher für Operationen; OP-Kleidung; Atemmasken für medizinische Zwecke; Schutzvorrichtungen gegen Röntgenstrahlen für medizinische Zwecke; Masken für medizinisches Personal; Mundschutz für medizinische Zwecke; Digitale Thermometer für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές μασαζ· Ιατρικά (Συσκευές και όργανα -)· Θερμόμετρα ιατρικά· Αναπνευστικές μάσκες για τεχνητή αναπνοή· Θεραπευτικές μάσκες προσώπου· Γάντια ιατρικής χρήσης· Αποστειρωμένα σεντόνια, χειρουργικά· Ενδύματα (Ειδικά για χειρουργεία -)· Αναπνευστικές μάσκες για ιατρικές χρήσεις· Διατάξεις προστασίας από τις ακτίνες Χ, για ιατρική χρήση· Μάσκες για το ιατρικό προσωπικό· Μάσκες υγιεινής για ιατρική χρήση· Ψηφιακά θερμόμετρα για ιατρική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Massage apparatus; medical apparatus and instruments; thermometers for medical purposes; respiratory masks for artificial respiration; therapeutic facial masks; gloves for medical purposes; sterile sheets, surgical; clothing especially for operating rooms; respiratory masks for medical purposes; protection devices against X-rays, for medical purposes; masks for use by medical personnel; sanitary masks for medical purposes; Digital thermometers for medical purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de masaje; Aparatos e instrumentos médicos; Termómetros para uso médico; Mascarillas respiratorias para la respiración artificial; Máscaras faciales terapéuticas; Guantes para uso médico; Campos quirúrgicos [sábanas estériles]; Ropa especial para quirófano; Mascarillas respiratorias para uso médico; Dispositivos de protección contra los rayos X para uso médico; Mascarillas para personal médico; Mascarillas sanitarias para uso médico; Termómetros digitales para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Massaažiaparaadid; Meditsiiniseadmed ja -riistad; Meditsiinilised termomeetrid; Kunstliku hingamise respiraatormaskid; Ravinäomaskid; Meditsiinilised kindad; Kirurgias kasutatavad steriilsed linad; Eririietus operatsioonisaalides viibimiseks, operatsiooniriietus; Meditsiinilised hingamismaskid; Röntgenikiirguse vastased meditsiinilised kaitsevahendid; Maskid meditsiinipersonalile; Meditsiinilised hügieenilised maskid; Digitaalsed termomeetrid (meditsiinilised).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hierontalaitteet; Lääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Kuumemittarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Hengitysnaamarit tekohengitykseen; Hoitavat kasvonaamiot; Käsineet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Steriloidut lakanat [kirurgiset]; Vaatteet leikkaussaleja varten, erikoisvalmisteiset; Hengitysnaamarit lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Röntgensäteilysuojavarusteet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Suojanaamarit lääkintähenkilökuntaa varten; Saniteettinaamarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Digitaaliset lämpömittarit lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils de massage; Appareils et instruments médicaux; Thermomètres à usage médical; Masques respiratoires pour la respiration artificielle; Masques thérapeutiques à porter sur le visage; Gants à usage médical; Champs opératoires [draps stériles]; Vêtements spéciaux pour salles d'opération; Masques respiratoires à usage médical; Dispositifs de protection contre les rayons X à usage médical; Masques utilisés par le personnel médical; Masques d'hygiène à usage médical; Thermomètres numériques à usage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Uređaji za masažu; Medicinski uređaji i instrumenti; Toplomjeri za medicinske potrebe; Respiracijske maske za umjetno disanje; Terapeutske maske za lice; Rukavice za medicinsku uporabu; Sterilne plahte, kirurške; Specijalna odjeća za operacijske dvorane; Maske za disanje za medicinske namjene; X zrake (uređaji za zaštitu od X zraka) za medicinske potrebe; Maske za medicinsko osoblje; Sanitarne maske za medicinske svrhe; Digitalni termometri za medicinske svrhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Masszázsberendezések; Gyógyászati készülékek és eszközök; Hőmérők gyógyászati célokra; Légzőmaszkok mesterséges lélegeztetéshez; Terápiás arcmaszkok; Kesztyűk gyógyászati használatra; Steril sebészeti lepedők; Speciális műtőruházat; Légzőmaszkok orvosi célokra; Röntgensugárzás elleni védőfelszerelések orvosi használatra; Maszkok egészségügyi személyzet általi használatra; Gyógyászati célú egészségügyi maszkok; Digitális hőmérők orvosi használatra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi per il massaggio; Apparecchi e strumenti medici; Termometri per uso medico; Maschere respiratorie per la respirazione artificiale; Maschere terapeutiche per il viso; Guanti per uso medico; Lenzuola sterili per uso nel campo operatorio; Vestiti speciali per sale operatorie; Maschere respiratorie per uso medico; Dispositivi di protezione contro i raggi X per uso medico; Maschere utilizzate dal personale medico; Maschere igieniche per uso medico; Termometri digitali per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Masažavimo aparatai; Medicinos aparatai ir instrumentai; Medicininiai termometrai; Respiratorių kaukės (dirbtinio kvėpavimo reikmėms); Terapinės veido kaukės; Pirštinės (medicinos reikmėms); Steriliosios paklodės [chirurgija]; Specialieji operaciniai drabužiai; Kvėpavimo kaukės medicinos reikmėms; Apsaugos nuo rentgeno spinduliuotės priemonės (medicinos reikmėms); Kaukės medicinos personalui; Higieninės kaukės (medicinos reikmėms); Skaitmeniniai termometrai medicinos reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Masāžas aparāti; Medicīniskā aparatūra un instrumenti; Medicīniskie termometri; Respiratoru maskas mākslīgajai elpināšanai; Ārstnieciskas sejas maskas; Cimdi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Sterili palagi ķirurģiskiem nolūkiem; Speciālie apģērbi operāciju zālēs; Elpošanas maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Medicīniskās ierīces aizsardzībai pret rentgena starojumu; Medicīnas personālam paredzētās maskas; Sanitārās maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Digitālie termometri medicīniskiem nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat għall-massaġġi; Apparat u strumenti mediċi; Termometri għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri respiratorji għan-nifs artifiċjali; Masks tal-wiċċ terapewtiċi; Ingwanti għal skopijiet mediċi; Lożor sterilizzati (kirurġiċi); Ilbies speċjali għas-swali tal-operazzjonijiet; Maskri respiratorji għal skopijiet mediċi; Tagħmir ta' protezzjoni kontra r-raġġi-X, għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri għal personal mediku; Maskri sanitarji għal skopijiet mediċi; Termometri diġitali għal skopijiet mediċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Massageapparaten; Medische apparaten en instrumenten; Thermometers voor medisch gebruik; Ademhalingsmaskers voor kunstmatige beademing; Therapeutische gezichtsmaskers; Handschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Operatielakens, steriel; Operatiekleding; Ademhalingsmaskers voor medische doeleinden; Inrichtingen ter bescherming tegen röntgenstralen, voor medisch gebruik; Maskers te gebruiken door medisch personeel; Hygiënische maskers voor medisch gebruik; Digitale thermometers voor medische doeleinden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia do masażu; Urządzenia i instrumenty medyczne; Termometry do celów medycznych; Maski do sztucznego oddychania; Maski terapeutyczne na twarz; Rękawice do celów medycznych; Prześcieradła sterylne chirurgiczne; Odzież specjalna używana w salach operacyjnych; Maski oddechowe do celów medycznych; Urządzenia zabezpieczające przed promieniami rentgenowskimi do celów medycznych; Maski stosowane przez personel medyczny; Maski sanitarne do celów medycznych; Termometry cyfrowe do celów medycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos de massagem; Aparelhos e instrumentos médicos; Termómetros para uso médico; Máscaras para respiração artificial; Máscaras faciais terapêuticas; Luvas para uso médico; Lençóis esterilizados para cirurgia; Vestuário especial para salas de operação; Máscaras respiratórias para uso médico; Dispositivos médicos de proteção contra raios-x; Máscaras para pessoal médico; Máscaras higiénicas para uso médico; Termómetros digitais para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate de masaj; Aparate și instrumente medicale; Termometre de uz medical; Măști respiratorii, altele decât cele pentru respirație artificială; Măști faciale terapeutice; Mănuși de uz medical; Câmpuri operatorii sterile, chirurgicale; Haine speciale pentru săli de operație; Măști respiratorii de uz medical; Dispozitive de protecție contra razelor X, pentru uz medical; Măști utilizate de personalul medical; Măşti sanitare de uz medical; Termometre digitale de uz medical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Masážne prístroje; Lekárske prístroje a nástroje; Lekárske teplomery; Dýchacie masky na umelé dýchanie; Terapeutické masky na tvár; Rukavice na lekárske použitie; Chirurgické, sterilné plachty; Odevy do operačných sál; Respiračné masky na lekárske účely; Ochranné zariadenia proti röntgenovému žiareniu na lekárske použitie; Rúška (pre nemocničný personál); Sanitárne masky na lekárske účely; Digitálne teplomery na lekárske účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Masažne naprave; Medicinski aparati in instrumenti; Termometri za medicinske namene; Dihalne maske za umetno dihanje; Terapevtske maske za obraz; Rokavice za medicinske namene; Kirurške sterilizirane rjuhe; Posebna oblačila za operacijske prostore; Dihalne maske za medicinske namene; Zaščitne naprave pred rentgenskimi žarki, za medicinske namene; Maske za medicinsko osebje; Higienske maske za medicinske namene; Digitalni termometri za medicinske namene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Massageapparater; Medicinska apparater och instrument; Termometrar för medicinska ändamål; Andningsmasker för konstgjord andning; Terapeutiska ansiktsmasker; Handskar för medicinska ändamål; Sterila lakan (kirurgiska); Kläder för användning i operationsrum; Andningsmasker för medicinska ändamål; Skyddsanordningar mot röntgenstrålar för medicinska ändamål; Munskydd för medicinsk personal; Sanitetsmasker för medicinska ändamål; Digitala termometrar för medicinska ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/079</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/148</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-06</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080376</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017950422</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-05-27</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
