<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-08T07:36:59</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226150</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226150</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-05</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-08</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>SANHEREN</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Налакътници [спортни артикули]; Наколенки [спортни артикули]; Ролери; Ролкови кънки; Играчки; Играчки маски; Ръкавици за водни ски; Снегоходки; Колани за щангисти; Украшения за коледни елхи; Спортни защитни подложки за лакти, за каране на кънки; Налакътници за спортна употреба; Играчки за домашни животни; Надуваеми играчки; Надуваеми игри за плувни басейни; Играчки палатки; Дронове [играчки]; Протектори за пищяли [спортни артикули]; Подплънки (Предпазни -) части от спортни облекла; Протектори за кръст за употреба в атлетиката.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Loketní chrániče [sportovní potřeby]; Kolení chrániče [sportovní potřeby]; Inline brusle; Kolečkové brusle; Hračky; Masky [na hraní]; Rukavice k vodním lyžím; Sněžnice; Vzpěračské pásy [sportovní výstroj]; Vánoční ozdoby; Sportovní chrániče loktů na bruslení; Chrániče zápěstí pro atlety; Hračky pro domácí mazlíčky; Nafukovací hračky; Nafukovací atrakce pro bazény; Stany na hraní; Drony [hračky]; Chrániče holení [sportovní potřeby]; Ochranné vycpávky [jako součást sportovní výstroje]; Bederní chrániče pro použití v atletice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Albuebeskyttere [sportsartikler]; Knæbeskyttere til atletik; In-line rulleskøjter; Rulleskøjter; Legetøj; Masker [lejetøj]; Handsker til vandski; Snesko; Nyrebælter [sportsartikler]; Juletræspynt; Albuebeskyttere til brug i forbindelse med skøjteløb; Håndledsbeskyttere til atletik; Legetøj til kæledyr; Oppusteligt legetøj; Oppustelige spil til svømmebassiner; Legetøjstelte; Droner [legetøj]; Skinnebensbeskyttere [sportsartikler]; Beskyttende polstringsmaterialer [sportsdragter]; Taljebeskyttere til sportsbrug.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Ellbogenschützer [Sportartikel]; Knieschützer [Sportartikel]; Rollschuhe, In-line Skates; Rollschuhe; Spielzeug; Masken [Spielzeug]; Wasserski-Handschuhe; Schneeschuhe; Gewichthebergürtel [Sportartikel]; Christbaumschmuck; Ellbogenschutzpolster für Rollschuh- und Schlittschuhläufer; Handgelenkschützer für Sportler; Spielzeug für Haustiere; Aufblasbares Spielzeug; Aufblasbare Spiele für Schwimmbecken; Spielzeugzelte; Drohnen [Spielwaren]; Schienbeinschutz [Sportartikel]; Schutzpolster [Sportausrüstungen]; Taillenschutz für Sportler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Προστατευτικά αγκώνων [αθλητικά είδη]· Επιγονατίδες για αθλητική χρήση· Πατίνια με ροδάκια γραμμής· Πατίνια με ροδάκια· Ατομικά παιχνίδια· Μάσκες παιχνιδιού· Γάντια για θαλάσσιο σκι· Παπούτσια για το χιόνι· Άρση βαρών (ζώνες για -) [αθλητικά είδη]· Διακοσμητικά χριστουγεννιάτικων δέντρων· Αθλητικές προστατευτικές αγκωνίδες για τροχοδρομία· Προστατευτικά καρπού για αθλητική χρήση· Παιχνίδια για κατοικίδια ζώα· Φουσκωτά παιχνίδια· Φουσκωτά παιχνίδια για πισίνες· Σκηνές για παιχνίδι· Τηλεκατευθυνόμενα αεροσκάφη [είδη παιχνιδιών]· Περικνήμια [αθλητικά είδη]· Προστασίας (παρεμβύσματα) [μέρη αθλητικών ένδυσης]· Προστατευτικά μέσης για αθλητική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Elbow guards [sports articles]; Knee guards [sports articles]; In-line roller skates; Roller skates; Toys; Toy masks; Water-skiing gloves; Snowshoes; weight lifting belts; Christmas tree decorations; Athletic protective elbow pads for skating; Wrist guards for athletic use; Toys for domestic pets; Inflatable toys; Inflatable games for swimming pools; Play tents; Drones [toys]; Shin guards [sports articles]; Protective paddings [parts of sports suits]; Waist protectors for athletic use.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Coderas [artículos de deporte]; Rodilleras [artículos de deporte]; Patines en línea; Patines de ruedas; Juguetes; Máscaras [juguetes]; Guantes de esquí acuático; Raquetas de nieve; Cinturones de halterofilia; Adornos para árboles de Navidad; Coderas protectoras de atletismo para patinar; Muñequeras para uso deportivo; Juguetes para animales de compañía; Juguetes hinchables; Artículos de juego inflables para piscinas; Tiendas de campaña de juguete; Drones [juguetes]; Espinilleras [artículos de deporte]; Protectores acolchados [partes de ropa de deporte]; Protectores de cadera para uso deportivo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Küünarnukikaitsmed [sporditarbed]; Põlvekaitsmed sportimisel kasutamiseks; Ühe rattareaga rulluisud; Rulluisud; Mänguasjad; Maskid (mänguasjad); Veesuusakindad; Räätsad; Tõstevööd [sporditarbed]; Jõulukuuseehted; Uisutajate küünarnukikaitsmed; Randmekaitsmed sportimiseks; Lemmikloomade mänguasjad; Täispuhutavad mänguasjad; Täispuhutavad mängud ujumisbasseinide jaoks; Mängutelgid; Mängudroonid; Säärekaitsmed [sporditarbed]; Kaitsepadjad [spordiriietuse osad]; Spordis kasutatavad vöökaitsmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kyynärsuojat [urheiluun]; Polvisuojukset [urheiluun]; In-line-rullaluistimet; Rullaluistimet; Lelut; Leikkinaamarit; Vesihiihdossa käytettävät käsineet; Lumikengät; Vyöt (painonnosto -) [urheiluun]; Joulukuusenkoristeet; Kyynärsuojukset luisteluun; Rannesuojukset urheilukäyttöön; Lelut lemmikkieläimille; Puhallettavat lelut; Puhallettavat pelit uima-altaisiin; Leikkiteltat; Radio-ohjattavat lentokoneet [lelut]; Säärisuojukset [urheiluun]; Suojapehmusteet [urheiluasujen osina]; Vyötärösuojukset urheilukäyttöön.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Protège-coudes [articles de sport]; Protège-genoux [articles de sport]; Patins à roulettes en ligne [rollers]; Patins à roulettes; Jouets; Masques [jouets]; Gants de ski nautique; Raquettes à neige; Ceintures d'haltérophilie [articles de sport]; Décorations pour sapins de Noël; Coudières de protection pour la pratique du patinage; Protections pour poignets pour l'athlétisme; Jouets pour animaux de compagnie; Jouets gonflables; Jeux gonflables pour piscine; Tentes [jouets]; Drones [jouets]; Protège-tibias [articles de sport]; Rembourrages de protection [parties d'habillement de sport]; Protections de poignets à des fins sportives.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Štitnici za laktove [sportski artikli]; Sportski štitnici za koljena; Koturaljke s kotačićima u nizu; Koturaljke; Igračke; Karnevalske maske; Rukavice za skijanje na vodi; Cipele za snijeg; Remenje za dizanje utega [sportski artikli]; Ukrasi za božićna drvca; Sportski zaštitni jastučići za laktove za klizanje ili koturanje; Štitnici za zglavke; Igračke za ljubimce; Igračke na napuhavanje; Igre na napuhavanje za bazene; Šatori za igru; Bespilotne letjelice [igračke]; Štitnici za cjevanice [sportski artikli]; Zaštitne ispune za sportsku odjeću [jastučići]; Sportski štitnici za struk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Könyökvédők [sportcikkek]; Térdvédők [sportcikkek]; Soros görkorcsolyák; Görkorcsolyák; Játékszerek; Játékálarcok; Vízisíkesztyűk; Hótalpak; Súlyemelő övek [sportcikkek]; Karácsonyfadíszek; Könyökvédők korcsolyázáshoz, görkorcsolyázáshoz; Csuklóvédők atlétikai használatra; Játékok kisállatoknak; Felfújható játékok; Felfújható játékok úszómedencékbe; Játéksátrak; Drónok [játékszerek]; Sípcsontvédők [sportcikkek]; Védőpárnázatok, védőtömések [sportruházat részei]; Derékvédők sportoláshoz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Paragomiti [articoli sportivi]; Paraginocchia [articoli sportivi]; Pattini a rotelle in linea; Pattini a rotelle; Giocattoli; Maschere [giocattoli]; Guanti per sci d'acqua; Racchette da neve; Cinture per sollevatore di pesi [articoli sportivi]; Decorazioni per alberi di Natale; Paragomiti per pattinaggio; Protezioni per i polsi per l'atletica; Giocattoli per animali domestici; Giocattoli gonfiabili; Giochi gonfiabili per piscine; Tende giocattolo; Droni [giocattoli]; Parastinchi [articoli per lo sport]; Imbottiture di protezione [parti dell'abbigliamento sportivo]; Tutori di protezione del girovita per uso atletico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Antalkūniai [sporto reikmenys]; Kelių apsaugos [sporto reikmenys]; Vienakrypčiai riedučiai; Riedučiai; Žaislai; Žaidimų kaukės; Vandens slidžių sporto pirštinės; Sniegpadžiai (neklimpti einant per sniegą); Sunkumų kilnojimo diržai [sporto reikmenys]; Kalėdų eglučių papuošalai; Sportinės minkštos čiuožėjų alkūnių apsaugos; Riešų apsaugos sporto reikmėms; Gyvūnų augintinių žaislai; Pripučiamieji žaislai; Pripučiamieji žaidimų reikmenys baseinams; Žaislinės palapinės; Bepiločiai orlaiviai [žaislai]; Blauzdų apsaugos [sporto reikmenys]; Apsauginės pagalvėlės [sportinių kostiumų dalys]; Juosmens apsaugai sporto reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elkoņu aizsargi [sporta preces]; Ceļu sargi lietošanai atlētikā; Skrituļslidas ar vienā līnijā izkārtotiem skrituļiem; Skrituļslidas; Rotaļlietas; Rotaļu maskas; Ūdensslēpošanas cimdi; Sniega kurpes; Svarcēlāju jostas [sporta piederumi]; Eglīšu rotājumi; Elkoņu aizsargi slidošanai; Plaukstu locītavu sargi izmantošanai sportā; Mājdzīvnieku rotaļlietas; Piepūšamās rotaļlietas; Piepūšamās spēles izmantošanai peldbaseinā; Spēļu teltis; Bezpilota lidmašīnas [rotaļlietas]; Sporta piederumi, proti, stilbsargi; Aizsargpolsteri [sporta apģērbu sastāvdaļa]; Vidukļa protektori izmantošanai atlētikā.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Protezzjoni għall-minkbejn [oġġetti sportivi]; Protezzjoni għall-irkoppa għall-użu atletiku; Pattini b'roti dritti waħda wara l-oħra; Pattini bir-roti; Ġugarelli; Maskri tal-logħob; Ingwanti għall-iskijar ta' fuq l-ilma; Żraben għas-silġ; Ċinturini għall-irfigħ tal-piżijiet [oġġetti sportivi]; Dekorazzjonijiet għas-siġar tal-Milied; Għata protettivi ikkuttunati atletiċi għall-minkeb għall-iskejzjar; Ilbies għall-protezzjoni tal-polz għall-użu atletiku; Ġugarelli għal annimali domestiċi; Ġugarelli li jintefħu; Logħob li jinkludi oġġetti li jintefħu għall-pixxini; Tined tal-logħob; Drones [ġugarelli]; Kuxxinetti għall-protezzjoni tal-qasba tas-sieq (oġġetti tal-isports); Kuttunar protettiv [partijiet minn ilbies sportiv]; Protetturi tal-qadd għall-użu atletiku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Elleboogbeschermers [sportartikelen]; Kniebeschermers [sportartikelen]; Skeelers; Rolschaatsen; Speelgoed; Maskers [speelgoed]; Handschoenen voor het waterskiën; Sneeuwschoenen; Gordels voor gewichtheffers; Versierselen voor kerstbomen; Elleboogbeschermers voor het schaatsen; Polsbeschermers voor gebruik bij atlethiek; Speelgoed voor huisdieren; Opblaasbaar speelgoed; Opblaasbare spellen voor zwembaden; Speelgoedtenten; Drones [speelgoed]; Scheenbeschermers [sportartikelen]; Beschermende vullingen [delen van sportkleding]; Taillebeschermers voor sportief gebruik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Ochraniacze na łokcie [artykuły sportowe]; Nakolanniki [artykuły sportowe]; Łyżworolki; Wrotki; Zabawki; Maski zabawkowe; Rękawice do jazdy na nartach wodnych; Rakiety śnieżne; Pasy do podnoszenia ciężarów [artykuły sportowe]; Ozdoby choinkowe; Sportowe nałokietniki do jazdy na łyżwach; Ochraniacze na nadgarstki do użytku sportowego; Zabawki dla zwierząt domowych; Zabawki dmuchane; Gry nadmuchiwane do basenów; Namioty zabawkowe; Drony (zabawki); Nagolenniki [artykuły sportowe]; Ochraniacze [części strojów sportowych]; Ochraniacze talii do użytku sportowego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cotoveleiras [artigos de desporto]; Joelheiras [artigos de desporto]; Patins em linha; Patins de rodas; Brinquedos; Máscaras [artigos de brincar]; Luvas para esqui aquático; Sapatos para a neve; Cintos para levantamento de pesos [artigos desportivos]; Decorações para árvores de Natal; Cotoveleiras protetoras para patinagem; Proteções de pulso para uso desportivo; Brinquedos para animais de estimação; Brinquedos insufláveis; Jogos insufláveis para uso em piscinas; Tendas para brincar; Drones [brinquedos]; Caneleiras [artigos desportivos]; Almofadas de proteção [partes de vestuário de desporto]; Protetores de cintura para atletismo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Apărători de cot [articole de sport]; Apărători de genunchi [articole de sport]; Patine cu role în linie; Patine cu rotile; Jucării; Măşti de carnaval; Mănuşi de schi nautic; Rachete de zăpadă; Centuri pentru halterofili [articole de sport]; Decoraţiuni (ornamente) pentru pomul de Crăciun; Accesorii de protecţie pentru coate pentru practicarea patinajului; Protecţii de încheieturi pentru atletism; Jucării pentru animale de companie; Jucării gonflabile; Jocuri gonflabile pentru piscine de înot; Corturi de joacă; Drone [jucării]; Apărători de tibie [articole de sport]; Căptuşeli de protecţie [piese vestimentare de sport]; Protectoare talie pentru atletism.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Chrániče na lakte (športové potreby); Chrániče na kolená (športový tovar); Kolieskové korčule (jednoradové); Kolieskové korčule; Hračky; Masky (hračky); Rukavice pre vodné lyžovanie; Snežnice; Opasky pre vzpieračov (športové potreby); Ozdoby na vianočný stromček; Športové chrániče lakťov pre korčuliarov; Atletické chrániče zápästia; Hračky pre zvieratá chované v domácnosti; Nafukovacie hračky; Nafukovacie hry do bazéna; Hračkárske stany; Dróny (hračky); Chrániče na píšťaly (športový tovar); Ochranné vypchávky (časti športových úborov); Športové chrániče pásu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Ščitniki za komolce [športni artikli]; Ščitniki za kolena [izdelki za šport]; Rolerji; Kotalke; Igrače; Maske (igrače); Rokavice za smučanje na vodi; Snežne krplje; Pasovi za dvigovanje uteži (izdelki za šport); Dekoracije za božična drevesa; Športni ščitniki za komolce za kotalkanje; Ščitniki za zapestje za atletiko; Igrače za hišne ljubljence; Napihljive igrače; Napihljiva igrala za plavalne bazene; Igralni šotori; Brezpilotni zrakoplovi [igrače]; Golenski ščitniki [izdelki za šport]; Zaščitne blazinice [del športne opreme]; Ščitniki za pas za uporabo v športu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Armbågsskydd [sportartiklar]; Knäskydd för idrott; In-line rullskridskor; Rullskridskor; Leksaker; Leksaksmasker; Handskar för vattenskidåkning; Snöskor; Bälte (tyngdlyftnings- -) [sportartiklar]; Prydnader för julgranen; Armbågsskydd för skridskoåkning; Handledsskydd för idrott; Leksaker för husdjur; Uppblåsbara leksaker; Uppblåsbara spel för pooler; Leksakstält; Drönare [leksaker]; Benskydd [sportartiklar]; Madrasseringar (skydds- -) [delar av idrottskläder]; Midjeskydd för idrottsutövning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/100</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/171</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-08</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080367</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>32203</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018058936</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Proprietor - Change of name and address</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>32203</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-22</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
