<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-05T16:31:33</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226740</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226740</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-31</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>YeSea</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>20</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Библиотеки; Чинове; Надуваеми възглавници за облягане; Надуваеми възглавници; Табуретки за крака; Офис кресла; Мебелировка за спални; Легла; Нощни шкафчета; Рамки за легла [дърво]; Етажерки за саксии [мебелировка]; Мебели, пригодени за употреба на открито; Надуваеми дюшеци за употреба при къмпингуване; Сгъваеми дивани; Възглавници; Мебели за бани; Шкафове за сервизи за чай; Масички за сервиране на чай; Рафтове за обувки; Офис бюра; Чинове; Табуретки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Knihovny; Psací stoly; Nafukovací polštářky na podložení krku; Nafukovací polštáře; Stoličky; Kancelářská křesla; Nábytek do ložnice; Postele; Noční stolky; Kostry postelí ze dřeva; Zahradní nábytek; Venkovní nábytek; Nafukovací matrace používané při kempování; Rozkládací gauče; Polštáře (na spaní); Koupelnový nábytek; Skříňky na čajové servisy; Čajové stolky; Přihrádky na boty; Kancelářské psací stoly; Psací stoly; Podnožky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Bogreoler; Skriveborde; Oppustelige nakkestøttepuder; Oppustelige puder; Taburetter; Kontorstole med armlæn; Soveværelsesmøbler; Senge; Natborde; Sengestel af træ; Havemøbler; Møbler til udendørsbrug; Luftmadrasser til campering; Udtrækssofaer; Hovedpuder; Badeværelsesmøbler; Skabe til teservice; Teborde; Skostativer; Kontorpulte; Skriveborde [chatoller]; Fodskamler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Büchergestelle; Schreibtische; Aufblasbare Nackenstützkissen; Luftgefüllte Kopfkissen; Hocker; Bürosessel; Schlafzimmermöbel; Betten [Möbel]; Beistellschränke; Bettgestelle aus Holz; Gartenmöbel; Möbel für den Außenbereich; Luftmatratzen für Campingzwecke; Schlafsofas; Kopfkissen; Badezimmermöbel; Schränke für Teeservices; Teetische; Schuhregale; Büroschreibtische; Schreibschränke; Schemel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Βιβλιοθηκών εταζέρες· Γραφεία· Φουσκωτά μαξιλάρια υποστήριξης λαιμού· Μαξιλάρια αέρα· Σκαμπό· Καρέκλες γραφείου· Έπιπλα κρεβατοκάμαρας· Κλίνες· Κομοδίνα· Κρεβάτια από ξύλο· Έπιπλα κήπου· Έπιπλα εξωτερικού χώρου· Στρώματα αέρος κατασκήνωσης· Καναπέδες που ανοίγουν· Μαξιλάρια ύπνου· Έπιπλα μπάνιου· Ερμάρια για σερβίτσια τσαγιού· Τραπέζια για τσάι· Παπουτσοθήκες· Γραφεία· Γραφεία· Σκαμπό.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Bookcases; desks; inflatable neck support cushions; inflatable pillows; stools; office seats; bedroom furniture; beds; nightstands; bedsteads of wood; garden furniture; outdoor furniture; air mattresses for use when camping; extendible sofas; pillows; bathroom furniture; cabinets for tea services; tea tables; shoe racks; office desks; Writing desks; Footstools.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bibliotecas [muebles]; Escritorios [muebles]; Cojines hinchables para apoyar el cuello; Almohadas hinchables; Taburetes; Sillones de oficina; Muebles de dormitorio; Camas; Armarios de cabecera; Armazones de cama de madera; Muebles de jardín; Muebles de exterior; Colchones de aire para su uso en acampadas; Sofás extensibles; Almohadas; Mobiliario de cuarto de baño; Armarios para servicios de té; Mesas de té; Estanterías [muebles] para calzado; Escritorios de oficina; Secreteres; Reposapiés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Raamaturiiulid; Kirjutuslauad, koolipingid; Täispuhutavad kaelatoed [padjad]; Täispuhutavad padjad; Taburetid; Kontoriistmed; Magamistoamööbel; Voodid; Öökapid; Puidust voodiraamid; Lillelauad, -kastid [mööbel]; Välimööbel; Matkamisel kasutatavad õhkmadratsid; Pikendatavad sohvad; Padjad; Vannitoamööbel; Teeserviisi kapid; Kohvilauad; Kingariiulid; Kirjutuslauad kontoritele; Kirjutuslauad; Jalapingid, järid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kirjahyllyt; Pulpetit; Ilmalla täytettävät niskatukityynyt; Ilmalla täytettävät tyynyt; Jakkarat; Toimistotuolit; Makuuhuoneiden huonekalut; Sängyt; Yöpöytälipastot; Puiset sängyt; Puutarhakalusteet; Ulkokalusteet; Ilmapatjat leirintäkäyttöön; Jatkettavat sohvat; Tyynyt; Kylpyhuonekalusteet; Kaapit teeastiastoille; Teepöydät; Kenkätelineet; Toimistotasot; Pulpetit; Jakkarat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bibliothèques [meubles]; Bureaux [meubles]; Coussins gonflables pour le support de la nuque; Oreillers gonflables; Tabourets; Fauteuils de bureau; Meubles de chambres à coucher; Lits; Tables de nuit; Bois de lit; Meubles de jardin; Meubles d'extérieur; Matelas pneumatiques pour le camping; Canapés convertibles; Oreillers; Mobilier de salle de bains; Armoires pour services à thé; Tables pour le thé; Meubles à chaussures; Tables à écrire de bureau; Secrétaires; Tabourets pour les pieds.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Police za knjige; Pisaći stolovi; Jastuci na napuhavanje za vrat; Jastuci na napuhavanje; Klupica za noge; Uredske stolice; Namještaj za spavaću sobu; Kreveti; Noćni ormarići; Drveni okviri za krevete; Vrtni namještaj; Namještaj prilagođen za vanjsku uporabu; Zračni madraci za uporabu kod kampiranja; Kauči na izvlačenje; Uzglavlja; Kupaonski namještaj; Vitrine za servise za čaj; Čajni stolići; Police za cipele; Uredski stolovi; Pisaći stolovi; Stolice bez naslona.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Könyvszekrények; Álló asztalok; Felfújható nyaktámasztó párnák; Felfújható párnák; Zsámolyok; Irodai székek; Hálószobabútor; Ágyak; Éjjeliszekrények; Fából készült ágyak; Kerti bútorok; Kültéri bútorok; Felfújható kempingmatracok; Kihúzható szófák, kanapék; Párnák, fejpárnák; Fürdőszobabútorok; Szekrények teáskészletekhez; Tea asztalok; Cipőtartók; Íróasztalok; Álló asztalok; Zsámolyok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Librerie [mobili]; Scrivanie [mobili]; Cuscini di sostegno per il collo gonfiabili; Guanciali gonfiabili; Sgabelli; Poltrone da ufficio; Mobili per camere da letto; Letti; Comodini con chiusura; Telaio del letto [legno]; Mobili da giardino; Mobili per esterni; Materassi ad aria per campeggio; Divani allungabili; Guanciali; Mobili per il bagno; Armadietti per servizi da tè; Tavoli da tè; Scarpiere; Scrivanie da ufficio; Scrivanie [mobili]; Sgabelli; Scrivanie da ufficio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Knygų lentynos; Rašomieji stalai; Pripučiamosios atraminės kaklo pagalvėlės; Pripučiamosios pagalvės; Taburetės; Biuro krėslai; Miegamojo baldai; Lovos; Užrakinamos lovų spintelės; Medinės lovos; Lauko baldai (statomi ant pievelės); Lauko baldai; Pripučiami čiužiniai, naudojami stovyklaujant; Sudedamosios sofos; Pagalvės; Vonios kambario baldai; Arbatos servizų spintelės; Arbatiniai staliukai; Batų lentynos; Biuro rašomieji stalai; Sekreterai (rašomieji stalai); Kojų suoleliai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Grāmatu skapji; Biroja galdi; Piepūšami spilveni kakla atbalstam; Piepūšamie spilveni; Taburetes; Biroja krēsli ar roku balstiem; Mēbeles guļamistabām; Gultas; Naktsskapīši; Gultu rāmji no koka; Puķu statīvi (mēbeles); Āra mēbeles; Piepūšamie matrači atpūtai pie dabas; Izvelkamie dīvāni; Spilveni; Vannasistabas mēbeles; Tējas servīzes skapīši; Tējas galdiņi; Kurpju plaukti; Biroja rakstāmgaldi; Rakstāmgaldi; Kājsoliņi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Xkafef għall-kotba; Skrivaniji; Kuxxini għas-serħan tal-għonq li jistgħu jintefħu; Imħaded li jintefħu bl-arja; Banketti; Pultruni tal-uffiċċju; Għamara tal-kmamar tas-sodda; Sodod; Armarji għal ma' ġenb is-sodda; Sodod tal-injam; Għamara tal-ġonna; Għamara ta' barra; Saqqijiet tal-arja għall-użu waqt il-kampeġġi; Sufani li jestendu; Mħaded; Għamara tal-kmamar tal-banju; Armarji għas-settijiet tat-te; Mwejjed tat-tè; Xtillieri għaż-żraben; Skrivaniji tal-uffiċju; Skrivaniji; Banketti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Boekenkasten; Bureaus [meubelen]; Opblaasbare kussens ter ondersteuning van de nek; Opblaasbare hoofdkussens; Zitkrukjes; Bureaustoelen; Slaapkamermeubilair; Bedden; Nachtkastjes; Bedframes van hout; Tuinmeubelen; Meubelen voor buiten; Luchtmatrassen voor het kamperen; Uitschuifbare sofa's; Hoofdkussens; Badkamermeubilair; Kasten voor theeserviezen; Theetafels; Schoenenrekken; Bureaus voor kantoren; Secrétaires; Zitkrukjes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Biblioteczki [regały na książki]; Pulpity do pracy w pozycji stojącej; Nadmuchiwane podgłówki; Poduszki nadmuchiwane; Taborety; Fotele biurowe; Meble sypialne; Łóżka; Szafki nocne; Łóżka drewniane; Meble ogrodowe; Meble przystosowane do użytku na zewnątrz; Materace dmuchane kempingowe; Sofy rozsuwane; Wezgłowia; Meble łazienkowe; Szafki na serwisy do herbaty; Stoliki do herbaty; Półki na buty; Biurka do celów biurowych; Pulpity do pracy w pozycji stojącej; Taborety.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Estantes para livros; Secretárias [mobiliário]; Almofadas insufláveis para apoio do pescoço; Almofadas insufláveis; Tamboretes; Cadeiras para escritório; Mobílias de quarto; Camas; Mesas de cabeceira; Armações de cama, em madeira; Mobiliário de jardim; Móveis de exterior; Colchões de ar para utilização em campismo; Sofás extensíveis; Almofadas; Mobiliário para casas de banho; Armários para serviços de chá; Mesas de chá; Prateleiras para calçado; Secretárias; Escrivaninhas; Bancos para apoio de pés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Biblioteci (Etajere pentru -); Birouri; Perne gonflabile pentru susținerea gâtului; Perne gonflabile; Taburete; Scaune de birou; Mobilier pentru dormitor; Paturi; Noptiere; Paturi din lemn; Mobilier de grădină; Mobilier de exterior; Saltele cu aer pentru camping; Canapele extensibile; Perne; Mobilier de baie; Dulapuri pentru servicii de ceai; Măsuțe de ceai; Etajere pentru încălțăminte; Mese de scris pentru birouri; Birouri; Taburete.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Knižnice (nábytok); Písacie stoly; Nafukovacie vankúšiky na opretie krku; Nafukovacie vankúše; Taburetky; Kancelárske kreslá; Spálňový nábytok; Postele; Nočné stolíky; Drevené kostry postelí; Záhradný nábytok; Exteriérový nábytok; Nafukovacie matrace používané pri kempovaní; Rozkladacie gauče; Vankúše; Nábytok do kúpeľne; Skrinky pre čajové servisy; Čajové stolíky; Stojany na topánky; Kancelárske písacie stoly; Písacie stoly; Taburety.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Knjižne omare; Pisalne mize; Napihljive oporne blazine za vrat; Napihljivi vzglavniki; Pručke; Pisarniški naslonjači; Pohištvo za spalnice; Postelje; Nočne omarice; Lesene postelje; Vrtno pohištvo; Pohištvo za uporabo na prostem; Zračne blazine za kampiranje; Raztegljivi kavči; Vzglavne blazine; Pohištvo za kopalnice; Omarice za čajne servise; Čajne mizice; Stojala za čevlje; Pisarniške pisalne mize; Pisalne mize; Stolčki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bokhyllor; Skolbänkar; Uppblåsbara nackstödsdynor; Uppblåsbara kuddar; Pallar; Kontorsfåtöljer; Sovrumsmöbler; Sängar; Nattduksbord; Sängstommar av trä; Trädgårdsmöbler; Utemöbler; Luftmadrasser för användning vid camping; Utdragssoffor; Kuddar; Möbler för badrum; Skåp för teserviser; Tebord; Skohyllor; Kontorsbord; Skrivbord; Fotpallar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/146</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>85806</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
