<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-21T08:40:59</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226185</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226185</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="1">Application published</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-21</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>INSTANCE</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Интелигентен контрол на осветление с регулируема светлина за употреба в груминг, стайлинг, грижа за кожата и лична грижа; Цифрови и електронни дисплеи с огледална функция и с вградено осветление, камери и датчици, които могат да получат достъп, да управляват и да покажат информация и друго цифрово съдържание от интернет на нещата; Електронни дисплеи с вградени функционалности на огледало, осветление и камера; Електронни екрани в вградени функционалности на огледало, осветление и камера с функционалност за мобилна свързаност; LED сензорни монитори; LED монитори с гласов контрол.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Chytré ovládání osvětlení s nastavitelným osvětlením pro použití při úpravě vzhledu, stylingu, péči o pleť a osobní péči; Digitální a elektronické displeje s funkcí zrcadla a s integrovaným osvětlením, kamerami a čidly, které mohou přistupovat k informacím a jinému digitálnímu obsahu z internetu věcí, spravovat je a zobrazovat; Elektronické displeje s integrovanou funkcí zrcadla, osvětlení a kamery; Elektronické displeje s integrovanou funkcí zrcadla, osvětlení a kamery s mobilní konektivitou; Dotykové LED monitory; Hlasem ovládané LED monitory.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Intelligent belysningsstyring med justerbar belysning til anvendelse inden for pleje, styling, hudpleje og personlig pleje; Digitale og elektroniske skærme med en spejlfunktion og med integreret belysning, kameraer og sensorer, der kan få adgang til, styre og vise information og andet digitalt indhold fra tingenes internet; Elektroniske skærme med integreret spejl, belysning og kamerafunktion; Elektroniske skærme med integreret spejl, belysning og kameraer med mobil opkobling; Berøringsfølsomme LED-skærme; Stemmestyrede LED-skærme.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Intelligente Beleuchtungssteuerung mit verstellbarem Licht zur Verwendung in den Bereichen Körperpflege, Styling, Hautpflege und persönliche Pflege; Digitale und elektronische Bildschirme mit Spiegelfunktion und mit integrierter Beleuchtung, Kameras und Sensoren, die Informationen und andere digitale Inhalte aus dem Internet der Dinge abrufen, verwalten und anzeigen können; Elektronische Bildschirme mit integriertem Spiegel, Beleuchtung und Kamerafunktion; Elektronische Bildschirme mit integriertem Spiegel, Beleuchtung und Kamera mit mobiler Konnektivitätsfunktion; LED-Touchscreen-Monitore; Sprachgesteuerte LED-Monitore.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Έξυπνα μέσα ελέγχου φωτισμού με ρυθμιζόμενο φωτισμό για χρήση σε καλλωπισμό, φορμάρισμα, περιποίηση του δέρματος, και ατομική φροντίδα· Ψηφιακές και ηλεκτρονικές οθόνες οπτικής παρουσίασης με λειτουργία καθρέπτη και με ενσωματωμένο φωτισμό, κάμερες και αισθητήρες με δυνατότητα πρόσβασης, διαχείρισης και οπτικής παρουσίασης πληροφοριών και λοιπού ψηφιακού περιεχομένου από το Διαδίκτυο των Πραγμάτων· Ηλεκτρονικές οθόνες οπτικής παρουσίασης με ενσωματωμένο καθρέπτη, φωτισμό και λειτουργία κάμερας· Ηλεκτρονικές οθόνες οπτικής παρουσίασης με ενσωματωμένο καθρέπτη, φωτισμό και κάμερα με λειτουργία κινητής συνδεσιμότητας· Οθόνες αφής με φωτοδιόδους· Οθόνες με φωνητικό έλεγχο με φωτοδιόδους.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Smart lighting control with adjustable lighting for use in grooming, styling, skin care, and personal care; digital and electronic display screens with a mirror function and with integrated lighting, cameras and sensors that can access, manage and display information and other digital content from internet of things; electronic display screens with integrated mirror, lighting, and camera functionality; electronic display screens with integrated mirror, lighting, and camera with mobile connectivity functionality; LED touchscreen monitors; LED voice-controlled monitors.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Control de iluminación inteligente con iluminación ajustable para su uso en el aseo, peinado, cuidado de la piel y cuidado personal; Pantallas digitales y electrónicas con una función de espejo y con iluminación, cámaras y sensores integrados que pueden acceder, gestionar y mostrar información y otro contenido digital de internet de las cosas; Pantallas electrónicas con funcionalidad de espejo, iluminación y cámara integradas; Pantallas electrónicas con espejo, iluminación y cámara integrados con funcionalidad de espejo, iluminación y cámara con conectividad móvil; Monitores de pantalla táctil LED; Monitores LED controlados por voz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Nutikas reguleeritav valgustite valgusjuhtimisseadmed karvkasvu hoolduseks, stiliseerimiseks, nahahoolduseks ja isiklikuks hoolduseks; Digitaalsed ja elektroonilised peegelfunktsiooniga kuvaekraanid koos integreeritud valgustuse, kaamerate ja anduritega, mis võimaldavad asjade internetis teabele ja muule digitaalsele sisule juurde pääseda, seda hallata ja kuvada; Elektroonilised kuvaekraanid koos integreeritud peegli, valgustuse ja kaamera funktsioonidega; Elektroonilised kuvaekraanid koos integreeritud peegli, valgustuse ja kaameraga, millel on mobiiliühenduse funktsioonid; LED-puutemonitorid; Hääljuhitavad LED-monitorid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Älyvalaistuksen hallintavälineet, joihin sisältyy mukautettava valaistus käytettäväksi huolittelussa, tyylittelyssä, ihonhoidossa ja henkilökohtaisessa hoidossa; Digitaaliset ja elektroniset näyttöruudut, joissa on peilitoiminto ja integroitu valaistus, kameroita ja antureita, jotka voivat käyttää, hallita ja näyttää tietoja ja muuta digitaalista sisältöä esineiden internetistä; Elektroniset näyttöruudut, joissa on integroitu peili-, valaistus- ja kameratoiminto; Elektroniset näyttöruudut, joissa on integroitu peili, valaistus ja kamera ja jotka on varustettu mobiiliyhteystoiminnolla; LED-kosketusnäyttömonitorit; Ääniohjatut LED-monitorit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Commandes d'éclairage intelligentes dotées d'un éclairage réglable destinées à la toilette, à la coiffure, aux soins de la peau et aux soins personnels; Écrans d'affichage numériques et électroniques dotés d'une fonction de miroir et dotés d'un éclairage, de caméras et de capteurs intégrés pouvant accéder à, gérer et afficher des informations et d'autres contenus numériques à partir de l'internet des objets; Écrans d'affichage électroniques dotés d'une fonctionnalité intégrée de miroir, d'éclairage et de caméra; Écrans d'affichage électroniques dotés d'un miroir, d'un éclairage et d'une caméra intégrés avec fonctionnalité de connectivité mobile; Moniteurs d'écran tactile LED; Moniteurs à commande vocale LED.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kontrole za pametnu rasvjetu s prilagodljivom rasvjetom za uporabu u dotjerivanju, oblikovanju, njezi kože i osobnoj njezi; Digitalni i elektronički zasloni s funkcijom ogledala i integriranom rasvjetom, kamerama i senzorima koji mogu pristupiti, upravljati i prikazivati informacije i drugi digitalni sadržaj s interneta stvari; Elektronički zasloni s integriranom funkcionalnošću ogledala, rasvjete i kamere; Elektronički zasloni s integriranom funkcionalnošću ogledala, rasvjete i kamere s mobilnom vezom; LED monitori sa zaslonima osjetljivim na dodir; LED monitori s glasovnim upravljanjem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Intelligens világításvezérlés állítható világítással szépítkezéshez, öltözködéshez, bőrápoláshoz és személyes ápoláshoz; Digitális és elektronikus kijelzők tükörfunkcióval, beépített világítással, kamerákkal és érzékelőkkel, amelyek hozzáférhetnek, kezelhetik és megjeleníthetik a tárgyak internetéről származó információkat és egyéb digitális tartalmakat; Elektronikus kijelzők beépített tükörrel, világítással és kamerafunkcióval; Elektronikus kijelzők beépített tükörrel, világítással és kamerával, mobil csatlakozási funkcióval; LED érintőképernyős monitorok; LED hangvezérelt monitorok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Controllo intelligente dell'illuminazione con illuminazione regolabile per l'uso in toelettatura, acconciature, cura della pelle e cura personale; Schermi digitali ed elettronici di visualizzazione con funzione di specchio e con illuminazione integrata, telecamere e sensori in grado di accedere, gestire e visualizzare informazioni e altri contenuti digitali dall'Internet delle cose; Schermi elettronici di visualizzazione con specchio integrato, illuminazione e funzionalità di telecamera; Schermi elettronici di visualizzazione con specchio integrato, illuminazione e telecamera con funzionalità di connettività mobile; Monitor a diodi per schermo tattile; Monitor a diodi a comando vocale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Išmanus apšvietimo valdymas su reguliuojamu apšvietimu, skirtas naudoti priežiūros, stiliaus, odos priežiūros ir asmeninės priežiūros reikmėms; Skaitmeniniai ir elektroniniai ekranai su veidrodžio funkcija ir su integruotu apšvietimu, fotoaparatai ir jutikliai, galintys pasiekti, valdyti ir rodyti informaciją ir kitą skaitmeninį turinį iš daiktų interneto; Elektroniniai ekranai su integruotu veidrodžiu, apšvietimu ir fotoaparato funkcijomis; Elektroniniai ekranai su integruotu veidrodžiu, apšvietimu ir fotoaparatu su mobiliojo ryšio funkcijomis; LED jutiklinio ekrano monitoriai; LED balsu valdomi monitoriai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vieda apgaismojuma vadība ar regulējamu apgaismojumu, kas paredzēta kopšanai, ieveidošanai, ādas kopšanai un personīgai kopšanai; Digitālie un elektroniskie displeji ar spoguļa funkciju un ar integrētu apgaismojumu, kamerām un sensoriem, kas var piekļūt, pārvaldīt un parādīt informāciju un citu digitālo saturu no lietu interneta; Elektroniski displeja ekrāni ar integrētu spoguli, apgaismojumu un kameras funkcionalitāti; Elektroniski displeja ekrāni ar integrētu spoguli, apgaismojumu un kameru ar mobilo savienojumu funkcionalitāti; LED skārienekrāna monitori; LED balss kontrolēti monitori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kontroll tat-tidwil intelliġenti b'tidwil aġġustabbli għall-użu fil-kura tal-isbuħija, l-istilizzar, il-kura tal-ġilda u l-kura personali; Skrins tad-displej diġitali u elettroniċi b'funzjoni ta' mera u b'tidwil, kameras u sensuri integrati li jistgħu jaċċessaw, jimmaniġġjaw u juru informazzjoni u kontenut diġitali ieħor mill-Internet tal-oġġetti; Skrins tad-displej elettroniċi b'mera, tidwil u funzjonalità tal-kamera integrati; Skrins tad-displej elettroniċi b'mera, tidwil u kamera integrati b'funzjonalità tal-konnettività mobbli; Moniters li jaħdmu bil-mess tal-LED; Moniters li jaħdmu bil-vuċi tal-LED.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Slimme lichtregeling met instelbare verlichting voor gebruik bij verzorging, styling, huidverzorging en persoonlijke verzorging; Digitale en elektronische weergaveschermen met een spiegelfunctie en met geïntegreerde verlichting, camera's en sensors voor toegang tot, beheer en weergave van informatie en ander digitaal materiaal vanaf het internet der dingen; Elektronische weergaveschermen met geïntegreerde spiegel, verlichting en camerafuncties; Elektronische weergaveschermen met geïntegreerde spiegel, verlichting en camera met functies voor mobiele connectiviteit; Led-monitors met aanraakscherm; Led-monitors met spraaksturing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Inteligentne urządzenia do sterowania oświetleniem z regulowanym oświetleniem do użytku w pielęgnacji, stylizacji, pielęgnacji skóry i pielęgnacji ciała; Cyfrowe i elektroniczne ekrany wyświetlające z funkcją lusterka i ze zintegrowanym oświetleniem, kamerami i czujnikami, które mogą uzyskiwać dostęp do informacji, zarządzać nimi i wyświetlać informacje i inne treści cyfrowe z internetu rzeczy (IoT); Elektroniczne ekrany wyświetlające ze zintegrowanym lusterkiem, oświetleniem i funkcją kamery; Elektroniczne ekrany wyświetlające ze zintegrowanym lusterkiem, oświetleniem i kamerą z funkcją łączności mobilnej; Monitory LED z ekranem dotykowym; Urządzenia LED sterowane głosowo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Controlos de iluminação inteligentes com iluminação ajustável para uso em cuidados de higiene e beleza, estilismo, cuidados da pele e cuidados pessoais; Ecrãs de visualização digitais e eletrónicos com uma função de espelho e com iluminação integrada, câmaras e sensores que permitem o acesso, a gestão e a visualização de informações e outros conteúdos digitais da Internet das Coisas (IoT); Ecrãs de visualização eletrónicos com funcionalidades integradas de espelho, iluminação e câmara; Ecrãs de visualização eletrónicos com funcionalidades integradas de espelho, iluminação e câmara com ligação móvel; Monitores LED de ecrã tátil; Monitores LED com controlo de voz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Unitate de control inteligentă pentru lumină cu iluminat reglabil destinată utilizării la aranjare, stil, îngrijirea pielii și îngrijirea personală; Ecrane de afișare digitale și electronice cu funcție de oglindă și cu lumină integrată, camere și senzori care pot accesa, administra și afișa informații și alt conținut digital din internetul obiectelor; Ecrane de afișare electronice cu oglindă, iluminat și funcție de cameră integrate; Ecrane de afișare electronice cu oglindă, iluminat și cameră integrate cu funcție de conexiune mobilă; Monitoare cu ecran tactil cu leduri; Monitoare cu leduri controlate vocal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Inteligentné ovládače osvetlenia s nastaviteľným osvetlením, určené na použitie pri starostlivosti o vzhľad, úprave štýlu, ošetrovaní pleti a osobnej starostlivosti; Digitálne a elektronické obrazovky s funkciou zrkadlenia a s integrovaným osvetlením, kamerami a senzormi, ktoré môžu pristupovať, spravovať a zobrazovať informácie a iný digitálny obsahu prostredníctvom internetu vecí; Elektronické obrazovky so zabudovaným zrkadlom, osvetlením a funkciami kamery; Elektronické obrazovky so zabudovaným zrkadlom, osvetlením a kamerou s funkciou mobilnej konektivity; LED monitory s dotykovou obrazovkou; LED monitory s hlasovým ovládaním.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pametno upravljanje razsvetljave z nastavljivo razsvetljavo za uporabo pri negi, oblikovanju, negi kože in osebni negi; Digitalni in elektronski prikazovalni zasloni s funkcijo ogledala ter vgrajeno razsvetljavo, kamerami in senzorji, ki lahko dostopajo do, upravljajo ter prikazujejo informacije in drugo digitalno vsebino z interneta stvari; Elektronski prikazovalni zasloni s funkcionalnostjo vgrajenega ogledala, razsvetljave in kamere; Elektronski prikazovalni zasloni z vgrajenim ogledalom, razsvetljavo in kamero s funkcionalnostjo mobilne povezljivosti; LED-monitorji na dotik; LED-glasovno upravljani monitorji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Smart belysningsreglering med justerbar belysning för användning i personvård, frisering, hudvård, och personlig vård; Digitala och elektroniska display-skärmar med en spegelfunktion och med inbyggd belysning, kameror och sensorer som kan komma åt, hantera och visa information och annat digitalt innehåll från sakernas internet; Elektroniska display-skärmar med inbyggd spegel, belysning, och kamerafunktion; Elektroniska display-skärmar med inbyggd spegel, belysning, och kamera med mobiluppkopplingsfunktion; LED-pekskärmsmonitorer; Röststyrda LED-monitorer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Електрически осветителни тела; Светлини; Куполно осветление; Куполни осветления за мебели; Електрически лампи; Осветителни апарати; Интелигентно осветление.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Chytrá svítidla; Světla; Stropní světla; Kopulovité osvětlení na nábytek; Elektrické světelné zdroje (žárovky, zářivky); Přístroje na osvětlení; Chytré osvětlení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Intelligente belysningsarmaturer; Lys; Ovenlys; Ovenlys til møbler; Lamper, elektriske; Belysningsapparater; Intelligent belysning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Intelligente Beleuchtungsgeräte; Leuchten; Deckenlampen; Einbaulampen für Möbel; Elektrische Lampen; Beleuchtungsgeräte; Intelligente Beleuchtung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Έξυπνα σταθερά εξαρτήματα φωτισμού· Φώτα· Φώτα οροφής· Φώτα οροφής για έπιπλα· Ηλεκτρικές λυχνίες· Μονάδες φωτισμού· Έξυπνος φωτισμός.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Smart lighting fixtures; lights; dome lights; dome lights for furniture; electric lighting; lighting fixtures; smart lighting.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Apliques de alumbrado inteligentes; Luces; Luces de cúpula; Luces para muebles; Lámparas eléctricas; Aparatos de iluminación; Iluminación inteligente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Nutivalgustid; Tuled; Sisevalgustid; Mööbli kuppelvalgustid; Elektrilambid; Valgustusaparaadid; Nutivalgustid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Älyvalaistuslaitteet; Valot; Kupuvalot; Kattovalot sisustukseen; Sähkölamput; Valaisinlaitteet; Älyvalaisimet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils d'éclairage intelligents; Lumières; Lampes de plafond; Lampes de plafond pour meubles; Lampes électriques; Appareils d'éclairage; Éclairage intelligent.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pametna oprema za rasvjetu; Svjetla; Rasvjeta za kupole; Kupolasta rasvjeta za namještaj; Električne svjetiljke; Rasvjetni uređaji; Pametna rasvjeta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Okos világítótestek; Lámpák; Tetővilágítás; Beépíthető világítás bútorokhoz; Elektromos lámpák; Világítókészülékek; Intelligens világítás.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Impianti d'illuminazione intelligenti; Luci; Luci a cupola; Luci a soffitto per mobili; Lampade elettriche; Apparecchi per illuminazione; Illuminazione intelligente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Išmanieji apšvietimo aparatai; Šviestuvai; Gaubtos lempos; Gaubtos lempos baldų reikmėms; Elektros lempos; Apšvietimo aparatai; Išmanusis apšvietimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Viedie apgaismes ķermeņi; Gaismas ķermeņi; Loka gaismas; Mēbeļu kupolveida apgaismojums; Elektriskās lampas un spuldzes; Apgaismes ķermeņi; Viedais apgaismojums.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Partijiet fissi tad-dawl intelliġenti; Dwal; Dwal forma ta' koppla; Dwal forma ta' koppla għall-għamara; Sistemi għad-dawl elettriku; Apparat għat-tidwil; Tidwil smart.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Slimme verlichtingsarmaturen; Lichten; Plafondlampen; Koepellampen voor meubels; Elektrische lampen; Verlichtingsapparaten; Slimme verlichting.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Inteligentne urządzenia oświetleniowe; Lampy; Oświetlenie w kopule; Oświetlenie kopułowe do mebli; Lampy elektryczne; Urządzenia oświetleniowe; Inteligentne oświetlenie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Acessórios de iluminação inteligentes; Luzes; Candeeiros esféricos; Luzes para móveis; Lâmpadas elétricas; Aparelhos de iluminação; Iluminação inteligente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Instalații de iluminat inteligente; Lămpi; Corpuri de iluminat pentru tavan; Spoturi pentru mobilier; Lămpi electrice; Aparate de iluminat; Iluminat inteligent.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Inteligentné svietidlá; Svietidlá; Stropné svetlá; Stropné svetlá pre nábytok; Elektrické lampy; Osvetľovacie prístroje; Inteligentné osvetlenie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pametne armature za osvetljevanje; Luči; Kupolaste luči; Kupolaste luči za pohištvo; Električne svetilke; Aparati za razsvetljavo; Pametna osvetlitev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Smarta belysningsarmaturer; Belysning; Taklampor; Taklampor för möbler; Elektriska lampor; Apparater för belysning; Smart belysning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>20</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Умни огледала; Шкафове с интелигентни огледала; Мебели за бани; Огледала, шкафове с огледала; Тоалетни масички за баня, включващи умивалници; Интелигентни огледала, шкафове с интелигентни огледала; Интелигентни огледала, а именно, огледала и шкафове с огледала с вградено осветление, камери и датчици, със софтуер и дисплеи, със сензорен и гласов контрол, и с възможност за свързване с мобилни устройства; Огледала и шкафове с огледала с интелигентно управление на осветлението и с вградени камери и датчици; Интелигентни огледала, съдържащи компютърни програми, използвани за показване на персонализирана информация на потребителя; Интелигентни огледала, с функция за мобилна свързаност, съдържащи компютърни програми, използвани за показване на персонализирана информация на потребителя.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Chytrá zrcadla; Chytré zrcadlové skříně; Koupelnový nábytek; Zrcadla, zrcadlové skříně; Koupelnové toaletní skříňky s umyvadlem; Chytrá zrcadla, chytré zrcadlové skříně; Chytrá zrcadla, jmenovitě zrcadla a zrcadlové skříně s integrovaným osvětlením, kamerami a čidly, se softwarem a displeji s dotykovým a hlasovým ovládáním a s možností připojení k mobilním zařízením; Zrcadla a zrcadlové skříně s chytrým ovládáním osvětlení a zabudovanými kamerami a čidly; Chytrá zrcadla obsahující počítačové programy používané k zobrazení personalizovaných informací o uživateli; Chytrá zrcadla, s funkcí mobilní konektivity, obsahující počítačové programy používané k zobrazení personalizovaných informací o uživateli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Smartspejle; Intelligente spejlkabinetter; Badeværelsesmøbler; Spejle, spejlskabe; Badeværelsesbord med kummer; Intelligente spejl, intelligente spejlkabinetter; Intelligente spejle, nemlig spejle og spejlkabinetter med integreret belysning, kameraer og sensorer med software og skærme med berøringsfølsomme og stemmestyrede styringer og med forbindelse til mobilenheder; Spejle og spejlkabinetter med styringer til intelligent belysning og indbyggede kameraer og sensorer; Intelligente spejle med computerprogrammer til visning af skræddersyet information vedrørende brugeren; Intelligente spejle med mobilopkobling, indeholdende computerprogrammer til visning af skræddersyet information vedrørende brugeren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Intelligente Spiegel; Intelligente Spiegelschränke; Badezimmermöbel; Spiegel, Spiegelschränke; Badezimmeruntertische mit eingelassenen Waschbecken; Intelligente Spiegel, intelligente Spiegelschränke; Intelligente Spiegel, nämlich Spiegel und Spiegelschränke mit integrierter Beleuchtung, Kameras und Sensoren, mit Software und Bildschirmen mit Berührungs- und Sprachsteuerung und mit einer Funktion zur Verbindung mit Mobiltelefonen; Spiegel und Spiegelschränke mit intelligenten Beleuchtungssteuerungen und eingebauten Kameras und Sensoren; Intelligente Spiegel mit Computerprogrammierung für die Anzeige personenbezogener Informationen der Nutzer; Intelligente Spiegel mit mobiler Konnektivitätsfunktion, mit Computerprogrammierung für die Anzeige personenbezogener Informationen der Nutzer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Έξυπνοι καθρέφτες· Ερμάρια με έξυπνους καθρέφτες· Έπιπλα μπάνιου· Καθρέφτες, ερμάρια με καθρέφτη· Τουαλέτες με ενσωματωμένο νιπτήρα· Έξυπνοι καθρέπτες, ερμάρια με έξυπνους καθρέφτες· Έξυπνοι καθρέφτες, συγκεκριμένα, καθρέφτες και ερμάρια με καθρέφτες με ενσωματωμένο φωτισμό, κάμερες, και αισθητήρες, με λογισμικό και οθόνες οπτικής παρουσίασης με μέσα ελέγχου αφής και φωνής και με δυνατότητα σύνδεσης σε κινητές διατάξεις· Καθρέφτες και ερμάρια με καθρέφτες με έξυπνα μέσα ελέγχου φωτισμού και ενσωματωμένες κάμερες και αισθητήρες· Έξυπνοι καθρέφτες με προγράμματα ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για χρήση για οπτική παρουσίαση εξατομικευμένων πληροφοριών του χρήστη· Έξυπνοι καθρέφτες, με λειτουργία κινητής συνδεσιμότητας, που περιέχει προγράμματα ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για χρήση για οπτική παρουσίαση εξατομικευμένων πληροφοριών χρήστη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Smart mirrors; smart mirror cabinets; bathroom furniture; mirrors, mirror cabinets; vanity units incorporating basins; smart mirrors, smart mirror cabinets; smart mirrors, namely, mirrors and mirror cabinets with integrated lighting, cameras, and sensors, with software and display screens with touch and voice controls, and with the ability to connect to mobile devices; mirrors and mirror cabinets with smart lighting controls and built-in cameras and sensors; smart mirrors containing computer programming used to display personalized information of the user; smart mirrors, with mobile connectivity functionality, containing computer programming used to display personalized information of the user.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Espejos inteligentes; Armarios de espejos inteligentes; Mobiliario de cuarto de baño; Espejos, armarios de espejo; Tocadores de baño que incorporan lavabos; Espejos inteligentes, armarios de espejos inteligentes; Espejos inteligentes, en concreto, espejos y armarios de espejo con iluminación, cámaras y sensores integrados con software y pantallas con controles táctiles y de voz, y con capacidad para conectarse a dispositivos móviles; Espejos y armarios de espejos con controles de iluminación inteligente y cámaras y sensores incorporados; Espejos inteligentes que contienen programación informática utilizada para mostrar información personalizada del usuario; Espejos inteligentes, con funcionalidad de conectividad móvil, que contienen programación informática utilizada para mostrar información personalizada del usuario.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Nutipeeglid; Nutikad peegelkapid; Vannitoamööbel; Peeglid, peegelkapid; Kraanikausiga vannitoakapid; Nutikad peeglid, nutikad peegelkapid; Nutikad peeglid, nimelt integreeritud valgustuse, kaamerate ja anduritega peeglid ja peegelkapid koos puutetundliku ja hääljuhitava tarkvara ja kuvaekraaniga ning võimalusega ühenduda mobiilseadmetega; Nutikad valgustuse juhtimise ning sisseehitatud kaamerate ja anduritega peeglid ja peegelkapid; Nutikad peeglid, mis sisaldavad arvutiprogramme, mida kasutatakse kasutaja isikustatud teabe kuvamisel; Nutikad peeglid koos mobiilse ühendusega, mis sisaldavad arvutiprogramme, mida kasutatakse kasutaja isikustatud teabe kuvamiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Älypeilit; Älypeilikaapit; Kylpyhuonekalusteet; Peilit, peilikaapit; Kylpyhuoneiden kampauspöydät, joihin sisältyy pesuallas; Älypeilit, älypeilikaapit; Älypeilit, nimittäin, peilit ja peilikaapit, joissa on integroitu valaistus, kameroita ja antureita ja jotka on varustettu ohjelmistoilla ja kosketus- ja ääniohjatuilla näyttöruuduilla ja kytkettävyydellä mobiililaitteisiin; Älyvalaistuksen hallintavälineillä ja sisäänrakennetuilla kameroilla ja antureilla varustetut peilit ja peilikaapit; Älypeilit, jotka sisältävät käyttäjän mukautettujen tietojen näyttöön käytettäviä tietokoneohjelmia; Matkapuhelinliitäntätoiminnolla varustetut älypeilit, jotka sisältävät käyttäjän mukautettujen tietojen näyttöön käytettäviä tietokoneohjelmia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Miroirs intelligents; Armoires à glace intelligentes; Mobilier de salle de bains; Miroirs, armoires à glace; Meubles de salle de bains avec lavabo incorporé; Miroirs intelligents, armoires à glace intelligentes; Miroirs intelligents, à savoir miroirs et armoires à glace dotés d'un éclairage, de caméras et de capteurs intégrés, dotés de logiciels et d'écrans d'affichage à commandes tactiles et vocales et capables de se connecter à des dispositifs mobiles; Miroirs et armoires à glace dotés de commandes d'éclairage intelligentes ainsi que de caméras et capteurs incorporés; Miroirs intelligents contenant des programmes informatiques utilisés pour l'affichage d'informations personnalisées de l'utilisateur; Miroirs intelligents, dotés d'une fonctionnalité de connectivité mobile, contenant des programmes informatiques utilisés pour l'affichage d'informations personnalisées de l'utilisateur.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pametna ogledala; Pametni ormarići s ogledalima; Kupaonski namještaj; Zrcala, ormari sa zrcalom; Kupaonski namještaj s umivaonicima; Pametna ogledala, pametni ormarići s ogledalima; Pametna ogledala, i to ogledala i ormarići s ogledalima s integriranom rasvjetom, kamerama i senzorima, sa softverom i zaslonima s dodirnim i glasovnim kontrolama te s mogućnošću povezivanja s mobilnim uređajima; Ogledala i ormarići s ogledalima s kontrolama za pametnu rasvjetu i ugrađenim kamerama i senzorima; Pametna ogledala koja sadržavaju računalno programiranje za prikaz personaliziranih korisničkih informacija; Pametna ogledala s funkcionalnošću mobilne veze koja sadržavaju računalno programiranje za prikaz personaliziranih korisničkih informacija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Intelligens tükrök; Intelligens tükrös szekrények; Fürdőszobabútorok; Tükrök, tükrös szekrények; Mosdóval egybeépített fürdőszobaszekrények; Intelligens tükrök, intelligens tükrös szekrények; Intelligens tükrök, nevezetesen tükrök és tükrös szekrények beépített világítással, kamerákkal és érzékelőkkel, szoftverrel és kijelzőképernyővel érintéses és hangvezérléssel, valamint a mobil eszközökhöz való csatlakozás képességével; Tükrök és tükrös szekrények intelligens világítási vezérléssel, beépített kamerákkal és érzékelőkkel; Intelligens tükrök számítógépes programozással a felhasználó személyre szabott információinak megjelenítésére; Intelligens tükrök, mobil csatlakozási funkcióval, számítógépes programozással a felhasználó személyre szabott információinak megjelenítésére.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Specchi intelligenti; Mobiletti a specchio intelligenti; Mobili per il bagno; Specchi, armadietti a specchio; Mobiletti da toletta con lavandino incorporato; Specchi intelligenti, mobiletti a specchio intelligenti; Specchi intelligenti, ovvero specchi e mobiletti a specchio con illuminazione integrata, telecamere e sensori, con software e schermi di visualizzazione con comandi tattili e vocali, e con la possibilità di collegarsi a dispositivi mobili; Specchi e mobiletti a specchio con controlli intelligenti di illuminazione, e telecamere e sensori incorporati; Specchi intelligenti con programmazione informatica utilizzata per visualizzare le informazioni personalizzate dell'utente; Specchi intelligenti, con funzionalità di connettività mobile, con programmazione informatica utilizzata per visualizzare informazioni personalizzate dell'utente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Išmanieji veidrodžiai; Išmaniųjų veidrodžių spintelės; Vonios kambario baldai; Veidrodžiai, spintos su veidrodžiais; Vonios dekoratyvinės spintelės su įmontuotomis kriauklėmis; Išmanieji veidrodžiai, išmaniųjų veidrodžių spintelės; Išmanieji veidrodžiai, būtent veidrodžiai ir veidrodžių spintelės su integruotu apšvietimu, fotoaparatai ir jutikliai, su programine įranga ir ekranais su jutikliniu ir balso valdymu ir galimybe prisijungti prie mobiliųjų prietaisų; Veidrodžiai ir veidrodžių spintelės su išmaniaisiais apšvietimo valdikliais ir įmontuotomis kameromis bei jutikliais; Išmanieji veidrodžiai su kompiuterių programavimu, naudojami individualizuotai vartotojo informacijai rodyti; Išmanieji veidrodžiai su mobiliojo ryšio funkcijomis, turintys kompiuterio programavimą, naudojamą individualizuotai vartotojo informacijai rodyti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Viedie spoguļi; Viedie spoguļu skapi; Vannasistabas mēbeles; Spoguļi, spoguļu skapīši; Vannas istabām paredzēti tualetes galdiņi ar izlietnēm; Viedie spoguļi, viedo spoguļu skapji; Viedie spoguļi, proti, spoguļi un spoguļu skapji ar integrētu apgaismojumu, kamerām un sensoriem, ar programmatūras un displeja ekrāniem ar pieskārienu un balss vadību un ar iespēju izveidot savienojumu ar mobilajām ierīcēm; Spoguļi un spoguļu skapji ar viedām apgaismojuma vadības ierīcēm un iebūvētām kamerām un sensoriem; Viedie spoguļi, kas satur datorprogrammu, ko izmanto, lai parādītu personalizētu lietotāja informāciju; Viedie spoguļi ar mobilās savienojamības funkcionalitāti, kas satur datorprogrammēšanu, ko izmanto, lai parādītu personalizētu lietotāja informāciju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Mirja smart; Armarji tal-mera intelliġenti; Għamara tal-kmamar tal-banju; Mirja, armarji bil-mera; Unitajiet kosmetiċi tal-kamra tal-banju li jinkorporaw sinkijiet; Mirja intelliġenti, armarji tal-mera intelliġenti; Mirja intelliġenti, jiġifieri, mirja u armarji tal-mirja b'tidwil, kameras u sensuri integrati b'software u skrins tad-displej b'kontrolli li jaħdmu bil-mess u l-vuċi u bil-ħila li jaqbdu ma' tagħmir mobbli; Mirja u armarji tal-mera b'kontrolli tat-tidwil intelliġenti u kameras u sensuri inkorporati; Mirja intelliġenti li fihom ipprogrammar tal-kompjuter użat biex juri informazzjoni personalizzata tal-utent; Mirja intelliġenti, b'funzjonalità tal-konnettività mobbli, li fihom ipprogrammar tal-kompjuter użat biex juri informazzjoni personalizzata tal-utent.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Slimme spiegels; Kasten met slimme spiegels; Badkamermeubilair; Spiegels, spiegelkasten; Badkamermeubilair met wastafels; Slimme spiegels, kasten met slimme spiegels; Slimme spiegels, te weten spiegels en spiegelkasten met geïntegreerde verlichting, camera's en sensors, met software en weergaveschermen met aanraak- en spraakbesturing en met mogelijkheden voor aansluiting op mobiele toestellen; Spiegels en spiegelkasten met slimme verlichtingsregeling en met ingebouwde camera's en sensors; Slimme spiegels met computerprogrammering voor het weergeven van gepersonaliseerde informatie van de gebruiker; Slimme spiegels met functies voor mobiele connectiviteit met computerprogrammering voor het weergeven van gepersonaliseerde informatie van de gebruiker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Inteligentne lustra; Inteligentne szafki z lustrami; Meble łazienkowe; Lustra, szafy z lustrami; Szafki łazienkowe z umywalkami; Inteligentne lustra, inteligentne szafki z lustrami; Inteligentne lustra, mianowicie lustra i szafki z lustrami ze zintegrowanym oświetleniem, kamerami i czujnikami, z oprogramowaniem i ekranem wyświetlającym oraz ze sterowaniem dotykowym i sterowaniem głosem oraz z możliwością podłączenia do urządzeń mobilnych; Lustra i szafki z lustrami z inteligentnymi urządzeniami do sterowania oświetleniem oraz z wbudowanymi kamerami i czujnikami; Inteligentne lustra zawierające oprogramowanie komputerowe służące do wyświetlania spersonalizowanych informacji o użytkowniku; Inteligentne lustra z funkcją łączności mobilnej, obejmujące programowanie komputerowe służące do wyświetlania spersonalizowanych informacji o użytkowniku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Espelhos inteligentes; Armários com espelho inteligentes; Mobiliário para casas de banho; Espelhos, armários de espelho; Unidades de toucadores com bacias incorporadas; Espelhos inteligentes, armários com espelho inteligentes; Espelhos inteligentes, especificamente espelhos e armários com espelho com iluminação integrada, câmaras e sensores, com software e ecrãs de visualização com controlos táteis e de voz e com capacidade de ligação a dispositivos móveis; Espelhos e armários com espelho com controlos de iluminação inteligentes e com câmaras e sensores integrados; Espelhos inteligentes contendo programação informática destinada à visualização de informações personalizadas do utilizador; Espelhos inteligentes com funcionalidade de ligação móvel contendo programação informática destinada à visualização de informações personalizadas do utilizador.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Oglinzi inteligente; Dulapuri inteligente cu oglindă; Mobilier de baie; Oglinzi, dulapuri cu oglinzi; Mobilă de toaletă incluzând lavoare; Oglinzi inteligente, dulapuri inteligente cu oglindă; Oglinzi inteligente, și anume oglinzi și dulapuri cu oglindă cu bec integrat, camere și senzori, cu software și cu ecrane de afișare cu comenzi tactile și vocale cu posibilitatea de a se conecta la dispozitive mobile; Oglinzi și dulapuri cu oglindă cu unități de control al iluminatului inteligente și camere și senzori integrați; Oglinzi inteligente care conțin programe informatice folosite pentru afișarea informațiilor personalizate ale utilizatorului; Oglinzi inteligente, cu funcție de conexiune mobilă, care conțin programe informatice folosite pentru afișarea informațiilor personale ale utilizatorului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Inteligentné zrkadlá; Inteligentné skrinky so zrkadlom; Nábytok do kúpeľne; Zrkadlá, zrkadlové skrine; Kúpeľňové toaletné skrinky s umývadlom; Inteligentné zrkadlá, inteligentné skrinky so zrkadlom; Inteligentné zrkadlá, menovite zrkadlá a skrinky so zrkadlom so zabudovaným osvetlením, kamerami a senzormi a so softvérom a obrazovkami s dotykovým a hlasovým ovládaním a s funkciou spájania sa s mobilnými prístrojmi; Zrkadlá a skrinky so zrkadlami, obsahujúce inteligentné ovládače osvetlenia a zabudované kamery a senzory; Inteligentné zrkadlá obsahujúce počítačové programy na zobrazovanie personalizovaných informácií o používateľovi; Inteligentné zrkadlá s funkciou mobilnej konektivity, obsahujúce počítačové programy na zobrazovanie personalizovaných informácií o používateľovi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pametna ogledala; Omarice za pametna ogledala; Pohištvo za kopalnice; Ogledalo, omarice z ogledalom; Kopalniški kozmetični elementi z vgrajenimi umivalniki; Pametna ogledala, omarice za pametna ogledala; Pametna ogledala, in sicer ogledala in omarice za ogledala z vgrajeno razsvetljavo, kamere in senzorji s programsko opremo ter prikazovalni zasloni z upravljanjem na dotik in glasovnim upravljanjem ter z možnostjo priključitve na mobilne naprave; Ogledala in omarice za ogledala s pametnim upravljanjem razsvetljave ter vgrajenimi kamerami in senzorji; Pametna ogledala, ki vsebujejo računalniško programiranje, ki se uporablja za prikaz osebnih informacij uporabnika; Pametna ogledala s funkcionalnostjo mobilne povezljivosti, ki vsebujejo računalniško programiranje, ki se uporablja za prikaz osebnih informacij uporabnika.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Smarta speglar; Smarta spegelskåp; Möbler för badrum; Speglar, spegelskåp; Tvättställ med inbyggt handfat; Smarta speglar, smarta spegelskåp; Smarta speglar, nämligen, speglar och spegelskåp med inbyggd belysning, kameror, och sensorer, med programvara och display-skärmar med pek- och röststyrning, och som kan kopplas upp till mobila anordningar; Speglar och spegelskåp med smart belysningsreglering och inbyggda kameror och sensorer; Smarta speglar som innehåller datorprogrammering som används för att visa personanpassad information för användaren; Smarta speglar, med mobiluppkopplingsfunktion, som innehåller datorprogrammering som används för att visa personanpassad information för användaren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/180</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-21</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>99320</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>10633</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
