<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-02T09:04:25</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018226151</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018226151</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="1">Application published</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-02</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>iDoStar</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162308364</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/226/018226151/000162308364.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.08</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.09</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.98</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.99.03</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.99.20</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.99.99</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Вентилационни капаци; Апарати за ароматизиране на въздух; Климатични инсталации; Инсталации за филтриране на въздух; Климатични апарати; Газопречистватели; Газоочистители [части за газови инсталации]; Въздухопречиствателни апарати и машини; Вентилационни [климатични] инсталации и апарати; Стерилизатори за въздух; Апарати за дехидратиране на органични храни; Уреди за парно гладене; Овлажнители на въздуха; Сешоари за коса; Водни пречиствателни инсталации; Филтри за питейна вода; Апарати за затопляне и охлаждане за дозиране на топли и студени напитки; Електрически вентилатори за лично ползване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Digestoře; Zařízení na dezodoraci vzduchu; Klimatizační zařízení; Zařízení na filtraci vzduchu; Ventilátory [klimatizace]; Zařízení na čištění plynu; Pračky plynů [části plynových zařízení]; Přístroje a stroje na čištění vzduchu; Ventilační [klimatizační] zařízení a přístroje; Sterilizátory vzduchu; Zařízení na dehydrataci potravinového odpadu; Napařovače oděvů; Zvlhčovače vzduchu; Vysoušeče vlasů; Zařízení na čištění vody; Filtry na přípravu pitné vody; Ohřívací a chladicí zařízení pro distribuci horkých a studených nápojů; Elektrické ventilátory pro osobní potřebu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Ventilationshætter; Luftdesodoriseringsapparater; Luftkonditioneringsanlæg; Luftfiltreringsinstallationer; Ventilatorer til luftkonditionering; Gasrensere; Gasskrubbere [dele af gasinstallationer]; Luftrenseapparater og -maskiner; Ventilationsinstallationer og apparater [aircondition]; Luftsteriliseringsapparater; Dehydreringsapparater til fødevareaffald; Steamere til tekstiler; Luftfugtere; Hårtørrere; Vandrenseinstallationer; Filtre til drikkevand; Opvarmnings- og køleapparater til udskænkning af varme og kolde drikke; Elektriske vifter til personlig brug.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Belüftungshauben; Luftdesodorierungsgeräte; Klimaanlagen; Luftfilteranlagen; Ventilatoren [Klimatisierung]; Gasfilter und -reiniger; Gaswäscher [Teile von Gasanlagen]; Luftreinigungsapparate und -maschinen; Lüftungsanlagen und -geräte [Klimatisierung]; Luftsterilisatoren; Apparate zur Dehydrierung von Speiseabfällen; Dampfglätter; Luftbefeuchter; Haartrockner; Wasserreinigungsanlagen; Trinkwasserfilter; Heiz- und Kühlgeräte zur Ausgabe von heißen und kalten Getränken; Elektrische Lüfter für den persönlichen Gebrauch.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Απορροφητήρες εξαερισμού· Αέρα (Συσκευές για την αφαίρεση των οσμών του -)· Εγκαταστάσεις κλιματισμού· Αέρα (Εγκαταστάσεις φιλτραρίσματος -)· Συσκευές ψύξης αέρα· Καθαριστήρες αερίου και συσκευές αφαίρεσης ρύπων αερίου· Αέριο (διαχωριστές -ου) [μέρη εγκαταστάσεων --ου]· Αέρα (Συσκευές και μηχανηματα καθαρισμού -)· Εξαερισμού [κλιματισμός] (συσκευές -)· Αέρα (Εγκαταστάσεις αποστείρωσης του -)· Συσκευές για αφυδάτωση απόβλητων τροφίμων· Ατμοκαθαριστές (υφασμάτων)· Συσκευές ύγρανσης, συσκευές αφύγρανσης· Στεγνωτήρες μαλλιών· Ύδωρ (εγκαταστάσεις καθαρισμού του -ος)· Φίλτρα για ύδωρ πόσιμο· Συσκευές θέρμανσης και ψύξης για τη διανομή ζεστών και κρύων ποτών· Ανεμιστήρες ηλεκτρικοί για προσωπική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Ventilation hoods; Air deodorizing apparatus; Air-conditioning installations; Air filtering installations; Fans [air-conditioning]; Gas scrubbing apparatus; Scrubbers [parts of gas installations]; Air purifying apparatus and machines; Ventilation [air-conditioning] installations and apparatus; Air sterilizers; Apparatus for dehydrating food waste; Fabric steamers; Humidifiers; Hair driers; Water purification installations; Filters for drinking water; Heating and cooling apparatus for dispensing hot and cold beverages; Electric fans for personal use.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Campanas de ventilación; Aparatos para desodorizar el aire; Instalaciones de aire acondicionado; Instalaciones de filtrado de aire; Ventiladores [climatización]; Depuradores y purificadores de gas; Lavadores de gas [partes de instalaciones de gas]; Aparatos y máquinas para purificar el aire; Aparatos e instalaciones de ventilación [aire acondicionado]; Esterilizadores de aire; Aparatos de deshidratación de residuos alimenticios; Aparatos vaporizadores para planchar tejidos; Saturadores; Secadores de pelo; Instalaciones de depuración de agua; Filtros para agua potable; Aparatos de calentamiento y refrigeración para la distribución de bebidas calientes y frías; Ventiladores eléctricos para uso personal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tõmbekapid; Õhudesodoreerseadmed, õhudesodoraatorid; Kliimaseadmed, klimaatorid; Õhufiltrimisseadmed, õhupuhastid; Ventilaatorid [kliimaseadmed]; Gaasipuhastid; Skraberid, gaasipuhastid [gaasiseadmete osad]; Õhupuhastusseadmed ja -masinad; Ventilatsiooniseadmed ja -aparaadid, kliimaseadmed ja -aparaadid; Õhusterilisaatorid; Toidujäätmete dehüdreerimise seadmed; Riideaurutajad; Õhuniisutajad; Juuksekuivatid; Veepuhastusseadmed; Joogiveefiltrid; Kuumutus- ja külmutusseadmed kuumade ja külmade jookide jaotamiseks; Elektriventilaatorid isiklikuks tarbeks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ilmanvaihtokuvut; Huoneilman hajunpoistolaitteet; Ilmastointilaitteistot; Ilmansuodatuslaitteet; Tuulettimet; Kaasunpuhdistimet; Kaasulaitteistojen osina käytettävät kaasunpuhdistimet; Ilmanpuhdistuslaitteet ja -koneet; Ilmanvaihtolaitteistot ja -laitteet; Ilman sterilointilaitteet; Ruuanjätteiden kuivatuslaitteet; Höyrypuhdistin kankaille; Ilmankostuttimet; Hiustenkuivaimet; Vedenpuhdistuslaitteet; Juomavesisuodattimet; Lämmitys- ja jäähdytyslaitteet kuumien ja kylmien juomien annosteluun; Tuulettimet (Sähkö -), henkilökohtaiseen käyttöön.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Hottes d'aération; Appareils pour la désodorisation de l'air; Installations de climatisation; Installations de filtrage d'air; Ventilateurs [climatisation]; Épurateurs et purificateurs de gaz; Laveurs de gaz [parties d'installations à gaz]; Appareils et machines pour la purification de l'air; Appareils et installations de ventilation [climatisation]; Stérilisateurs d'air; Appareils de déshydratation de déchets alimentaires; Défroisseurs de tissus à vapeur; Humidificateurs d'air; Sèche-cheveux; Installations pour la purification de l'eau; Filtres pour l'eau potable; Appareils chauffants et rafraîchissants pour la distribution de boissons chaudes et froides; Ventilateurs électriques à usage personnel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Nape (Ekstrator -) za kuhinje; Uređaji za osvježavanje zraka; Instalacije za klimatizaciju; Instalacije za filtriranje zraka; Ventilatori za klima uređaje; Čistači i pročiščivaći plina; Pročišćivači plina [dijelovi plinskih instalacija]; Zrak (uređaji i strojevi za pročišćavanje zraka); Ventilacijski [klimatizacijski] uređaji i aparati; Sterilizatori zraka; Uređaji za dehidrataciju prehrambenog otpada; Parna glačala za tkanine; Ovlaživači; Sušila za kosu; Uređaj za pročišćavanje vode; Filtri za pitku vodu; Uređaji za grijanje i hlađenje za doziranje toplih i hladnih napitaka; Električni ventilatori za osobnu uporabu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Elszívóernyők; Levegő szagtalanító készülékek; Légkondicionáló berendezések; Légszűrő berendezések; Légkondicionáló ventilátorok; Gáztisztítók; Gázmosók, gáztisztítók; Légtisztító készülékek és gépek; Szellőző [légkondicionáló] berendezések; Légfertőtlenítők; Élelmiszerhulladékok vízelvonására szolgáló készülékek; Textilgőzölők; Légnedvesítők; Hajszárítók; Víztisztító berendezések; Ivóvízszűrők; Meleg és hideg italok adagolására szolgáló melegítő- és hűtőkészülékek; Elektromos ventilátorok személyes használatra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cappe di aerazione; Apparecchi per la deodorizzazione dell'aria; Impianti di climatizzazione dell'aria; Impianti per filtrare l'aria; Ventilatori [climatizzazione]; Pulitori e purificatori di gas; Depuratori di gas [parti di impianti del gas]; Apparecchi e macchine per la depurazione dell'aria; Apparecchi ed installazioni di ventilazione [climatizzazione]; Sterilizzatori dell'aria; Apparecchi per disidratare prodotti alimentari organici; Macchine a vapore per stirare tessuti; Saturatori; Asciugacapelli; Impianti per la depurazione dell'acqua; Filtri per l'acqua potabile; Apparecchi di riscaldamento e raffreddamento per l'erogazione di bevande calde e fredde; Ventilatori elettrici per uso personale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Traukos gaubtai; Oro dezodoravimo aparatai; Oro kondicionavimo įrenginiai; Oro filtravimo įrenginiai; Ventiliatoriai [oro kondicionavimas]; Dujų valymo įrenginiai; Dujų valytuvai [dujinių įrenginių dalys]; Oro valymo aparatai ir mašinos; Ventiliacijos [oro kondicionavimo] įrenginiai ir aparatai; Oro sterilizatoriai; Maisto atliekų dehidratavimo aparatai; Audinių garintuvai; Oro drėkintuvai; Plaukų džiovintuvai; Vandens valymo įrenginiai; Geriamojo vandens filtrai; Šildymo ir šaldymo aparatai karštiems ir šaltiems gėrimams tiekti; Elektriniai asmeniniai ventiliatoriai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ventilācijas sistēmu nosūcēji; Gaisa dezodorēšanas ierīces; Gaisa kondicionēšanas sistēmu daļas; Gaisa filtrēšanas sistēmu daļas; Ventilatori gaisa kondicionēšanai; Gāzu attīrīšanas iekārtas; Skruberi (gāzes iekārtu daļas); Gaisa attīrīšanas iekārtas un ierīces; Ventilācijas vai gaisa kondicionēšanas iekārtas un ierīces; Gaisa sterilizatori; Iekārtas pārtikas atkritumu dehidratizēšanai; Tvaika apstrādes ierīces (audumiem); Ierīces gaisa mitrināšanai; Matu žāvēšanas ierīces; Ūdens attīrīšanas iekārtas; Dzeramā ūdens filtri; Sildīšanas un dzesēšanas iekārtas karstu un aukstu dzērienu izsniegšanai; Elektriskie ventilatori personiskai lietošanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Għata għall-ventilazzjoni; Apparat li jfewwaħ l-arja; Installazzjonijiet għall-ikkondizzjonar tal-arja; Installazzjonijiet li jiffiltraw l-arja; Tagħmir għat-tkessiħ tal-arja; Tagħmir għat-tindif tal-gass u purifikaturi; Broxkijiet tal-gass [partijiet ta' impjanti tal-gass]; Apparat u magni li jippurifikaw l-arja; Apparat u installazzjonijiet ta' ventilazzjoni (kondizzjonar tal-arja); Sterilizzaturi tal-arja; Apparat għad-deidrazzjoni tal-iskart tal-ikel; Apparat elettriku li jaħdem bil-fwar (għal tessuti); Tagħmir għas-saturazzjoni; Nixxiefa tax-xagħar; Sistemi għat-tisfija tal-ilma; Filtri għall-ilma tax-xorb; Apparat għat-tisħin jew it-tkessiħ għat-tqassim ta' xorb kiesaħ u sħun; Fannijiet tal-elettriku għal użu personali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Luchtafzuigkappen; Apparaten voor het desodoriseren van lucht; Airconditioninginstallaties; Luchtfiltreerinstallaties; Ventilatoren [airconditioning]; Gasreinigings- en -zuiveringsinstallaties; Gaswassers [delen van gasinstallaties]; Luchtzuiveringsapparaten en -machines; Ventilatie-apparaten [airconditioning]; Luchtsterilisatoren; Dehydratatie-apparatuur voor organische voedingsstoffen; Stoomapparaten voor het gladstrijken van stoffen; Bevochtigers; Haardrogers; Waterzuiveringsinstallaties; Drinkwaterfilters; Verwarmings- en koelapparatuur voor de afgifte van warme en koude dranken; Elektrische ventilatoren voor persoonlijk gebruik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Wyciągi wentylacyjne; Urządzenia do dezodoryzacji powietrza; Instalacje klimatyzacyjne; Instalacje do filtrowania powietrza; Agregaty klimatyzacyjne; Urządzenia do oczyszczania gazu; Płuczki gazowe [części instalacji gazowych]; Urządzenia i maszyny do oczyszczania powietrza; Instalacje i urządzenia wentylacyjne [klimatyzacyjne]; Sterylizatory powietrza; Urządzenia do odwadniania odpadków spożywczych; Prasowacze parowe; Nawilżacze powietrza; Suszarki do włosów; Instalacje do uzdatniania wody; Filtry do wody pitnej; Urządzenia grzewcze lub chłodnicze do wydawania gorących i zimnych napojów; Wentylatory elektryczne do użytku osobistego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Tabiques de ventilação; Aparelhos para a desodorização do ar; Instalações de climatização [condicionamento de ar]; Instalações de filtragem de ar; Ventiladores [climatização]; Produtos de limpeza e purificação do gás; Lavadores de gás [partes de instalações de gás]; Aparelhos e máquinas para a purificação da ar; Aparelhos de ventilação [climatização]; Esterilizadores de ar; Aparelhos de desidratação de desperdícios alimentares; Aparelhos a vapor para tecidos; Saturadores; Secador de cabelo; Instalações para a purificação da água; Filtros para a água potável; Aparelhos de aquecimento e refrigeração para bebidas quentes e frias; Ventiladores elétricos para uso pessoal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Hote de aerisire; Aparate pentru dezodorizarea aerului; Instalații de climatizare; Instalații de filtrare a aerului; Ventilatoare de aer condiționat; Epurare și purificare a gazelor; Spălatoare de gaze [părți ale instalațiilor de gaze]; Aparate și mașini pentru purificarea aerului; Instalații și aparate de ventilație [aer condiționat]; Sterilizatoare de aer; Aparate pentru deshidratarea resturilor alimentare; Aparate vaporizatoare pentru haine; Umidificatoare; Uscătoare de păr; Instalații pentru purificarea apei; Filtre pentru apa potabilă; Aparate de încălzire și de răcire pentru distribuirea de băuturi calde și reci; Ventilatoare electrice de uz personal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Dymníky; Zariadenia na osvieženie vzduchu; Klimatizačné zariadenia; Zariadenia na filtrovanie vzduchu; Ventilátory (klimatizácia); Prístroje na čistenie plynu; Práčky plynu (skrubre) (časti plynových zariadení); Stroje a prístroje na čistenie vzduchu; Vetracie zariadenia; Sterilizátory vzduchu; Prístroje na dehydratáciu potravinového odpadu; Parné prístroje na žehlenie textílií; Sýtiace zariadenia; Sušiče na vlasy; Zariadenia na úpravu vody; Filtre na pitnú vodu; Ohrievacie a chladiace zariadenia na distribúciu horúcich a studených nápojov; Elektrické ventilátory (stolové).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Prezračevalne nape; Aparati za dezodoriziranje zraka; Instalacije za klimatizacijo; Inštalacije za filtriranje zraka; Ventilatorji za klimatizacijo; Plinske naprave za čiščenje in prečiščevanje; Naprave za čiščenje plina [deli plinskih napeljav]; Naprave in stroji za čiščenje zraka; Aparati in napeljave za prezračevanje [klimatizacijo]; Sterilizatorji zraka; Aparati za dehidracijo odpadkov hrane; Parni gladilci tkanin; Saturatorji; Sušilniki za lase; Čistilne naprave za vodo; Filtri za pitno vodo; Aparati za segrevanje in hlajenje za doziranje toplih in hladnih napitkov; Električni ventilatorji za osebno uporabo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Ventilationskåpor; Luftuppfriskningsapparater; Luftkonditioneringsinstallationer; Luftfiltreringsinstallationer; Fläktar för luftkonditionering; Gasrenings- och gasrengöringsanordningar; Tvättare [delar av gasinstallationer]; Luftreningsapparater och -maskiner; Ventilationsinstallationer och -apparater (luftkonditionering); Luftsteriliseringsapparater; Apparater för torkning av matavfall; Ånganordningar för textiler; Saturatorer; Hårtorkar; Vattenreningsinstallationer; Filter för dricksvatten; Uppvärmnings- och kylapparater för utmatning av varma och kalla drycker; Elektriska fläktar för personligt bruk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/188</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-01</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080372</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15345</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018181233</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15345</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-16</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018063803</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>86428</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Decision to reject (final)</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-29</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
