<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-31T08:41:08</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224202</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224202</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-28</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-31</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>AETKFO</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162206721</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/224/018224202/000162206721.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.04</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.05</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.19</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.24</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Лампи; Електрическо фенерче; Електрическо фенерче; Противобактерийни лампи за пречистване на въздух; Светлини, електрически, за коледни елхи; Сценична осветителна апаратура; Машини за печене на хляб; Климатични апарати; Сешоари за коса; Въздухопречиствателни апарати и машини; Вентилатори (Електрически -) за лично ползване; Инсталации за овлажняване на въздуха; Електрически сешоари за коса; Водопроводни инсталации за баня; Уреди за изсушаване на ръце; Прожектори за светлина.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Svítidla; Vyhledávací světlomety; Vyhledávací světlomety; Germicidní lampy na čištění vzduchu; Elektrická osvětlení na vánoční stromky; Zařízení na osvětlení pódií; Stroje na pečení chleba; Ventilátory [klimatizace]; Vysoušeče vlasů; Stroje a přístroje na čištění vzduchu; Elektrické ventilátory pro osobní potřebu; Instalace na zvlhčování vzduchu; Elektrické vysoušeče vlasů; Koupelnové instalace; Sušiče rukou; Světelné projektory.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Lamper; Lyskastere; Lyskastere; Bakteriedræbende lamper til rensning af luft; Juletræslys, elektriske; Apparater til scenebelysning; Brødbagemaskiner; Ventilatorer til luftkonditionering; Hårtørrere [tørreapparater]; Luftrenseapparater og -maskiner; Elektriske vifter til personlig brug; Luftbefugtningsapparater; Elektriske hårtørrere; Badeinstallationer; Håndtørrere; Spotlamper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Beleuchtungslampen; Suchscheinwerfer; Suchscheinwerfer; Luftreinigungslampen mit keimtötender Wirkung; Christbaumbeleuchtungen [elektrisch]; Bühnenbeleuchtungsanlagen; Brotbackmaschinen; Klimageräte; Haartrockner; Luftreinigungsapparate und -maschinen; Elektrische Lüfter für den persönlichen Gebrauch; Luftbefeuchtungsgeräte; Elektrohaartrockner; Badinstallationen; Händetrockner; Lichtprojektoren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Φωτισμός (λαμπτήρες -ού)· Προβολείς εντοπισμού· Προβολείς εντοπισμού· Μικροβιοκτόνες (- λυχνίες) για το καθαρισμό του αέρα· Λαμπάκια ηλεκτρικά για δένδρα χριστουγεννιάτικα· Σκηνικός φωτιστικός εξοπλισμός· Αρτοπαρασκευαστές· Συσκευές ψύξης αέρα· Στεγνωτήρες μαλλιών· Αέρα (Συσκευές και μηχανηματα καθαρισμού -)· Ανεμιστήρες ηλεκτρικοί για προσωπική χρήση· Συσκευές ύγρανσης αέρα· Ηλεκτρικοί στεγνωτήρες μαλλιών· Λουτρού (Εγκαταστάσεις -)· Στεγνωτήρες χειρών· Προβολείς φωτισμού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Lamps; Searchlights; flashlights [torches]; Germicidal lamps for purifying air; Electric lights for Christmas trees; Stage lighting apparatus; Bread baking machines; Fans [air-conditioning]; Hair driers; Air purifying apparatus and machines; Electric fans for personal use; Air humidifying apparatus; Electrical hair driers; Bath installations; Hand dryers; Light projectors.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Lámparas [aparatos de iluminación]; Proyectores de luz; Proyectores de luz; Lámparas germicidas para purificar el aire; Luces eléctricas para árboles de Navidad; Aparatos de alumbrado para escenarios; Hornos de pan; Ventiladores de climatización; Secadores de pelo; Aparatos y máquinas para purificar el aire; Ventiladores eléctricos para uso personal; Aparatos para la humidificación del aire; Secadores de pelo eléctricos; Instalaciones de baño; Secadores de manos; Proyectores de luz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Lambid [valgustid]; Taskulambid [valgustusseadmed], helgiheitjad, prožektorid; Taskulambid [valgustusseadmed], helgiheitjad, prožektorid; Bakterihävituslambid, bakteritsiidlambid õhupuhastuseks; Jõulupuu elektriküünlad; Lavavalgustusseadmed; Leivaküpsetusmasinad; Ventilaatorid [kliimaseadmed]; Juuksekuivatid; Õhupuhastusseadmed ja -masinad; Elektriventilaatorid isiklikuks tarbeks; Õhuniisutusseadmed; Elektrilised juukseföönid; Vanni sanitaarseadmed; Kätekuivatid; Valgusprožektorid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lamput; Soihdut valaistukseen; Soihdut valaistukseen; Itiöitä ja mikro-organismeja tuhoavat lamput ilmanpuhdistukseen; Joulukuusten sähkövalaisimet; Näyttämövalaisimet; Leipäkoneet; Tuulettimet; Hiustenkuivaimet; Ilmanpuhdistuslaitteet ja -koneet; Tuulettimet (Sähkö -), henkilökohtaiseen käyttöön; Ilmankostutuslaitteet; Sähkökäyttöiset hiustenkuivaajat; Kylpyhuoneen saniteettivarusteet; Käsienkuivaimet; Valoprojektorit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Lampes d'éclairage; Projecteurs d'éclairage; Projecteurs d'éclairage; Lampes germicides pour la purification de l'air; Guirlandes électriques pour sapins de Noël; Appareils d'éclairage scénique; Machines pour cuire du pain; Ventilateurs [climatisation]; Sèche-cheveux; Appareils et machines pour la purification de l'air; Ventilateurs électriques à usage personnel; Installations d'humidification de l'air; Sèche-cheveux électriques; Installations de bain; Sèche-mains; Projecteurs de lumière.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Rasvjetne svjetiljke; Džepne svjetiljke za rasvjetu; Džepne svjetiljke za rasvjetu; Svjetiljke za uništavanje klica radi pročišćavanja zraka; Svjećice (električne svjećice za božićna drvca); Uređaji za osvjetljivanje pozornica; Aparati za pečenje kruha; Ventilatori za klima uređaje; Sušila za kosu; Zrak (uređaji i strojevi za pročišćavanje zraka); Električni ventilatori za osobnu uporabu; Instalacije za ovlaživanje zraka; Električna sušila za kosu; Sanitarna oprema za kupaonice; Sušila za ruke; Svjetlosni projektori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Lámpák; Keresőlámpák, zseblámpák; Keresőlámpák, zseblámpák; Csíraölő lámpák a levegő tisztításához; Lámpák karácsonyfákhoz, elektromos; Színpadvilágító berendezések; Kenyérsütő gépek; Légkondicionáló ventilátorok; Hajszárítók; Légtisztító készülékek és gépek; Elektromos ventilátorok személyes használatra; Légpárásító berendezések; Elektromos hajszárítók; Fürdőszobai vízvezeték szerelvények; Kézszárítók; Fényprojektorok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Lampade per illuminazione; Proiettori; Proiettori; Lampade germicide per la depurazione dell'aria; Lampadine elettriche per alberi di natale; Apparecchi d'illuminazione scenica; Macchine per cuocere il pane; Impianti di climatizzazione; Asciugacapelli; Apparecchi e macchine per la depurazione dell'aria; Ventilatori elettrici per uso personale; Apparecchi per l'umidificazione dell'aria; Asciugacapelli elettrici; Impianti di bagni; Apparecchi per asciugare le mani; Lampade lenticolari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Lempos; Prožektoriai; Prožektoriai; Oro valymo baktericidinės lempos; Kalėdų eglučių elektros lemputės; Scenos apšvietimo aparatūra; Duonos kepimo mašinos; Ventiliatoriai [oro kondicionavimas]; Plaukų džiovintuvai; Oro valymo aparatai ir mašinos; Elektriniai asmeniniai ventiliatoriai; Oro drėkinimo įrenginiai; Elektriniai plaukų džiovintuvai; Vonių kambarių įrenginiai; Rankų džiovintuvai; Šviesos prožektoriai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Lampas; Kabatas baterijas; Kabatas baterijas; Baktericīdas lampas gaisa attīrīšanai; Elektriskās spuldzītes Ziemassvētku eglītēm; Skatuves apgaismošanas ierīces; Maizes cepšanas mašīnas; Ventilatori [gaisa kondicionēšanai]; Matu žāvētāji; Gaisa attīrīšanas aparāti un iekārtas; Elektriskie ventilatori personīgai lietošanai; Gaisa mitrināšanas iekārtas; Elektriskie matu žāvējamie aparāti; Vannas iekārtas; Roku žāvēšanas aparāti; Prožektori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Lampi; Torċ għad-dawl; Torċ għad-dawl; Lampi li jnaddfu l-arja u li joqtlu l-imnibbta; Dwal elettriċi għas-siġar tal-Milied; Apparat tad-dawl għall-palk; Magni li jaħmu l-ħobż; Tagħmir għat-tkessiħ tal-arja; Nixxiefa tax-xagħar; Apparat u magni li jippurifikaw l-arja; Fannijiet tal-elettriku għal użu personali; Apparat għall-umdità tal-arja; Apparat tal-elettriku għat-tnixxif tax-xagħar; Partijiet tal-plàming tal-banju; Magni li jnixxfu l-idejn; Projetturi tad-dawl.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Lampen voor verlichting; Toortsen voor verlichting; Toortsen voor verlichting; Kiemdodende lampen voor het zuiveren van lucht; Elektrische lampen voor kerstbomen; Podiumverlichtingstoestellen; Broodbakmachines; Luchtkoelapparaten; Haardrogers; Luchtzuiveringsapparaten en -machines; Elektrische ventilatoren voor persoonlijk gebruik; Luchtbevochtigingsinstallaties; Elektrische haardrogers; Badinstallaties; Droogapparaten voor de handen; Lichtprojectoren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Lampy oświetleniowe; Latarki; Latarki; Lampy bakteriobójcze do oczyszczania powietrza; Lampki elektryczne na choinki; Urządzenia do oświetlenia scenicznego; Urządzenia do pieczenia chleba; Agregaty klimatyzacyjne; Suszarki do włosów; Urządzenia i maszyny do oczyszczania powietrza; Wentylatory elektryczne do użytku osobistego; Instalacje nawilżające powietrze; Elektryczne suszarki do włosów; Łazienkowe instalacje wodno-kanalizacyjne; Suszarki do rąk; Rzutniki światła.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Lâmpadas; Tochas [archotes] para a iluminação; Tochas [archotes] para a iluminação; Lâmpadas germicidas para a purificação do ar; Lâmpadas elétricas para árvores de natal; Aparelhos de iluminação cénica; Máquinas para cozinhar pão; Ventiladores para refrigerar o ar; Secador de cabelo; Aparelhos e máquinas para a purificação da ar; Ventiladores elétricos para uso pessoal; Instalações de humidificação do ar; Secadores elétricos de cabelos; Instalações de banho; Secadores de mão; Projetores de luz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Lămpi de iluminat; Lanterne pentru iluminat; Lanterne pentru iluminat; Lămpi germicide pentru purificarea aerului; Instalaţii luminoase pentru pomul de Crăciun; Aparate pentru iluminarea scenei; Maşini de făcut pâine; Ventilatoare de aer condiţionat; Uscătoare de păr; Aparate şi maşini pentru purificarea aerului; Ventilatoare electrice de uz personal; Instalaţii de umidificare a aerului; Uscătoare de păr electrice; Instalaţii sanitare de baie; Uscătoare de mâini; Proiectoare de lumină.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Lampy; Baterky (svietidlá); Baterky (svietidlá); Lampy na čistenie vzduchu od baktérií (germicídne); Elektrické svetlá na vianočné stromčeky; Zariadenia na osvetľovanie pódií; Zariadenia na pečenie chleba; Ventilátory (klimatizácia); Sušiče na vlasy; Stroje a prístroje na čistenie vzduchu; Elektrické ventilátory (stolové); Zariadenia na zvlhčovanie vzduchu; Elektrické sušiče na vlasy; Kúpeľňové armatúry; Sušiče na ruky; Svetlomet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Svetilke; Žepne svetilke za razsvetljavo; Žepne svetilke za razsvetljavo; Germicidne svetilke za prečiščevanje zraka; Električne lučke za božična drevesca; Aparati za osvetljevanje odra; Naprave za peko kruha; Ventilatorji za klimatizacijo; Sušilniki za lase; Naprave in stroji za čiščenje zraka; Električni ventilatorji za osebno uporabo; Instalacije za vlaženje zraka; Električni sušilniki za lase; Oprema za kopalniške vodovodne napeljave; Sušilniki za roke; Projektorji svetlobe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Lampor; Handlyktor; Handlyktor; Bakteriedödande lampor för luftrening; Elektriska belysningar för julgranar; Scenbelysningsapparater; Brödbakningsmaskiner; Fläktar för luftkonditionering; Hårtorkar; Luftreningsapparater och -maskiner; Elektriska fläktar för personligt bruk; Luftfuktningsapparater; Elektriska hårtorkar; Badinstallationer; Handtorkar; Ljusprojektorer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Мухогонки; Капани за насекоми; Капани за мишки; Насекоми (Електрически уреди за привличане и унищожаване -); Ултразвукови устройства срещу комари; Кухненски ръкавици; Килимочистачки; Ръкавици за домакински цели; Изтъркващи гъбички от метални влакна; Изотермични чанти; Напитки (Топлоизолирани съдове за -); Четки; Пръскачки за поливане на цветя и растения; Саксии; Сервизи за кафе, не от благороден метал.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Plácačky na mouchy; Pasti na hmyz; Pasti na krysy nebo potkany; Elektrická zařízení na vábení a hubení hmyzu; Ultrazvuková zařízení na odpuzování komárů; Chňapky (rukavice); Zametače na koberce; Rukavice pro použití v domácnosti; Kovové drátěnky; Termoizolační tašky; Tepelně izolované nádoby na nápoje (termosky); Kartáče; Rozstřikovače na zalévání květin a rostlin; Květináče; Kávové servisy [stolní nádobí].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Fluesmækkere; Insektfangere; Rottefælder; Elektriske apparater til tiltrækning og udryddelse af insekter; Ultralydsapparater til fordrivelsae af myg; Ovnhandsker; Tæppefejeredskaber; Handsker til husholdningsbrug; Grydesvampe af metal; Isotermiske tasker; Varmeisolerende beholdere til drikke; Børster; Håndsprøjter til blomster og planter; Urtepotter; Kaffeservicer [bordservice].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Fliegenklatschen; Insektenfallen; Rattenfallen; Insektenanlock- und -vertilgungsgeräte, elektrische; Ultraschallgeräte zur Mückenabwehr; Ofenhandschuhe; Teppichkehrer; Haushaltshandschuhe; Scheuerkissen aus Metall; Kühltaschen; Isoliergefäße für Getränke; Bürsten; Blumen- und Pflanzenspritzen; Blumentöpfe; Kaffeeservice [Tafelgeschirr].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μυγοσκοτώστρες· Εντομοπαγίδες· Ποντικοπαγίδες· Ηλεκτρικές διατάξεις προσέλκυσης και εξόντωσης εντόμων· Απωθητικά κουνουπιών με υπερήχους· Γάντια φούρνου χωρίς χωρίσματα για τα δάκτυλα· Σκούπες μηχανικές· Γάντια οικιακής χρήσης· Συρματόβουρτσες· Τσάντες ισοθερμικές· Ποτά (Θερμαινόμενα δοχεία για -)· Βούρτσες· Πότισμα λουλουδιών και φυτών (Τρόμπες για το -)· Γλάστρες· Σερβίτσια καφέ [επιτραπέζια σκεύη].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Fly swatters; Insect traps; Rat traps; Electric devices for attracting and killing insects; Ultrasonic mosquito repellers; Barbecue mitts; Carpet sweepers; Gloves for household purposes; Saucepan scourers of metal; Isothermic bags; Heat-insulated containers for beverages; Brushes; Syringes for watering flowers and plants; Flower pots; Coffee services [tableware].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Matamoscas; Trampas para insectos; Trampas para ratas; Insectos (Dispositivos eléctricos para atraer y eliminar -); Repelentes de mosquitos que funcionan por ultrasonidos; Manoplas de cocina; Barrealfombras mecánicos; Guantes para uso doméstico; Esponjas metálicas para fregar; Bolsas isotérmicas; Bebidas (Recipientes térmicos para -); Cepillos; Jeringas para regar flores y plantas; Macetas [tiestos]; Servicios de café [vajilla].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kärbsepiitsad; Putukapüünised; Rotilõksud; Elektrilised vahendid putukate püüdmiseks ja tapmiseks; Ultraheliga töötavad sääsetõrjevahendid; Pajakindad; Mehaanilised vaibaharjad; Kindad (Majapidamis -), majapidamiskindad; Metallist küürimisnuustikud; Isotermilised kotid; Joogimahutid (Soojusisolatsiooniga); Harjad; Lille- ja taimekastmispiserdid, - pritsid; Lillepotid; Kohviserviisid [lauanõud].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kärpäslätkät; Hyönteispyydykset; Hiirenloukut; Hyönteisten houkutus- ja hävityslaitteet [sähkökäyttöiset]; Hyttysten ultraäänikarkottimet; Patakintaat; Mattomikot; Käsineet kotitalouskäyttöön; Teräsvillatyynyt hankaamiseen; Isotermiset laukut; Juomien säilytykseen tarkoitetut lämpöeristetyt astiat; Harjat; Ruiskut kukkien ja kasvien kasteluun; Kukkaruukut; Kahviastiastot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Tapettes à mouches; Pièges à insectes; Ratières; Dispositifs électriques pour attirer et détruire les insectes; Répulsifs anti-moustiques à ultrasons; Gants de cuisine; Balais mécaniques; Gants de ménage; Tampons métalliques à récurer; Sacs isothermes; Récipients calorifuges pour boissons; Brosses; Seringues pour l'arrosage des fleurs et des plantes; Pots de fleurs; Services à café.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Muhomlati; Zamke za insekte; Mišolovke; Električni uređaji za privlačenje i uništavanje insekata; Ultrazvučni uređaji za odbijanje komaraca; Kuhinjske rukavice; Mehaničke metle; Rukavice za kućanstvo; Metalni jastučići za ribanje; Termičke izolacijske vrećice; Toplinski izolirane posude za pića; Četke; Poljevače za cvijeće i biljke; Lončanice za cvijeće; Servisi za kavu [stolno posuđe].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Légycsapók; Rovarcsapdák; Egérfogók; Elektromos rovarcsapdák; Ultrahangos szúnyogriasztók; Grillkesztyűk; Szőnyegseprők; Kesztyűk háztartási használatra; Fém súrolópárnák; Izotermikus táskák; Hőszigetelt tartályok italokhoz; Kefék; Öntözők virágok és más növények locsolásához; Virágcserepek; Kávéskészletek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Acchiappamosche; Trappole per insetti; Trappole per topi; Dispositivi elettrici per l'attrazione e distruzione di insetti; Repellenti a ultrasuoni per zanzare; Guanti da forno; Scope meccaniche; Guanti per uso domestico; Paglietta; Borse isotermiche; Recipienti coibenti per bevande; Spazzole; Spruzzatoi per l'innaffiamento di fiori e di piante; Vasi da fiori; Servizi da caffè.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Musmušiai; Vabzdžių gaudyklės; Pelių spąstai; Elektriniai vabzdžių viliojimo ir naikinimo prietaisai; Ultragarsiniai uodų atbaidymo prietaisai; Orkaitės pirštinės; Kilimų valymo įtaisai; Buitinės pirštinės; Kaistuvų metaliniai raizginiai (šveistukai); Izoterminiai maišeliai; Gėrimų termosai; Šepečiai; Gėlių ir augalų švirkštuvai; Vazonai; Kavos servizai [valgomieji reikmenys].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mušu sitamie; Kukaiņu lamatas; Peļu slazdi; Kukaiņu pievilināšanas un iznīcināšanas elektriskās ierīces; Ultraskaņas ierīces moskītu atbaidīšanai; Grila cimdi; Birstes tepiķu tīrīšanai; Mājsaimniecībā izmantojami cimdi; Beržamie sūkļi no metāla; Izotermiskas somas; Siltumizturīgas tvertnes dzērieniem; Sukas; Smidzināšanas aparāti puķu un augu laistīšanai; Puķu podi; Kafijas servīzes [galda piederumi].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat għall-esterminazzjoni tad-dubbien; Nases għall-insetti; Nases għall-ġrieden; Apparat tal-elettriku biex jattira u joqtol l-insetti; Tagħmir ultrasoniku li jbiegħed lin-nemus; Ingwanti tal-forn; Oġġetti li jikinsu t-twapet; Ingwanti għal skopijiet domestiċi; Sponoż tal-metall biex tobrox; Boroż isotermiċi; Xorb (Kontenituri bl-iżolazzjoni għax- -); Pniezel; Injezzjonijiet għas-saqi ta' fjuri u pjanti; Qsari; Servizzi tal-kafè [oġġetti tal-mejda].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Vliegenmeppers; Vallen voor insecten; Rattenvallen; Elektrische inrichtingen voor het aantrekken en doden van insecten; Ultrasone instrumenten voor het weren van muggen; Ovenhandschoenen; Rolbezems; Handschoenen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Schuursponzen van metaal; Koeltassen; Warmte-isolerende houders voor dranken; Borstels; Plantenspuiten; Bloempotten; Koffieserviezen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Packi na muchy; Łapki na insekty; Pułapki na myszy; Owady [Elektryczne urządzenia do wabienia i zabijania -]; Ultradźwiękowe odstraszacze komarów; Rękawice kuchenne; Szczotki do dywanów; Rękawice do użytku domowego; Druciaki metalowe; Torby izotermiczne; Termosy do napojów; Szczotki; Zraszacze do podlewania kwiatów i roślin; Doniczki na kwiaty; Serwisy do kawy [zastawa stołowa].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Mata-moscas; Armadilhas para insetos; Ratoeiras para ratazanas; Dispositivos elétricos para atrair e eliminar insetos; Repelentes de mosquitos por ultrassons; Luvas para forno; Espanadores para carpetes; Luvas de uso doméstico; Esfregões metálicos [palha de aço]; Sacos isotérmicos; Recipientes térmicos para bebidas; Escovas; Seringas para regar flores e plantas; Vasos [recipientes] para flores; Serviços de café [louça de mesa].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Pliciuri de muşte; Capcane pentru insecte; Capcane pentru şobolani; Dispozitive electrice pentru atragerea şi omorârea insectelor; Dispozitive cu ultrasunete pentru îndepărtarea țânțarilor; Mănuşi de bucătărie; Mături mecanice; Mănuşi de menaj; Bureţi din sârmă; Sacoşe termoizolante; Băuturi (Recipiente termoizolante pentru -); Perii; Seringi pentru stropit flori şi plante; Ghivece de flori; Servicii de cafea [veselă].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Lapačky na muchy; Lapače hmyzu; Myši (Pasce na -); Elektrické zariadenia na priťahovanie a ničenie hmyzu; Ultrazvukové zariadenia na odpudzovanie komárov; Kuchynské rukavice, chňapky; Mechanické metly; Rukavice pre domácnosť; Kovové drôtenky; Izotermické vrecká; Tepelnoizolačné nádoby na nápoje (termosky); Kefy; Kropiace ružice na polievanie kvetov; Kvetináče; Kávové súpravy (stolový riad).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Muhalniki; Pasti za insekte; Mišolovke; Električne naprave, ki privlačijo in uničujejo mrčes; Ultrazvočne naprave za odganjanje komarjev; Rokavice za žar; Pometači za preproge; Rokavice za gospodinjske namene; Žičnate (kovinske) gobice za čiščenje; Termične izolacijske vrečke; Toplotno izolirane posode za pijače; Krtače; Razpršilniki za vrt; Lončki za rože; Kavni servisi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Flugsmällor; Insektsfällor; Musfällor; Elektriska anordningar för att dra åt sig och döda insekter; Myggavvisande ultraljudsapparater; Grillvantar; Mattsopare; Handskar för hushållsändamål; Viska av stålull; Isotermiska väskor; Värmeisolerande behållare för drycker; Borstar; Vattenspridare för blommor och plantor; Blomkrukor; Kaffeserviser [bordsserviser].</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/095</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-21</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/165</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-31</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>32203</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
