<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-07T08:44:40</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224225</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224225</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-03</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>nl</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-07</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>HAPPYSOAPS</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162210175</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/224/018224225/000162210175.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.11</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.13</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.15</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>25.07.99</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Сапуни; Парфюмерия, етерични масла, козметика, лосиони за коса; Козметични и почистващи средства за тяло и коса; Сапун за тяло; Шампоани, В т.ч. такива под формата на шампоан бар; Средства за почистване на зъби; Паста или прах за зъби.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Mýdla; Parfumerie, vonné oleje, kosmetika, vlasové vody (lotions); Kosmetické a čisticí prostředky pro tělo a vlasy; Mýdla na tělo; Šampony, Včetně ve formě tuhých šamponů; Zubní pasty; Prostředky ústní hygieny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sæber; Parfumevarer, æteriske olier, kosmetiske præparater, hårlotion; Kosmetiske og rensende midler til krop og hår; Kropssæbe; Shampoo, Inklusive i form af en shampoo-bar; Tandplejemidler; Tandplejemidler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Seifen; Parfümeriewaren, ätherische Öle, Mittel zur Körper- und Schönheitspflege, Haarwässer; Kosmetische und Reinigungsmittel für Körper und Haar; Zeep voor het lichaam; Shampoos, Einschließlich in Form von festem Shampoo; Zahnputzmittel; Zahnputzmittel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Σαπούνια· Είδη αρωματοποιίας, αιθέρια έλαια, καλλυντικά, λοσιόν για τα μαλλιά· Καλλυντικά προϊόντα και προϊόντα καθαρισμού για το σώμα και τα μαλλιά· Σαπούνι για το σώμα· Σαμπουάν, Μεταξύ άλλων με τη μορφή μπάρας σαμπουάν· Οδοντοσκευάσματα· Οδοντόκρεμες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Soaps; Perfumery, essential oils, cosmetics, hair lotions; Cosmetics and cleansing preparations for the body and hair; Body soaps; Shampoo, Including in the form of a shampoo bar; Dentifrices; Dentifrice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Jabones; Productos de perfumería, aceites esenciales, cosméticos, lociones capilares; Productos cosméticos y de limpieza para el cuerpo y el cabello; Jabón para el cuerpo; Champús, Incluyendo en forma de barra de champú; Dentífricos; Dentífricos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Seebid; Parfümeeriatooted, eeterlikud õlid, kosmeetikavahendid, juukseveed; Kosmeetilised puhastusvahendid kehale ja juustele; Kehaseep; Šampoonid, Sh tahked šampoonid; Hambapastad; Hambapuhastusained.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Saippuat; Hajuvedet, eteeriset öljyt, kosmeettiset tuotteet, hiustenhoitovalmisteet; Kosmeettiset ja puhdistusaineet keholle ja hiuksille; Vartalosaippuat; Shampoot, Mukaan lukien palashampoon muodossa; Hampaidenpuhdistusaineet; Hampaidenpuhdistusaineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Savons; Parfumerie, huiles essentielles, cosmétiques, lotions pour les cheveux; Produits cosmétiques et nettoyants pour le corps et les cheveux; Savon pour le corps; Shampooings, Y compris sous la forme de shampooings solides; Dentifrices; Dentifrices.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sapuni; Parfumerijski proizvodi, eterična ulja, kozmetički proizvodi, losioni za kosu; Kozmetička sredstva i sredstva za čišćenje za tijelo i kosu; Sapuni za tijelo; Šamponi, Uključujući u obliku šampona u obliku pločica; Prpoizvodi za njegu zubi; Preparati za čišćenje zubi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szappanok; Illatszerek, illóolajok, kozmetikai cikkek, hajmosó szerek; Kozmetikai és tisztító szerek a test és a haj számára; Testszappan; Samponok, Azon belül sampontömb formájában; Fogkrémek; Fogkrémek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Saponi; Profumeria, olii essenziali, cosmetici, lozioni per capelli; Prodotti detergenti e cosmetici per il corpo e i capelli; Sapone per il corpo; Shampoo, Anche sotto forma di confezione di shampoo; Dentifrici; Dentifrici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Muilas; Parfumerija, eteriniai aliejai, kosmetika, plaukų losjonai; Kūno ir plaukų kosmetika ir valikliai; Kūno muilas; Šampūnai, Įskaitant šampūno pavidalą; Dantų milteliai ir pastos; Dantų milteliai ir pastos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ziepes; Parfimērijas izstrādājumi, ēteriskās eļļas, kosmētiskie un matu kopšanas līdzekļi; Kosmētiskie un tīrīšanas līdzekļi ķermenim un matiem; Ziepes ķermenim; Šampūni, Tostarp cieto šampūnu veidā; Zobu kopšanas līdzekļi; Zobu kopšanas līdzekļi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Sapun; Fwejjaħ, żjut essenzjali, kożmetiċi, lozjonijiet tax-xagħar; Prodotti kożmetiċi u għat-tindif tal-ġisem u tax-xagħar; Sapun tal-ġisem; Xampù, Inkluż fil-forma ta' sapun bħala xampù; Dentifriċi; Dentifriċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Zepen; parfumerieën, etherische oliën, cosmetische middelen, haarlotions; cosmetische- en reinigende middelen voor lichaam en haar; zeep voor het lichaam; shampoo, waaronder in de vorm van een shampoo bar; tandreinigingsmiddelen; tandpasta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Mydła; Środki perfumeryjne, olejki eteryczne, kosmetyki, płyny do pielęgnacji włosów; Kosmetyki i środki myjące do ciała i włosów; Mydło do ciała; Szampony, W tym w postaci szamponu w kostce; Środki do czyszczenia zębów; Środki do czyszczenia zębów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Sabões; Perfumaria, óleos essenciais, cosméticos, loções para os cabelos; Produtos cosméticos e de limpeza para o corpo e os cabelos; Sabão para o corpo; Champôs, Incluindo sob a forma de champô em barra; Dentífricos; Dentífricos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Săpunuri; Parfumerie, uleiuri esenţiale, cosmetice, loţiuni pentru păr; Produse cosmetice și de curățare pentru corp și păr; Săpun pentru corp; Şampoane, Inclusiv sub formă de șampon solid; Produse pentru îngrijirea dinţilor; Produse pentru curăţarea dinţilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Mydlá; Voňavkárske výrobky, éterické oleje, kozmetické prípravky, vlasové vodičky; Kozmetické a čistiace prípravky na telo a vlasy; Mydlo na telo; Šampóny, Vrátane vo forme tuhých šampónov; Prípravky na čistenie zubov; Prípravky na čistenie zubov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Mila; Parfumerijski izdelki, eterična olja, kozmetična sredstva, losioni za lase; Kozmetična in čistilna sredstva za telo in lase; Milo za telo; Šamponi, Vključno v obliki tablice šampona; Sredstva za čiščenje zob; Sredstva za čiščenje zob.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tvål; Parfymer, eteriska oljor, kosmetika, hårvårdspreparat; Kosmetiska medel och rengöringsmedel för kropp och hår; Kroppstvål; Schampon, Inklusive i form av schampokakor; Tandpulver, -kräm och -pastor; Tandpulver, -kräm och -pastor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Домакински прибори и съдове; Гребени и гъби; Естествени гъби; Четки, четки за зъби; Сапунерки/чинии за сапун; Контейнери за съхранение и сашета за сапун.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Náčiní a nádoby pro domácnost; Hřebeny a mycí houby; Přírodní houby na mytí; Kartáče, zubní kartáčky; Držáky na mýdlo / misky na mýdlo; Nádobky a pytlíky na uchovávání mýdla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Husholdnings- og køkkenredskaber samt beholdere; Kamme og svampe; Naturlige vaskesvampe; Børster, tandbørster; Sæbeholdere og -skåle; Opbevaringsskåle og -poser til sæbe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Geräte und Behälter für den Hausgebrauch und Haushaltszwecke; Kämme und Schwämme; Meerschwämme; Bürsten, Zahnbürsten; Seifenhalter/Seifenschalen; Seifendosen und -beutel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μικρά σκεύη και δοχεία οικιακής και μαγειρικής χρήσης· Χτένια και σφουγγάρια· Φυσικά σφουγγάρια· Βούρτσες, οδοντόβουρτσες· Σαπουνοθήκες/πιατάκια για σαπούνι· Κουτιά και σακουλάκια φύλαξης για σαπούνι.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Domestic and household utensils and containers; Combs and sponges; Natural sponges; Brushes, toothbrushes; soap holders/dishes for soap; Soap storage containers and bags.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Utensilios y recipientes domésticos y para la casa; Peines y esponjas; Esponjas naturales; Cepillos, cepillos de dientes; Jaboneras/platos para jabón; Recipientes y bolsas para conservar el jabón.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Maja- ja köögitarbed ning nõud; Kammid ja käsnad; Looduslikud käsnad; Harjad, hambaharjad; Seebialused; Seebikarbid ja -kotid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Talous- ja keittiövälineet ja -astiat; Kammat ja pesusienet; Luonnon sienet; Harjat, hammasharjat; Saippuatelineet ja saippua-astiat; Säilytysastiat ja -pussit saippualle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Ustensiles et récipients à usage domestique et pour le ménage; Peignes et éponges; Éponges naturelles; Brosses, brosses à dents; Porte-savons; Boîtes et sachets de conservation pour le savon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pribor i posuđe za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju; Češljevi i spužve; Prirodne spužve; Četke, četkice za zube; Držači za sapun; Spremnici i vrećice za sapun.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Eszközök, edények és tartályok háztartási és konyhai célokra; Fésűk és szivacsok; Természetes szivacsok; Kefék, fogkefék; Szappantartók; Tároló dobozok és zacskók szappan számára.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Utensili e recipienti per la casa; Pettini e spugne; Spugne naturali; Spazzole, spazzolini da denti; Portasapone; Vaschette e sacchetti portasapone.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Buitiniai ir namų apyvokos reikmenys ir indai; Šukos ir kempinės; Natūralios kempinės; Šepečiai, dantų šepetukai; Muilinės; Muilo laikymo indai ir maišeliai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mājas un mājsaimniecības piederumi un tilpnes; Ķemmes un sūkļi; Dabīgie sūkļi; Birstes, zobu birstes; Ziepju trauki/ ziepju turētāji; Ziepju uzglabāšanas trauciņi un maisiņi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Għodda u kontenituri domestiċi u tad-dar; Pettnijiet u sponoż; Sponoż naturali; Xkupilji, xkupilji tas-snien; Sapunieri/kontenitur għas-sapun; Kontenituri tal-ħżin u basktijiet għas-sapun.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Gerei en vaatwerk voor de huishouding; kammen en sponzen; natuurlijke sponzen; borstels, tandenborstels; zeephouders, zeepbakjes; bewaarbakjes en -zakjes voor zeep.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przybory kuchenne i gospodarstwa domowego oraz pojemniki; Grzebienie i gąbki; Naturalne gąbki; Szczotki, szczoteczki do zębów; Mydelniczki/mydelniczki; Pojemniki i saszetki na mydło.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Utensílios e recipientes para uso doméstico e para o lar; Pentes e esponjas; Esponjas naturais; Escovas, escovas dos dentes; Suportes para sabão/saboneteiras; Recipientes e bolsas para armazenamento de sabão.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ustensile si recipiente casnice si de menaj; Piepteni şi bureţi; Bureți naturali; Perii, periuţe de dinţi; Suporturi pentru săpun/vase pentru săpun; Recipiente și săculețe de păstrare pentru săpun.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Domáce potreby a nádoby; Hrebene a špongie; Prírodné špongie; Kefy, zubné kefky; Držiaky na mydlo, misky na mydlo; Nádoby a vrecká na ukladanie mydiel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Gospodinjski pripomočki in posode; Glavniki in gobe; Naravne gobe; Ščetke, zobne ščetke; Držala za milo/posode za milo; Posode za shranjevanje in vrečke za milo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Redskap och behållare för hem och hushåll; Kammar och tvättsvampar; Natursvampar; Borstar, tandborstar; Tvålhållare/koppar för tvålar; Tvålfat och -påsar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Реклама; Управление на търговски сделки; Търговска администрация; Административна дейност; Издаване на рекламни печатни материали; Разпространение на рекламни материали; Промоционални дейности; Рекламиране и рекламни услуги; Консултиране относно фирмената организация, икономика и администрация; Маркетингови услуги; Пазарно проучване, пазарно изследване и пазарен анализ; Търговско посредничество при покупко-продажба, внос и износ, както и търговия на едро и дребно със сапуни, парфюмерия, етерични масла, козметични средства, лосиони за коса, козметични и почистващи средства за тяло и коса, сапун за тяло, шампоан, в т.ч. под формата на шампоан бар, средства за почистване на зъби, паста за зъби; Търговско посредничество при покупко-продажба, внос и износ, както и търговия на едро и дребно с домакински прибори и съдове, гребени и гъби, естествени гъби, четки, четки за зъби, държачи за сапун, чинии за сапун, контейнери за съхранение на сапун и торбички за сапуни; Търговска информация; Организиране на събития за търговски и рекламни цели; Съставяне и управление на бази данни; Консултации и информация относно горепосочените услуги; Горепосочени услуги също предоставени чрез електронни мрежи като интернет.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Propagační činnost, reklama; Pomoc při řízení obchodní činnosti; Obchodní administrativa; Kancelářské práce; Vydávání reklamních tiskárenských výrobků; Distribuce reklamních materiálů; Propagační činnosti; Propagace; Podnikově-organizační, podnikově-ekonomické a podnikově-administrativní poradenství; Marketing; Marketing, průzkum a analýzy trhu; Komerčně-obchodní zprostředkování nákupu a prodeje, dovozu a vývozu a velkoobchodních a maloobchodních služeb, týkající se výrobků, jako jsou mýdla, parfumerie, éterické oleje, kosmetické přípravky, vlasová tonika, kosmetické a čisticí prostředky pro tělo a vlasy, mýdla na tělo, šampony, včetně ve formě tuhých šamponů, prostředky na čištění zubů, zubní pasty; Komerčně-obchodní zprostředkování nákupu a prodeje, dovozu a vývozu a velkoobchodních a maloobchodních služeb, týkající se výrobků, jako jsou pomůcky a nádoby do domácnost, hřebeny a houby na mytí, přírodní houby na mytí, kartáče, zubní kartáčky, misky na mýdlo, krabičky na mýdlo, nádobky a pytlíky na uchovávání mýdla; Poskytování komerčních informací; Organizování akcí pro komerční a reklamní účely; Sestavování a správa datových souborů; Poradenství a poskytování informací týkající se výše uvedených služeb; Výše uvedené služby poskytované také prostřednictvím elektronických sítí, jako je internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed; Forretningsledelse; Forretningsadministration; Varetagelse af kontoropgaver; Udgivelse af reklametryksager; Distribution af reklame- og annoncemateriale; Salgsfremmende aktiviteter; Reklamevirksomhed; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsorganisation, virksomhedsøkonomi og virksomhedsadministration; Marketing; Markedsbearbejdelse, markedsundersøgelse og markedsanalyse; Kommerciel og forretningsmæssig formidling ved køb og salg, import og eksport samt engros- og detailhandel vedrørende sæbe, parfumerivarer, æteriske olier, kosmetiske midler, hårlotioner, kosmetiske og rensende midler til krop og hår, sæbe til kroppen, shampoo, inklusive i form af en shampoo-bar, midler til tandrensning, tandpasta; Kommerciel og forretningsmæssig formidling ved køb og salg, import og eksport samt engros- og detailhandel vedrørende redskaber og beholdere til husholdningen, kamme og svampe, naturlige vaskesvampe, børster, tandbørster, sæbeholdere, sæbeskåle, opbevaringsskåle og -poster til sæbe; Tilvejebringelse af kommerciel information; Organisering af arrangementer med kommercielle og reklamemæssige formål; Sammensætning og styring af databaser; Rådgivning og information vedrørende førnævnte tjenesteydelser; Førnævnte tjenesteydelser ydes også via elektroniske netværk såsom internettet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Werbung; Geschäftsführung; Unternehmensverwaltung; Büroarbeiten; Herausgabe von Werbedrucksachen; Verbreitung von Werbematerial; Verkaufsfördernde Aktivitäten; Werbung; Beratung bei der Organisation und Führung von Unternehmen sowie betriebsverwaltungstechnische Beratung; Marketing; Marktbearbeitung, -forschung und -analyse; Vermittlungsdienste in Geschäftsangelegenheiten beim Ankauf und Verkauf, Import und Export sowie Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Seifen, Parfümeriewaren, ätherische Öle, Kosmetika, Haarlotionen, Kosmetika und Reinigungsmittel für Körper und Haar, Körperseife, Shampoo, einschließlich in Form von festem Shampoo, Zahnputzmittel, Zahnpasta; Vermittlungsdienste in Geschäftsangelegenheiten beim Ankauf und Verkauf, Import und Export sowie Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Geräte und Behälter für Haushalt und Küche, Kämme und Schwämme, Meerschwämme, Bürsten, Zahnbürsten, Seifenspender, Seifenhalter, Seifendosen und -beutel; Auskünfte über den Warenverkehr; Organisation von Veranstaltungen zu Reklame- und Werbezwecken; Zusammenstellung und Verwaltung von Dateien; Beratung und Informationen in Bezug auf die vorstehend genannten Dienstleistungen; Vorstehend genannte Dienstleistungen auch über elektronische Netze wie das Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαφήμιση· Διοίκηση επιχειρήσεων· Διαχείριση επιχειρήσεων· Εργασίες γραφείου· Έκδοση διαφημιστικού έντυπου υλικού· Διανομή διαφημιστικού υλικού· Προωθητικές ενέργειες· Διαφήμιση· Παροχή συμβουλών σε θέματα οργάνωσης επιχειρήσεων, οικονομικών των επιχειρήσεων και διοίκησης επιχειρήσεων· Υπηρεσίες μάρκετινγκ· Επεξεργασία, έρευνα και ανάλυση αγοράς· Εμπορική-επιχειρηματική διαμεσολάβηση κατά την αγορά και πώληση, τις εισαγωγές και εξαγωγές, καθώς και υπηρεσίες χονδρικού και λιανικού εμπορίου σε σχέση με τα εξής προϊόντα: σαπούνια, είδη αρωματοποιίας, αιθέρια έλαια, καλλυντικά, λοσιόν για τα μαλλιά, καλλυντικά προϊόντα και προϊόντα καθαρισμού για το σώμα και τα μαλλιά, σαπούνι για το σώμα, σαμπουάν, μεταξύ άλλων με τη μορφή μπάρας σαμπουάν, οδοντοσκευάσματα, οδοντόκρεμες· Εμπορική-επιχειρηματική διαμεσολάβηση κατά την αγορά και πώληση, τις εισαγωγές και εξαγωγές, καθώς και υπηρεσίες χονδρικού και λιανικού εμπορίου σε σχέση με τα εξής προϊόντα: μικρά σκεύη και δοχεία οικιακής και μαγειρικής χρήσης, χτένια και σφουγγάρια, φυσικά σφουγγάρια, βούρτσες, οδοντόβουρτσες, σαπουνοθήκες, υποδοχές για σαπούνια, κουτιά και σακουλάκια φύλαξης για σαπούνι· Παροχή εμπορικών πληροφοριών· Οργάνωση εκδηλώσεων για εμπορικούς διαφημιστικούς σκοπούς· Σύσταση και διαχείριση αρχείων δεδομένων· Παροχή συμβουλών και πληροφοριών σχετικά με τις προαναφερθείσες υπηρεσίες· Οι προαναφερθείσες υπηρεσίες παρεχόμενες επίσης μέσω ηλεκτρονικών δικτύων, όπως το Διαδίκτυο.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Advertising; Business management; Business administration; Office functions; Publication of advertising texts; Distribution of advertising material; Promotional activities; Advertising; Business organisation, business economic and business administration consultancy; Marketing services; Market canvassing, market research and market analysis; Business mediation in the purchase and sale, import and export, and wholesaling and retailing of soaps, perfumery, essential oils, cosmetics, hair lotions, cosmetics and cleansing preparations for the body and hair, body soap, shampoo, including in the form of a shampoo bar, dentifrices, toothpaste; Business mediation in the purchase and sale, import and export, and wholesaling and retailing of household utensils and containers, combs and sponges, natural sponges, brushes [except paintbrushes], toothbrushes, dishes for soap, soap holders, soap storage containers and bags; Provision of commercial information; Organisation of events for commercial and advertising purposes; Compilation and management of data files; Consultancy and information regarding the aforesaid services; The aforesaid services also provided via electronic networks, such as the Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicidad; Gestión de negocios comerciales; Administración comercial; Trabajos de oficina; Edición de impresos publicitarios; Distribución de material publicitario; Servicios de anuncios; Publicidad; Asesoramiento en materia de organización de empresas, economía empresarial y administración empresarial; Servicios de marketing; Prospección, estudio y análisis de mercados; Mediación comercial y empresarial para la compra y venta, la importación y exportación, así como para servicios de comercio mayorista y minorista en relación con jabones, artículos de perfumería, aceites esenciales, productos cosméticos, lociones capilares, productos cosméticos y de limpieza para el cuerpo y el cabello, jabón para el cuerpo, champú, incluyendo en forma de barra de champú, dentífricos, pasta dentífrica; Mediación comercial y empresarial para la compra y venta, importación y exportación, así como para servicios de comercio minorista y mayorista de utensilios y recipientes para el hogar, peines y esponjas, esponjas naturales, cepillos, cepillos de dientes, soportes para jabón, jaboneras, recipientes y bolsas para conservar el jabón; Provisión de información comercial; Servicios de organización de eventos con fines comerciales y promociones; Composición y gestión de bases de datos; Asesoramiento e información sobre los servicios mencionados; Los servicios mencionados suministrados también a través de redes electrónicas, como Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Reklaam; Ärijuhtimine; Ärikorraldus; Kontoriteenused; Reklaamtrükiste väljaandmine; Reklaammaterjalide levitamine; Müügiedendus; Reklaam; Ärijuhtimise ja -majanduse ja -halduse alased konsultatsioonid; Turundus; Turundus, turu-uuringud ja turuanalüüs; Ärivahendus, sh jae- ja hulgimüügiteenused järgmiste kaupade ostu, müügi, impordi ja ekspordi alal: seebid, parfümeeriatooted, eeterlikud õlid, kosmeetikavahendid, juukseveed, kosmeetilised puhastusvahendid kehale ja juustele, kehaseebid, šampoonid, sh tahked šampoonid, hambapuhastusained, hambapasta; Ärivahendus, sh jae- ja hulgimüügiteenused järgmiste kaupade ostu, müügi, impordi ja ekspordi alal: majapidamistarbed ja -nõud, kammid ja käsnad, looduslikud käsnad, harjad, hambaharjad, seebialused, seebikarbid ja -kotid; Kaubandusinfo; Kaubandus- ja reklaamürituste korraldamine; Andmebaaside koostamine ja haldamine; Eespool nimetatud teenustega seotud info ja nõustamine; Eespool nimetatud teenused, mida pakutakse ka elektrooniliste võrkude, nagu Interneti kaudu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Mainonta; Liikkeenjohto; Yrityshallinto; Toimistotehtävät; Mainospainotuotteiden julkaisu; Mainosmateriaalin jakelu; Myynninedistämistoimet; Mainonta; Yritysorganisatorinen, yritystaloudellinen ja yrityshallinnollinen neuvonta; Markkinointipalvelut; Markkinointi, markkinatutkimus ja -analyysi; Kaupallis-liiketoiminnallinen välitys seuraavien oston, myynnin, tuonnin ja viennin alalla sekä niihin liittyvät tukku- ja vähittäiskauppapalvelut: saippuat, hajuvedet, eteeriset öljyt, kosmeettiset valmisteet, hiusvedet, kosmeettiset ja puhdistusaineet keholle ja hiuksille, saippua keholle, shampoo, mukaan lukien shampoopalan muodossa, hampaidenpuhdistusaineet, hammastahna; Kaupallis-liiketoiminnallinen välitys seuraavien oston, myynnin, tuonnin ja viennin alalla sekä niihin liittyvät tukku- ja vähittäiskauppapalvelut: kotitalousvälineet ja astiat, kammat ja sienet, luonnolliset sienet, harjat, hammasharjat, saippuatelineet, saippuakupit, säilytysastiat ja -pussit saippualle; Kaupallisten tietojen tarjonta; Tapahtumien järjestäminen kaupallisiin tai mainontatarkoituksiin; Tietokantojen kokoaminen ja hallinta; Edellä mainittuihin palveluihin liittyvä neuvonta ja tiedotus; Edellä mainitut palvelut tarjotaan myös sähköisten verkkojen, kuten Internetin kautta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publicité; Gestion des affaires commerciales; Administration commerciale; Travaux de bureau; Édition d'imprimés publicitaires; Services de distribution de matériel publicitaire; Activités promotionnelles; Publicité; Conseils en organisation, économie et administration des entreprises; Services de marketing; Prospection de marché, étude et analyse de marché; Médiation commerciale et professionnelle pour l'achat et la vente, l'importation et l'exportation ainsi que services de vente en gros et au détail de savons, produits de parfumerie, huiles essentielles, produits cosmétiques, lotions pour les cheveux, produits cosmétiques et nettoyants pour le corps et les cheveux, savon pour le corps, shampooings, y compris sous la forme de shampooings solides, produits d’hygiène dentaire, dentifrices; Médiation commerciale et professionnelle pour l'achat et la vente, l'importation et l'exportation ainsi que services de vente en gros et au détail d’ustensiles et récipients pour le ménage, de peignes et éponges, d'éponges naturelles, de brosses, de brosses à dents, de porte-savon, de supports à savon, de boîtes et sachets de conservation pour le savon; Mise à disposition d'informations commerciales; Organisation d'événements à des fins commerciales et publicitaires; Composition et gestion de bases de données; Conseils et informations concernant les services précités; Services précités également fournis par l’intermédiaire de réseaux électroniques, comme l’internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Oglašavanje; Vođenje komercijalnih poslova; Komercijalna administracija; Uredski poslovi; Objavljivanje reklamnih tekstova; Distribucija reklamnih materijala; Promotivne akcije; Oglašavanje; Savjeti o organizaciji i vođenju poslova; Marketing; Proučavanje, istraživanje i analiza tržišta; Komercijalno-poslovno posredovanje u vezi s kupnjom i prodajom, uvozom i izvozom, kao i usluge veleprodaje i maloprodaje u vezi sa sapunima, parfimerijskim proizvodima, eteričnim uljima, kozmetičkim sredstvima, losionima za kosu, kozmetikom i sredstvima za čišćenje za tijelo i kosu, sapunima za tijelo, šamponima, uključujući u obliku šampona u obliku pločica, sredstvima za pranje zuba, pastom za zube; Komercijalno-poslovno posredovanje u vezi s kupnjom i prodajom, uvozom i izvozom, kao i usluge veleprodaje i maloprodaje u vezi s priborom i posuđem za kućanstvo, češljevima i spužvama, prirodnim spužvama, četkama, četkicama za zube, držačima sapuna, posudicama za sapun, spremnicima i vrećicama za sapun; Pružanje komercijalnih informacija; Organiziranje događanja u komercijalne i reklamne svrhe; Izrada i administracija baze podataka; Savjetovanje i informacije u pogledu navedenih usluga; Navedene usluge također se pružaju putem elektroničkih mreža, poput interneta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Reklámozás; Kereskedelmi ügyletek; Kereskedelmi adminisztráció; Irodai munkák; Reklámszövegek kiadása; Reklámanyagok szétosztása; Promóciós tevékenységek; Hirdetési- és reklámszolgáltatások; Üzletvezetési, gazdasági és üzletszervezési szaktanácsadás; Marketing szolgáltatások; Marketing felmérések, piackutatás és piacanalízis; Kereskedelmi-üzleti közvetítés az alábbiak adásvétele, importja és exportja, valamint nagy- és kiskereskedelme során: szappanok, illatszerek, eszenciaolajok, kozmetikai készítmények, hajszeszek, kozmetikai és tisztítószerek a test és haj számára, testápoló szappan, sampon, azon belül sampontömb formájában, fogtisztító szerek, fogkrém; Kereskedelmi-üzleti közvetítés az alábbiak adásvétele, importja és exportja, valamint nagy- és kiskereskedelme során: háztartási vagy konyhai edények és eszközök, fésűk és szivacsok, természetes szivacsok, kefék, fogkefék, szappantartók, szappantartó tálak, tároló dobozok és zacskók szappan számára; Kereskedelmi információk szolgáltatása; Kereskedelmi és reklámcélú rendezvények szervezése; Adatállományok összeállítása és kezelése; Szaktanácsadás és információnyújtás az előbb felsorolt szolgáltatásokkal kapcsolatban; Az előbb felsorolt szolgáltatások nyújtása elektronikus hálózatokon, úgymint interneten keresztül is.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pubblicità; Gestione di affari commerciali; Amministrazione commerciale; Lavori di ufficio; Pubblicazione di stampati pubblicitari; Distribuzione di materiale pubblicitario; Attività promozionali; Pubblicità; Consulenza in materia d'organizzazione, gestione economica e amministrazione aziendale; Marketing; Ricerche, analisi e interventi sul mercato; Mediazione commerciale per acquisto e vendita, importazione ed esportazione, nonché vendita all'ingrosso e al dettaglio di saponi, prodotti di profumeria, oli essenziali, preparati cosmetici, lozioni per i capelli, prodotti detergenti e cosmetici per il corpo e i capelli, sapone per il corpo, shampoo, anche sotto forma di confezione di shampoo, dentifrici; Mediazione commerciale per acquisto e vendita, importazione ed esportazione, nonché vendita all'ingrosso e al dettaglio di utensili e recipienti per uso domestico, pettini e spugne, spugne naturali, spazzole, spazzolini, erogatori di sapone, contenitori di sapone, vaschette e sacchetti portasapone; Fornitura di informazioni commerciali; Organizzazione di eventi a scopo commerciale e pubblicitario; Creazione e gestione d'archivi di dati; Consulenza e informazioni in materia dei suddetti servizi; I suddetti servizi anche offerti su reti elettroniche, quali Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Reklama; Verslo vadyba; Verslo tvarkyba; Įstaigų veikla; Reklaminių spaudinių leidyba; Reklaminės medžiagos platinimas; Pardavimų skatinimo veikla; Reklama; Įmonės veiklos organizavimo, įmonės ekonominės veiklos ir įmonės administravimo konsultacijos; Rinkodara; Rinkos agitacija, rinkos tyrimai ir rinkos analizė; Komercinis verslo tarpininkavimas perkant ir parduodant, importuojant ir eksportuojant, taip pat didmeninės ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos tokių prekių kaip muilai, parfumerija, eteriniai aliejai, kosmetika, plaukų losjonai, kosmetika ir kūno ir plaukų valymo priemonės, kūno muilas, šampūnas, taip pat šampūno pavidalo, dantų pastos, dantų pastos pavidalu; Komercinis verslo tarpininkavimas perkant ir parduodant, importuojant ir eksportuojant, taip pat didmeninės ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos tokių prekių kaip buitiniai indai ir indai, šukos ir kempinės, natūralios kempinės, šepetėliai, dantų šepetėliai, muilo laikikliai, muilo indai, muilo indai ir paketėliai; Komercinės informacijos teikimas; Renginių organizavimas komercijos ir reklamos reikmėms; Duomenų rinkmenų sudarymas ir tvarkymas; Konsultacijos ir informacija, susijusios su aukščiau išvardytomis paslaugomis; Minėtos paslaugos, taip pat teikiamos elektroniniais tinklais, pavyzdžiui, internetu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Reklāma; Darījumu vadīšana; Uzņēmumu pārvaldīšana; Biroja darbi; Reklāmas iespieddarbu izdošana; Reklāmas materiālu izplatīšana; Veicināšanas pakalpojumi; Reklāma; Uzņēmējdarbības organizatoriskā, ekonomiskā un administratīvā konsultēšana; Tirgvedības pakalpojumi; Tirgus aģitācija, tirgus izpēte un tirgus analīze; Uzņēmējdarbības starpniecība iepērkot un pārdodot, importējot un eksportējot, kā arī vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar ziepēm, smaržām, ēteriskajām eļļām, kosmētiku, matu losjoniem, kosmētiskajiem un tīrīšanas līdzekļiem ķermenim un matiem, ķermeņa ziepēm, šampūniem, tostarp cietajiem šampūniem, zobu tīrīšanas līdzekļiem, zobu pastām; Uzņēmējdarbības starpniecība iepērkot un pārdodot, importējot un eksportējot, kā arī vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar mājsaimniecības piederumiem, ķemmēm un sūkļiem, dabīgiem sūkļiem, sukām, zobu sukām, ziepju turētājiem, ziepju traukiem, ziepju uzglabāšanas traukiem un maisiņiem; Komerciālās informācijas nodrošināšana; Pasākumu organizēšana komerciāliem un reklāmas nolūkiem; Datu bāzu izveide un pārvaldība; Ieteikumi, konsultācijas un informācija saistībā ar iepriekš minētajiem pakalpojumiem; Iepriekš minētie pakalpojumi, kas nodrošināti, izmantojot elektroniskos tīklus, kā internetu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Reklamar; Il-ġestjoni ta' negozju; L-amministrazzjoni ta' negozju; Funzjonijiet ta' uffiċċju; Il-pubblikazzjoni ta' testi tar-reklamar; Distribuzzjoni ta' materjal ta' reklamar; Attivitajiet ta' promozzjoni; Reklamar; Konsulenza dwar il-ġestjoni u l-organizzazzjoni tan-negozju, kif ukoll pariri dwar l-amministrazzjoni ta' negozju; Servizzi ta' kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Riċerka tas-suq billi thabbat il-bibien, ir-riċerka dwar is-suq u l-analiżi tas-suq; Medjazzjoni kummerċjali ta' negozju fix-xiri u bejgħ, importazzjoni u esportazzjoni, kif ukoll servizzi tal-bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut ta' sapun, fwejjaħ, żjut essenzjali, preparazzjonijiet kożmetiċi, lozjonijiet tax-xagħar, prodotti kosmetiċi u tat-tindif tal-ġisem u x-xagħar, sapun tal-ġisem, xampù, inkluż fil-forma ta' sapun bħala xampù, preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif, dentifriċi; Medjazzjoni kummerċjali tan-negozju fix-xiri u bejgħ, importazzjoni u esportazzjoni, kif ukoll servizzi tal-bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut ta' utensili u kontenituri oħra għad-dar, pettnijiet u sponoż, sponoż naturali, xkupilji, xkupilji tas-snien, dispensers tas-sapun, ħowlders tas-sapun, kontenituri tal-ħżin u boroż għas-sapun; Il-provvista ta' informazzjoni kummerċjali; L-organizzazzjoni ta' avvenimenti għal skopijiet kummerċjali u ta' reklamar; Ġabra flimkien u ġestjoni ta' dejtabejżis; Servizzi ta' konsulenza u informazzjoni dwar is-servizzi msemmija; Is-servizzi msemmija qabel anke provduti permezz ta' netwerks elettroniċi bħalma hu l-Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reclame; beheer van commerciële zaken; zakelijke administratie; administratieve diensten; uitgeven van reclamedrukwerken; verspreiding van reclamemateriaal; promotionele activiteiten; publiciteit; bedrijfsorganisatorische, bedrijfseconomische en bedrijfsadministratieve advisering; marketing; marktbewerking, marktonderzoek en marktanalyse; commercieel-zakelijke bemiddeling bij de aankoop en verkoop, de import en export, alsmede groot- en detailhandelsdiensten betreffende zepen, parfumerieën, etherische oliën, cosmetische middelen, haarlotions, cosmetische- en reinigende middelen voor lichaam en haar, zeep voor het lichaam, shampoo, waaronder in de vorm van een shampoo bar, tandreinigingsmiddelen, tandpasta; commercieel-zakelijke bemiddeling bij de aankoop en verkoop, de import en export, alsmede groot- en detailhandelsdiensten betreffende gerei en vaatwerk voor de huishouding, kammen en sponzen, natuurlijke sponzen, borstels, tandenborstels, zeephouders, zeepbakjes, bewaarbakjes en -zakjes voor zeep; handelsinformatie; organisatie van evenementen voor publicitaire en/of commerciële doeleinden; samenstellen en beheren van gegevensbestanden; advisering, voorlichting en informatie inzake voornoemde diensten; voornoemde diensten tevens via elektronische netwerken, zoals internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Reklama; Zarządzanie w działalności gospodarczej; Administrowanie działalności gospodarczej; Prace biurowe; Publikowanie tekstów reklamowych; Dystrybucja materiałów reklamowych; Działania promocyjne; Reklama; Doradztwo w zakresie organizowania, prowadzenia, administracji działalności gospodarczej; Usługi marketingowe; Sondowanie rynku, badania rynkowe i analiza rynku; Pośrednictwo handlowe przy zakupie i sprzedaży, imporcie i eksporcie, jak również usługach handlu hurtowego i detalicznego w zakresie takich towarów, jak mydła, perfumy, olejki eteryczne, kosmetyki, emulsje do włosów, kosmetyki i środki myjące do ciała i włosów, mydło do ciała, szampon, w tym w postaci szamponu w kostce, środki do czyszczenia zębów, pasta do zębów; Pośrednictwo handlowe przy zakupie i sprzedaży, imporcie i eksporcie, jak również usługach handlu hurtowego i detalicznego w zakresie takich towarów, jak przybory i naczynia do gospodarstwa domowego, grzebienie i gąbki, naturalne gąbki, szczotki, szczoteczki do zębów, mydelniczki, mydelniczki, pojemniki i saszetki na mydło; Dostarczanie informacji handlowych; Organizowanie imprez w celach handlowych i reklamowych; Gromadzenie plików danych i zarządzanie nimi; Doradztwo i usługi informacyjne w zakresie wyżej wymienionych usług; Uprzednio wymienione usługi świadczone także przez sieci elektroniczne, takie jak Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicidade; Gestão de negócios comerciais; Administração comercial; Trabalhos de escritório; Edição de produtos de impressão publicitários; Distribuição de materiais publicitários; Atividades promocionais; Serviços publicitários; Serviços de assessores para a organização de negócios, para a economia de negócios e para a administração de negócios; Serviços de marketing; Prospeção, pesquisa e análise de mercado; Mediação comercial profissional na compra e venda, importação e exportação, bem como serviços de comércio grossista e retalhista relacionados com sabões, perfumaria, óleos essenciais, cosméticos, loções para os cabelos, produtos cosméticos e de limpeza para o corpo e os cabelos, sabão para o corpo, champô, incluindo sob a forma de champô em barra, dentífricos, pastas dentífricas; Mediação comercial profissional na compra e venda, importação e exportação, bem como serviços de comércio grossista e retalhista de utensílios e recipientes para uso doméstico, pentes e esponjas, esponjas naturais, escovas, escovas de dentes, saboneteiras, recipientes para sabonetes, recipientes e bolsas para armazenamento de sabão; Fornecimento de informação comercial; Organização de eventos com fins comerciais e publicitários; Composição e gestão de bases de dados; Serviços de consultadoria e informação referentes os serviços atrás referidos; Os serviços atrás referidos também prestados através de redes eletrónicas, tais como a Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicitate; Gestiunea afacerilor comerciale; Administraţie comercială; Lucrări de birou; Editare a produselor de imprimerie publicitare; Distribuire de materiale publicitare; Activităţi promoţionale; Publicitate; Consultanţă privind organizarea, economia şi administrarea întreprinderilor; Servicii de marketing; Prospectare pe piaţă, cercerate de piaţă şi analiză de piaţă; Intermediere comercial-profesională la achiziția și vânzarea, importul și exportul, precum și servicii de vânzare cu ridicata și cu amănuntul cu privire la săpunuri, parfumerie, uleiuri esențiale, cosmetice, loțiuni pentru păr, produse cosmetice și de curățare pentru corp și păr, săpun de corp, șampon, inclusiv sub formă de șampon solid, produse pentru îngrijirea dinților, pastă de dinți; Intermediere comercial-profesională la achiziția și vânzarea, importul și exportul, precum și servicii de vânzare cu ridicata și cu amănuntul cu privire la ustensile și recipiente pentru menaj și bucătărie, piepteni și bureți, bureți naturali, perii, periuțe de dinți, dozatoare de săpun, săpuniere, recipiente și săculeți de păstrare pentru săpun; Furnizarea de informaţii comerciale; Organizare de evenimente în scopuri comerciale şi publicitare; Alcătuire şi gestionare a fişierelor de date; Consultanţă şi informaţii privind serviciile menţionate anterior; Serviciile menţionate anterior, furnizate de asemenea prin intermediul reţelelor electronice, precum Internetul.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reklamné služby; Obchodný manažment, obchodná správa; Obchodná administratíva; Kancelárske práce; Vydávanie reklamných tlačovín; Šírenie reklamných materiálov; Propagačné služby; Reklama; Organizačné, komerčné a administratívne poradenstvo súvisiace s podnikaním; Marketing; Vyhľadávanie zákaziek (canvassing), prieskum trhu a analýza trhu; Komerčno-obchodné sprostredkovanie pri kúpe a predaji, dovoze a vývoze, ako aj veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby v súvislosti s mydlami, voňavkárskymi výrobkami, éterickými olejmi, kozmetickými prípravkami, vlasovými vodičkami, kozmetickými a čistiacimi prípravkami na telo a vlasy, mydlami na telom, šampónmi vrátane vo forme tuhých šampónov, prípravkami na čistenie zubov, zubnými pastami; Komerčno-obchodné sprostredkovanie pri kúpe a predaji, dovoze a vývoze, ako aj veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby v súvislosti s domácimi potrebami a nádobami, hrebeňmi a špongiami, prírodnými špongiami, kefami, zubnými kefkami, držiakmi mydla, nádobkami na mydlo, nádobami a vreckami na ukladanie mydiel; Poskytovanie komerčných informácií; Organizovanie podujatí na obchodné alebo reklamné účely; Zostavovanie a správa databáz; Poradenstvo a informácie súvisiace s vyššie uvedenými službami; Vyššie uvedené služby tiež ponúkané aj prostredníctvom elektronických sietí ako je internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oglasna dejavnost; Vodenje komercialnih poslov; Poslovna administracija; Pisarniški posli; Izdajanje oglasnih besedil; Distribucija oglasnega materiala; Promocijske dejavnosti; Oglaševanje in oglaševalske storitve; Poslovno organizacijsko, poslovno ekonomsko in poslovno administrativno svetovanje; Storitve trženja; Tržne ankete, raziskave in analize; Komercialno-poslovno posredovanje pri nakupu in prodaji, uvozu in izvozu, kot tudi storitvah veleprodaje in maloprodaje v zvezi z izdelki, kot so mila, parfumerijski izdelki, eterična olja, kozmetična sredstva, losjoni za lase, kozmetična in čistilna sredstva za telo in lase, milo za telo, šamponi, vključno v obliki tablice šampona, sredstva za čiščenje zob, zobne paste; Komercialno-poslovno posredovanje pri nakupu in prodaji, uvozu in izvozu, kot tudi storitvah veleprodaje in maloprodaje v zvezi z izdelki, kot so pripomočki in posode za gospodinjstvo, glavniki in gobice, naravne gobe, krtače, zobne ščetke, nosilci za milo, posode za milo, posode za shranjevanje in vrečke za milo; Zagotavljanje komercialnih informacij; Organizacija dogodkov za komercialne in oglasne namene; Sestavljanje in vodenje podatkovnih baz; Svetovanje in informacije v zvezi z omenjenimi storitvami; Omenjene storitve, nudene prek elektronskih omrežij, kot internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Annons- och reklamverksamhet; Företagsledning; Företagsadministration; Kontorstjänster; Utgivning av reklamtrycksaker; Distribution av annons- och reklammaterial; Annonseringsverksamhet; Reklam; Konsultverksamhet avseende företagsorganisation, företagsekonomi och företagsledning; Marknadsföringstjänster; Marknadsbearbetning, marknadsundersökning och marknadsanalys; Kommersiell affärsförmedling vid köp och försäljning, import och export samt parti- och detaljhandelstjänster avseende tvålar, parfymerivaror, eteriska oljor, kosmetiska medel, hårlotioner, kosmetiska medel och rengöringsmedel för kropp och hår tandpulver, tvålar för kroppen, schampon, inklusive i form av schampokakor, tandrengöringsmedel, tandpastor; Kommersiell affärsförmedling vid köp och försäljning, import och export samt parti- och detaljhandelstjänster avseende redskap och behållare för hushållsändamål, kammar och svampar, natursvampar, borstar, tandborstar, tvålhållare, tvålfat- och -påsar; Kommersiell information; Anordnande av tillställningar för kommersiella- och reklamändamål; Sammanställning och hantering av datafiler; Rådgivning och information avseende nämnda tjänster; Nämnda tjänster även för upplåtande via elektroniska nät, såsom Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/099</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-27</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/169</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>934132</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>18322</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
