<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:43</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224424</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224424</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Roluck</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Еротични кукли [секс кукли]; Секс играчки; Изкуствени гърди [бюст]; Вагинални помпи; Торбички за интимен душ; Презервативи; Уретрални сонди; Помощни средства за сексуална стимулация за възрастни; Вибратори като помощни сексуални пособия за възрастни.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nafukovací panny [erotické pomůcky]; Erotické hračky; Umělá poprsí; Vaginální stříkačky; Nádoby na vaginální výplachy; Kondomy; Uretrální sondy; Sexuální pomůcky pro dospělé; Vibrátory jako sexuální pomůcky pro dospělé.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sexdukker; Sexlegetøj; Brystproteser; Vaginalsprøjter; Poser til udskyldning; Kondomer; Urinrørskateter; Hjælpemidler til seksuel stimulering til brug for voksne; Vibratorer i form af seksuelle hjælpemidler til voksne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Sexpuppen; Sexspielzeug; Brustprothesen; Vaginalspritzen; Intimduschen; Präservative [Kondome]; Harnröhrensonden; Hilfsmittel für die sexuelle Stimulierung für Erwachsene; Vibratoren als sexuelle Hilfsmittel für Erwachsene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κούκλες ως σεξουαλικά παιχνίδια· Σεξουαλικά παιχνίδια· Τεχνητές προσθήκες στήθους· Κολπικές (Σύριγγες -)· Ασκοί κολπικών πλύσεων· Προφυλακτικά· Ουρήθρας (Καθετήρες -)· Βοηθήματα για σεξουαλική διέγερση ενηλίκων· Δονητές, ως σεξουαλικά βοηθήματα για ενήλικες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Love dolls [sex dolls]; Sex toys; Artificial breasts; Vaginal syringes; Douche bags; Condoms; Urethral probes; Adult sexual aids; Vibrators, being adult sexual aids.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Muñecas eróticas [muñecas sexuales]; Juguetes sexuales; Prótesis mamarias; Jeringas vaginales; Bolsas para lavados internos; Preservativos; Sondas uretrales; Artículos de estimulación sexual para adultos; Vibradores, como ayuda sexual para adultos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Armunukud [seksnukud]; Sekslelud; Rinnaproteesid; Vaginaalsüstlad, tupesüstlad; Loputus- või klistiiripritsid; Kondoomid, preservatiivid; Uroloogilised sondid; Täiskasvanute seksuaalse stimulatsiooni abivahendid; Vibraatorid täiskasvanute seksiabiseadmetena.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Seksinuket; Seksilelut; Tekorinnat; Emätinneulat [-ruiskut]; Huuhteluvälineet intiimikäyttöön; Kondomit; Virtsaputkikoettimet; Aikuisten seksuaaliseen stimulointiin tarkoitetut apuvälineet; Hieromasauvat aikuisten seksiapuvälineinä.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Poupées érotiques [poupées sexuelles]; Jouets sexuels; Seins artificiels; Seringues vaginales; Poches pour lavages internes; Préservatifs; Sondes urétrales; Articles de stimulation sexuelle pour adultes; Vibromasseurs en tant qu'accessoires sexuels pour adultes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Lutke za odrasle [erotske]; Seksualne igračke; Umjetne dojke; Vaginalne šprice; Vrećice za vaginalno ispiranje; Kondomi; Ureterske sonde; Seksualna pomagala za odrasle; Vibratori, kao seksualna pomagala za odrasle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szexbabák; Szexuális játékszerek; Műmellek; Hüvelyi [vaginális] fecskendők; Hüvely irrigátorok; Óvszerek; Húgycső szondák; Felnőtteknek szánt szexuális segédeszközök; Vibrátorok mint felnőtt szexuális segédeszközök.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Bambole erotiche [bambole per il sesso]; Giocattoli del sesso [sex toys]; Seni artificiali; Siringhe vaginali; Irrigatori per lavande interne; Preservativi; Sonde uretrali; Articoli di stimolazione sessuale per adulti; Vibratori, ovvero accessori sessuali per adulti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Meilės lėlės [sekso lėlės]; Sekso žaislai; Krūtų protezai; Makšties švirkštai; Dušo krepšeliai; Prezervatyvai; Šlaplės zondai; Suaugusiųjų seksualinio stimuliavimo pagalbinės priemonės; Vibratoriai (pagalbinės sekso priemonės suaugusiems).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Lelles seksam; Seksa rotaļlietas; Krūts protēzes; Vaginālās šļirces; Klizmu ierīces; Prezervatīvi; Urīnizvadkanāla zondes; Pieaugušo seksuālās stimulēšanas palīglīdzekļi; Vibratori, seksa palīglīdzekļi pieaugušajiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pupi għas-sess; Ġugarelli tas-sess; Sider artifiċjali; Siringi tal-vaġina; Boroż għat-tindif vaġinali; Kondoms; Sondi għall-uretra; Tagħmir ta' għajnuna ta' stimulazzjoni sesswali għall-adulti; Vibraturi, li huma għajnuniet għas-sess għall-adulti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Opblaaspoppen voor seksuele stimulatie; Seksspeeltjes; Borstprothesen; Vaginaspuiten; Zakken voor vaginale baden; Condooms; Urineleidersondes; Seksuele hulpmiddelen voor volwassen; Vibrators, zijnde seksuele hulpmiddelen voor volwassenen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Gumowe lalki [akcesoria seksualne]; Zabawki erotyczne; Sztuczne piersi; Strzykawki dopochwowe; Zestawy do irygacji; Prezerwatywy; Sondy do cewki moczowej; Środki pomocnicze do stymulacji seksualnej dla dorosłych; Wibratory jako akcesoria erotyczne dla dorosłych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Bonecas eróticas [bonecas sexuais]; Brinquedos sexuais; Seios artificiais; Seringas vaginais; Bolsas para higiene vaginal; Preservativos; Sondas uretrais; Auxiliares sexuais para adultos; Vibradores, sendo auxiliares sexuais para adultos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Păpuși gonflabile [păpuși sexuale]; Jucării erotice; Proteze mamare; Vaginale (Seringi -); Dușuri vaginale; Prezervative; Sonde uretrale; Stimulente sexuale pentru adulți; Vibratoare sub formă de accesorii sexuale pentru adulți.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nafukovacie panny; Erotické pomôcky; Umelé prsníky; Vaginálne irigátory; Vrecká na výplachy telesných dutín; Kondómy, prezervatívy; Uretrálne sondy; Pomôcky pre sexuálnu stimuláciu dospelých; Vibrátory ako erotické pomôcky pre dospelých.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Lutke za odrasle [seksualni pripomoček]; Spolni pripomočki; Umetne dojke; Vaginalne brizgalke; Vrečke za vaginalno izpiranje; Kondomi; Sonde za sečnico; Pripomočki za spolno stimulacijo, za odrasle; Vibratorji, ki so spolni pripomočki za odrasle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Erotiska dockor [sexdockor]; Sexleksaker; Bröstproteser; Vaginalsprutor; Duschpåsar för vaginalt bruk; Kondomer; Urinrörssonder; Sexuella stimuleringshjälpmedel för vuxna; Vibratorer, utgörande sexhjälpmedel för vuxna.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>26721</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
