<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:44</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224180</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224180</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>YOve</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Декоративни и художествени материали и средства; Печатни произведения; Филтри и филтриращи материали от хартия; Лепила за канцеларски цели и домашна употреба; Произведения на изкуството и фигурки от хартия и картон, както и архитектурни макети; Хартия и картон; Канцеларски и учебни материали; Чанти и изделия за пакетиране, опаковане и съхранение от хартия, картон или пластмаса; Хартиени торби за смет [за домакинска употреба]; Лопатки, изработени от картон за изхвърляне на животински екскременти; Салфетки хартия за почистване на грим; Бебешки лигавници от хартия; Хартиени знамена; Подложки за бирени чаши; Хартиени чадърчета за коктейли; Хартия за рафтове; Хартия за опаковане на храна.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nosiče a dekorační materiály a materiály pro umělce; Tiskoviny; Papírové filtrační materiály; Klovatina (lepidlo) pro kancelářské potřeby nebo pro domácnost; Umělecké předměty a figuríny z papíru a lepenky a architektonické modely; Papír a lepenka; Papírnické zboží a učební pomůcky; Pytle a balicí a obalové materiály a materiály pro skladování z papíru, lepenky nebo z plastů; Papírové sáčky na odpad (pro použití v domácnosti); Lopatky z lepenky na odklízení exkrementů domácích zvířat; Papírové odličovací ubrousky; Papírové bryndáčky pro miminka; Papírové bannery; Podtácky pod pivní sklenice; Papírové slunečníčky do koktejlů; Papír na vykládání polic; Papír na balení potravin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Materialer og medier til dekoration og kunst; Tryksager; Filtrermaterialer af papir; Gummi [klæbemiddel] til papirvarer og til husholdningsbrug; Kunstværker og statuetter af papir og pap samt arkitektmodeller; Papir og karton; Kontor- og uddannelsesartikler; Poser og artikler til emballering, indpakning og opbevaring af papir, pap eller plastic; Affaldsposer af papir til husholdningsbrug; Skovle af pap til fjernelse af kæledyrsekskrementer; Papirservietter til fjernelse af make-up; Papirhagesmække til spædbørn; Papirbannere; Bordskånere til ølkrus; Papirsparasoller til cocktails; Hyldepapir; Indpakningspapir til fødevarer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Dekorations- und Künstlerbedarfsmaterialien und -mittel; Druckereierzeugnisse; Filtermaterial aus Papier; Klebstoffe für Papier- und Schreibwaren oder für Haushaltszwecke; Kunstwerke und Figuren aus Papier oder Pappe sowie Architekturmodelle; Papier und Pappe; Papier- und Schreibwaren sowie Lehr- und Unterrichtsmittel; Taschen, Beutel und Waren für Verpackungs-, Einpack- und Ablagezwecke aus Papier, Pappe oder Kunststoff; Abfallbeutel aus Papier für Haushaltszwecke; Abfalltüten aus Pappe zur Entsorgung von Tierexkrementen; Abschminktücher aus Papier; Babylätzchen aus Papier; Banner aus Papier; Bierdeckel; Cocktailschirmchen aus Papier; Einschlagpapier; Einschlagpapier für Nahrungsmittel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υλικά και μέσα διακόσμησης και τέχνης· Έντυπο υλικό· Φίλτρα και υλικά φιλτραρίσματος από χαρτί· Κολλητικές ύλες για γραφική ύλη ή για οικιακούς σκοπούς· Έργα τέχνης και φιγούρες από χαρτί και χαρτόνι, και αρχιτεκτονικές μακέτες· Χαρτί, χαρτόνι· Γραφική ύλη και εκπαιδευτικό υλικό· Τσάντες και είδη συσκευασίας, αποθήκευσης και περιτυλίγματος από χαρτί, χαρτόνι ή πλαστικό· Χάρτινες σακούλες απορριμμάτων για οικιακή χρήση· Σέσουλες από χαρτόνι για την απόρριψη περιττωμάτων κατοικιδίων ζώων· Χαρτομάντιλα για την αφαίρεση του μακιγιάζ· Βρεφικές σαλιάρες από χαρτί· Πανό από χαρτί· Μπύρας (Σουβέρ ποτηριών -)· Χάρτινες ομπρέλες για κόκτειλ· Χαρτί επένδυσης ραφιών· Χαρτί περιτυλίγματος τροφίμων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Decoration and art materials and media; Printed matter; Filtering materials of paper; Gums [adhesives] for stationery or household purposes; Works of art and figurines of paper and cardboard, and architects' models; Paper and cardboard; Stationery and educational supplies; Bags and articles for packaging, wrapping and storage of paper, cardboard or plastics; Garbage bags of paper [for household use]; Scoops made of card for the disposal of pet excrement; Tissues of paper for removing make-up; Paper baby bibs; Banners of paper; Mats for beer glasses; Paper cocktail parasols; Shelf paper; Food-wrapping paper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Materiales para arte y decoración; Material impreso; Filtros y materiales filtrantes de papel; Gomas [colas] de papelería o para uso doméstico; Piezas de arte, figuras de papel y maquetas de arquitectos de papel y cartón; Papel y cartón; Productos de papelería y material educativo; Bolsas y artículos para empaquetar, envasar y almacenar, de papel, cartón y materias plásticas; Bolsas de basura de papel [para uso doméstico]; Palas de cartón para recoger excrementos de animales de compañía; Toallitas de papel para desmaquillar; Baberos de papel para bebés; Banderolas de papel; Posavasos para cerveza; Sombrillas de papel para cócteles; Papel de forrar; Papel de envolver alimentos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kunsti- ja dekoreerimismaterjalid ja -vahendid; Trükitooted; Paberist filtermaterjalid; Kummiliimid kantseleis või majapidamises kasutamiseks; Kunstiteosed, taiesed (Paberist ja papist) ning arhitektuursed maketid; Paber ja papp; Kantseleitarbed ja õppevahendid; Paberist, papist või plastist kotid ja muud tooted pakkimiseks ja ladustamiseks; Paberist prügikotid (majapidamises kasutamiseks); Pappkühvlid lemmikloomade väljaheidete kõrvaldamiseks; Paberist salvrätikud meigi eemaldamiseks; Imikute paberist pudipõlled; Paberist ribareklaamid; Õllekannualused; Paberist kokteilipäikesevarjud; Riiulipaberid; Toidupakkepaber.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Koriste- ja taidemateriaalit ja -välineet; Painotuotteet; Paperista tehdyt suodatinmateriaalit; Liimat toimisto- ja kotitalouskäyttöön; Paperista ja pahvista tehdyt taideteokset ja pienoisveistokset ja arkkitehtien pienoismallit; Paperi ja pahvi; Paperikauppatavarat ja opetustarvikkeet; Paperista, pahvista tai muovista tehdyt pussit ja tavarat pakkaamista, käärimistä ja säilytystä varten; Paperiset roskapussit kotitalouskäyttöön; Kartongista tehdyt lapiot lemmikkieläinten ulosteiden keräämiseen; Paperipyyhkeet ehostusaineiden poistamiseen; Paperiset leukalaput vauvoille; Paperiviirit; Alustat olutlaseille [paperia tai pahvia]; Paperiset päivänvarjot cocktaileihin; Hyllypaperi; Käärepaperi ruokaa varten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Matériaux de décoration et d'art et supports; Produits de l'imprimerie; Matériel de filtrage en papier; Gommes [colles] pour la papeterie ou le ménage; Objets d'art, figurines en papier et en carton, maquettes d'architecture; Papier et carton; Papeterie et fournitures scolaires; Sacs et articles d'emballage, d'empaquetage et de stockage en papier, carton ou plastique; Sacs-poubelles en papier à usage domestique; Spatules en carton pour ramasser les excréments d'animaux de compagnie; Lingettes en papier pour le démaquillage; Bavoirs en papier pour bébés; Bannières en papier; Dessous de chopes à bière; Parasols en papier pour cocktails; Papier à étagères; Papier pour l’emballage des aliments.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Dekoracije i umjetnički materijali i mediji; Tiskani materijali; Filtrirni materijali od papira; Ljepila za papirnate proizvode ili kućanske potrebe; Umjetnička djela i figurice od papira i kartona i arhitektonski modeli; Papir i karton; Uredski i školski pribor; Papirnate, kartonske i plastične vreče i artikli za pakiranje, zamatanje i skladištenje; Papirnate vrećice za otpad [za kućanske potrebe]; Kartonske lopatice za uklanjanje izmeta kućnog ljubimca; Ubrusi od papira za skidanje šminke; Papirnati podbradnjaci za bebe; Papirnate zastavice; Podlošci za pivo; Papirnati suncobrani za koktele; Papir za police; Papir za omatanje hrane.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Dekorációs és művészeti anyagok és hordozók; Nyomtatványok; Papírból készült szűrőanyagok; Ragasztók irodai és otthoni célokra; Művészeti alkotások és szobrocskák papírból és kartonból, építészmodellek; Papír és karton; Irodai és oktatási segédanyagok; Papírból, kartonból vagy műanyagból készült tasakok és cikkek árucikkek csomagolásához és tárolásához; Papír szemeteszsákok [háztartási használatra]; Kartonlapátok házikedvencek ürülékének eltávolítására; Sminkeltávolító papírkendők; Előkék csecsemőknek papírból; Papír feliratok, zászlók; Söröskorsó alátétek; Koktélesernyők papírból; Polcpapír; Ételcsomagoló papír.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Decorazioni, materiali e mezzi di produzione artistica; Stampati; Materiale filtrante in carta; Adesivi per la cartoleria o per uso domestico; Produzioni artistiche e statuette in carta e cartone, e plastici per architetti; Carta e cartone; Cartoleria e materiale di insegnamento; Sacche ed articoli per imballaggio, impacchettatura e immagazzinaggio di carta, cartone o plastica; Sacchetti di carta per le immondizie [per uso domestico]; Palette in cartone per lo smaltimento degli escrementi di animali domestici; Tovagliolini per struccare di carta; Bavaglini in carta per neonati; Striscioni di carta; Sottobicchieri per boccali da birra; Ombrellini di carta per cocktail; Carta per ripiani; Carta per la confezione di alimenti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Dekoravimo ir dailės medžiagos ir reikmenys; Spaudiniai; Filtravimo medžiagos [popierius]; Augaliniai klijai (raštinės ar buities reikmėms); Popieriaus, kartono meno dirbiniai ir figūrėlės bei architektūriniai modeliai; Popierius ir kartonas; Raštinės reikmenys ir mokymo priemonės; Popieriniai, kartoniniai ar plastikiniai pakavimo, vyniojimo ir laikymo maišeliai ir reikmenys; Popieriniai šiukšlių maišai [buities reikmėms]; Kartoniniai vienkartiniai kaušeliai (išmatoms išmesti); Popierinės servetėlės (grimui valytis); Popieriniai kūdikių seilinukai; Popierinės reklamjuostės; Servetėlės (alaus bokalams); Popieriniai kokteilių skėčiai; Lentynų popierius; Maisto vyniojamasis popierius.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Materiāli un līdzekļi māksliniekiem un dekoratoriem; Iespiedprodukcija; Filtru materiāli no papīra; Sveķi (līmvielas) kancelejas un mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Mākslas darbi un statuetes no papīra un kartona, arhitektūras maketi; Papīrs un kartons; Kancelejas preces un izglītojoši materiāli; Papīra, kartona vai plastmasas maisi un maisiņi (somas) iepakošanai, ietīšanai vai uzglabāšanai; Atkritumu maisi no papīra [mājsaimniecības nolūkiem]; Kartona liekšķeres mājdzīvnieku ekskrementu savākšanai; Papīra salvetes dekoratīvās kosmētikas noņemšanai; Papīra krūšautiņi bērniem; Papīra reklāmplakāti; Alus kausu un glāžu paliktņi; Kokteiļu lietussardziņi; Papīrs ieklāšanai plauktos; Papīrs pārtikas iesaiņošanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Materjali tad-dekorazzjoni u l-arti u l-midja; Materjal stampat; Materjali filtranti tal-karta; Adeżivi għal skopijiet ta' kartolerija jew domestiku; Xogholijiet tal-arti u figurini tal-karti u l-kartunċin, u mudelli tal-periti; Karti u kartunċin; Forniment ta' kartolerija u oġġetti edukattivi; Basktijiet u oġġetti tal-karti, kartunċin jew plastiks għall-ippakkjar, tgeżwir u ħażna; Boroż tal-karti għaż-żibel [għall-użu domestiku]; Sassli tal-kartun biex jintużaw fir-rimi tal-ħmieġ tal-annimali domestiċi; Karta tat-tixù, għat-tneħħija tal-mejkapp; Vavalori tal-karti tat-trabi; Banners tal-karti; Metts għal taħt it-tazzi tal-birra; Umbrelel tal-karta użati mal-koktejls; Karta għall-kisi tal-ixkaffar; Karta għat-tgeżwir tal-ikel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Decoratiemateriaal en materialen voor kunst en media; Drukwerken; Filtreermateriaal van papier; Gom [lijm] voor kantoorgebruik of voor de huishouding; Kunstwerken, beeldjes en maquettes van papier en karton; Papier en karton; Kantoorbehoeften en onderwijsbenodigdheden; Zakken en artikelen voor verpakking, omwikkeling en bewaring van papier, karton of plastic; Vuilniszakken van papier voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Schepjes vervaardigd uit karton voor de verwijdering van de uitwerpselen van huisdieren; Afschminkdoekjes van papier; Babyslabbetjes van papier; Vaandels van papier; Bierviltjes; Papieren cocktailparapluutjes; Kastpapier; Voedselverpakkingspapier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Materiały i środki dla artystów i do dekoracji; Materiały drukowane; Materiały filtracyjne z papieru; Kleje do materiałów papierniczych lub do użytku domowego; Dzieła sztuki oraz figurki z papieru i kartonu, modele architektoniczne; Papier i karton; Materiały piśmienne i wyposażenie edukacyjne; Torebki oraz artykuły do pakowania i przechowywania z papieru, kartonu lub tworzyw sztucznych; Worki na śmieci z papieru [do użytku domowego]; Łopatki wykonane z kartonu do usuwania odchodów zwierząt domowych; Chusteczki papierowe do usuwania makijażu; Niemowlęce śliniaki papierowe; Transparenty z papieru; Podstawki pod kufle do piwa; Papierowe parasolki do koktaili; Papier do wykładania półek; Papier do pakowania żywności.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Materiais e utensílios para decoração e arte; Material impresso; Materiais de filtragem em papel; Adesivos para papelaria ou uso doméstico; Obras de arte e estatuetas de papel e cartão, e modelos de arquitetos; Papel e cartão; Artigos de papelaria e material escolar; Sacos e artigos para o acondicionamento, embrulho e armazenamento de papel, cartão ou matérias plásticas; Sacos para o lixo em papel [para uso doméstico]; Pás feitas de cartão para eliminação de excrementos de animais domésticos; Lenços de papel para remover maquilhagem; Babetes em papel para bebés; Estandartes em papel; Bases para copos de cerveja; Chapéus-de-sol em papel para cocktails; Papel de forrar; Papel de embrulho para alimentos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Materiale și mijloace pentru decorare și artă; Produse de imprimerie; Materiale pentru filtrare din hârtie; Adezivi; Obiecte de artă și figurine din hârtie și carton și machete arhitectonice; Hârtie și carton; Articole de papetărie și accesorii educative; Sacoșe și articole pentru ambalare, împachetare și depozitare din hârtie, carton sau plastic; Saci de gunoi din hârtie [pentru uz casnic]; Lopățele din carton pentru eliminarea excrementelor animalelor de companie; Șervețele pentru demachiat, din hârtie; Bavete din hârtie pentru bebeluși; Bannere din hârtie; Suporturi pentru halbe de bere; Umbreluțe din hârtie pentru cocteiluri; Hârtie pentru raft; Hârtie de împachetat alimente.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ozdobné a umelecké prostriedky a materiály; Tlačoviny; Filtračné materiály (papier); Lepiace gumy na kancelárske použitie alebo pre domácnosť; Umelecké diela a figúrky z papiera alebo lepenky a architektonické modely; Papier a lepenka; Papierenský tovar a učebné pomôcky; Papierové, lepenkové alebo plastové vrecia a výrobky na balenie, obaľovanie a skladovanie; Vrecká na smeti z papiera [pre domáce použitie]; Kartónové lopatky na odstraňovanie výkalov domácich zvierat; Odličovacie papierové obrúsky; Papierové podbradníky pre bábätká; Papierové stolové vlajky; Podložky pod pivové poháre; Papierové dáždniky do miešaných nápojov; Papier na vystielanie; Papier na balenie potravín.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Dekorativni in umetniški materiali in oprema; Tiskovine; Filtrirni proizvodi iz papirja; Lepila za pisarniške in gospodinjske namene; Umetniška dela in kipi iz papirja in kartona ter arhitekturne makete; Papir in lepenka; Pisalne in izobraževalne potrebščine; Vrečke in proizvodi za pakiranje, zavijanje in shranjevanje iz papirja, lepenke ali plastike; Papirnate vreče za smeti [za gospodinjsko uporabo]; Lopatke iz lepenke za odstranjevanje živalskih iztrebkov; Robčki iz papirja za odstranjevanje make-upa; Slinčki iz papirja, za dojenčke; Papirnati transparenti; Podstavki za pivske kozarce; Papirnati dežnički za koktajle; Papir za police; Papir za zavijanje hrane.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Dekorations- och konstnärsmaterial; Trycksaker; Filtreringsmaterial av papper; Gummi [bindemedel] för kontors- eller hushållsändamål; Konstföremål och figuriner av papper och kartong samt arkitektmodeller; Papper och kartong; Pappersvaror och undervisningsmaterial; Påsar och artiklar för emballering, förpackning och förvaring, av papper, kartong eller plast; Soppåsar av papper för hushållsanvändning; Skopor av papp för borttagning av exkrementer från sällskapsdjur; Pappersservetter för avsminkning; Pappershaklappar; Pappersfanor; Underlägg för ölglas; Pappersparasoller för cocktailar; Hyllpapper; Inslagspapper för livsmedel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Облекло; Украшения за глава, шапки; Обувки; Части от облекло, обувки, шапки и принадлежности за глава.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Oděvy; Pokrývky hlavy; Obuv; Části oděvů, obuvi a pokrývek hlavy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beklædningsgenstande; Hovedbeklædning; Fodtøj; Dele af beklædningsgenstande, fodtøj og hovedbeklædning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bekleidungsstücke; Kopfbedeckungen; Schuhwaren; Teile von Bekleidungsstücken, Schuhwaren und Kopfbedeckungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ενδύματα· Είδη πιλοποιίας· Υποδήματα· Μέρη ενδυμάτων, υποδημάτων και ειδών πιλοποιίας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Clothing; Headgear; Footwear; Parts of clothing, footwear and headgear.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Prendas de vestir; Artículos de sombrerería; Calzado; Partes de indumentaria, calzado y sombrerería.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Rõivad; Peakatted; Jalatsid; Rõivaste, jalatsite ja peakatete osad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatteet; Päähineet; Jalkineet; Vaatteiden, jalkineiden ja päähineiden osat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Vêtements; Chapellerie; Chaussures; Parties de vêtements, articles chaussants et articles de chapellerie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Odjeća; Pokrivala za glavu; Obuća; Dijelovi odjeće, obuće i pokrivala za glavu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ruházati cikkek; Kalapáruk; Lábbelik; Ruházat, lábbelik és fejfedők részei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Abbigliamento; Cappelleria; Calzature; Parti di abbigliamento, calzature e articoli di cappelleria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Drabužiai, apranga; Galvos apdangalai; Apavas; Drabužių, avalynės ir galvos apdangalų dalys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apģērbi; Galvassegas; Apavi; Apģērbu, apavu un galvassegu daļas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ilbies; Xedd ir-ras; Xedd is-saqajn; Partijiet minn ħwejjeġ, xedd is-saqajn u xedd ir-ras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kleding; Hoofddeksels; Schoeisel; Delen van kleding, schoeisel en hoofdbedekking.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Odzież; Nakrycia głowy; Obuwie; Części odzieży, obuwia i nakryć głowy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Vestuário; Chapelaria; Calçado; Partes de vestuário, calçado e chapelaria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole de îmbrăcăminte; Articole pentru acoperirea capului; Articole de încălțăminte; Părți de îmbrăcăminte, încălțăminte și articole pentru acoperirea capului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Odevy; Pokrývky hlavy; Obuv; Časti oblečenia, obuvi a pokrývok hlavy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oblačila; Pokrivala; Obutev; Deli oblačil, obutve in pokrival.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kläder; Huvudbonader; Fotbeklädnader; Delar av kläder, fotbeklädnader och huvudbonader.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Съоръжения за панаири и детски площадки; Играчки, игри и артикули за игра; Спортни артикули и оборудване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přístroje a zařízení pro zábavní parky a hřiště; Hračky, hry a žertovné předměty; Sportovní potřeby a vybavení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Apparater til legepladser og forlystelsesparker; Legetøj, spil og festartikler; Sportsartikler og -udstyr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Geräte für Jahrmärkte und Spielplätze; Spielwaren, Spiele und Spielzeug; Sportartikel und -ausrüstungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εξοπλισμός για παιδικές χαρές και παιδότοπους· Παιδικά παιχνίδια, παιχνίδια και αθύρματα· Είδη και εξοπλισμός άθλησης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Fairground and playground apparatus; Toys, games, and playthings; Sporting articles and equipment.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de parques de recreo y ferias; Juguetes, juegos y artículos para jugar; Equipamientos y artículos deportivos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Lõbustuspargi- ja mänguväljakuseadmed; Mänguasjad, mängud ja peotarbed, pilakaubad; Sporditarbed ja -riistad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Huvipuisto- ja leikkipuistolaitteet; Lelut, pelit ja leikkivälineet; Urheiluvälineet ja -varusteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils pour champ de foire et terrain de jeux; Jouets, jeux et articles de jeux; Articles et équipement de sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Uređaji za sajmišta i igrališta; Igračke, igre, predmeti za igranje i zabavu; Sportski artikli i oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vásártéri és játszótéri berendezések; Játékszerek, játékok és játéktárgyak; Sportcikkek és felszerelések.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Attrezzature per parchi divertimento e parchi gioco; Giochi, giocattoli, balocchi e ninnoli; Articoli e attrezzature sportive.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Atrakcionų ir žaidimų aikštelių įrenginiai; Žaislai, žaidimai, žaisliukai ir niekučiai (dovanėlės); Sporto reikmenys ir įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Atrakciju un rotaļu laukumu ierīces; Rotaļlietas, spēles un spēļlietas; Sporta preces un sporta inventārs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat għall- grawnds fejn jilgħabu t-tfal; Ġugarelli, logħob, oġġetti tal-logħob; Artikli u tagħmir sportivi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Toestellen voor kermissen en speelplaatsen; Speelgoed, spelletjes en speelgoed; Sportartikelen en -uitrustingen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Wyposażenie placów zabaw i wesołych miasteczek; Gry, zabawki i akcesoria do zabawy; Artykuły i sprzęt sportowy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos para feiras e recreios; Brinquedos, jogos, artigos de brincar e de festa; Artigos e equipamento de desporto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate pentru parcuri de distracții și terenuri de joacă; Jucării, jocuri și articole de joacă; Articole și echipament de sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zariadenia pre lunaparky a detské ihriská; Hračky, hry a drobný hračkársky tovar; Športové potreby a športový výstroj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Naprave za zabaviščne parke in za otroška igrišča; Igrače, igre, predmeti za zabave; Športne potrebščine in oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Åkattraktioner och lekplatsutrustningar; Leksaker, spel och skämtartiklar; Sportartiklar och sportutrustning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Търговско подпомагане, търговско управление и административни услуги; Рекламни, маркетингови и промоционални услуги; Организиране на търгове; Абонаменти за вестници; Услуги свързани с посредничество и финализиране на търговски сделки за трети лица; Административно обработване на поръчки за покупка, направени по телефона или чрез компютър; Административно обработване на компютъризирани поръчки за покупка; Административна обработка и организиране на услуги за пощенски поръчки; Административна обработка на поръчки за покупки в рамките на услугите, предоставяни от компании за поръчки по пощата; Търговия на дребно и едро с фармацевтични, ветеринарни, санитарни и медицински препарати; Услуги за продажби на дребно, свързани със строителни материали; Услуги на магазин за продажба на дребно в сферата на облеклата; Услуги за продажба на дребно, свързани с продажбата на облекла и аксесоари за облекла; Услуги за продажба на дребно във връзка с цветя; Услуги за търговия на дребно във връзка с компютърен хардуер; Услуги за търговия на дребно във връзка с компютърен софтуер; Услуги за търговия на дребно във връзка с изделия от хартия за еднократна употреба.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pomoc v obchodní a podnikatelské činnosti, management a administrativní služby; Reklamní, marketingové a propagační služby; Vedení dražeb; Předplatné novin; Zprostředkování a uzavírání obchodních transakcí pro třetí osoby; Administrativní zpracování nákupních objednávek zadaných telefonicky nebo přes počítač; Administrativní zpracování počítačových nákupních objednávek; Administrativní zpracování a organizování zásilkových služeb; Administrativní zpracovávání nákupních objednávek v rámci služeb poskytovaných zásilkovými společnostmi; Služby pro maloobchod nebo velkoobchod s farmaceutickými, veterinárními a sanitárními přípravky a zdravotnickým materiálem; Maloobchodní služby ve vztahu ke stavebním materiálům; Maloobchodní prodej oděvů; Maloobchodní služby zaměřené na prodej oděvů a oděvních doplňků; Maloobchodní služby zaměřené na květiny; Maloobchodní služby v souvislosti s počítačovým hardwarem; Maloobchodní služby v oboru počítačového softwaru; Maloobchodní prodej jednorázových papírových výrobků.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Bistand ved forretningsudførelse, -ledelse og -administration; Virksomhed vedrørende reklame, marketing og salgsfremstød; Auktionsvirksomhed; Avisabonnementer; Formidling og gennemførelse af kommercielle transaktioner for andre; Administrativ behandling af indkøbsordrer, der er afgivet via telefon eller computer; Administrativ behandling af computerbaserede indkøbsordrer; Administrativ behandling og organisering af postordrevirksomhed; Administrativ behandling af købsordrer inden for rammerne af de tjenesteydelser som postordrevirksomheder leverer; Detail- eller engroshandel med farmaceutiske, veterinære og hygiejniske præparater og medicinske artikler; Detailhandel med byggematerialer; Detailhandel inden for beklædningsgenstande; Detailhandel i forbindelse med salg af beklædningsgenstande og tilbehør til beklædningsgenstande; Detailhandel med blomster; Detailhandel med computerhardware; Detailhandel med computersoftware; Detailhandel med engangspapirprodukter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Hilfe in Geschäftsangelegenheiten, Geschäftsführung und administrative Dienstleistungen; Werbung, Marketing und Verkaufsförderung; Auktions- und Versteigerungsdienste; Abonnementvermittlung für Zeitungen; Abschluss und Vermittlung von Handelsgeschäften für Dritte; Administrative Abwicklung von Kaufaufträgen per Telefon oder Computer; Administrative Abwicklung von computergestützten Kaufaufträgen; Administrative Bearbeitung und Organisation von Versandhandelsdienstleistungen; Administrative Bearbeitung von Bestellungen im Rahmen der Dienstleistungen von Versandhäusern; Einzelhandels- oder Großhandelsdienstleistungen für pharmazeutische, veterinärmedizinische Artikel, Hygienepräparate sowie medizinische Artikel; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Baumaterialien; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Bekleidung; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Bekleidungsstücke und Bekleidungsaccessoires; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Blumen; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Computerhardware; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Computersoftware; Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Einweg- Papiererzeugnisse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Επιχειρηματική υποστήριξη, υπηρεσίες διοίκησης και διαχείρισης· Διαφήμιση, ενέργειες πώλησης (μάρκετινγκ) και υπηρεσίες προώθησης· Υπηρεσίες δημοπρασιών· Υπηρεσίες συνδρομής σε εφημερίδες· Μεσιτεία και σύναψη εμπορικών συμφωνιών για τρίτους· Διοικητική διεκπεραίωση εντολών αγοράς που υποβάλλονται μέσω τηλεφώνου ή υπολογιστή· Διοικητική διεκπεραίωση μηχανογραφημένων εντολών αγοράς· Υπηρεσίες διοικητικής διαχείρισης και οργάνωσης ταχυδρομικών παραγγελιών· Διοικητική επεξεργασία παραγγελιών αγοράς στα πλαίσια υπηρεσιών που παρέχονται από εταιρίες ταχυδρομικών παραγγελιών· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής ή χονδρικής για προμήθειες φαρμακευτικών, κτηνιατικών, ιατρικών και ειδών υγιεινής· Υπηρεσίες μετά την πώληση σχετικά με οικοδομικά υλικά· Υπηρεσίες καταστημάτων λιανικής πώλησης στον τομέα των ενδυμάτων· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με την πώληση ενδυμάτων και αξεσουάρ ενδυμάτων· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με άνθη· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με υλικό ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης στον τομέα του λογισμικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής πώλησης σε σχέση με χάρτινα προϊόντα μίας χρήσης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Business assistance, management and administrative services; Advertising, marketing and promotional services; Auctioneering services; Newspaper subscriptions; Mediation and conclusion of commercial transactions for others; Administrative processing of purchase orders placed by telephone or computer; Administrative processing of computerized purchase orders; Administrative processing and organising of mail order services; Administrative processing of purchase orders within the framework of services provided by mail-order companies; Retail or wholesale services for pharmaceutical, veterinary and sanitary preparations and medical supplies; Retail services in relation to building materials; Retail store services in the field of clothing; Retail services connected with the sale of clothing and clothing accessories; Retail services relating to flowers; Retail services in relation to computer hardware; Retail services in relation to computer software; Retail services in relation to disposable paper products.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de asistencia, dirección y administración de negocios; Servicios promocionales, de marketing y publicidad; Prestación de servicios de subasta; Suscripciones a periódicos; Mediación y cierre de negocios comerciales para terceros; Procesamiento administrativo de pedidos de compra realizados por teléfono u ordenador; Procesamiento administrativo de pedidos de compra realizados por ordenador; Tratamiento administrativo y organización de servicios de venta por correo; Gestión administrativa de pedidos de compra en el marco de los servicios prestados por parte de empresas de pedidos por correo; Venta minorista o mayorista de preparaciones farmacéuticas, veterinarias y sanitarias, así como de suministros médicos; Servicios de venta al por menor relacionados con materiales de construcción; Servicios de venta al por menor en el ámbito de la ropa; Servicios de venta al por menor relacionados con la venta de prendas de vestir y sus accesorios; Servicios de venta al por menor en relación con flores; Servicios de venta minorista en relación con hardware de ordenador; Servicios de venta al por menor en relación con el software de ordenador; Servicios de venta al por menor relacionados con productos de papel desechables.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ärijuhtimisteenused ja ärialane abi; Reklaam ja turundus; Oksjonid, enampakkumised; Ajalehetellimused; Kaubandustehingute vahendamine ja sõlmimine teenusena; Telefoni või arvuti teel esitatud ostutellimuste haldustöötlemine; Elektrooniliste ostutellimuste haldustöötlemine; Postitellimuste töötlemine ja korrastamine; Postimüügifirmade ostutellimuste töötlemine; Farmaatsia- ja veterinaariapreparaatide ning hügieeni- ja meditsiinitarvete jae- ja hulgimüük; Ehitusmaterjalide jaemüügiteenused; Rõivaste jaemüük kolmandatele isikutele; Rõivaste ja rõivaaksessuaaride jaemüük kolmandatele isikutele; Lillede jaemüügiteenused; Arvutiriistvara jaemüük; Arvutitarkvara jaemüügiteenused; Ühekorra-pabertoodete jaemüügiteenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Yritystoiminnan avustamis-, liikkeenjohto- ja hallintopalvelut; Mainonta-, markkinointi- ja myynninedistämispalvelut; Huutokauppapalvelut; Sanomalehtien tilauspalvelut; Kauppojen välitys ja solmiminen muiden lukuun; Puhelimitse tai tietokoneella tehtyjen ostotilausten hallinnollinen käsittely; Tietokoneohjattujen ostotilausten hallinnollinen käsittely; Postimyyntipalvelujen hallinnollinen käsittely ja järjestäminen; Postimyyntiyrityksen palveluihin liittyvä tilausten hallinnollinen käsittely; Farmaseuttisten ja eläinlääkinnällisten valmisteiden, saniteettivalmisteiden sekä lääkintätarvikkeiden vähittäiskauppa- tai tukkukauppapalvelut; Rakennusmateriaalien vähittäismyyntipalvelut; Vähittäismyyntipalvelut vaatteiden alalla; Vaatteiden ja asusteiden myyntiin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut; Vähittäismyyntipalvelut, jotka liittyvät kukkiin; Tietokonelaitteistojen vähittäismyyntipalvelut; Tietokoneohjelmistoihin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut; Kertakäyttöisiin paperituotteisiin liittyvät vähittäismyyntipalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d'aide et de gestion des affaires et services administratifs; Services de publicité, de marketing et de promotion; Services de vente aux enchères; Abonnements à des journaux; Conclusion de transactions commerciales pour le compte de tiers; Traitement administratif de commandes d’achats passées par téléphone ou par ordinateur; Traitement administratif de commandes d’achats informatisées; Traitement administratif et organisation des services de vente par correspondance; Traitement administratif de commandes d'achat dans le cadre de services fournis par des entreprises de vente par correspondance; Services de vente au détail ou en gros de préparations pharmaceutiques, vétérinaires et hygiéniques ainsi que de fournitures médicales; Services de vente au détail liés aux matériaux de construction; Services de vente au détail dans le domaine de l'habillement; Services de vente au détail de vêtements et d'accessoires vestimentaires; Services de vente au détail liés aux fleurs; Services de vente au détail de matériel informatique; Services de vente au détail dans le domaine des logiciels informatiques; Services de vente au détail concernant les produits jetables en papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge poslovne pomoći, upravljanja i administracije; Usluge oglašavanja, marketinga i promidžbe; Usluge prodaja na dražbi; Pretplata na novine; Posredovanje i zaključenje komercijalnih transakcija za druge; Administrativna obrada računalnih narudžbi izvršenih telefonom ili računalom; Administrativna obrada računalnih narudžbi; Usluge administrativne obrade i organiziranja narudžbi putem pošte; Administrativna obrada narudžbi za kupnju unutar okvira usluga koje pružaju tvrtke za naručivanje putem pošte; Usluge maloprodaje ili veleprodaje za farmaceutske, veterinarske i sanitarne pripravke i za medicinske potrepštine; Maloprodajne usluge u vezi s građevinskim materijalima; Usluge trgovina za prodaju na malo odjevnih artikala; Maloprodajne usluge za prodaju odjeće i odjevnih predmeta; Maloprodajne usluge u vezi s cvijećem; Maloprodajne usluge u vezi s računalnim hardverom; Maloprodajne usluge u vezi s računalnim softverom; Maloprodajne usluge vezane uz jednokratne papirnate proizvode.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Üzleti segítségnyújtás, menedzseri és adminisztratív szolgáltatások; Reklámozási, marketing és promóciós szolgáltatások; Árverési szolgáltatások; Újságelőfizetések; Kereskedelmi tranzakciók közvetítése és lebonyolítása; Telefonon vagy számítógépen leadott megrendelések adminisztratív feldolgozása; Számítógépes megrendelések adminisztratív feldolgozása; Postai csomagküldő szolgáltatások adminisztratív feldolgozása és megszervezése; Vásárlói megrendelések adminisztratív feldolgozása postai csomagküldő vállalatok által biztosított szolgáltatások keretében; Gyógyszerészeti, állatgyógyászati és higiéniai készítmények valamint gyógyászati eszközök kis- és nagykereskedelme; Építőanyagokkal kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Kiskereskedelmi bolti szolgáltatások a ruházat területén; Ruházati cikkek és ruházati kiegészítők értékesítésével kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások; Kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások virágokkal kapcsolatban; Kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások számítógépes hardverrel kapcsolatban; Kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások számítógépes szoftverrel kapcsolatban; Egyszer használatos papírtermékekkel kapcsolatos kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Assistenza negli affari, servizi gestionali ed amministrativi; Servizi pubblicitari, di marketing e promozionali; Servizi di vendita all'asta; Abbonamenti a giornali; Mediazione e stipulazione di transazioni commerciali per conto terzi; Elaborazione amministrativa di ordini d'acquisto effettuati tramite telefono o computer; Elaborazione amministrativa di ordini d'acquisto computerizzati; Elaborazione amministrativa e organizzazione di ordini di vendita per corrispondenza; Elaborazione amministrativa di ordini d'acquisto nell'ambito dei servizi resi da società di ordinazione per corrispondenza; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio o all'ingrosso di preparati farmaceutici, veterinari e sanitari e di forniture mediche; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio in materia di materiali da costruzione; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio in materia di abbigliamento; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio in materia di abbigliamento e accessori per abbigliamento; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio di fiori; Servizi di vendita al dettaglio in materia di materiale informatico; Servizi di commercio al dettaglio nel campo del software informatico; Servizi al dettaglio in relazione a prodotti di carta usa e getta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Verslo pagalba, vadyba ir administravimas; Reklamos, rinkodaros ir pardavimų skatinimo paslaugos; Pardavimas aukcione; Laikraščių prenumerata; Tarpininkavimas ir prekybinių sandorių sudarymas (kitiems); Telefonu arba kompiuteriu teikiamų pirkimo užsakymų administracinis apdorojimas; Kompiuterizuotų pirkimo užsakymų administracinis apdorojimas; Paštu užsakomų paslaugų administravimas ir organizavimas; Bendrovių, teikiančių užsakymų paštu paslaugas, prekių užsakymų administracinis tvarkymas; Mažmeninė ar didmeninė prekyba farmacijos, veterinarijos ir higienos preparatais bei medicinos reikmenimis; Mažmeninė prekyba statybinėmis medžiagomis; Aprangos mažmeninės prekybos parduotuvių paslaugos; Mažmeninė prekyba apranga ir aprangos aksesuarais; Mažmeninė prekyba gėlėmis; Mažmeninė prekyba kompiuterių aparatine įranga; Mažmeninė prekyba kompiuterių programine įranga; Mažmeninė prekyba vienkartiniais popieriniais gaminiais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Atbalsta, pārvaldības un biroju administratīvie pakalpojumi uzņēmējdarbībai; Reklāmas, tirgvedības un preču noieta veicināšanas pakalpojumi; Izsoļu organizēšana; Laikrakstu abonēšana; Komercdarījumu starpniecība un noslēgšana trešajām personām; Pa tālruni vai datorizēti iesniegtu pirkšanas pasūtījumu administratīvā apstrāde; Datorizētu pirkšanas pasūtījumu administratīvā apstrāde; Preču pasūtījumu pa pastu administratīvā apstrāde un organizācija; Pirkumu pasūtījumu administratīvā apstrāde pasta pasūtījumu uzņēmumu nodrošināto pakalpojumu ietvaros; Farmaceitisko, veterināro un higiēnas preparātu un medicīnisko preču mazumtirdzniecība un vairumtirdzniecība; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar celtniecības materiāliem; Mazumtirdzniecības veikalu pakalpojumi apģērbu jomā; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar apģērbu un apģērbu aksesuāru pārdošanu; Ziedu mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi saistībā ar datoru aparatūru; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi datoru programmatūras jomā; Mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi attiecībā uz vienreizlietojamiem papīra izstrādājumiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' assistenza, ġestjoni u amministrazzjoni fin-negozju; Servizzi ta' reklamar, kummerċjaliżżazzjoni u promozzjonali; Servizzi ta' irkantijiet; Abbonamenti tal-gazzetti; Medjazzjoni u konklużjoni ta' transazzjonijiet kummerċjali għal oħrajn; Ipproċessar amministrattiv ta’ ordnijiet tax-xiri magħmula permezz ta’ telefown jew kompjuter; Ipproċessar amministrattiv ta’ ordnijiet tax-xiri kompjuterizzati; L-ipproċessar amministrattiv u l-organizzazzjoni ta' servizzi ta' ordnijiet bil-posta; Pproċessar amministrattiv ta' ordnijiet tax-xiri fil-qasam tas-servizzi pprovduti minn kumpaniji tal-ordnijiet bil-posta; Servizzi kemm bl-imnut jew bl-ingrossa għall-forniment ta' oġġetti farmaċewtiċi, veterinarji, medikali u preparazzjonijiet sanitarji; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut fir-rigward ta' materjali tal-bini; Servizzi ta' ħanut tal-bejgħ bl-imnut fil-qasam ta' ilbies; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut konnessi mal-bejgħ ta' lbies u ta' aċċessorji tal-ilbies; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut relatati mal-fjuri; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut fir-rigward ta' ħardwer tal-kompjuter; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut fil-qasam tas-softwer tal-kompjuter; Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-imnut fir-rigward ta' prodotti tal-karti li jintremew wara li jintużaw.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Commercieel-zakelijke assistentie, commercieel-zakelijk beheer en administratieve diensten; Reclame, marketing en promotionele diensten; Veilingdiensten; Krantenabonnementen; Bemiddeling bij en afwikkeling van commerciële transacties voor derden; Administratieve verwerking van bestelorders geplaatst per telefoon of computer; Administratieve verwerking van automatisch gegenereerde bestelorders; Administratieve verwerking en organisatie van postorderdiensten; Administratieve verwerking van verkooporders in het kader van diensten verleend door postorderbedrijven; Detailhandels- of groothandelsdiensten in farmaceutische, veterinaire en hygiënische preparaten en medische hulpmiddelen; Detailhandel in bouwmaterialen; Detailhandelsdiensten op het gebied van kleding; Detailhandel met betrekking tot verkoop van kleding en kledingaccessoires; Detailhandelsdiensten op het gebied van bloemen; Detailhandelsdiensten met betrekking tot computerhardware; Detailhandelsdiensten met betrekking tot computersoftware; Detailhandelsdiensten op het gebied van papieren wegwerpproducten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pomoc w prowadzeniu działalności gospodarczej, zarządzanie i administrowanie działalnością gospodarczą; Usługi reklamowe, marketingowe i promocyjne; Usługi aukcyjne; Prenumerowanie gazet; Pośredniczenie i zawieranie transakcji handlowych dla osób trzecich; Procedury administracyjne związane ze składaniem zleceń kupna za pośrednictwem telefonu lub komputera; Procedury administracyjne związane ze składaniem zleceń kupna za pośrednictwem komputera; Administrowanie i organizacja usług sprzedaży wysyłkowej; Zarządzanie administracyjne zamówieniami na zakup w ramach usług świadczonych przez firmy wysyłkowe; Sprzedaż detaliczna lub hurtowa środków farmaceutycznych, weterynaryjnych i sanitarnych oraz zaopatrzenia medycznego; Usługi handlu detalicznego w zakresie materiałów budowlanych; Usługi w zakresie sklepów detalicznych w branży odzieżowej; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej związane ze sprzedażą odzieży i dodatków odzieżowych; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej w zakresie kwiatów; Usługi handlu detalicznego w odniesieniu do sprzętu komputerowego; Usługi handlu detalicznego w odniesieniu do oprogramowania komputerowego; Usługi sprzedaży detalicznej w związku z jednorazowymi wyrobami papierowymi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de assistência, gestão e administração de negócios; Serviços de publicidade, de marketing e de promoção; Serviços de leilões; Subscrição de jornais; Mediação e conclusão de transações comerciais para terceiros; Processamento administrativo de ordens de compra efectuadas por telefone ou computador; Processamento administrativo de ordens de compra informáticas; Processamento e organização administrativo de serviços de encomenda postal; Tratamento administrativo de ordens de encomenda no âmbito dos serviços prestados por empresas de vendas por correspondência; Serviços de venda a retalho ou a grosso de preparações farmacêuticas, veterinárias e higiénicas e provisões médicas; Serviços de venda a retalho relacionados com materiais de construção; Serviços de lojas de venda a retalho no domínio do vestuário; Serviços de comércio a retalho relacionados com a venda de vestuário e acessórios de vestuário; Serviços de venda a retalho relativos a flores; Serviços de venda a retalho relacionados com hardware informático; Serviços de venda a retalho relacionados com programas informáticos; Serviços retalhistas relacionados com produtos de papel descartáveis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Asistență în afaceri, management și servicii administrative; Servicii de publicitate, marketing și promovare; Vânzare prin licitație publică; Abonamente la ziare; Mediere și încheiere de tranzacții comerciale pentru terți; Prelucrare administrativă de comenzi de achiziție plasate prin telefon sau calculator; Prelucrare administrativă de comenzi de achiziție computerizate; Prelucrare și organizare administrativă de comenzi prin poștă; Prelucrarea administrativă a comenzilor de achiziție în cadrul serviciilor furnizate de societăți de comandă prin poștă; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul sau en-gros pentru preparate farmaceutice, veterinare și sanitare și produse medicale; Servicii de comerț cu amănuntul cu privire la materiale de construcții; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul în domeniul vestimentar; Servicii de comercializare cu amănuntul de articole de îmbrăcăminte și accesorii pentru îmbrăcăminte; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul referitoare la flori; Servicii de comerț cu amănuntul cu privire la hardware de calculator; Servicii de comerț cu amănuntul cu privire la software de calculator; Servicii de vânzare cu amănuntul în legătură cu produse din hârtie de unică folosință.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Pomoc pri podnikaní, riadenie podniku a obchodná správa; Reklamné, marketingové a propagačné služby; Dražby; Predplatné novín; Sprostredkovanie a uzavieranie komerčných transakcií pre tretie osoby; Administratívne spracovanie nákupných objednávok zadaných prostredníctvom telefónu alebo počítača; Administratívne spracovanie počítačových nákupných objednávok; Administratívne spracovanie a organizovanie zásielkového predaja; Administratívne spracovanie objednávok v rámci služieb poskytovaných zásielkovými spoločnosťami; Maloobchodné alebo veľkoobchodné služby s farmaceutickými, zverolekárskymi a zdravotníckymi prípravkami a s lekárskymi potrebami; Maloobchodné služby v oblasti stavebných materiálov; Maloobchodné služby v oblasti odevov; Maloobchodné služby spojené s predajom odevov a odevných doplnkov; Maloobchodné služby v oblasti kvetov; Maloobchodné služby s počítačovým hardvérom; Maloobchodné služby s počítačovým softvérom; Maloobchodné služby s jednorazovými papierovými výrobkami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Poslovna asistenca, poslovno vodenje in administrativne storitve; Oglaševalske, tržne in promocijske storitve; Storitve v zvezi s prodajami na dražbi; Časopisne naročnine; Posredovanje in sklepanje komercialnih transakcij za druge; Administracijska obdelava naročil nakupov, oddanih preko telefona ali računalnika; Administrativna obdelava računalniško podprtih naročil; Administrativna obdelava in organizacija storitev poštnega naročanja; Administrativna obdelava naročil za nakup v okviru storitev, ki jih nudijo podjetja za naročanje po pošti; Maloprodajne ali veleprodajne storitve za farmacevtske, veterinarske in sanitarne proizvode in medicinske potrebščine; Maloprodajne storitve v zvezi z gradbenimi materiali; Maloprodajne storitve na področju oblačil; Maloprodajne storitve v zvezi s prodajo oblačil in dodatkov k oblačilom; Maloprodajne storitve v zvezi s cvetjem; Maloprodajne storitve v zvezi z računalniško strojno opremo; Maloprodajne storitve v zvezi z računalniško programsko opremo; Storitve prodaje na drobno v zvezi z izdelki iz papirja za enkratno uporabo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Företagsassistans, -ledning och -administration; Reklam, marknadsföring och säljfrämjande tjänster; Auktionering; Tidningsprenumerationer; Förmedling och avslut av kommersiella affärsuppgörelser för andra; Administrativ behandling av inköpsorder som läggs via telefon eller dator; Administrativ behandling av datoriserade inköpsordrar; Administrativ behandling och organisering av postordertjänster; Administrativ behandling av beställningar inom ramen för tjänster från ett postorderföretag; Återförsäljning eller detaljhandelstjänster för farmaceutiska, veterinära och sanitära preparat och medicinska varor; Återförsäljning avseende byggnadsmaterial; Återförsäljning i butik avseende kläder; Återförsäljartjänster i samband med avyttring av kläder och klädesaccessoarer; Återförsäljning avseende blommor; Återförsäljartjänster avseende maskinvara; Återförsäljartjänster avseende programvara; Återförsäljning avseende engångsprodukter av papper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за образование, развлечение и спорт; Издателска дейност, репортажи и писане на текстове; Преводачески услуги; Услуги за резервация и резервация на билети за образователни, развлекателни и спортни дейности и събития.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby v oblasti vzdělávání, zábavy a sportu; Zveřejňování, oznamování a psaní textů; Překladatelské služby; Rezervace vstupenek na vzdělávací, zábavní a sportovní aktivity a akce a související rezervační služby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Uddannelsesvirksomhed, underholdningsvirksomhed og sportsydelser; Publicering, journalistvirksomhed og tekstforfatning; Tolkning og oversættelse; Reservation af billetter og booking af aktiviteter og arrangementer vedrørende uddannelse, underholdning og sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bildung, Erziehung, Unterhaltung und sportliche Aktivitäten; Verlagsdienstleistungen und Berichterstattung sowie Verfassen von Texten; Übersetzung und Dolmetschen; Ticketreservierung und -buchung für Bildungs- und Unterhaltungsveranstaltungen sowie für sportliche Veranstaltungen und Äktivitäten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες εκπαίδευσης, ψυχαγωγίας και αθλητισμού· Υπηρεσίες έκδοσης, αναφοράς, και σύνταξης κειμένων· Μετάφραση και ερμηνεία· Υπηρεσίες κράτησης εισιτηρίων και θέσεων για εκπαιδευτικές, ψυχαγωγικές και αθλητικές δραστηριότητες και εκδηλώσεις.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Education, entertainment and sport services; Publishing, reporting, and writing of texts; Translation and interpretation; Ticket reservation and booking services for education, entertainment and sports activities and events.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de educación, entretenimiento y de actividades deportivas; Publicación, edición de reportajes y redacción de textos; Traducción e interpretación; Servicios de reserva de entradas para actividades y eventos de educación, entretenimiento y deporte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Haridus-, meelelahutus- ja sporditeenused; Kirjastamine, reporteriteenused ja tekstide kirjutamine; Tõlkimine; Haridus-, meelelahutus- ja sporditegevuste ja -ürituste piletite reserveerimise ja broneerimise teenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Koulutus-, ajanviete- ja urheilupalvelut; Tekstien julkaisu, raportointi ja kirjoittaminen; Käännös ja tulkkaus; Lippujen varauspalvelut koulutus-, viihde- ja urheilutoimintaan ja -tilaisuuksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d’éducation, de divertissement et de sport; Édition, établissement de rapports et rédaction de textes; Traduction et interprétation; Services de réservation et de préréservation de billets concernant les activités et les événements dans les domaines de l’éducation, du divertissement et des sports.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Obrazovne, zabavne i sportske usluge; Objavljivanje, izvještavanje i pisanje tekstova; Prevođenje i tumačenje; Predbilježba i rezervacija ulaznica za događanja i aktivnosti u području obrazovanja, zabave i sporta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Oktatási, szórakoztatási és sportszolgáltatások; Kiadói és híradói, beszámolói szolgáltatások, illetve szövegek írása; Fordítás és tolmácsolás; Jegyfoglalás és foglalási szolgáltatások oktatási, szórakoztató és sporttevékenységekhez, illetve -rendezvényekhez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi relativi a educazione, divertimento e sport; Pubblicazione, comunicazione e redazione di testi; Traduzioni ed interpretariato; Servizi di prenotazione di biglietti per attività ed eventi in ambito educativo, ricreativo e sportivo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Švietimo, pramogų ir sporto paslaugos; Tekstų leidyba, reportažų rengimas ir tekstų rašymas; Vertimai; Bilietų į mokomuosius, pramoginius ir sporto renginius ir užsiėmimus rezervavimo ir užsakymo paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Izglītības, izklaides un sporta pakalpojumi; Tekstu rakstīšana, publicēšana un reportāžu sagatavošana; Mutvārdu un rakstveida tulkošanas pakalpojumi; Biļešu rezervēšanas un pasūtīšanas pakalpojumi izglītības, izklaides un sporta nodarbībām un pasākumiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' edukazzjoni, ta' divertiment u ta' sports; Il-pubblikazzjoni, ir-rapportaġġ u l-kitba ta' testi; Traduzzjoni u interpretazzjoni; Servizzi ta' riservazzjoni u riservazzjoni ta' biljetti għall-edukazzjoni, id-divertiment u l-attivitajiet sportivi u eventi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diensten op het gebied van opvoeding, ontspanning en sport; Publiceren, rapporteren en schrijven van teksten; Vertaling en vertolking; Ticketreserverings- en boekingsdiensten voor onderwijs-, entertainment- en sportactiviteiten en -evenementen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi edukacyjne, rozrywkowe i sportowe; Publikowanie, sprawozdawczość i pisanie tektów; Tłumaczenia; Usługi rezerwacji biletów na atrakcje i wydarzenia edukacyjne, rozrywkowe i sportowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de educação, entretenimento e desporto; Publicação, relato e redação de textos; Tradução e interpretação; Serviços de reserva de bilhetes para atividades e eventos educativos, de entretenimento e desportivos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii educative, de divertisment și sportive; Editare, întocmire de rapoarte și redactare de texte; Traducere și interpretare; Servicii de rezervare de bilete în domeniul educației, divertismentului și sportului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Služby v oblasti vzdelávania, zábavy a športu; Uverejňovanie, oznamovanie a písanie textov; Prekladateľské a tlmočnícke služby; Rezervácia vstupeniek a rezervačné služby v oblasti vzdelávacích, zábavných a športových činností a podujatí.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Izobraževalne, razvedrilne in športne storitve; Objava, priprava poročil in pisanje besedil; Prevajanje in tolmačenje; Storitve rezervacije vstopnic za izobraževalne, razvedrilne in športne dejavnosti in dogodke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tjänster avseende utbildning, underhållning och sport; Publicering, rapportering och författande av texter; Översättning och tolkning; Reservation och bokning av biljetter för aktiviteter och evenemang inom utbildning, underhållning och sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>35004</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
