<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:43</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224170</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224170</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>sv</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ACAMP</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги за запазване на билети и резервации за мероприятия, свързани с развлечение и свободно време; Осигуряване на условия за отмора; Информационни услуги за отмора и почивка; Информационни услуги за отмора и почивка; Осигуряване на он-лайн публикации; Осигуряване на съоръжения за отмора и почивка на открито; Лагери за възстановяване; Предоставяне на отзиви от страна на потребителите за развлекателни или културни цели; Предоставяне на развлекателна информация чрез интернет.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Rezervace lístků a objednávkové služby pro rekreační a volnočasové akce; Provozování rekreačních zařízení; Informace o rekreaci; Informační služby vztahující se k rekreaci; Poskytování on-line publikací; Provozování prostor pro venkovní rekreační činnosti; Rekreační kempy; Poskytování uživatelských recenzí pro zábavní nebo kulturní účely; Poskytování informací o zábavě prostřednictvím internetu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Billetreservations- og bestillingstjenester til rekreative arrangementer og fritidsarrangementer; Stillen rekreative faciliteter til rådighed; Stillen information til rådighed om rekreative aktiviteter; Informationstjenester vedrørende fritid og underholdning; Stille online publikationer til rådighed; Tilvejebringelse af faciliteter til udendørs, rekreative aktiviteter; Fritidslejre; Tilvejebringelse af brugeranmeldelser til underholdningsmæssige eller kulturelle formål; Formidling af information vedrørende underholdning via internettet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Reservierung und Buchung von Eintrittskarten für Freizeitveranstaltungen; Dienstleistungen bezüglich Freizeitgestaltung; Auskünfte über Freizeitaktivitäten; Erteilen von Auskünften in Bezug auf Freizeitangebote; Bereitstellen von Online-Veröffentlichungen; Betrieb von Einrichtungen für Freizeitaktivitäten im Freien; Veranstaltung von Freizeitcamps; Bereitstellung von Nutzerbewertungen für Unterhaltungs- oder kulturelle Zwecke; Zurverfügungstellen von Information in Bezug auf Unterhaltung über das Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες κράτησης εισιτηρίων και θέσεων για εκδηλώσεις ψυχαγωγικής φύσεως και δραστηριότητες ελεύθερου χρόνου· Παροχή εγκαταστάσεων ψυχαγωγίας· Πληροφόρηση για θέματα αναψυχής· Υπηρεσίες παροχής πληροφοριών σε σχέση με την αναψυχή· Παροχή εκδόσεων σε διαδικτυακή σύνδεση (on-line)· Παροχή εγκαταστάσεων για υπαίθριες δραστηριότητες αναψυχής· Κατασκηνώσεις αναψυχής· Παροχή αξιολογήσεων χρηστών για ψυχαγωγικούς ή πολιτιστικούς σκοπούς· Παροχή πληροφοριών σχετικά με ψυχαγωγία μέσω του Διαδικτύου.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Ticket reservation and booking services for recreational and leisure events; Providing recreation facilities; Recreation information; Information services relating to recreation; Providing on-line publications; Provision of facilities for outdoor recreational activities; Recreational camps; Providing user reviews for entertainment or cultural purposes; Provision of entertainment information via the Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de reserva de localidades para eventos recreativos y de ocio; Puesta a disposición de instalaciones recreativas; Información sobre actividades recreativas; Servicios de información relacionados con el recreo; Facilitación de publicaciones en línea (online); Facilitación de instalaciones para actividades recreativas de exterior; Campamentos recreativos; Suministro de reseñas de usuarios con fines de esparcimiento o culturales; Suministro de información sobre entretenimiento por Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Puhke- ja vabaajaürituste piletite reserveerimise ja broneerimise teenused; Puhke-, ajaviitealade pakkumine; Puhke-, rekreatsioonialane teave; Rekreatsioonialased teabeteenused; Veebiväljaannete pakkumine; Välistingimustes rekreatsiooni-, puhketegevuseks rajatiste pakkumine; Puhkelaagrid; Kasutajaretsensioonide pakkumine meelelahutuse või kultuuri valdkonnas; Meelelahutusteabe pakkumine Interneti kaudu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Virkistys- ja vapaa-ajantapahtumien lippujen varauspalvelut; Virkistyspalveluiden tarjoaminen; Viihdeneuvonta; Huvitukseen liittyvät tiedotuspalvelut; Online-julkaisujen tarjoaminen; Tilojen tarjoaminen ulkovirkistystoimintaan; Virkistysleirit; Käytttäjäarvostelujen tarjoaminen viihde- tai kulttuuritarkoituksiin; Viihdetietojen tarjoaminen Internetin välityksellä.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de réservation de billets [tickets] pour des manifestations de loisirs et de divertissement; Mise à disposition d'installations de loisirs; Informations en matière de récréation; Services de renseignements concernant les loisirs; Services de publication en ligne; Mise à disposition d'équipements et d'installations pour loisirs en plein air; Services de camps de loisirs; Mise à disposition des critiques d'utilisateurs à des fins culturelles ou de divertissement; Mise à disposition d'informations en matière de divertissement par le biais d'Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge predbilježbe i rezervacije ulaznica za rekreacijske i zabavne manifestacije; Rekreacijski objekti (Pružanje -); Obavijesti u svezi rekreacije; Informativne usluge u svezi s rekreacijom; Pružanje online publikacija; Pružanje objekata i opreme za rekreacijske aktivnosti na otvorenom; Rekreativni kampovi; Pružanje korisničkih recenzija u zabavne ili kulturne svrhe; Pružanje razonodnih informacija putem Interneta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Jegyfoglalási szolgáltatások szórakoztató és szabadidős rendezvényekre; Szabadidős létesítmények üzemeltetése; Szabadidős tevékenységekkel kapcsolatos tájékoztatás; Rekreációval, szabadidővel kapcsolatos információs szolgáltatások; Online kiadványok megjelentetése; Létesítmények biztosítása kültéri szabadidős tevékenységekhez; Szabadidős táborok; Felhasználói értékelések szolgáltatása szórakoztató vagy kulturális célokra; Szórakoztatással kapcsolatos információk biztosítása interneten keresztül.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Prenotazione di biglietti per eventi ricreativi e per il tempo libero; Servizi di fornitura di strutture ricreative; Informazioni in materia di ricreazione; Servizi di informazione in materia di svago; Fornitura di pubblicazioni on-line; Offerta di strutture per attività ricreative all'aperto; Campi ricreativi; Fornitura di recensioni di utenti a scopo ricreativo o culturale; Fornitura di informazioni sui servizi d'intrattenimento tramite internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Bilietų į poilsio ir laisvalaikio renginius rezervavimo ir užsakymo paslaugos; Poilsio ir pramogų vietų paslaugos; Informacija apie poilsio ir pramogų renginius; Poilsio ir pramogų informacijos paslaugos; Publikacijų pateikimas internete; Laisvalaikio lauko pramogų vietų ir įrengimų teikimas; Poilsinės ir pramoginės stovyklos; Vartotojų atsiliepimų teikimas (pramogų ar kultūros reikmėms); Pramoginės informacijos teikimas internete.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Biļešu rezervācijas un pārdošanas pakalpojumi izklaides un brīvā laika pavadīšanas pasākumiem; Atpūtas iespēju nodrošināšana; Informācijas sniegšana par atpūtas pasākumiem; Informācijas pakalpojumi saistībā ar atpūtu; Tiešsaistes publikāciju nodrošināšana; Brīvdabas atpūtas pasākumu aprīkojuma nodrošināšana; Izklaidējošas nometnes; Lietotāju atsauksmju sniegšana izklaides vai kultūras nolūkiem; Izklaides informācijas nodrošināšana ar interneta palīdzību.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta’ prenotazzjoni u ta’ bbukkjar ta’ biljetti għal avvenimenti rikreattivi u ta’ divertiment; Faċilitajiet għar-rikreazzjoni (Provvista ta' -); Informazzjoni dwar rikreazzjoni; Servizzi ta' informazzjoni relatati mar-rikreazzjoni; Il-provvista ta' pubblikazzjonijiet online; Provvista ta' faċilitajiet għal attivitajiet rikreattivi ta' barra; Kampeġġi rikreattivi; Provvista ta' reċensjonijiet tal-utent għal skopijiet ta' divertiment jew ta' kultura; Provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar id-divertiment permezz tal-Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Reservering en boeking van plaatsbewijzen voor evenementen op het vlak van recreatie en vrijetijdsbesteding; Ter beschikking stellen van installaties voor vrijetijdsbesteding; Verschaffen van informatie op het gebied van recreatie; Informatie op het gebied van recreatie; Publicatie online; Ter beschikking stellen van faciliteiten voor buiten recreatieactiviteiten; Recreatieve kampen; Het verstrekken van gebruikersreviews voor entertainment of culturele doeleinden; Informatieverstrekking over entertainment via het internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi rezerwacji biletów i rezerwacji miejsc na wydarzenia rekreacyjne i rozrywkowe; Udostępnianie obiektów i sprzętu rekreacyjnego; Informacja o rekreacji; Usługi informacyjne dotyczące rekreacji; Udostępnianie publikacji on-line; Zapewnianie obiektów i sprzętu na potrzeby zajęć rekreacyjnych na świeżym powietrzu; Obozy rekreacyjne; Zapewnianie recenzji użytkowników w celach rozrywkowych lub kulturalnych; Udzielanie informacji dotyczących rozrywki za pośrednictwem Internetu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de marcação e reserva de bilhetes para eventos recreativos e de lazer; Exploração de instalações recreativas; Informação sobre atividades recreativas; Serviços de informação relacionados com atividades de recreio; Disponibilização de publicações on-line; Fornecimento de instalações para atividades recreativas de exterior; Acampamentos recreativos; Fornecimento de comentários de utilizador [reviews] para fins de entretenimento ou culturais; Disponibilização de informação sobre entretenimento e atividades recreativas através da Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de rezervare de bilete și locuri la evenimente recreative și de petrecere a timpului liber; Furnizare de instalații de recreere; Informații în materie de recreere; Servicii de informare referitoare la recreere; Furnizare de publicații on-line; Furnizarea de instalații pentru activități de recreere în aer liber; Tabere de recreere; Furnizare de evaluări ale utilizatorilor în scopuri de divertisment sau culturale; Furnizare de informații despre divertisment prin intermediul internetului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Služby rezervácie a objednávania lístkov na rekreačné a voľnočasové podujatia; Poskytovanie zariadení na oddych a rekreáciu; Informácie o možnostiach rekreácie; Informácie o možnostiach rekreácie; Poskytovanie on-line publikácií; Poskytovanie priestorov pre rekreačné činnosti v exteriéri; Služby táborov pre oddych a rekreáciu (okrem ubytovania); Poskytovanie recenzií používateľov na zábavné alebo kultúrne účely; Poskytovanie informácií v oblasti zábavy prostredníctvom internetu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve rezervacije vstopnic za rekreativne dogodke in dogodke za prosti čas; Nudenje rekreacijskih prostorov in opreme; Informiranje o rekreaciji; Informacijske storitve v zvezi z rekreacijo; Nudenje spletnih publikacij; Nudenje prostorov in opreme za rekreacijske dejavnosti na prostem; Rekreacijski kampi; Zagotavljanje ocen uporabnikov za razvedrilne ali kulturne namene; Nudenje razvedrilnih informacij po internetu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tjänster för reservation och bokning av biljetter till fritids- och rekreationsevenemang; Rekreationstjänster; Rekreationsinformation; Rekreationsinformationstjänster; Upplåtande av publikationer online; Upplåtande av anläggningar för utomhusfritidsaktiviteter; Upplåtande av anläggningar för rekreation; Tillhandahållande av användarrecensioner för underhållnings- eller kulturändamål; Tillhandahållande av underhållningsinformation via internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>43</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Запазване на места за лагерно настаняване; Предоставяне на онлайн информация относно резервации за ваканционно настаняване; Предоставяне на временно настаняване за гости; Предоставяне на информация за квартири чрез интернет; Услуги за предоставяне на информация за настаняване и услуги на агенция за резервации за настаняване на пътници; Предоставяне на информация за временно настаняване чрез интернет; Предоставяне на информация за услуги за временно настаняване; Резервации за временен подслон; Услуги за информация, съвети и резервации за временно настаняване; Резервиране на временни квартири чрез интернет; Предоставяне на информация, свързана с резервиране на помещения за настаняване; Резервиране на временни квартири от рода на ваканционни жилища; Резервация на квартири за пътници; Услуги за временно настаняване във ваканционни селища; Ваканционни лагери [настаняване]; Отдаване под наем на квартири за ваканция; Оценяване на места за настаняване във връзка с ваканции; Услуги за запазване на ваканционно настаняване; Услуги за ваканционно настаняване; Временно настаняване; Предоставяне на временен подслон; Услуги на туристическа агенция за извършването на резервации за настаняване; Услуги за предоставяне на съоръжения за паркиране на каравани; Осигуряване на временни квартири.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Rezervace ubytování v kempech; Poskytování on-line informací vztahujících se k rezervacím ubytování na dovolenou; Poskytování dočasného ubytování pro hosty; Poskytování informací vztahujících se k ubytování přes internet; Poskytování informací o možnostech ubytování na cestách a rezervování ubytování pro turisty; Poskytování informací o dočasném ubytování přes internet; Poskytování informací o službách dočasného ubytování; Rezervace přechodného ubytování; Informace o dočasném ubytování, poradenské a rezervační služby; Rezervace dočasného ubytování prostřednictvím internetu; Poskytování informací vztahujících se k rezervování ubytování; Rezervace dočasného ubytování v podobě prázdninových domů; Rezervace ubytování pro turisty; Služby dočasného ubytování poskytované prázdninovými tábory; Prázdninové tábory [ubytování]; Zajišťování ubytování o dovolených; Hodnocení prázdninového ubytování; Služby v oblasti rezervování ubytování na dovolenou; Služby týkající se ubytování o dovolených; Dočasné ubytování; Pronájem přechodného ubytování; Služby cestovních agentur v oblasti rezervace ubytování; Poskytování karavanových parků; Poskytování přechodného ubytování.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Bookning af indkvartering på lejrpladser; Formidling af online-information vedrørende reservationer af ferieindkvartering; Service i forbindelse med midlertidig indkvartering til gæster; Tilvejebringelse af information om indkvartering via internettet; Formidling af information om ferieindkvartering, samt booking heraf; Tilvejebringelse af information om overnatning, via internettet; Tilvejebringelse af information om overnatning; Reservation af midlertidig indkvartering; Information, rådgivning og reservation i forbindelse med midlertidig indkvartering; Reservation af midlertidigt indkvartering via internet; Information vedrørende reservation af indkvartering; Reservation af midlertidig indkvartering i form af ferieboliger; Reservation af indkvartering til rejsende; Midlertidig indkvarteringsservice udbudt af ferielejre; Indlogering i ferielejre; Arrangering af midlertidig indkvartering for ferierejsende; Bedømmelse af ferieindkvartering; Reservationsvirksomhed i forbindelse med ferieindkvartering; Ferieindlogeringsvirksomhed; Midlertidig indkvartering; Udlejning af midlertidig indkvartering; Rejsebureautjenester til bookning af indkvartering; Tilvejebringelse af parkeringsfaciliteter til husvogne; Tilvejebringelse af midlertidig indlogering.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Buchung von Campingplätzen; Zurverfügungstellen von Onlineinformationen zur Buchung von Ferienunterkünften; Bereitstellung von vorübergehenden Unterkünften für Gäste; Zurverfügungstellen von Unterkunftsinformationen über das Internet; Zurverfügungstellen von Unterkunftsinformation sowie Dienstleistungen einer Unterkunftsbuchungsstelle für Reisende; Zurverfügungstellen von Informationen zu vorübergehender Beherbergung via Internet; Zurverfügungstellen von Informationen zu Beherbergungsdienstleistungen; Zimmerreservierung; Informations, Beratungs- und Reservierungsdienste in Bezug auf die vorübergehende Beherbergung von Gästen; Reservierung von vorübergehender Beherbergung via Internet; Erteilen von Auskünften in Bezug auf die Buchung von Unterkünften; Reservierung von vorübergehender Beherbergung in Ferienheimen; Buchung von Unterkünften für Reisende; Von Feriencamps zur Verfügung gestellte vorübergehende Beherbergung; Beherbergungsdienstleistungen im Rahmen von Feriencamps; Vermietung von Ferienanlagen; Bewertung von Ferienunterkünften; Dienstleistungen zur Reservierung von Ferienunterkünften; Dienstleistungen in Bezug auf Ferienunterkünfte; Vorübergehende Beherbergung von Gästen; Vermietung von Gästezimmern; Reiseagenturdienstleistungen für die Buchung von Unterkünften; Vermietung von Wohnwagenparkeinrichtungen; Vermietung von Unterkünften für Gäste.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κρατήσεις σε εγκαταστάσεις κατασκήνωσης· Παροχή πληροφοριών στο διαδίκτυο σε σχέση με κρατήσεις παραθεριστικών καταλυμάτων· Παροχή προσωρινού καταλύματος σε φιλοξενούμενους· Διάθεση πληροφοριών για καταλύματα μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Υπηρεσίες παροχής πληροφοριών για ταξιδιωτικά καταλύματα και υπηρεσίες πρακτορείων κρατήσεων καταλύματος για ταξιδιώτες· Παροχή πληροφοριών σχετικά με προσωρινά καταλύματα μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Παροχή πληροφοριών σχετικά με υπηρεσίες προσωρινών καταλυμάτων· Κράτηση εποχιακής στέγασης· Υπηρεσίες παροχής πληροφοριών, συμβουλών και κρατήσεων για προσωρινή κατάλυση· Κρατήσεις προσωρινών καταλυμάτων μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Παροχή πληροφοριών σχετικά με την κράτηση καταλυμάτων· Κράτηση προσωρινού καταλύματος με τη μορφή παραθεριστικής κατοικίας· Κρατήσεις καταλυμάτων για ταξιδιώτες· Υπηρεσίες προσωρινού καταλύματος παρεχόμενες από παραθεριστικές κατασκηνώσεις· Κατασκηνώσεων διακοπών (υπηρεσίες -) [φιλοξενία]· Παραθεριστικά καταλύματα· Αξιολογική κατάταξη παραθεριστικών καταλυμάτων· Υπηρεσίες για την κράτηση παραθεριστικών καταλυμάτων· Υπηρεσίες παραθεριστικού καταλύματος· Προσωρινή κατάλυση· Μίσθωση εποχιακής στέγασης· Υπηρεσίες ταξιδιωτικών πρακτορείων για την κράτηση καταλύματος· Παροχή εγκαταστάσεων για στάθμευση τροχοσπίτων· Παροχή προσωρινής στέγασης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Booking of campground accommodation; Providing on-line information relating to holiday accommodation reservations; Providing temporary lodging for guests; Providing lodging information via the Internet; Providing travel lodging information services and travel lodging booking agency services for travelers; Providing information about temporary accommodation via the Internet; Providing information about temporary accommodation services; Temporary accommodation reservations; Temporary accommodation information, advice and reservation services; Booking of temporary accommodation via the Internet; Provision of information relating to the booking of accommodation; Reservation of temporary accommodation in the nature of holiday homes; Booking of accommodation for travellers; Temporary accommodation services provided by holiday camps; Holiday camp services [lodging]; Arranging of accommodation for holiday makers; Rating holiday accommodation; Services for reserving holiday accommodation; Holiday accommodation services; Temporary accommodation; Rental of temporary accommodation; Travel agency services for booking accommodation; Provision of caravan park facilities; Providing temporary housing accommodations.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Reserva de alojamiento en camping; Suministro de información en línea sobre reservas de alojamientos de vacaciones; Servicios de hospedaje temporal para huéspedes; Suministro de información por Internet sobre alojamiento; Suministro de información sobre hospedaje para viajeros y servicios prestados por agencias de reserva de alojamientos para viajeros; Suministro de información sobre alojamiento temporal por Internet; Suministro de información sobre servicios de hospedaje temporal; Reserva de alojamiento temporal; Servicios de información, asesoramiento y reserva de alojamiento temporal; Reserva de alojamientos temporales por Internet; Facilitación de información relativa a la reserva de alojamiento; Reserva de alojamiento temporal en casas de vacaciones; Servicios de reservas de alojamiento para viajeros; Servicios de hospedaje temporal en campamentos de vacaciones; Servicios de campamentos de vacaciones [hospedaje]; Organización de alojamiento para veraneantes; Valoración de alojamientos de vacaciones; Servicios para la reserva de alojamiento de vacaciones; Servicios de alojamiento para vacaciones; Servicios de hospedaje temporal; Alquiler de alojamiento temporal; Servicios de reserva de alojamiento prestados por agencias de viajes; Instalaciones de parques de caravanas; Alojamiento temporal en casas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Laagriplatsi majutuskohtade broneerimine; Teabe pakkumine veebis seoses puhkusereisi majutuse reserveerimisega; Külalistele ajutise majutuse pakkumine; Majutusinfo pakkumine Interneti kaudu; Reisijatele reisimajutuse teabe ja reisimajutuse broneerimisagentuuri teenuste pakkumine; Ajutise majutuse teabe pakkumine Interneti kaudu; Ajutise majutuse teabe pakkumine; Ajutise elamispinna ettetellimine, reserveerimine; Ajutise majutuse teabe, nõustamise ja reserveerimise teenused; Ajutise majutuse broneerimine Interneti kaudu; Majutusbroneeringute teabeteenused; Ajutise majutuskoha rentimine puhkekodudes; Majutuskohtade broneerimine reisijaile; Turismibaasides ajutise majutusteenuse pakkumine; Puhkelaagriteenused [majutus]; Puhkusemajutuse korraldamine; Puhkusemajutuse hindamine; Puhkemajutuse reserveerimine; Majutusteenused puhkajaile; Tähtajaline majutamine; Ajutise elamispinna üürimine; Majutuskohtade broneerimine reisiagentuuri kaudu; Karavanipargiteenused; Tähtajaline majutus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Leirimajoitusvaraukset; Lomamajoitusvarauksiin liittyvän online-tiedotuksen tarjoaminen; Tilapäismajoituksen tarjoaminen vieraille; Majoitustietojen tarjoaminen Internetin kautta; Majoitustietopalvelujen ja majoituksen varausta koskevien toimistopalvelujen tarjoaminen matkailijoille; Tilapäismajoitusta koskevan tiedotuksen tarjoaminen Internetin välityksellä; Tilapäismajoituspalveluita koskevan tiedotuksen tarjoaminen; Tilapäismajoitusvaraukset; Tilapäismajoitusta koskevat tiedotus-, neuvonta- ja varauspalvelut; Tilapäisen majoituksen varaaminen Internetin kautta; Majoitusvarauksiin liittyvän tiedon tarjoaminen; Väliaikaismajoituksen varaaminen lomakotien muodossa; Majoituksen varaaminen matkailijoille; Lomakylien tarjoamat tilapäismajoituspalvelut; Lomamajoituspalvelut leirintäalueiden yhteydessä; Lomamajoitukset; Lomamajoitusten luokitus; Lomamajoituksen varauspalvelut; Lomamajoituspalvelut; Tilapäismajoitus; Tilapäisten majoitustilojen vuokraus; Matkatoimistojen majoitusvarauspalvelut; Asuntovaunualueiden tarjoaminen; Tilapäismajoituksen tarjoaminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Réservation de logements dans des campings; Mise à disposition d'informations en ligne en matière de réservation de logements de vacances; Mise à disposition de logements temporaires pour des clients; Mise à disposition d'informations en matière d'hébergement par le biais d'internet; Services d'informations en matière d'hébergements dans le domaine du voyage et services de réservation d'hébergements pour voyageurs; Mise à disposition d'informations en matière d'hébergement temporaire par le biais d'Internet; Mise à disposition d'informations en matière de services d'hébergement temporaire; Réservation de logements temporaires; Services d’information, de conseil et de réservation relatifs à des hébergements temporaires; Réservation de logements temporaires par le biais d'Internet; Services d'informations en matière de réservation de logements; Réservation de logements temporaires sous la forme de maisons de vacances; Services de réservations de logement pour voyageurs; Services d'hébergement temporaire fournis par des camps de vacances; Services de camps de vacances [hébergement]; Location de logements de vacances; Classification de logements de vacances; Services de réservation de logements de vacances; Services de logements pour vacances; Logement temporaire; Location de logements temporaires; Services d'agences de voyage pour la réservation de logements; Mise à disposition d'infrastructures pour aires de caravaning; Mise à disposition de logements temporaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Rezerviranje smještaja u kampu; Pružanje informacija na Internetu o rezervaciji smještaja za odmor; Pružanje privremenog smještaja za goste; Pružanje informacija o smještaju, putem Interneta; Pružanje usluga informacija o smještaju i usluga rezervacije smještaja za putnike; Pružanje informacija o privremenom smještaju putem Interneta; Pružanje informacija o uslugama privremenog smještaja; Usluge rezervacije smještaja; Usluge pružanja informacija, savjetovanja i rezervacija u vezi privremenog smještaja; Rezervacija privremenog smještaja putem Interneta; Pružanje informacija u svezi s rezerviranjem smještaja; Rezervacija privremenog smještaja u obliku vikendica; Rezerviranje smještaja za putnike; Usluge privremenog smještaja koje pružaju kampovi; Ljetovanje [usluge kampova za ljetovanje]; Organiziranje smještaja za turiste; Rangiranje turističkog smještaja; Usluge za rezervaciju turističkog smještaja; Usluge turističkog smještaja; Privremeni smještaj; Iznajmljivanje privremenih smještaja; Usluge turističkih agencija za rezerviranje smještaja; Usluge parkirališta za kamp-kućice; Pružanje privremenog smještaja za stanovanje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kempingszállások foglalása; Online információnyújtás nyaralási szállások lefoglalásával kapcsolatban; Ideiglenes szálláshelyek biztosítása vendégek számára; Szállásinformációk biztosítása az interneten; Utazási szállásadási információs szolgáltatások és utazási szállásfoglalási ügynökségi szolgáltatások utazók számára; Információk biztosítása ideiglenes szálláslehetőségekkel kapcsolatosan az interneten keresztül; Információk biztosítása ideiglenes szálláslehetőségek biztosításával kapcsolatban; Szállásfoglalás; Időszakos szállásfoglalással kapcsolatos információs, tanácsadási és foglalási szolgáltatások; Ideiglenes szállások foglalása az interneten keresztül; Szállásfoglalással kapcsolatos információnyújtás; Ideiglenes szállás foglalása nyaralókban; Szállásfoglalás utazók számára; Üdülőtáborok által biztosított ideiglenes szálláshelyek; Üdülőtáborok szolgáltatásai [szállásadás]; Szállásbiztosítás nyaralók számára; Üdülőszállások értékelése; Üdülési szállásfoglalási szolgáltatások; Üdülési szállás biztosítása; Ideiglenes szállásbiztosítás; Átmeneti szállások kiadása; Utazási irodák által nyújtott szállásfoglalási szolgáltatások; Lakókocsipark létesítmények biztosítása; Ideiglenes elszállásolás biztosítása.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Prenotazione di sistemazione in campeggio; Fornitura di informazioni online in tema di prenotazione di alloggi di vacanza; Fornitura di alloggi temporanei per gli ospiti; Fornitura di informazioni in tema di alloggio tramite internet; Fornitura di informazioni inerenti gli alloggi di viaggio e servizi di agenzia di viaggio per la prenotazione di alloggi per viaggiatori; Fornitura di informazioni in tema di alloggi temporanei tramite internet; Fornitura di informazioni in tema di servizi di alloggio temporaneo; Prenotazione di abitazioni temporanee; Servizi di informazione, consulenza e prenotazione in materia di alloggi temporanei; Prenotazione di alloggi temporanei tramite internet; Servizio fornitura informazioni relative alla prenotazione di alloggi; Prenotazione di alloggi temporanei sotto forma di case per vacanze; Prenotazione di alloggi per viaggiatori; Servizi di alloggio temporaneo forniti da campeggi per vacanze; Servizi di campi di vacanze [alloggio]; Organizzazione di alloggi per vacanze; Valutazione di alloggi per vacanze; Servizi per la prenotazione di alloggi per vacanze; Servizi relativi ad alloggi per vacanze; Alloggi temporanei; Locazione di alloggi temporanei; Servizi di agenzia di viaggi per prenotazioni alberghiere; Fornitura di strutture per aree per roulotte; Fornitura di alloggi temporanei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Poilsio stovyklaviečių užsakymas; Informacijos apie poilsinės gyvenamosios vietos rezervavimą teikimas internetu; Laikinas svečių apgyvendinimas; Informacijos apie apgyvendinimą teikimas internetu; Informacinių paslaugų apie laikiną keliautojų apgyvendinimą teikimas ir laikiną keliautojų apgyvendinimą užsakančių agentūrų paslaugos keliautojams; Informacijos apie laikiną apgyvendinimą teikimas internetu; Informacijos apie laikino apgyvendinimo paslaugas teikimas; Laikino būsto parūpinimas; Laikinojo apgyvendinimo informacijos, patarimų ir rezervavimo paslaugos; Laikino būsto rezervavimas internetu; Informacija apie laikino būsto rezervavimą; Vasarnamių laikinai apsigyventi rezervavimas; Būsto keliautojams užsakymas; Poilsio stovyklų teikiamos laikino apgyvendinimo paslaugos; Trumpo poilsio stovyklų paslaugos [nuomojamos patalpos]; Laikino apgyvendinimo patalpų atostogautojams nuoma; Apgyvendinimo patalpų vertinimas; Laikino apgyvendinimo patalpų atostogoms rezervavimo paslaugos; Apgyvendinimo atostogų metu paslaugos; Laikinas apgyvendinimas; Trumpa patalpų nuoma; Kelionių agentūrų paslaugos nakvynei užsakyti; Priekabinių namelių stovėjimo aikštelių paslaugos; Laikino būsto parūpinimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Nometņu vietu rezervēšanas pakalpojumi; Informācijas sniegšana tiešsaistē par brīvdienu mītņu rezervēšanu; Pagaidu mājvietu nodrošināšana viesiem; Informācijas sniegšana par naktsmītnēm ar interneta starpniecību; Informācijas sniegšana par ceļotāju mītnēm un ceļotāju mītņu rezervēšanas aģentūru pakalpojumiem; Informācijas sniegšana ar interneta starpniecību par īslaicīgās uzturēšanās mītņu piedāvātajiem pakalpojumiem; Informācijas sniegšana par īslaicīgās uzturēšanās mītņu piedāvātajiem pakalpojumiem; Īslaicīgās uzturēšanās mītņu rezervēšana; Īslaicīgās uzturēšanās informācijas, padomu un rezervēšanas pakalpojumi; Īslaicīgās uzturēšanās mītņu rezervēšana ar interneta starpniecību; Informācijas sniegšana saistībā ar apmešanās vietu rezervēšanu; Īslaicīgās uzturēšanās brīvdienu māju rezervēšana; Apmešanās vietu rezervēšana ceļotājiem; Īslaicīgās uzturēšanās nodrošināšana brīvdienu nometnēs; Brīvdienu nometņu pakalpojumi (izmitināšana); Brīvdienu mājvietu noma; Brīvdienu mājvietu novērtēšana; Pakalpojumi, kas paredzēti brīvdienu mājvietu rezervēšanai; Tūristu apmešanās vietu pakalpojumi; Viesu izmitināšana; Īslaicīgās uzturēšanās mītņu izīrēšana; Ceļojumu aģentūru pakalpojumi mājvietu rezervēšanai; Autofurgonu parku nodrošināšana; Īslaicīgās uzturēšanās mājokļu nodrošināšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Prenotazzjoni ta' akkomodazzjoni tal-postijiet tal-kampeġġ; Il-provvista ta' informazzjoni onlajn dwar ibbukkjar ta' alloġġ għal vaganzi; Provvista ta' akkomodazzjoni temporanja għall-mistednin; Il-provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar alloġġ permezz tal-Internet; Provvista ta' servizzi ta' informazzjoni dwar l-akkomodazzjoni waqt l-ivvjaġġar u servizzi ta' aġenziji tal-ibbukkjar ta' akkomodazzjoni waqt l-ivjaġġar għall-vjaġġaturi; Provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar akkomodazzjonijiet temporanja permezz tal-Internet; Provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar servizzi ta' akkomodazzjoni temporanja; Servizzi ta' riservazzjoni ta' kmamar; Servizzi ta' informazzjoni, pariri u riservazzjoni ta' akkomodazzjoni temporanja; Ibbukkjar ta' akkomodazzjoni temporanja minn fuq l-internet; Il-provvista ta' informazzjoni relatata mal-prenotazzjoni ta' akkomodazzjoni; Reservar ta' akkomodazzjoni temporanja fl-għamla ta' djar tal-vaganzi; Servizzi ta' prenotazzjoni ta' akkomodazzjoni għall-vjaġġaturi; Servizzi ta' akkomodazzjoni temporanja pprovduti minn kampijiet tal-vaganzi; Servizzi ta' kampeġġ għall-vaganzi [alloġġ]; L-arranġament għall-akkomodazzjoni għal dawk li jmorru vaganza; Ikklassifikar ta' akkomodazzjonijiet tal-vaganzi; Servizzi għar-riservazzjoni ta' akkomodazzjoni għall-vaganzi; Servizzi ta' akkomodazzjoni għall-vaganzi; Akkomodazzjoni temporanja; Il-kiri ta' akkomodazzjoni temporanja; Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-ivvjaġġar għall-prenotazzjoni ta' akkomodazzjoni; Il-provvista ta' faċilitajiet ta' parkeġġ għall-karavans; Il-provvista ta' akkomodazzjoni temporanja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kampeeraccommodatie (Reserveren van -); Verstrekken van online informatie met betrekking tot reserveringen voor vakantieaccommodaties; Verstrekken van tijdelijke accommodatie voor gasten; Verstrekken van informatie over accommodaties via internet; Informatieverstrekking over diensten voor reisaccommodatie en agentschappen voor het boeken van de reisaccommodatie, voor reizigers; Het verstrekken van informatie over tijdelijke huisvesting via het internet; Het verstrekken van informatie over tijdelijke huisvesting; Reservering van tijdelijke accommodaties; Informatie-, advies- en reserveringsdiensten inzake tijdelijke accommodatie; Reservering van tijdelijke huisvesting via het internet; Boeken van accomodatie (Informatie inzake -); Reservering van tijdelijke huisvesting in de aard van vakantiehuizen; Accomodatie voor reizigers (Het boeken van -); Tijdelijke huisvesting door vakantiekampen; Vakantiekampen [logies]; Verhuur van vakantiehuisvesting; Informatie met betrekking tot de kwaliteit van vakantiehuisvesting; Reservering van vakantiehuisvesting; Diensten op het gebied van vakantieaccommodatie; Tijdelijke huisvesting; Verhuur van tijdelijke huisvesting; Reisbureaudiensten voor het boeken van accommodatie; Het ter beschikking stellen van faciliteiten voor een caravan park; Tijdelijke huisvesting (Verstrekken van -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Rezerwacja miejsc na kempingach; Udzielanie informacji online dotyczących rezerwacji zakwaterowania na czas wakacji; Udostępnianie zakwaterowania tymczasowego dla gości; Udostępnianie informacji na temat zakwaterowania przez Internet; Świadczenie usług informacyjnych dotyczących zakwaterowania dla podróżnych oraz usług agencyjnych w zakresie rezerwacji zakwaterowania dla podróżnych; Udostępnianie informacji o tymczasowym zakwaterowaniu za pośrednictwem Internetu; Udostępnianie informacji o usługach tymczasowego zakwaterowania; Usługi rezerwacji pokojów; Usługi informacji, doradztwa i rezerwacji w zakresie zakwaterowania tymczasowego; Rezerwacja zakwaterowania tymczasowego za pośrednictwem Internetu; Udzielanie informacji dotyczących rezerwacji zakwaterowania; Rezerwowanie tymczasowego zakwaterowania w postaci domów wakacyjnych; Rezerwacja zakwaterowania na rzecz podróżnych; Usługi zakwaterowania tymczasowego świadczone przez obozy wakacyjne; Usługi w zakresie obozów wakacyjnych [zakwaterowanie]; Organizowanie zakwaterowania dla wczasowiczów; Ocena zakwaterowania wakacyjnego; Usługi rezerwacji zakwaterowania na wakacje; Usługi w zakresie kwater wczasowych; Tymczasowe zakwaterowanie; Wynajmowanie zakwaterowania na pobyt czasowy; Usługi biur podróży w zakresie rezerwacji zakwaterowania; Udostępnianie obiektów i sprzętu dla przyczep kempingowych; Zapewnianie zakwaterowania tymczasowego w domach i mieszkaniach.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Reserva de alojamento em parques de campismo; Disponibilização de informação online sobre reservas de alojamento em férias; Disponibilização de alojamento temporário para hóspedes; Fornecimento de informação de alojamento via Internet; Prestação de serviços de informação sobre alojamento de viagens e de serviços de agências de reserva de alojamento de viagens para viajantes; Disponibilização de informação sobre alojamento temporário via Internet; Disponibilização de informação sobre serviços de alojamento temporário; Reservas de alojamento temporário; Serviços de informação, aconselhamento e reserva relativos a alojamento temporário; Reserva de alojamento temporário via Internet; Prestação de informações relacionadas com reserva de alojamento; Reserva de alojamento temporário em casas de férias; Reserva de alojamento para viajantes; Serviços de alojamento temporário em campos de férias; Serviços de campos de férias [hospedagem/albergaria]; Organização de alojamentos de férias; Classificação de alojamentos para férias; Serviços para reserva de alojamento de férias; Serviços de alojamentos para férias; Alojamento temporário; Aluguer de alojamento temporário; Serviços de agência de viagens para reserva de alojamento; Fornecimento de instalações para estacionamento de caravanas; Fornecimento de alojamento habitacional temporário.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Rezervare de spații de cazare în cadrul campingurilor; Furnizare de informații online despre rezervări de cazare pentru concediu; Furnizare de cazare temporară pentru oaspeți; Furnizare de informații pe internet despre cazare; Prestare de servicii de informații despre cazare pe timpul călătoriilor și servicii de agenții pentru rezervarea cazării pe timpul călăloriilor, oferite călătorilor; Furnizare de informații pe internet despre cazarea temporară; Furnizare de informații despre servicii de cazare temporară; Rezervări de spații de cazare temporară; Servicii de informare, de consiliere și de rezervare în legătură cu cazarea temporară; Rezervare pe internet de cazare temporară; Furnizare de informații cu privire la rezervarea de locuri de cazare; Rezervare de cazare temporară sub formă de case de vacanță; Rezervare de locuri de cazare pentru călători; Servicii de cazare temporară oferite de campinguri de vacanță; Servicii oferite de tabere de vacanță [cazare]; Organizare de locuri de cazare pentru vacanțe; Evaluare locuri de cazare pe timp de vacanță; Servicii de rezervare de locuri de cazare pentru vacanțe; Servicii de cazare pentru vacanțe; Cazare temporară; Închirieri de spații de cazare temporară; Servicii de agenții de turism privind rezervări de cazare; Furnizare de instalații pentru parcuri de rulote; Furnizare de găzduire temporară în locuințe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Rezervovanie kempingového ubytovania; Poskytovanie on-line informácií v oblasti rezervovania dovolenkového ubytovania; Poskytovanie dočasného ubytovania pre hostí; Poskytovanie ubytovacích informácií prostredníctvom internetu; Poskytovanie informácií o cestovnom ubytovaní a služieb agentúr v oblasti rezervovania ubytovania pre cestujúcich; Poskytovanie informácií o dočasnom ubytovaní prostredníctvom internetu; Poskytovanie informácií o službách dočasného ubytovania; Rezervácie prechodného ubytovania; Informačné, poradenské a rezervačné služby týkajúce sa dočasného ubytovania; Rezervácia dočasného ubytovania cez internet; Poskytovanie informácií týkajúcich sa rezervácie ubytovania; Rezervácia dočasného ubytovania v podobe rekreačných domov; Rezervovanie ubytovania pre cestovateľov; Poskytovanie služieb prechodného ubytovania v dovolenkových táboroch; Prázdninové tábory (ubytovacie služby); Zabezpečenie ubytovania pre dovolenkárov; Hodnotenie dovolenkového ubytovania; Služby v oblasti rezervácie dovolenkového ubytovania; Zabezpečenie ubytovania pre dovolenkárov; Prechodné ubytovanie; Prenájom prechodného ubytovania; Služby cestovných kancelárií pre rezervovanie ubytovania; Poskytovanie karavanových parkov; Poskytovanie prechodného ubytovania.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Rezervacije nastanitev v kampu; Nudenje spletnih informacij v zvezi z rezervacijami počitniške nastanitve; Nudenje začasne nastanitve za goste; Nudenje informacij o nastanitvah preko interneta; Nudenje informacijskih storitev v zvezi s potovalno nastanitvijo in agencijskih storitev rezervacije nastanitve za popotnike; Nudenje informacij o nudenju začasne nastanitve preko interneta; Nudenje informacij o storitvah začasne nastanitve; Storitve rezervacije sob; Storitve informacij, svetovanja in rezervacij v zvezi z začasnimi namestitvami; Rezervacije začasne nastanitve preko interneta; Nudenje informacij v zvezi z rezervacijo nastanitve; Rezervacije začasne nastanitve v obliki počitniških domov; Rezervacija nastanitve za popotnike; Storitve začasne nastanitve, ki jih nudijo počitniški kampi; Storitve počitniških kampov [nastanitve]; Organizacija nastanitev za turiste; Ocenjevanje počitniške nastanitve; Storitve za rezervacijo počitniške nastanitve; Storitve počitniških nastanitev; Začasna nastanitev; Najem začasnih nastanitev; Storitve potovalnih agencij za rezervacijo nastanitev; Nudenje zmogljivosti parkirišč za bivalne prikolice; Nudenje začasne stanovanjske nastanitve.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bokning av boende på campingplatser; Tillhandahållande av direktansluten information om bokningar av semesterboende; Tillhandahållande av tillfällig inkvartering för gäster; Tillhandahållande av information om logi via internet; Tillhandahållande av tjänster avseende information om semesterboende och av byråtjänster avseende bokning av semesterboende; Tillhandahållande av information om tillfälligt boende via internet; Tillhandahållande av information om tillfälliga boendetjänster; Bokning av tillfälligt boende; Bokningstjänster avseende tillfälligt boende; Reservationer för bokning av logi; Information, rådgivning och bokning avseende tillfälligt boende; Bokning av tillfälligt boende via internet; Upplåtande av information avseende bokning av kortvarigt boende; Bokning av tillfälligt boende i form av semesterhem; Bokning av logi för resenärer; Tjänster avseende tillfälligt boende på semesterläger; Semesteranläggningar [logi]; Semesterlogi; Bedömning av semesterinkvartering; Bokningstjänster beträffande semesterboende; Tjänster rörande semesterboende; Tillfälligt boende; Uthyrning av tillfälliga bostäder; Resebyråtjänster för bokning av inkvartering; Tillhandahållande av parkeringsfaciliteter för husvagnar; Upplåtande av kortvarigt boende.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079052</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>21043</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
