<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:43</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224429</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224429</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>CHANGEN</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Радио; Смартфони; Електрически инсталации за дистанционно управление на производствени операции; Предаватели на електронни сигнали; Материали за електропроводи [проводници, кабели]; Уреди за отчитане; Апарати за връзка; Измервателни устройства, електрически; Високочестотни апарати; Видеоекрани.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Rádia; Chytré telefony (smartphony); Elektrická zařízení pro dálkové řízení průmyslových procesů; Vysílače elektronických signálů; Materiály pro elektrická vedení [vodiče, kabely]; Měřící nástroje a zařízení; Interkomunikační zařízení; Elektrické měřicí přístroje; Vysokofrekvenční přístroje a zařízení; Obrazovky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Radioapparater; Smartphones; Elektriske installationer til fjernkontrol af industrielle processer; Sendere af elektroniske signaler; Materiel til elektriske hovedledninger [tråd, kabler]; Måleapparater; Apparater til kommunikation mellem flere; Måleapparater, elektriske; Højfrekvensapparater; Videoskærme.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Radios; Smartphones; Elektrische Anlagen für die Fernsteuerung industrieller Arbeitsvorgänge; Sender für elektronische Signale; Material für elektrische Leitungen [Drahte, Kabel]; Messgeräte; Wechselsprechapparate; Elektrische Messgeräte; Hochfrequenzgeräte; Videobildschirme.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές ραδιοφωνικές· Έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Ηλεκτρικές εγκαταστάσεις για τον έλεγχο από απόσταση βιομηχανικών εργασιών· Πομποί ηλεκτρονικών σημάτων· Υλικά για δίκτυα ηλεκτρισμού [σύρματα, καλώδια]· Μέτρηση (όργανα -ης)· Ενδοεπικοινωνία (συσκευές -ας)· Μέτρηση (ηλεκτρικές συσκευές -ης)· Συχνότητα (συσκευές υψηλής -ας)· Οθόνες βίντεο.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Radios; Smartphones; Electric installations for the remote control of industrial operations; Transmitters of electronic signals; Materials for electricity mains [wires, cables]; Measuring apparatus; Intercommunication apparatus; Measuring devices, electric; High-frequency apparatus; Video screens.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de radio; Teléfonos inteligentes [smartphones]; Instalaciones eléctricas para el control remoto de operaciones industriales; Emisores de señales electrónicas; Material para conducciones eléctricas [hilos, cables]; Aparatos de medición; Aparatos de intercomunicación; Aparatos eléctricos de medición; Aparatos de alta frecuencia; Pantallas de vídeo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Raadiod; Nutitelefonid; Tööstusoperatsioonide kaugjuhtimise elektriseadmed; Elektronsignaalide saatjad; Elektriliinimaterjalid [juhtmed, kaablid]; Mõõteaparaadid, mõõteseadmed; Sisekommunikatsiooniseadmed; Elektrilised mõõteseadmed; Kõrgsagedusaparaadid; Videoekraanid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Radiot; Älypuhelimet; Sähkölaitteistot teollisten toimintojen kauko-ohjaukseen; Lähettimet (elektronisten signaalien); Sähköjakeluverkkokaapelit; Mittalaitteet; Sisäpuhelinlaitteet; Mittalaitteet, sähkötoimiset; Suurtaajuuslaitteet; Videokuvaruudut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils de radio; Ordiphones [smartphones]; Installations électriques pour la commande à distance d'opérations industrielles; Émetteurs de signaux électroniques; Matériel pour conduites d'électricité [fils, câbles]; Mesureurs; Appareils d'intercommunication; Appareils électriques de mesure; Appareils à haute fréquence; Écrans vidéo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Radioaparati; Pametni telefoni; Električne instalacije za daljinsku kontrolu industrijskih operacija; Odašiljači elektroničkih signala; Materijali za električne mreže [žice, kablovi]; Mjerni instrumenti; Interkom uređaji; Električne naprave za mjerenje; Visokofrekventni uređaji; Videoekrani.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Rádiókészülékek; Okostelefonok; Ipari műveletek távirányítására szolgáló elektromos berendezések; Elektronikus jeladók; Anyagok elektromos hálózatokhoz, fővezetékekhez [huzalok, kábelek]; Mérőműszerek; Interkommunikációs berendezések, készülék; Mérőkészülékek, elektromos; Nagyfrekvenciás készülékek; Videoképernyők.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi radio; Smartphone; Installazioni elettriche per il telecomando di operazioni industriali; Emettitori elettronici di segnali; Materiale per condotte per l'elettricità [fili, cavi]; Misuratori; Apparecchi di intercomunicazione; Apparecchi elettrici di misura; Apparecchi ad alta frequenza; Videoschermi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Radijo aparatai; Išmanieji telefonai; Gamybos operacijų nuotolinio valdymo elektros įranga; Elektroninių signalų siųstuvai; Elektros linijų medžiagos [laidai, kabeliai]; Matavimo aparatai; Dupleksinio ryšio aparatai; Elektriniai matavimo prietaisai; Aukštojo dažnio aparatai; Vaizdo ekranai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Radioaparāti; Viedtālruņi; Elektroiekārtas ražošanas procesu tālvadībai; Elektronisko signālu raidītāji; Elektrotīklu materiāli (vadi, kabeļi); Mēraparatūra; Iekšējo sakaru ierīces; Elektriskie mēraparāti; Augstfrekvences aparatūra; Videoekrāni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Radjijiet; Smartfowns; Installazzjonijiet elettriċi għall-kontroll mill-bogħod ta' operazzjonijiet industrijali; Trasmettituri ta' sinjali elettroniċi; Materjali għall-mejns tal-elettriku (linji); Strumenti tal-kejl; Apparat għall-interkomunikazzjoni; Strumenti tal-kejl elettriċi; Apparat bi frekwenza għolja; Skrins tal-vidjo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Radio's; Smartphones; Elektrische apparatuur voor de bediening op afstand van industriële installaties; Zenders van elektronische signalen; Materiaal voor elektrische leidingen [draden, kabels]; Meetapparaten; Intercoms; Elektrische meetapparaten; Hoogfrequentie-apparaten; Videoschermen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Radia [odbiorniki radiowe]; Smartfony; Instalacje elektryczne do zdalnego sterowania procesami przemysłowymi; Nadajniki sygnałów elektronicznych; Materiały na przewody instalacji elektrycznych [kable]; Przyrządy pomiarowe; Urządzenia do komunikacji wewnętrznej; Elektryczne urządzenia pomiarowe; Urządzenia wysokiej częstotliwości; Ekrany wideo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos de rádio; Smartphones; Instalações elétricas para o comando à distância de operações industriais; Emissores de sinais eletrónicos; Materiais para condução elétrica [fios, cabos]; Aparelhos de medição; Aparelhos de intercomunicação; Aparelhos elétricos de medida; Aparelhos de alta frequência; Ecrãs de vídeo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Radiouri; Telefoane inteligente; Instalații electrice pentru controlul de la distanță al operațiilor industriale; Emițătoare de semnale electronice; Materiale pentru rețeaua de electricitate [fire, cabluri]; Instrumente de măsurare; Aparate pentru intercomunicații; Aparate electrice de măsurare; Aparate de înaltă frecvență; Ecrane video.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Rádiá; Smartfóny; Elektrické zariadenia na diaľkové ovládanie priemyselných operácií; Vysielače elektronických signálov; Materiály na elektrické vedenie (drôty, káble); Meracie prístroje; Prístroje na vnútornú komunikáciu; Elektrické meracie zariadenia; Vysokofrekvenčné prístroje; Video displeje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Radii; Pametni telefoni; Električne inštalacije za daljinsko upravljanje industrijskih procesov; Oddajniki za elektronske signale; Materiali za električno napeljavo [žice, kabli]; Merilni instrumenti; Aparati za medsebojno zvezo; Električne merilne naprave; Visokofrekvenčni aparati; Video zasloni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Radioapparater; Smartphones; Elektriska installationer för fjärrkontroll av industriella funktioner; Sändare av elektroniska signaler; Material för elektriska huvudledningar [tråd, kablar]; Mätapparater; Internkommunikationsapparater; Elektriska mätredskap; Högfrekvensapparater; Videoskärmar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>38</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Доставка на телекомуникационни връзки с глобална компютърна мрежа; Предаване на цифрови файлове; Телевизионни предавания, емисии; Комуникации чрез компютърни терминали; Информационни услуги в областта на телекомуникациите; Предоставяне на достъп до глобална компютърна мрежа [услуги на доставчици]; Комуникации чрез фиброоптични мрежи; Стрийминг на данни; Предаване на съобщения и образи с помощта на компютри; Предоставяне на достъп до бази данни.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Poskytování telekomunikačního připojení ke globální počítačové síti; Přenos digitálních souborů; Televizní vysílání; Komunikace prostřednictvím počítačových terminálů; Informace o telekomunikaci; Poskytování uživatelského přístupu do globální počítačové sítě; Komunikace po síti optických vláken; Streaming dat; Přenos zpráv a obrázků pomocí počítačů; Poskytování přístupu do databází.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Etablering af forbindelse til et computernetværk [telekommunikation]; Transmission af digitale filer; Fjernsynsudsendelse; Kommunikation via computerskærme; Stillen information til rådighed om telekommunikation; Stille brugeradgange til rådighed på globale computernetværk; Fiberoptisk netværkskommunikation; Streaming af data; Computerunderstøttet transmission af meddelelser og billeder; Tilvejebringelse af adgang til databaser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bereitstellen von Telekommunikationsverbindungen zu einem weltweiten Computernetzwerk; Übermittlung digitaler Dateien; Ausstrahlung von Fernsehprogrammen; Kommunikationsdienste mittels Computerterminals; Auskünfte über Telekommunikation; Bereitstellen des Zugriffs auf ein weltweites Computernetzwerk; Kommunikation durch faseroptische Netzwerke; Streaming von Daten; Nachrichten- und Bildübermittlung mittels Computer; Verschaffen des Zugriffs zu Datenbanken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Σύνδεση τηλεπικοινωνιακή σε παγκόσμιο δίκτυο πληροφορικής· Μετάδοση ψηφιακών αρχείων· Αναμετάδοση τηλεοπτικών εκπομπών· Υπηρεσίες επικοινωνίας μέσω τερματικών ηλεκτρονικού υπολογιστή· Πληροφόρηση τηλεπικοινωνιών· Παροχή σε χρήστες πρόσβασης σε παγκόσμια δίκτυα ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Επικοινωνία μέσω δικτύων οπτικών ινών· Συνεχής ροή δεδομένων· Διαβίβαση μηνυμάτων και εικόνων με ηλεκτρονικό υπολογιστή· Παροχή πρόσβασης σε βάσεις δεδομένων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Providing telecommunications connections to a global computer network; Transmission of digital files; Television broadcasting; Communications by computer terminals; Information about telecommunication; Providing user access to global computer networks; Communications by fibre optic networks; Streaming of data; Computer aided transmission of messages and images; Providing access to databases.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de conexión telemática a una red informática mundial; Transmisión de archivos digitales; Teledifusión; Comunicaciones por terminales de ordenador; Información sobre telecomunicaciones; Servicios de proveedores de acceso a usuario a redes informáticas mundiales; Comunicaciones por redes de fibra óptica; Transmisión de flujo continuo de datos [streaming]; Transmisión de mensajes e imágenes asistida por ordenador; Suministro de acceso a bases de datos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Globaalsesse arvutivõrku ühenduse pakkumine teenusena; Digitaalsete failide edastus; Teleringhääling; Kompuuterside, arvutiside; Sideinfo; Globaalsetesse arvutivõrkudesse juurdepääsu pakkumine; Side kiudoptiliste võrkude kaudu; Andmete voogedastamine; Info- ja pildiedastus arvuti abil; Juurdepääsu pakkumine andmebaasidele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Yhteyksien tarjoaminen maailmanlaajuiseen tietoverkkoon; Sähköisten tiedostojen lähetys; Televisiolähetys; Viestintä tietokonepäätteiden välityksellä; Kaukoviestintään liittyvä neuvonta; Pääsyn tarjoaminen maailmanlaajuisiin tietoverkkoihin; Viestintä valokuituverkoissa; Datan suoratoisto; Tietokoneavusteinen viestien ja kuvamateriaalin siirto; Yhteyden tarjoaminen tietokantoihin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Raccordement par télécommunications à un réseau informatique mondial; Transmission de fichiers numériques; Télédiffusion; Communications par terminaux d'ordinateurs; Informations en matière de télécommunications; Fourniture d'accès utilisateur à des réseaux informatiques mondiaux; Communications par réseaux de fibres optiques; Transmission de données en flux continu [streaming]; Transmission de messages et d'images assistée par ordinateur; Fourniture d'accès à des bases de données.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Telekomunikacijsko povezivanje na svjetsku informatičku mrežu; Prijenos digitalnih datoteka; Televizijski prijenos; Komunikacije pomoću računalnih terminala; Obavijesti o telekomunikacijama; Omogućavanje pristupa globalnoj računalnoj mreži; Komunikacija optičkim mrežama; Streaming podataka; Prijenos poruka i slika računalom; Omogućavanje pristupa bazama podataka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Telekommunikációs csatlakozások biztosítása egy globális számítógépes hálózathoz; Digitális fájlok továbbítása; Televíziós műsorszórás, közvetítés; Kommunikáció számítógép terminálokkal; Információszolgáltatás távközlési ügyekben; Felhasználói hozzáférés biztosítása számítógépes világhálókhoz; Kommunikáció száloptikás hálózatok segítségével; Nagysebességű adatátvitel; Üzenetek és képek továbbítása számítógépek segítségével; Hozzáférés biztosítása adatbázisokhoz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Allacciamento [per telecomunicazioni] ad una rete informatica mondiale; Trasmissione di file digitali; Telediffusione; Comunicazioni tramite terminali di computers; Informazioni in materia di telecomunicazioni; Fornitura di accesso ad una rete informatica mondiale; Comunicazioni attraverso reti di fibre ottiche; Trasmissione di dati in streaming; Trasmissione di messaggi e di immagini con l'aiuto di un computer; Fornitura di accesso a delle banche dati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Telekomunikacinio prijungimo prie visuotinio kompiuterių tinklo parūpinimas; Skaitmeninių rinkmenų perdavimas; Televizijos transliavimas; Ryšiai per kompiuterių terminalus; Informacija apie telekomunikacijas; Naudotojų kreipties į visuotinį kompiuterių tinklą parūpinimas; Ryšiai per pluoštinį optinį tinklą; Srautinis duomenų perdavimas; Kompiuterizuotas pranešimų ir vaizdų perdavimas; Prieigos prie duomenų bazių parūpinimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Telesakaru pieslēgumu nodrošināšana globālajam datortīklam; Digitālo datņu (failu) pārraide; Televīzijas apraide; Sakaru pakalpojumi ar datoru terminālu starpniecību; Informācijas sniegšana par telesakariem; Lietotāju piekļuves nodrošināšana globālajiem datortīkliem; Sakaru pakalpojumu nodrošināšana caur optisko šķiedru tīkliem; Datu straumēšana; Datorizēta ziņojumu un attēlu pārraide; Piekļuves nodrošināšana datubāzēm.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Il-provvista ta' konnessjonijiet tat-telekomunikazzjoni ma' netwerk tal-kompjuter globali; It-trasmissjoni ta' fajls diġitali; Xandir fuq it-televiżjoni; Komunikazzjoni permezz ta' terminals tal-kompjuter; Informazzjoni dwar telekomunikazzjoni; L-għoti ta' aċċess lill-utenti għal netwerks globali tal-kompjuters; Komunikazzjoni permezz ta' netwerks tal-fibra ottika; Strimjar ta' dejta; It-trasmissjoni ta' messaġġi u xbihat bl-għajnuna tal-kompjuter; Provvista ta' aċċess għal bażi ta' dati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Het tot stand brengen van telecommunicatieverbindingen met een wereldwijd computernetwerk; Transmissie van digitale bestanden; Uitzending van televisieprogramma's; Communicatie via computerterminals; Verschaffen van informatie op het gebied van telecommunicatie; Verschaffen van toegang tot wereldwijde computernetwerken; Communicatie via optische vezelnetwerken; Streamen van data; Computerondersteunde verzending van berichten en beelden; Verschaffen van toegang tot gegevensbestanden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Oferowanie połączeń telekomunikacyjnych z globalną siecią komputerową; Transmisja plików cyfrowych; Transmisja programów telewizyjnych; Łączność poprzez terminale komputerowe; Informacja o telekomunikacji; Zapewnianie dostępu do globalnych sieci komputerowych; Komunikacja za pośrednictwem sieci światłowodowych; Transfer strumieniowy danych; Wspomagane komputerowo przesyłanie wiadomości i obrazów; Zapewnianie dostępu do baz danych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Fornecimento de ligações para telecomunicações a uma rede informática mundial; Transmissão de ficheiros digitais; Teledifusão; Comunicações por terminais de computadores; Informações sobre telecomunicações; Fornecimento de acesso a uma rede informática mundial; Comunicações por redes de fibra ótica; Transmissão de dados por fluxo contínuo [streaming]; Transmissão de mensagens e de imagens assistida por computador; Fornecimento de acesso a bases de dados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Furnizarea conexiunilor de telecomunicații la o rețea informatică mondială; Transmisia de fișiere digitale; Difuzare de programe de televiziune; Comunicații prin terminale de calculator; Informații în domeniul telecomunicațiilor; Furnizarea accesului utilizatorilor la rețelele globale de computere; Comunicații prin rețele de fibră optică; Difuzare de date; Transmitere de mesaje și de imagini cu ajutorul calculatorului; Furnizarea accesului la baze de date.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Poskytovanie telekomunikačného pripojenia do svetovej počítačovej siete; Prenos digitálnych súborov; Televízne vysielanie; Komunikácia prostredníctvom počítačových terminálov; Informácie v oblasti telekomunikácií; Poskytovanie užívateľského prístupu do svetovej počítačovej siete; Komunikácia prostredníctvom optických sietí; Kontinuálny prenos dát (streaming); Prenos správ a obrazových informácií prostredníctvom počítačov; Poskytovanie prístupu do databáz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Omogočanje telekomunikacijskih povezav z globalno računalniško mrežo; Prenos digitalnih datotek; Televizijsko oddajanje; Komuniciranje preko računalniških terminalov; Informacije o telekomunikacijah; Nudenje uporabniškega dostopa do globalne računalniške mreže; Komuniciranje prek omrežij iz optičnih vlaken; Pretok podatkov; Računalniško podprt prenos sporočil in slik; Nudenje dostopa do računalniških baz podatkov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Upplåtande av telekommunikationsanslutningar till ett globalt datanätverk; Överföring av digitala filer; Televisionssändning; Kommunikationer via datorterminaler; Information avseende telekommunikation; Upplåtande av åtkomst till datanätverk; Kommunikation via fiberoptiska nät; Streaming av data; Datorstödd överföring av meddelanden och bilder; Upplåtande av åtkomst till databaser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Услуги на научни лаборатории; Промишлен дизайн; Проектиране на софтуер; Технически надзор; Технически изследвания; Консултантски услуги в областта на компютърния хардуер; Изчисления в облак; Услуги в областта на химията; Изпитване на материали; Тестване [преглед] на превозни средства за годност.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby vědecké laboratoře; Průmyslový design; Tvorba počítačového softwaru; Provádění průzkumů; Technický výzkum; Poradenství v oblasti navrhování a vývoje počítačového hardwaru; Cloud computing; Služby v oblasti chemie; Testování materiálů; Technické kontroly vozidel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Laboratorieydelser, videnskabelige; Industriel design; Design af computerprogrammer; Landmåling; Teknologisk forskning; Rågivning vedrørende design og udvikling af computerhardware; Cloud computing; Tjenesteydelser inden for kemi; Afprøvning af materialer; Test af befordringsmidlers for trafiksikkerhed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wissenschaftliche Labordienstleistungen; Industriedesign; Design von Computer-Software; Erstellung von technischen Gutachten; Forschung auf dem Gebiet der Technik; Beratung im Bereich Entwurf und Entwicklung von Computern; Cloud-Computing; Dienstleistungen eines Chemikers; Materialprüfung; Überprüfen der Straßentauglichkeit von Fahrzeugen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εργαστηριακές (επιστημονικές) υπηρεσίες· Υπηρεσίες βιομηχανικού σχεδιασμού· Σχεδιασμός λογισμικού· Χωρομετρία· Τεχνικές έρευνες· Παροχή συμβουλών σε σχέση με τον σχεδιασμό και την ανάπτυξη υλικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Υπολογιστικό νέφος· Χημείου (Υπηρεσίες -)· Υλικών δοκιμασία· Δοκιμή [επιθεώρηση] οχημάτων όσον αφορά την καταλληλότητά τους για κυκλοφορία.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Scientific laboratory services; Industrial design; Computer software design; Surveying; Technical research; Consultancy in the design and development of computer hardware; Cloud computing; Chemistry services; Material testing; Vehicle roadworthiness testing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de laboratorios científicos; Diseño industrial; Diseño de software; Peritajes [trabajos de ingenieros]; Investigación tecnológica; Consultoría sobre diseño y desarrollo de hardware; Servicios informáticos en la nube; Servicios de química; Ensayo de materiales; Inspección técnica de vehículos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Teaduslikud laboriteenused; Tööstusdisain, tootekujundus; Tarkvara projekteerimine; Mõõdistamine; Tehnilised uuringud; Arvutiriistvara disaini ja arenduse konsultatsioonid ja nõuanded; Pilvandmetöötlus; Keemiateenused; Materjalitestid, materjalide teimimine, testimine, katsetamine; Sõidukite tehnoülevaatus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Laboratoriopalvelut (tieteelliset); Teollinen muotoilu; Ohjelmistosuunnittelu; Maanmittaus; Tekninen tutkimus; Konsultointi liittyen tietokonelaitteiden suunnitteluun ja kehittämiseen; Pilvilaskenta; Kemistipalvelut; Tekstiilien koestus; Ajoneuvojen katsastus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de laboratoires scientifiques; Dessin industriel; Élaboration [conception] de logiciels; Expertises [travaux d'ingénieurs]; Recherches technologiques; Services de conseillers en matière de conception et de développement de matériel informatique; Informatique en nuage; Services de chimie; Essai de matériaux; Contrôle technique de véhicules automobiles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Laboratorijske znanstvene usluge; Industrijski dizajn; Izrada [koncipiranje] računalnih progama; Geodetska mjerenja; Tehnička istraživanja; Savjetovanje o računalima; Cloud računarstvo; Kemijske usluge; Ispitivanje materijala; Tehničko ispitivanje [pregled] vozila.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tudományos laboratóriumi szolgáltatások; Ipari formatervezés; Szoftvertervezés; Mérnöki munkával kapcsolatos mérések, földmérés; Műszaki kutatás; Számítógéphardver tervezésével és fejlesztésével kapcsolatos tanácsadás; Felhőalapú számítástechnika; Vegyészeti szolgáltatások; Anyagtesztelés; Gépjárművek műszaki vizsgálata [közúti közlekedési alkalmasság].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di laboratori scientifici; Disegni industriali; Elaborazione [ideazione] di software; Perizie [lavori d'ingegneria]; Ricerche tecnologiche; Servizi di consulenza nella progettazione e nello sviluppo di materiale informatico; Cloud computing; Servizi di chimica; Collaudi di materiali; Controllo tecnico per autoveicoli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Mokslinių laboratorijų paslaugos; Pramoninis konstravimas; Kompiuterių programinės įrangos projektavimas; Inžineriniai darbai [ekspertizė]; Techniniai tyrimai; Kompiuterių aparatinės įrangos projektavimo ir tobulinimo konsultacijos; Debesų kompiuterija; Chemikų paslaugos; Medžiagų bandymai; Transporto priemonių techninė apžiūra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Zinātnisko laboratoriju pakalpojumi; Rūpnieciskā dizaina pakalpojumi; Datorprogrammu projektēšana; Zemes mērīšanas darbi; Tehnisko pētījumu veikšana; Konsultāciju sniegšana par datortehnikas projektēšanu un izstrādi; Mākoņdatošanas pakalpojumi; Pakalpojumi ķīmijas jomā; Materiālu pārbaude; Automobiļu tehniskā apskate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi (xjentifiċi) fil-laboratorju; Disinn u pjanar industrijali; L-iżvilupp ta' softwer tal-kompjuter; Agrimensura [Perizja]; Riċerka teknika; Konsulenza fid-disinn u l-iżvilupp tal-ħardwer tal-kompjuter; Kunċetti ta' kompjuterizzazzjoni; Servizzi ta' kimika; Testijiet ta' materjali; Ittestjar [Spezzjoni] tal-kondizzjoni ta' vetturi għas-sewqan fit-toroq.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diensten van wetenschappelijke laboratoria; Industrieel ontwerp; Software-ontwikkeling; Expertises [ingenieursdiensten]; Technisch onderzoek; Advisering op het gebied van ontwerp en ontwikkeling van computer hardware; Cloud computing; Diensten van chemici; Testen van materialen; Technische inspectie van vervoermiddelen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi świadczone przez laboratoria naukowe; Wzornictwo przemysłowe; Projektowanie oprogramowania komputerowego; Miernictwo [pomiary]; Badania techniczne; Doradztwo w zakresie projektowania i rozbudowy sprzętu komputerowego; Chmura obliczeniowa; Usługi chemiczne; Testowanie materiałów; Testowanie [kontrola] pojazdów pod kątem sprawności.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços científicos de laboratórios; Design industrial; Design de software; Peritagens [trabalhos de engenheiros]; Pesquisas tecnológicas; Consultoria na conceção e desenvolvimento de hardware; Computação em nuvem; Serviços de química; Testes a materiais; Inspeção técnica de veículos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de laboratoare științifice; Design industrial; Proiectare de software; Expertize tehnice; Cercetare tehnică; Consultanță în proiectarea și dezvoltarea hardware-ului pentru computere; Cloud computing; Servicii in domeniul chimiei; Testarea materialelor textile; Testarea [inspecție] vehiculelor pentru verificarea stării adecvate pentru circulația pe drumuri publice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vedecké laboratórne služby; Priemyselné dizajnérstvo; Tvorba softvéru; Expertízy (inžinierske práce); Technický výskum; Poradenstvo v oblasti návrhu a vývoja počítačového hardvéru; Poskytovanie počítačových technológií prostredníctvom internetu (cloud computing); Chemické služby; Testovanie materiálov; Technická kontrola automobilov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve znanstvenih laboratorijev; Industrijsko oblikovanje; Oblikovanje programske opreme; Geodetske storitve; Tehnične raziskave; Svetovanje na področju oblikovanja in razvoja računalniške opreme; Računalništvo v oblaku; Kemijske storitve; Testiranje materialov; Tehnično preizkušanje vozil glede primernosti za vožnjo [preverjanje].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Vetenskapliga laboratorietjänster; Industriell formgivning; Utformning av programvara; Besiktnings- och inspektionstjänster; Teknisk forskning; Konsultationer inom området för design och utveckling av datorhårdvara; Molntjänster; Kemitjänster; Materialprovning; Testning av fordon för vägsäkerhet [inspektion].</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079099</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>16011</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
