<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-31T14:41:04</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224923</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224923</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-26</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>it</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-31</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>AD VANXE Sports and Supports</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162203841</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/224/018224923/000162203841.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>25.07.05</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.03.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.03.23</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.02</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.08</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.10</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.11</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.22</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.24</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.98</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.99</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.02</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.08</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>29.01.03</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Хирургически маски; Защитно облекло за медицински цели; Хирургическо облекло; Медицински престилки; Облекло, шапки и принадлежности за глава, обувки за медицински персонал и пациенти; Хирургически калъфи за обувки; Хирургически бонета; Гумени ръкавици за медицинска употреба; Маски за лице за медицинска употреба за антибактериална защита; Предпазни очила за медицинска употреба; Листове със силиконов гел за лечение на белези; Химично активирани студени гелови превръзки за медицинска употреба.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Chirurgické masky; Ochranné oděvy pro lékařské účely; Chirurgické oděvy; Lékařské pláště; Oděvy, pokrývky hlavy a obuv pro zdravotnické pracovníky a pacienty; Chirurgické návleky na obuv; Chirurgické čepičky; Gumové rukavice k lékařskému použití; Roušky k použití v chirurgii jako antibakteriální ochrana; Ochranné štíty pro lékařské použití; Silikonové gelové obklady na léčení jizev; Chemicky aktivované chladící gelové sáčky pro lékařské účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Operationsmasker; Beskyttelsesbeklædning til medicinske formål; Operationsdragter; Medicinske operationskitler; Beklædningsgenstande, hovedbeklædning og fodtøj til medicinsk personale og patienter; Kirurgiske skoovertræk; Kirurgiske hætter; Gummihandsker til medicinske formål; Ansigtsmasker til kirurgiske formål til beskyttelse mod bakterier; Beskyttelsesskærme til medicinske formål; Folie af silikonegele til behandling af ar; Kemisk aktiverede kolde gelomslag til medicinske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Chirurgischer Mundschutz; Schutzbekleidung für medizinische Zwecke; Operationsbekleidung; Medizinische Kittel; Bekleidung, Kopfbedeckungen und Schuhwaren für medizinisches Personal und Patienten; Chirurgische Schuhüberzüge; Chirurgische Kappen; Gummihandschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Gesichtsmasken für chirurgische Zwecke zum Schutz vor Bakterien; Schutzvisiere für medizinische Zwecke; Silikongelauflagen zur Narbenbehandlung für medizinische Zwecke; Chemisch aktivierte Kühlgelkompressen für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Χειρουργικές μάσκες· Προστατευτικά ενδύματα για ιατρική χρήση· Χειρουργικές στολές· Ιατρικές ρόμπες· Ενδύματα, είδη πιλοποιίας και υποδήματα για ιατρικό προσωπικό και ασθενείς.· Χειρουργικά καλύμματα παπουτσιών· Χειρουργικοί σκούφοι· Γάντια από καουτσούκ για ιατρική χρήση· Μάσκες χειρουργείου για αντιβακτηριδιακή προστασία· Προστατευτικές προσωπίδες για ιατρική χρήση· Γέλη σιλικόνης σε φύλλα για τη θεραπεία ουλών· Χημικά ενεργοποιούμενες παγοκύστες γέλης για ιατρική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Surgical masks; Protective clothing for medical purposes; Surgical scrub suits; Medical gowns; Clothing, headgear and footwear for medical personnel and patients.; Surgical shoe covers; Surgical caps; Rubber gloves for medical use; Face masks for surgical use for anti bacterial protection; Protective visors for medical use; Silicone gel sheeting for the treatment of scars; Chemically activated cold gel packs for medical use.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Mascarillas quirúrgicas; Ropa protectora para fines médicos; Trajes quirúrgicos; Batas médicas; Prendas de vestir, artículos de sombrerería y calzado para el personal médico y los pacientes; Cubrezapatos quirúrgicos; Gorros quirúrgicos; Guantes de látex para uso médico; Máscaras faciales para protección antibacteriana de uso quirúrgico; Viseras de protección para uso médico; Revestimiento de gel de silicona para el tratamiento de cicatrices; Bolsas de gel para crioterapia activadas mediante reacción química para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kirurgimaskid; Meditsiinis kasutatavad kaitserõivad; Kirurgilised operatsioonikitlid; Meditsiinilised kitlid; Meditsiinitöötajate ja patsientide rõivad, peakatted ja jalatsid; Kirurgilised kingakatted; Kirurgimütsid; Meditsiinilised kummikindad; Kirurgias kasutatavad bakteritevastased kaitsvad näomaskid; Meditsiinilised kaitsesirmid; Silikoongeellehed armide raviks; Meditsiinis kasutatavad keemiliselt aktiveeritud külmad geelipakid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kirurgin naamarit; Suojavaatteet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Pesupuvut kirurgeille; Leikkaussalivaatteet; Vaatteet, päähineet ja jalkineet lääkintähenkilöstölle ja potilaille; Kirurgiset kengänsuojukset; Kirurgiassa käytettävät lakit; Kumikäsineet lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Kasvosuojukset kirurgiseen käyttöön suojaksi bakteereilta; Suojalipat lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Silikonigeelikalvot arpien hoitoon; Kemiallisesti aktivoitavat kylmägeelikääreet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Masques chirurgicaux; Vêtements de protection à usage médical; Tenues chirurgicales stériles; Blouses à usage médical; Vêtements, articles de chapellerie et articles chaussants pour personnel médical et patients; Sur-chaussures à usage chirurgical; Bonnets de chirurgiens; Gants en caoutchouc à usage médical; Masques de protection antibactériens à usage chirurgical; Visières de protection à usage médical; Pellicules de gel de silicone pour le traitement des cicatrices; Compresses de gel froides activées chimiquement à usage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kirurške maske; Zaštitna odjeća za medicinske namjene; Kirurška odijela; Medicinske kute; Odjeća, pokrivala za glavu i obuća za medicinsko osoblje i pacijente; Kirurška pokrivala za cipele; Kirurške kape; Gumene rukavice za medicinsku uporabu; Maske za lice za kiruršku uporabu za antibakterijsku zaštitu; Zaštitni viziri za medicinsku uporabu; Trake od silicijskog gela za liječenje ožiljaka; Kemijski aktivirani oblozi s hladnim gelom za medicinske svrhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Sebészeti maszkok; Védőruházat orvosi célokra; Sebészeti ruhák, műtős ruhák; Orvosi köpenyek; Ruházat, fejfedők és lábbelik ápolószemélyzet és páciensek számára; Sebészeti cipőborítók, cipővédők; Műtős sapkák; Orvosi gumikesztyűk; Arcmaszkok sebészeti használatra baktériumok elleni védelemhez; Orvosi arcvédők, arcvédő maszkok; Hegek, sebhelyek kezelésére szolgáló szilikongél lapok; Kémiailag aktivált hideg zselés pakolások gyógyászati használatra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Mascherine chirurgiche; Abbigliamento protettivo per uso medico; Camici chirurgici; Camici medici; Capi d'abbigliamento, articoli di cappelleria e calzature per personale medico e pazienti; Copriscarpe chirurgici; Cuffie chirurgiche; Guanti di gomma per uso medico; Maschere per il viso per protezione antibatterica; Visiere protettive per uso medico; Gel al silicone per il trattamento di cicatrici; Pacchetti di gel freddo attivati chimicamente per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Chirurginės kaukės; Apsauginiai drabužiai medicininėms reikmėms; Chirurginiai kostiumai [operaciniai]; Medicininiai chalatai; Apranga, galvos apdangalai ir avalynė medicinos personalui ir pacientams; Chirurginiai antbačiai; Chirurginės kepuraitės; Guminės pirštinės medicinos reikmėms; Chirurginės antibakterinės veido kaukės; Medicininiai apsauginiai antveidžiai; Silikono gelio patiesalai randams gydyti; Chemiškai aktyvinami šaldomieji paketai su gelio užpildu (medicinos reikmėms).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ķirurģiskās maskas; Aizsargtērpi medicīniskām vajadzībām; Ķirurģisko operāciju personāla apģērbs; Medicīniskais apģērbs; Apģērbi, galvassegas un apavi medicīnas personālam un pacientiem; Apavu pārvalki ķirurgiem; Ķirurgu cepures; Gumijas cimdi medicīniskam nolūkam; Antibakteriālas sejas maskas ķirurģiskām vajadzībām; Aizsargvizieri, kas paredzēti lietošanai medicīnā; Silikona želejas aizsargpārklājums rētu ārstēšanai; Ķīmiski aktivizēta aukstā gela pakas medicīniskiem nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Maskri kirurġiċi; Ħwejjeġ protettivi għall-użu mediku; Ilbies għall-kirurgi; Ġagagi mediċi; Ħwejjeġ, xedd ir-ras u xedd is-saqajn għall-persunal fil-qasam mediku u għall-pazjenti; Għata taż-żraben kirurġiċi; Brieret għall-kirurġija; Ingwanti tal-lastku għall-użu mediku; Maskri tal-wiċċ għal użu kirurġiku għall-protezzjoni kontra l-batterji; Viżieri protettivi għall-użu mediku; Folji tal-ġell tas-silikon għat-trattament ta' ċikatriċi; Pakketti tal-ġell tal-kesħa attivati kimikament għal skopijiet mediċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Gezichtsmaskers voor chirurgisch gebruik; Beschermende kledingstukken voor medische doeleinden; Operatiepakken (voor chirurgisch gebruik); Schorten (Medische -); Kleding, hoofdbedekking en schoeisel voor medisch personeel en patiënten; Hoezen voor schoenen voor chirurgisch gebruik; Chirurgische mutsen; Rubberen handschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Maskers voor chirurgisch gebruik ter bescherming tegen bacteriën; Beschermbrillen voor medisch gebruik; Siliconengelvellen voor de behandeling van littekens; Chemisch geactiveerde koude gelkompressen voor medische doeleinden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Maski chirurgiczne; Odzież ochronna do celów medycznych; Chirurgiczna odzież operacyjna; Kitle; Odzież, nakrycia głowy i obuwie dla personelu medycznego i pacjentów; Chirurgiczne pokrowce na obuwie; Czepki chirurgiczne; Rękawice gumowe do użytku medycznego; Maski na twarz do użytku w chirurgii dla ochrony przeciwbakteryjnej; Osłony ochronne na twarz do użytku medycznego; Silikonowe plastry żelowe do leczenia blizn; Chemicznie aktywowane zimne kompresy żelowe do celów medycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máscaras cirúrgicas; Vestuário de proteção para uso médico; Vestuário para cirurgia; Batas médicas; Vestuário, chapelaria e calçado para pessoal médico e doentes; Proteções para sapatos cirúrgicos; Toucas cirúrgicas; Luvas de borracha para uso médico; Máscaras cirúrgicas para o rosto para proteção antibacteriana; Viseiras de proteção para uso médico; Folhas de gel de silicone para tratamento de cicatrizes; Bolsas de gel frias ativadas quimicamente, para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Măşti chirurgicale; Îmbrăcăminte de protecţie de uz medical; Costume chirurgicale sterile; Halate medicale; Îmbrăcăminte, articole pentru acoperirea capului și încălțăminte pentru personal medical și pacienți; Huse pentru încălţăminte chirurgicală; Bonete chirurgicale; Mănuşi din cauciuc de uz medical; Măşti chirurgicale pentru protecţie antibacteriană; Viziere de protecţie pentru uz medical; Foi cu gel de silicon pentru tratarea cicatricilor; Pachete cu gel rece activate chimic de uz medical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Chirurgické masky; Ochranné odevy na lekárske účely; Operačné chirurgické odevy; Lekárske nemocničné plášte; Odevy, pokrývky hlavy a obuv pre zdravotníckych pracovníkov a pacientov; Chirurgické návleky na topánky; Chirurgické čiapky; Gumené rukavice na lekárske účely; Chirurgické masky na tvár na antibakteriálnu ochranu; Ochranné čiapkové štíty na lekárske použitie; Silikónové gélové obklady na liečenie jaziev; Chemicky aktivované studené gélové obklady na lekárske účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kirurške maske; Zaščitna oblačila za medicinske namene; Kirurška oblačila za operacije; Medicinske halje; Oblačila, pokrivala in obutev za medicinsko osebje in bolnike; Kirurške prevleke za čevlje; Kirurške kape; Gumijaste rokavice za medicinsko uporabo; Obrazne maske za kirurško uporabo za zaščito pred bakterijami; Zaščitni vizirji za medicinsko uporabo; Obloge s silikonskim gelom za zdravljenje brazgotin; Kemično aktivirane hladilne obloge z gelom, za medicinsko uporabo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Operationsmasker; Skyddskläder för medicinska ändamål; Operationskläder; Läkarrockar; Kläder, huvudbonader och fotbeklädnader för medicinsk personal och patienter; Operationsskoskydd; Operationsmössor; Gummihandskar för medicinskt bruk; Bakterieskyddande ansiktsmasker för kirurgiskt bruk; Skyddsskärmar för medicinskt bruk; Silikondynor för behandling av ärr; Kemiskt aktiverade kalla gelpaket för medicinskt bruk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Спортни артикули и оборудване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Sportovní potřeby a vybavení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sportsartikler og -udstyr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Sportartikel und -ausrüstungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Είδη και εξοπλισμός άθλησης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Sporting articles and equipment.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Equipamientos y artículos deportivos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sporditarbed ja -riistad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Urheiluvälineet ja -varusteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Articles et équipement de sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sportski artikli i oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Sportcikkek és felszerelések.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Articoli e attrezzature sportive.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Sporto reikmenys ir įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Sporta preces un sporta inventārs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Artikli u tagħmir sportivi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Sportartikelen en -uitrustingen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Artykuły i sprzęt sportowy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Artigos e equipamento de desporto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole şi echipament de sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Športové potreby a športový výstroj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Športne potrebščine in oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Sportartiklar och sportutrustning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/093</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-19</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/164</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>478257</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15066</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
