<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T11:10:21</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224439</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224439</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>it</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ALCOL MASK</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Детергенти, с изключение на такива за употреба в производствени операции и за медицински цели; Препарати за почистване на ръце; Препарати за почистване на ръце.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Čisticí prostředky, jiné než pro použití při výrobních procesech a pro lékařské účely; Přípravky na čištění rukou; Přípravky na čištění rukou.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Rensemidler, ikke til brug i fabrikationsprocesser eller til medicinsk brug; Præparater til rengøring af hænderne; Præparater til håndvask.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Detergenzien, ausgenommen zur Verwendung in Herstellungsverfahren und für medizinische Zwecke; Reiniger für die Hände; Handwaschmittel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Απορρυπαντικά, όχι για κατασκευαστικές εργασίες ούτε για ιατρική χρήση· Καθαριστικά χεριών· Παρασκευάσματα για τον καθαρισμό των χεριών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Detergents, other than for use in manufacturing operations and for medical purposes; Hand cleansers; Hand cleaning preparations.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Detergentes que no sean para procesos de fabricación ni para uso médico; Productos para limpiar las manos; Preparaciones para lavarse las manos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Puhastusvahendid, v.a meditsiinilised ja tööstuslikud; Preparaadid käte puhastamiseks; Kätepuhastustooted.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Pesuaineet, paitsi teollisiin ja lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Käsienpuhdistusaineet; Valmisteet käsien puhdistamiseen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Détergents [détersifs] autres que ceux utilisés au cours d'opérations de fabrication et ceux à usage médical; Produits nettoyants pour les mains; Préparations de nettoyage pour les mains.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Deterdženti [osim onih za medicinske potrebe ili za proizvodnju]; Sredstva za čišćenje ruku; Preparati za čišćenje ruku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Mosószerek/tisztítószerek, nem gyártási műveletekhez és nem gyógyászati használatra; Kéztisztítók; Kéztisztító készítmények.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Detergenti, eccetto quelli utilizzati nei procedimenti di fabbricazione e quelli per uso medico; detergenti per le mani; preparati per la pulizia delle mani.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Plovikliai (detergentai) (ne pramonės ir medicinos reikmėms); Rankų plovimo priemonės; Rankų valymo preparatai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mazgāšanas līdzekļi, izņemot ražošanas procesiem un medicīniskiem nolūkiem paredzētos; Roku tīrīšanas līdzekļi; Preparāti roku tīrīšanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Diterġenti, minbarra għal użu f'ħidmiet tal-manifattura u skopijiet mediċi; Prodotti għat-tindif fil-fond tal-idejn; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif tal-idejn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Detergentia, anders dan voor gebruik tijdens fabricageprocessen of voor geneeskundig gebruik; Handreinigers; Preparaten voor het reinigen van de handen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Detergenty, inne niż do użytku w procesach produkcyjnych oraz inne niż do celów medycznych; Środki do czyszczenia rąk; Preparaty do mycia rąk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Detergentes, sem ser para processos de fabrico nem para fins medicinais; Limpadores para mãos; Preparações para a higiene das mãos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Detergenţi, alţii decât cei folosiţi în timpul proceselor de fabricaţie şi decât cei de uz medical; Produse pentru curăţarea mâinilor; Preparate pentru curățarea mâinilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Detergenty (nie na použitie vo výrobnom procese a na lekárske použitie); Čističe na ruky; Prípravky na čistenie rúk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Detergenti, razen za uporabo v proizvodnji in za medicinske namene; Čistila za roke; Sredstva za čiščenje rok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Rengöringsmedel, inte för användning i industriprocesser eller för medicinska ändamål; Handrengöringsmedel; Preparat för handrengöring.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Медицински спирт; Антисептици; Детергенти за медицински цели; Почистващи средства за борба с бактериите; Препарати за дезинфекция на повърхности; Дезинфектанти; Дезинфектанти от всеки вид; Дезинфектанти за медицински апарати и инструменти; Дезинфекциращи средства за измиване на ръце; Дезинфектанти за хигиенни цели; Кърпички, напоени с антибактериални препарати; Дезинфекциращи антибактериални гелове за кожата на основата на алкохол; Гел за почистване на кожата; Антибактериални гелове за ръце; Дезинфекция на ръкавици; Дезинфекция на маски; Антибактериали лосиони за ръце; Средства за дезинфекция на помещения и повърхности; Многофункционални дезинфектанти и дезодоранти; Препарати за дезинфектанти за домакинство; Дезинфектанти за болнична употреба; Почистващи препарати за стерилизация; Санитарни препарати за лична хигиена, с изключение на тоалетни продукти; Антибактериални препарати за миене на ръце; Дезинфектантни разтвори за употреба върху повърхности; Препарат за дезинфекциране и хигиенизиране на повърхности; Санитарни кърпички за еднократна употреба; Антибактериален сапун; Дезинфектиращ сапун; Хидроалкохолен хигиенизиращ разтвор; Почистващи разтвори за медицински цели; Антибактериални спрейове; Дезинфекциращ и хигиенизиращ спрей.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Alkohol pro farmaceutické účely; Antiseptika; Detergenty pro lékařské účely; Antibakteriální čisticí přípravek; Dezinfekční čističe na povrchy; Dezinfekční přípravky; Dezinfekční přípravky všeho druhu; Dezinfekční přípravky na lékařské nástroje a přístroje; Dezinfekční prostředky na mytí rukou; Dezinfekční prostředky pro hygienické účely; Ubrousky napuštěné antibakteriálními přípravky; Antibakteriální gely na dezinfekci pleti na bázi alkoholu; Pleťové dezinfekční gely; Antibakteriální gely na ruce; Dezinfekční přípravky pro rukavice; Dezinfekční přípravky pro masky; Antibakteriální vody na ruce; Přípravky pro dezinfekci prostor a ploch; Víceúčelové dezinfekční a deodorační přípravky; Dezinfekční přípravky pro použití v domácnosti; Dezinfekční přípravky pro nemocniční použití; Hygienické sterilizační přípravky; Hygienické přípravky pro osobní hygienu, s výjimkou toaletních potřeb; Antibakteriální prostředky na mytí rukou; Dezinfekční roztoky pro použití na povrchy; Povrchové dezinfekční a sanitační prostředky; Dezinfekční ubrousky; Antibakteriální mýdla; Dezinfekční mýdla; Hydroalkoholický dezinfekční roztok; Čisticí roztoky pro lékařské použití; Antibakteriální spreje; Dezinfekční a sanitační spreje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Alkohol til farmaceutiske formål; Antiseptiske midler; Rensemidler til medicinsk brug; Bakteriedræbende rensemidler; Desinficerende rengøringsmidler til overflader; Desinfektionsmidler; Desinfektionsmidler af enhver art; Desinfektionsmidler til medicinske instrumenter og apparater; Desinficerende håndvaskemidler; Desinfektionsmidler til hygiejniske formål; Papirlommetørklæder imprægneret med antibakterielle præparater; Alkoholbaserede, antibakterielle desinfektionsgeléer til huden; Gele til desinfektion af huden; Antibakterielle geléer til hænderne; Præparater til desinfektion af handsker; Præparater til desinfektion af masker; Antibakterielle håndlotioner; Desinfektionsmidler til rum og arealer; Desinfektionsmidler og desodoriseringsmidler til flere formål; Desinfektionsmidler til husholdningsbrug; Desinfektionsmidler til brug på hospitaler; Steriliserende hygiejniske præparater; Sanitære præparater til personlig hygiejne, dog ikke toiletpræparater; Antibakterielle håndvaskemidler; Desinficerende opløsninger til brug på overflader; Desinfektionsmidler og sanitære midler til overflader; Renseservietter; Antibakteriel sæbe; Desinficerende sæbe; Vandige alkoholopløsninger til sanitære formål; Renseopløsninger til medicinske formål; Antibakterielle sprayer; Desinfektionsmidler og -spray.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Alkohol für pharmazeutische Zwecke; Antiseptika; Detergenzien für medizinische Zwecke; Antibakterielle Reinigungsmittel; Oberflächen-Desinfektionsreiniger; Desinfektionsmittel; Desinfektionsmittel aller Art; Desinfektionsmittel für medizinische Geräte und Instrumente; Desinfizierende Handwaschmittel; Desinfektionsmittel für hygienische Zwecke; Tücher mit antibakterieller Lösung; Antibakterielle Hautdesinfektionsgele auf Alkoholbasis; Hautdesinfektionsgel; Antibakterielle Handgele; Desinfektionsmittel für Handschuhe; Desinfektionsmittel für Masken; Antibakterielle Handlotionen; Raum- und Flächendesinfektionsmittel; Desinfektions- und Desodorierungsmittel für verschiedene Zwecke; Desinfektionsmittel für Haushaltszwecke; Desinfektionsmittel für den Krankenhausbedarf; Hygienepräparate zum Sterilisieren; Hygienepräparate für die Körperhygiene, ausgenommen Körperpflegemittel; Antibakterielle Handwaschmittel; Desinfektionslösungen zur Anwendung auf Oberflächen; Desinfektionsmittel und Sanitärprodukte zur Behandlung von Oberflächen; Desinfektionstücher für medizinische Zwecke; Antibakterielle Seifen; Desinfizierende Seifen; Desinfektionslösung auf Wasser-Alkohol-Basis; Reinigungslösungen für medizinische Zwecke; Antibakterielle Sprays; Desinfektionsmittel und Sanitärprodukte in Sprayform.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Φαρμακευτικό οινόπνευμα· Αντισηπτικά· Απορρυπαντικά για ιατρική χρήση· Αντιβακτηριακό προϊόν καθαρισμού· Μέσα απολύμανσης επιφανειών· Απολυμαντικά· Απολυμαντικά εν γένει· Απολυμαντικά προϊόντα για ιατρικά εργαλεία και συσκευές· Απολυμαντικά σαπούνια χεριών· Απολυμαντικά για υγειονομική χρήση· Μαντιλάκια εμποτισμένα με αντιβακτηριακά παρασκευάσματα· Αλκοολούχα αντιβακτηριακά αντισηπτικά ζελ[έ] για το δέρμα· Ζελέ για αποστείρωση του δέρματος· Αντιβακτηριακά ζελέ για τα χέρια· Απολυμαντικό για γάντια· Απολυμαντικό για μάσκες· Αντιβακτηριακές λοσιόν για τα χέρια· Απολυμαντικά χώρων και επιφανειών· Απολυμαντικά και αποσμητικά παρασκευάσματα πολλαπλών χρήσεων· Απολυμαντικά παρασκευάσματα για οικιακή χρήση· Απολυμαντικά παρασκευάσματα για νοσοκομειακή χρήση· Παρασκευάσματα υγιεινής για αποστείρωση· Υγειονομικά παρασκευάσματα προσωπικής υγιεινής, με εξαίρεση τα προϊόντα προσωπικής περιποίησης· Αντιβακτηριακά προϊόντα για το πλύσιμο των χεριών· Απολυμαντικά διαλύματα για χρήση σε επιφάνειες· Απολυμαντικά επιφανειών· Μαντιλάκια καθαρισμού· Αντιβακτηριακά σαπούνια· Απολυμαντικά σαπούνια· Απολυμαντικό μίγμα νερού-αλκοόλης· Διαλύματα καθαρισμού για ιατρική χρήση· Αντιβακτηριακά σπρέι· Σπρέι απολύμανσης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Alcohol for pharmaceutical purposes; Antiseptics; Detergents for medical purposes; Bacteria fighting cleanser; Disinfectant surface cleaners; Disinfectants; Disinfectants in general; Disinfectants for medical apparatus and instruments; Disinfecting handwash; Disinfectants for hygiene purposes; Tissues impregnated with antibacterial preparations; Alcohol-based antibacterial skin sanitizer gels; skin sanitizer gels; Antibacterial hand gels; Sanitisers for gloves; Sanitisers for face masks; Antibacterial hand lotions; Room and surface disinfectants; Multi-purpose disinfectant and deodorising preparations; Disinfectant preparations for household purposes; Disinfectant preparations for hospital use; Sanitary sterilising preparations; Sanitary preparations for personal hygiene, except toiletry preparations; Antibacterial handwashes; Disinfectant solutions for use on surfaces; Surface disinfectant and sanitizer; Sanitizing wipes; Anti-bacterial soap; Disinfectant soap; Hydroalcoholic sanitisers; Cleansing solutions for medical use; Antibacterial sprays; Disinfectant and sanitizing spray.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Alcohol para uso farmacéutico; Antisépticos; Detergentes para uso médico; Productos de limpieza antibacterianos; Desinfectantes para superficies; Desinfectantes; Desinfectantes de todo tipo; Desinfectantes para equipos e instrumentos médicos; Producto desinfectante para lavar las manos; Desinfectantes para uso higiénico; Toallitas impregnadas de preparaciones antibacterianas; Geles desinfectantes antibacterianos para la piel a base de alcohol; Geles desinfectantes para la piel; Geles para manos antibacterianos; Desinfectante para guantes; Desinfectante para mascarillas; Lociones antibacterianas para las manos; Productos para desinfectar espacios y superficies; Preparaciones desinfectantes y desodorantes multiusos; Preparaciones desinfectantes para uso doméstico; Preparaciones desinfectantes para uso hospitalario; Preparaciones higiénicas de esterilización; Preparaciones sanitarias para la higiene personal, a excepción de los productos de aseo; Productos antibacterianos para lavar las manos; Soluciones desinfectantes para su uso en superficies; Desinfectante e higienizante de superficie; Paños desinfectantes; Jabones antibacterianos; Jabones desinfectantes; Soluciones hidroalcohólicas definfectantes; Soluciones de limpieza para uso médico; Espráis antibacterianos; Aerosol desinfectante e higienizante.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Alkohol farmaatsias kasutamiseks; Antiseptikumid; Meditsiinilised detergendid; Antibakteriaalsed puhastusvahendid; Pealispinda desinfitseerivad puhastusvahendid; Desinfektsioonivahendid; Igat liiki desinfektsioonivahendid; Meditsiiniseadmete ja -riistade desinfitseerimisvahendid; Desinfitseerivad kätepesuvahendid; Hügieenilised desinfektsioonivahendid; Antibakteriaalsete preparaatidega immutatud salvrätid; Alkoholipõhised antibakteriaalsed nahahügieenigeelid; Nahahügieenigeelid; Antibakteriaalsed kätegeelid; Puhastusvahendid kinnaste jaoks; Puhastusvahendid maskide jaoks; Antibakteriaalsed kätekreemid; Ruumide ja pindade desinfektsioonivahendid; Desinfitseerivad preparaadid ja multifunktsionaalsed deodorandid; Majapidamise desinfitseerimispreparaadid; Haiglates kasutatavad desinfitseerimispreparaadid; Steriliseerivad hügieenipreparaadid; Sanitaarpreparaadid isikliku hügieeni tarbeks, v.a tualett-tarbed; Antibakteriaalsed kätepesuained; Pindadel kasutatavad desinfitseerivad lahused; Pihdade desinfitseerimis- ja saniteerimisvahendid; Desinfitseerivad lapid; Antibakteriaalne seep; Desinfitseeriv seep; Hüdroalkohoolne desinfitseerimislahus; Meditsiinilised puhastuslahused; Antibakteriaalsed pihused; Desinfitseerimis- ja saniteerimispihustid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lääkealkoholi; Antiseptiset aineet; Pesujauheet lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Antibakteeriset puhdistusaineet; Pintojen desinfiointipuhdistajat; Desinfiointiaineet; Kaikenlaiset desinfiointiaineet; Lääketieteellisten välineiden ja laitteiden desinfiointiaineet; Desinfioivat käsihuuhteet; Desinfiointiaineet hygieenisiin tarkoituksiin; Bakteereja tuhoavilla valmisteilla käsitellyt paperipyyhkeet; Alkoholipohjaiset bakteereja tappavat ihon desinfiointigeelit; Ihon desinfiointigeelit; Bakteereja tuhoavat käsigeelit; Käsineille tarkoitettu desinfiointiaine; Kasvonaamareille tarkoitettu desinfiointiaine; Bakteereja tuhoavat käsiemulsiot; Tilojen ja pintojen desinfiointiaineet; Desinfiointivalmisteet ja monikäyttöiset deodorantit; Desinfiointivalmisteet kotitalouskäyttöön; Desinfiointivalmisteet sairaalakäyttöön; Hygieeniset sterilointivalmisteet; Hygieniavalmisteet henkilökohtaiseen hygieniaan, paitsi toilettituotteet; Antibakteeriset käsienpesuliuokset; Desinfiointiliuokset käytettäväksi pinnoilla; Pintojen desinfiointi- ja puhdistusaineet; Desinfiointipyyhkeet; Antibakteerinen saippua; Desinfioiva saippua; Hydroalkoholinen desinfiointiliuos; Puhdistusliuokset lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Bakteereja tuhoavat suihkeet; Desinfioivat ja puhdistavat suihkeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Alcools à usage pharmaceutique; Antiseptiques; Détergents [détersifs] à usage médical; Nettoyant antibactérien; Désinfectants pour surfaces; Désinfectants; Désinfectants en tout genre; Désinfectants pour instruments et appareils médicaux; Produit lavant désinfectant pour les mains; Désinfectants à usage hygiénique; Lingettes imprégnées de préparations antibactériennes; Gels assainissants antibactériens pour la peau à base d'alcool; Gels désinfectants pour la peau; Gels antibactériens pour les mains; Produit désinfectant pour les gants; Produit désinfectant pour les masques; Lotions antibactériennes pour les mains; Désinfectants pour pièces et surfaces; Préparations désinfectantes et désodorisantes à usages multiples; Préparations désinfectantes à usage domestique; Préparations désinfectantes à usage hospitalier; Préparations hygiéniques de stérilisation; Préparations sanitaires pour l'hygiène personnelle, à l'exception des produits de toilette; Produits antibactériens pour le lavage des mains; Solutions désinfectantes à utiliser sur des surfaces; Produit désinfectant et assainissant pour surfaces; Lingettes désinfectantes; Savons antibactériens; Savons désinfectants; Solution hydro alcoolique désinfectante; Solutions nettoyantes à usage médical; Sprays antibactériens; Spray désinfectant et assanissant.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Medicinski alkohol; Antiseptici; Deterdženti za medicinske potrebe; Antibakterijsko sredstvo za čišćenje; Dezinfekcijsko sredstvo za površine; Dezinfekcijska sredstva; Dezinfekcijska sredstva svih vrsta; Sredstva za dezinfekciju medicinskih uređaja i instrumenata; Dezinfekcijsko sredstvo za pranje ruku; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za higijenske namjene; Maramice natopljene antibakterijskim pripravcima; Antibakterijski gelovi za higijenu kože, na bazi alkohola; Gelovi za dezinfekciju kože; Antibakterijski gel za ruke; Dezinfekcijsko sredstvo za rukavice; Dezinfekcijsko sredstvo za maske; Antibakterijski losioni za ruke; Sredstva za dezinfekciju prostora i površina; Dezinfekcijski preparati i višenamjenski dezodoransi; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za kućnu uporabu; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za uporabu u bolnici; Higijenski preparati za sterilizaciju; Sanitarni pripravci za osobnu higijenu, osim toaletnih proizvoda; Antibakterijska sredstva za pranje ruku; Dezinfekcijske otopine za uporabu na površinama; Dezinficijens i sredstvo za dezinfekciju površina; Dezinfekcijske maramice; Antibakterijski sapun; Dezinfekcijski sapuni; Hidroalkoholna otopina za dezinfekciju; Otopine za čišćenje za medicinske potrebe; Antibakterijski sprejevi; Sprejevi za dezinfekciju i dezinfekcijska sredstva.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Orvosi alkohol; Fertőtlenítőszerek, antiszeptikus készítmények; Tisztítószerek gyógyászati célokra; Antibakteriális tisztítószerek; Felületfertőtlenítő tisztítószerek; Fertőtlenítőszerek; Mindenféle fertőtlenítők; Fertőtlenítőszerek orvosi műszerekhez és készülékekhez; Fertőtlenítő kézmosó; Fertőtlenítőszerek higiéniai célokra; Antibakteriális készítményekkel átitatott kendők; Alkohol alapú antibakteriális bőrfertőtlenítő zselék; Bőrfertőtlenítő gélek; Antibakteriális kézápoló krémek; Kesztyű fertőtlenítők; Szájmaszk fertőtlenítők; Baktériumölő kézápolók; Szobai és felületi fertőtlenítőszerek; Többfunkciós fertőtlenítő és dezodoráló készítmények; Fertőtlenítő készítmények háztartási használatra; Fertőtlenítő készítmények kórházi használatra; Egészségügyi készítmények sterilizáláshoz; Egészségügyi készítmények személyes higiéniához, a piperecikkel kivételével; Antibakteriális kézmosók; Fertőtlenítő oldatok felületeken való használatra; Felületeket fertőtlenítő és tisztító készítmények; Fertőtlenítő törlőkendők; Antibakteriális szappan; Fertőtlenítő szappanok; Fertőtlenítő alkoholos oldatok; Tisztítóoldatok gyógyászati alkalmazásra; Antibakteriális spray-k; Fertőtlenítő és tisztító spray-k.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Alcool per uso farmaceutico; antisettici; detergenti [detersivi] per uso medico; detergenti antibatterici; detergenti igienizzanti per superfici; disinfettanti; disinfettanti di ogni genere; disinfettanti per apparati e strumenti medici; disinfettanti per il lavaggio delle mani; disinfettanti per uso igienico; fazzolettini imbevuti di preparazioni antibatteriche; gel igienizzante antibatterico per la pelle a base di alcol; gel igienizzante per la pelle; gel igienizzante per le mani; igienizzante per guanti; igienizzante per mascherine; lozioni antibatteriche per le mani; preparati disinfettanti per ambienti e superfici; preparazioni disinfettanti e deodoranti multiuso; preparazioni disinfettanti per uso domestico; preparazioni disinfettanti per uso ospedaliero; preparazioni igieniche di sterilizzazione; preparazioni sanitarie per l'igiene personale, a esclusione dei prodotti da toeletta; prodotti antibatterici per lavare le mani; prodotti disinfettanti per le superfici; prodotti igienizzanti per le superfici; salviette disinfettanti; saponi antibatterici; saponi disinfettanti; soluzione idroalcolica igienizzante; soluzioni detergenti per uso medico; spray antibatterici; spray igienizzanti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Spiritas (farmacijos reikmėms); Antiseptikai [vaistai nuo pūlinės infekcijos]; Detergentai (medicinos reikmėms); Antibakteriniai valikliai; Dezinfekuojamieji paviršių valikliai; Dezinfekavimo preparatai; Įvairios dezinfekcinės medžiagos; Medicininių aparatų ir instrumentų dezinfekavimo preparatai; Dezinfekuojantys rankų plovikliai; Dezinfekavimo priemonės (higienos reikmėms); Servetėlės, įmirkytos antibakteriniais preparatais; Antibakteriniai odos dezinfekavimo geliai alkoholio pagrindu; Odos dezinfekavimo geliai; Antibakterinės rankų želė; Pirštinių dezinfekavimo priemonė; Kaukių dezinfekavimo priemonė; Antibakteriniai rankų losjonai; Patalpų ir paviršių dezinfekavimo priemonės; Dezinfekavimo preparatai ir universalūs dezodorantai; Buitiniai dezinfekavimo preparatai; Dezinfekavimo preparatai ligoninių reikmėms; Higieniniai sterilizavimo preparatai; Asmens higienos sanitarijos preparatai, išskyrus tualeto reikmenis; Antibakteriniai rankų plovimo skysčiai; Dezinfekuojantys tirpalai, naudojami paviršių valymui; Paviršių dezinfekantas ir sanitarinė priemonė; Dezinfekuojamosios šluostės; Antibakterinis muilas; Dezinfekcinis muilas; Hidroalkoholio sanitarinis tirpalas; Valomieji tirpalai medicinos reikmėms; Antibakteriniai purškalai; Dezinfekavimo ir sanitarinis purškalas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Medicīniskais spirts; Antiseptiskie līdzekļi; Detergenti medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Antibakteriāli tīrīšanas līdzekļi; Dezinficējoši virsmu tīrīšanas līdzekļi; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi; Visu veidu dezinficējošie līdzekļi; Dezinfektanti medicīniskiem instrumentiem un iekārtām; Dezinficējoši roku mazgāšanas līdzekļi; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi higiēniskiem nolūkiem; Ar antibakteriāliem preparātiem piesūcinātas salvetes; Spirtotas antibakteriālas ādas dezinficēšanas želejas; Ādas dezinficēšanas geli; Antibakteriālās roku želejas; Higiēniskie līdzekļi cimdiem; Higiēniskie līdzekļi maskām; Antibakteriāli roku losjoni; Telpu un virsmu dezinfekcijas līdzekļi; Dezinficējoši un dezodorējoši preparāti dažādiem nolūkiem; Dezinficējošie līdzekļi izmantošanai mājās; Dezinficējošie līdzekļi izmantošanai slimnīcās; Higiēnas sterilizācijas līdzekļi; Sanitārie preparāti personīgajai higiēnai, izņemot tualetes preces; Antibakteriālie roku mazgāšanas līdzekļi; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi, kurus izmanto uz virsmām; Virsmas dezinfekcijas līdzeklis un higiēnas līdzeklis; Dezinfekcijas drāniņas; Antibakteriālās ziepes; Dezinficējošas ziepes; Higiēniskie hidroalkoholiskie šķīdumi; Tīrīšanas šķīdumi medicīniskai lietošanai; Antibakteriālie smidzinātāji; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi un higiēnisks aerosols.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Alkoħol mediċinali; Antisettiċi; Diterġenti għal skopijiet mediċi; Prodott tat-tindif kontra l-batterji; Diżinfettanti ta' wċuħ; Diżinfettanti; Diżinfettanti ta' kull tip; Diżinfettanti għal strumenti u apparat mediku; Sapun likwidu tal-idejn diżinfettanti; Diżinfettanti għal skopijiet ta' iġjene; Tixus imxarrba bi preparazzjonijiet antibatteriċi; Ġellijiet antibatteriċi bbażati fuq l-alkoħol għad-diżinfezzjoni tal-ġilda; Ġellijiet li jissanitizza l-ġilda; Ġellijiet antibatteriċi għall-idejn; Sanitizzatur għall-ingwanti; Sanitizzatur għall-maskri protettivi; Lozjonijiet tal-idejn antibatteriċi; Diżinfettanti ta' kmamar u wċuħ; Preparazzjonijiet diżinfettanti u deodoranti għal ħafna użi; Preparazzjonijiet diżinfettanti għall-użu domestiku; Preparazzjonijiet diżinfettanti għall-użu fl-isptar; Preparazzjonijiet tal-iġjene għall-isterilizzazzjoni; Preparazzjonijiet sanitarji għall-iġjene personali, minbarra l-prodotti tat-twaletta; Ħasil tal-idejn antibatteriku; Soluzzjonijiet diżinfettanti għall-użu fuq l-uċuħ; Prodotti ta' iġjene u diżinfettanti għas-superfiċji; Biċċiet tal-imsiħ għal skop ta' iġjene; Sapun antibatteriku; Sapun diżinfettanti; Sanitizzatur b'bażi ta' alkoħol; Soluzzjonijiet tat-tindif għall-użu mediku; Sprejs antibatteriċi; Sprej diżinfettanti u sanitizzanti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Alcohol voor farmaceutisch gebruik; Antiseptische middelen; Detergentia voor medisch gebruik; Bacteriebestrijdende reinigingsmiddelen; Ontsmettingsreinigers voor oppervlakken; Ontsmettingsmiddelen; Alle soorten ontsmettingsmiddelen; Ontsmettingsmiddelen voor medische apparaten en instrumenten; Handreinigingsmiddelen (Desinfecterende -); Desinfecterende middelen voor hygiënisch gebruik; Doekjes geïmpregneerd met antibacteriële preparaten; Antibacteriële huidreinigingsgels op basis van alcohol; Huidreinigingsgels; Antibacteriële handgels; Desinfecterende middelen voor handschoenen; Desinfecterende middelen voor maskers; Antibacteriële handlotions; Ontsmettingsmiddelen voor ruimtes en oppervlakken; Ontsmettingsmiddelen en multifunctionele deodorantia; Ontsmettingsmiddelen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Ontsmettingsmiddelen voor ziekenhuisgebruik; Hygiënische sterilisatiepreparaten; Hygiënische preparaten voor persoonlijke hygiëne, met uitzondering van toiletartikelen; Antibacteriële handzeep; Ontsmettingsoplossingen voor gebruik op oppervlakken; Middelen voor het desinfecteren en steriliseren van oppervlakken; Hygiënische doekjes; Antibacteriële zeep; Desinfecterende zeep; Desinfecterende hydroalcoholische oplossing; Reinigingsoplossingen voor medisch gebruik; Antibacteriële sprays; Desinfecterende en steriliserende spray.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Alkohol leczniczy; Antyseptyki; Detergenty do celów medycznych; Antybakteryjne środki do mycia; Środki do dezynfekcji powierzchni; Środki odkażające; Środki dezynfekcyjne różnego rodzaju; Środki odkażające do przyrządów i aparatury medycznej; Odkażający preparat do mycia rąk; Środki dezynfekcyjne do celów higienicznych; Chusteczki nasączone preparatami przeciwbakteryjnymi; Antybakteryjne żele na bazie alkoholu do odkażania skóry; Żele do odkażania skóry; Antybakteryjne żele do rąk; Środki odkażające do rękawiczek; Środki odkażające do masek; Antybakteryjne płyny do rąk; Środki do dezynfekcji pomieszczeń i powierzchni; Preparaty odkażające i dezodoranty uniwersalne; Środki dezynfekujące do użytku domowego; Środki dezynfekujące do użytku szpitalnego; Preparaty higieniczne do sterylizacji; Preparaty medyczne do higieny osobistej, z wyjątkiem produktów toaletowych; Antybakteryjne środki do mycia rąk; Roztwory odkażające do powierzchni; Preparaty odkażające i dezynfekujące powierzchnie; Chusteczki odkażające; Mydła antybakteryjne; Mydła dezynfekujące; Odkażający roztwór alkoholu; Roztwory oczyszczające do użytku medycznego; Spraye antybakteryjne; Dezynfektanty i spraye do odkażania.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Álcool para fins farmacêuticos; Antisséticos; Detergentes para uso medicinal; Produtos de limpeza bacterianos; Detergentes desinfetantes de superfícies; Desinfectantes; Desinfectantes de todos os tipos; Desinfetantes para aparelhos e instrumentos médicos; Desinfetante para lavar as mãos; Desinfetantes para uso higiénico; Tecidos impregnados com preparações antibacterianas; Geles antibacterianos à base de álcool para a limpeza da pele; Geles para higienização da pele; Geles antibacterianos para as mãos; Desinfetantes para luvas; Desinfetantes para máscaras; Loções antibacterianas para as mãos; Produtos para a desinfeção de espaços interiores e de superfícies; Produtos desinfetantes e desodorizantes multiuso; Desinfetantes para uso doméstico; Desinfetantes para uso hospitalar; Produtos higiénicos de esterilização; Produtos sanitários para a higiene pessoa, com exceção de produtos de toilette; Preparações antibacterianas de lavagem de mãos; Soluções desinfectantes para superfícies; Produtos de desinfecção e higienização de superfícies; Toalhetes higiénicos; Sabão antibacteriano; Sabão desinfetante; Soluções hidroalcoólicas desinfetantes; Soluções de limpeza para uso médico; Sprays antibacterianos; Aerossóis desinfectantes e de higienização.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Alcool medicinal; Antiseptice; Detergenţi [detersivi] de uz medical; Produs de curăţare antibacterian; Produse de curăţare şi dezinfectare a suprafeţelor; Dezinfectante; Dezinfectante de orice tip; Dezinfectanţi pentru instrumente şi aparate medicale; Produse dezinfectante pentru spălarea mâinilor; Dezinfectante folosite pentru igienă; Şerveţele impregnate cu preparate antibacteriene; Geluri dezinfectante antibacteriene cu alcool; Geluri igienizante pentru piele; Geluri antibacteriene pentru mâini; Igienizant pentru mănuși; Igienizant pentru măști; Loţiuni antibacteriene pentru mâini; Dezinfectanţi pentru spaţii şi suprafeţe; Preparate dezinfectante şi deodorante multifuncţionale; Preparate dezinfectante de uz casnic; Preparate dezinfectante de uz spitalicesc; Preparate pentru sterilizare; Produse sanitare pentru igiena personală, cu excepția produselor de toaletă; Soluţii antibacteriene pentru spălarea mâinilor; Solutii dezinfectante pentru utilizare pe suprafete; Produse pentru dezinfectarea si curatarea suprafetelor; Şerveţele dezinfectante; Săpun antibacterian; Săpunuri dezinfectante; Soluție hidroalcoolică igienizantă; Soluţii de curăţare de uz medical; Sprayuri antibacteriene; Dezinfectante si spray pentru dezinfectare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Alkoholy na farmaceutické použitie; Antiseptické prípravky, dezinfekčné prípravky; Detergenty na lekárske použitie; Antibakteriálne čistiace prípravky; Dezinfekčné čističe povrchov; Dezinfekčné prostriedky; Dezinfekčné prostriedky každého druhu; Dezinfekčné prostriedky na lekárske nástroje a prístroje; Dezinfekčný prípravok na umývanie rúk; Dezinfekčné prípravky na hygienické použitie; Obrúsky napustené antibakteriálnymi prípravkami; Antibakteriálne dezinfekčné pleťové gély na báze alkoholu; Gély na dezinfekciu pokožky; Antibakteriálne gély na ruky; Dezinfekčné prípravky na rukavice; Dezinfekčné prípravky na rúška; Antibakteriálne mlieka na ruky; Priestorové a plošné dezinfekčné prostriedky; Dezinfekčné a dezodoračné viacúčelové prípravky; Dezinfekčné prípravky na použitie v domácnosti; Dezinfekčné prípravky na použitie v nemocnici; Hygienické sterilizačné prípravky; Hygienické prípravky na osobnú hygienu, s výnimkou toaletných prípravkov; Antibakteriálne tekuté mydlá; Dezinfekčné roztoky na využitie na povrchoch; Povrchové dezinfekčné a zdravotné prípravky; Dezinfekčné utierky; Antibakteriálne mydlá; Dezinfekčné mydlá; Hydroalkoholický dezinfekčný roztok; Čistiace roztoky na lekárske použitie; Antibakteriálne spreje; Dezinfekčné a zdravotné spreje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Medicinski alkohol; Antiseptiki; Detergenti za medicinske namene; Antibakterijska čistilna sredstva; Razkuževalno čiščenje površin; Dezinfekcijska sredstva; Razkuževalna sredstva vseh vrst; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za medicinske aparate in instrumente; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za umivanje rok; Razkužila za higienske namene; Robčki, ki so prepojeni z antibakterijskimi pripravki; Antibakterijski dezinfekcijski geli za kožo, na osnovi alkohola; Geli za dezinfekcijo kože; Antibakterijski geli za roke; Sredstvo za razkuževanje rokavic; Sredstvo za razkuževanje mask; Antibakterijski losjoni za roke; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za prostore in površine; Dezinfekcijski pripravki in večnamenski dezodoranti; Dezinfekcijski pripravki za uporabo v gospodinjstvu; Dezinfekcijski pripravki za uporabo v bolnišnici; Higienski pripravki za sterilizacijo; Sanitarni preparati za osebno higieno, razen toaletnih izdelkov; Antibakterijska čistila za roke; Dezinfekcijske raztopine za uporabo na površinah; Dezinfekcijsko sredstvo in razkužilo za površine; Dezinfekcijski robčki; Antibakterijska mila; Dezinfekcijsko milo; Vodno-alkoholna raztopina za razkuževanje; Čistilne raztopine za medicinsko uporabo; Antibakterijska razpršila; Dezinfekcijska sredstva in razkuževalno pršilo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Medicinsk alkohol; Antiseptiska medel; Renande medel för medicinska ändamål; Bakteriebekämpande rengöringsmedel; Desinficerande rengöringsmedel för ytor; Desinfektionsmedel; Desinfektionsmedel av olika slag; Desinfektionsmedel för medicinska instrument och apparater; Desinficerande handtvätt; Desinfektionsmedel för hygieniska ändamål; Servetter impregnerade med antibakteriella preparat; Alkoholbaserade bakteriedödande hudsaneringsgeléer; Hudsaneringsgelé; Bakteriedödande handgeléer; Desinfektionsmedel för handskar; Desinfektionsmedel för ansiktsmasker; Bakteriedödande handlotioner; Rum- och ytdesinfektionsmedel; Desinfektionsmedel och deodoranter med multisyfte; Desinficerande preparat för hushållsbruk; Desinficerande preparat för användning inom sjukvården; Hygieniska steriliseringspreparat; Sanitära preparat för personlig hygien, med undantag för toalettartiklar; Bakteriedödande handtvättmedel; Desinfektionslösningar för användning på ytor; Desinfektionsmedel och saneringsmedel för ytor; Steriliserande torkservetter; Bakteriedödande tvål; Desinficerande tvål; Vattenbaserad alkohollösning för desinfektion; Rengöringslösningar för medicinskt bruk; Bakteriedödande sprejer; Desinficerande och sanerande sprej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/081</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-30</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/150</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>255203</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>21237</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
