<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T08:53:02</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224921</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224921</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162203006</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/224/018224921/000162203006.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>28.03</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>12</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Външни гуми за колела на превозни средства; Гуми за моторни превозни средства; Вътрешни гуми за пневматични гуми; Пневматични гуми; Вериги гъсеничен тип за трактори; Шипове за външни гуми; Външни гуми за пневматични гуми; Външни гуми за превозни средства; Външни гуми за велосипеди; Външни гуми.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Pneumatiky pro kola vozidel; Pneumatiky pro automobily; Duše do pneumatik; Pneumatiky; Pásy pro pásová vozidla; Hroty do pneumatik; Pláště pneumatik (plněných vzduchem); Pneumatiky na kola; Pneumatiky na jízdní kola; Pneumatiky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Dæk til hjul til befordringsmidler; Automobildæk; Slanger til pneumatiske dæk; Luftgummidæk; Bæltetræk til befordringsmidler; Søm til pigdæk; Slidbaner til automobildæk; Luftringe til køretøjer; Cykeldæk; Dæk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Reifen für Fahrzeugräder; Autoreifen; Schläuche für Reifen; Reifen [Pneus]; Raupenketten für Fahrzeuge; Spikes für Reifen; Laufmäntel für Luftreifen; Fahrzeugreifen; Fahrradreifen; Reifen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ελαστικά για τροχούς οχημάτων· Ελαστικά για μηχανοκίνητα οχήματα· Αέρα (Θάλαμοι -) για ελαστικά· Ελαστικά με αεροθαλάμους· Ερπυστριες [τρακτέρ] για οχήματα· Καρφιά ελαστικών· Επενδύσεις ελαστικών· Ελαστικά οχημάτων· Λάστιχα για ποδήλατα· Ελαστικά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Tires for vehicle wheels; Tyres for vehicle wheels; Automobile tires [tyres]; Inner tubes for pneumatic tires [tyres]; Pneumatic tires [tyres]; Treads for vehicles [roller belts]; Spikes for tires [tyres]; Casings for pneumatic tires [tyres]; Vehicle wheel tires [tyres]; Bicycle tires [tyres].; Tyres.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cubiertas de neumáticos para vehículos; Neumáticos para automóviles; Cámaras de aire para neumáticos; Neumáticos; Orugas para vehículos; Clavos para neumáticos; Cubiertas para neumáticos; Neumáticos para vehículos; Neumáticos de bicicleta; Llantas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sõidukirehvid; Autorehvid; Õhkrehvide sisekummid [lohvid]; Õhkrehvid, pneumorehvid; Sõidukiroomikud [lindid], roomikud traktori tüüpi sõidukitele; Rehvinaastud; Õhkrehvide, pneumorehvide väliskummid; Sõidukirehvid; Jalgrattarehvid; Rehvid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ulkorenkaat ajoneuvojen pyöriin; Autonrenkaat; Sisäkumit ilmarenkaisiin; Ilmarenkaat; Kulutuspinnat ajoneuvojen renkaisiin; Nastat renkaisiin; Ulkorenkaat; Kulkuneuvojen ulkorenkaat; Ulkorenkaat polkupyöriin; Autonrenkaat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bandages de roues pour véhicules; Pneus d'automobile; Chambres à air pour pneumatiques; Pneus; Chenilles pour véhicules; Clous pour pneus; Enveloppes [pneumatiques]; Pneumatiques pour véhicules; Pneus de bicyclette; Pneus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kotači (vanjske gume za kotače vozila); Pneumatici za motorna vozila; Zračnice za pneumatske gume; Pneumatske gume; Gusjenice vozila (tipa transportne trake); Čavli za gume; Gumeni kotači [vanjski omotači gumenih kotača]; Gume za vozila; Gume za bicikle; Pneumatici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Gumiabroncsok járműkerekekhez; Gumiabroncsok gépjárművekhez; Belső gumiabroncstömlők; Tömör gumiabroncsok járműkerekekhez; Futófelületek járművekhez [szíjgörgők]; Abroncstüskék, abroncsszegek; Gumiabroncs köpenyek; Járműabroncsok; Kerékpár abroncsok, gumik; Gumiabroncsok, abroncsgumik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cerchioni di ruote per veicoli; Pneumatici per automobili; Camere d'aria per pneumatici; Pneumatici; Cingoli per veicoli; Chiodi per pneumatici; Copertoni per pneumatici; Pneumatici per motoveicoli; Pneumatici per cicli; Pneumatici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Transporto priemonių padangos; Automobilių padangos; Pneumatinių padangų kameros; Pneumatinės padangos; Transporto priemonių vikšrai [traktoriniai]; Padangų dygliai; Pneumatinių padangų karkasai; Transporto priemonių padangos; Dviračių ratų padangos; Padangos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Transportlīdzekļu riteņu riepas; Motorizēto transportlīdzekļu riepas; Riepu kameras; Pneimatiskās riepas; Kāpurķēdes transportlīdzekļiem; Riepu radzes; Pneimatisko riepu pārvalki; Riepas transportlīdzekļiem; Velosipēdu riepas; Riepas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tajers għar-roti tal-vetturi, pnewmatiċi; Tajers tal-karozzi; Tubi interni għal tajers pnewmatiċi [tajers]; Tajers solidi għal roti ta' vetturi; Ċineg kontinwi għall-vetturi [bħal ta' trakter]; Pernijiet imqabbżin għat-tajers; Għata għat-tajers; Tajers għar-roti tal-vetturi, pnewmatiċi; Tajers għar-roti, roti bil-mutur; Tajers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Wielbanden voor voertuigen; Autobanden; Binnenbanden; Luchtbanden; Rupsbanden voor voertuigen; Spijkers voor spijkerbanden; Buitenbanden; Voertuigbanden; Fietsbanden; Banden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Opony do pojazdów; Opony do pojazdów mechanicznych; Dętki do opon pneumatycznych; Opony pneumatyczne; Gąsienicowy układ bieżny do pojazdów [taśmy gąsienicowe]; Kolce do opon; Korpusy opon; Opony do pojazdów; Opony rowerowe; Opony.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Pneus para jantes de veículos; Pneus para automóveis; Câmaras-de-ar para pneumáticos; Pneus [pneumáticos]; Lagartas para veículos [tração]; Picos para pneus; Lonas para pneumáticos; Pneus de veículos; Pneus para bicicletas; Pneumáticos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Bandaje de roți pentru vehicule; Pneuri pentru autovehicule; Camere de aer pentru pneuri; Pneuri [anvelope]; Șenile pentru vehicule; Crampoane pentru pneuri; Anvelope [pneuri]; Anvelope pentru vehicule; Pneuri pentru vehicule pe două roți; Pneuri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Plášte na kolesá vozidiel; Automobilové pneumatiky; Duše pneumatík; Pneumatiky; Pásy na pásové vozidlá; Hroty na pneumatiky; Pneumatikové plášte; Pneumatiky pre vozidlá; Plášte na bicyklové kolesá; Pneumatiky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pnevmatike za kolesa vozil; Pnevmatike za motorna vozila; Zračnice za pnevmatike; Trde pnevmatike za vozila; Gosenice za vozila [transportni trakovi]; Žeblji za pnevmatike; Plašči za pnevmatike; Pnevmatike za vozila; Pnevmatike za kolesa; Pnevmatike.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Däck för fordonshjul; Däck för motorfordon och -farkoster; Innerslangar för pneumatiska däck; Pneumatiska däck; Larvfötter för fordon; Dobbar för däck; Hjulhus; Däck för fordon och farkoster; Cykeldäck; Däck.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>505521</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017950422</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-05-27</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
