<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-01T00:57:10</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224204</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224204</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-02</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>IvyLife</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Калъфи за пренасяне на компютри; Компютърни мишки; Подложки за мишки; Електрически везни; Калъфи за слушалки; Слушалки; Защитни маски; Защитни очила; Калъфи за таблети; Водолазни очила; Ръкавици за водолази; Калъфи, пригодени за мобилни телефони; Кабели за предаване на данни; Стойки за фотографска апаратура; Калъфи за очила.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Tašky na přenosné počítače (laptopy); Počítačové myši; Podložky pod myš; Elektrické váhy; Pouzdra na sluchátka; Sluchátka; Ochranné masky; Bezpečnostní brýle; Pouzdra na tabletové počítače; Potápěčské brýle; Potápěčské rukavice; Obaly na mobilní telefony; Kabely na přenos dat; Fotografické stativy; Pouzdra na brýle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tasker tilpasset til laptops; Computermus; Musemåtter; Elektriske vægte; Etuier til hovedtelefoner; Høretelefoner; Beskyttelsesmasker; Beskyttelsesbriller; Etuier til tablet-computere; Dykkerbriller; Dykkerhandsker; Etuier til mobiltelefoner; Kabler til datatransmission; Stativer til fotografiapparater; Etuier til briller.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Laptoptaschen; Computermaus; Mauspads [Mausmatten]; Elektrische Waagen; Etuis für Kopfhörer; Kopfhörer; Schutzmasken; Korbbrille; Etuis für Tablet-Computer; Taucherbrillen; Taucherhandschuhe; Etuis für Mobiltelefone; Kabel für die Datenübertragung; Stative für Fotoapparate; Brillenetuis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Θήκες μεταφοράς φορητών ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Ποντίκια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Προστατευτικές βάσεις για ποντίκια (ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών)· Ηλεκτρικοί ζυγοί· Θήκες για κεφαλόφωνα· Ακουστικά· Προστατευτικές μάσκες· Προστατευτικά γυαλιά· Θήκες για φορητούς ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Προστατευτικά γυαλιά για καταδύσεις· Γάντια κατάδυσης· Θήκες για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Καλώδια μετάδοσης δεδομένων· Τρίποδα φωτογραφικών μηχανών· Επιρρίνιων γυαλιών οράσεως θήκες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Laptop cases; Computer mouses; Computer mouse pads; Electrical scales; Cases for headphones; Earphones; Protection masks; Protective eyeglasses; Protective cases for tablet computers; Diving goggles; Divers' gloves; Cases for mobile phones; Data cables; Camera stands; Boxes [cases] for glasses.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bolsas especiales para ordenadores portátiles; Ratones de ordenador; Alfombrillas de ratón; Balanzas eléctricas; Estuches para cascos; Auriculares intraurales; Máscaras de protección; Gafas protectoras; Estuches para ordenadores tipo tablilla; Gafas de buceo; Guantes de buceo; Estuches adaptados para teléfonos móviles; Cables para la transmisión de datos; Pies para aparatos fotográficos; Estuches para gafas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sülearvutikotid; Arvutihiired; Hiirematid; Elektrilised kaalud; Kõrvaklapiümbrised; Kõrvaklapid; Kaitsemaskid; Ohutusprillid; Tahvelarvutite vutlarid; Sukeldumisprillid; Kindad sukeldujatele; Mobiiltelefonivutlarid; Andmeedastuskaablid; Fotoseadmete statiivid; Prillitoosid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tietokoneen kantokotelot; Tietokonehiiret; Hiirimatot; Sähkövaa'at; Kuulokkeille tarkoitetut kotelot; Kuulokkeet; Suojanaamarit; Turvasuojalasit; Taulutietokoneille tarkoitetut kotelot; Sukelluslasit; Käsineet (Sukellus -); Matkapuhelinkotelot; Tiedonsiirtokaapelit; Kolmijalat kameroille; Silmälasikotelot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Sacoches conçues pour ordinateurs portables; Souris d'ordinateur; Tapis de souris; Balances électriques; Étuis pour casques d’écoute; Casques d'écoute; Masques de protection; Lunettes de protection; Etuis pour tablettes électroniques; Lunettes de plongée; Gants de plongée; Étuis pour téléphones portables; Câbles de transmission de données; Pieds d'appareils photographiques; Étuis à lunettes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Torbe za prijenosna računala; Računalni miševi; Podloge za miša; Električne vage; Kutijice za slušalice; Slušalice; Zaštitne maske; Zaštitne naočale; Futrole za tablet računala; Naočale za ronioce; Rukavice za ronioce; Futrole prilagođene za mobilne telefone; Kablovi za prijenos podataka; Foto tronošci; Navlake za cvikere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Számítógép hordozó tokok, táskák; Számítógépes egerek; Egérpadok; Elektromos mérlegek; Tokok fejhallgatókhoz; Fejhallgatók; Védőálarcok/-maszkok; Védőszemüvegek; Tokok táblagépekhez; Búvárszemüvegek; Búvárkesztyűk; Mobiltelefonokhoz kialakított tokok; Adatátviteli kábelek; Háromlábú állványok fényképezőgépekhez; Szemüvegtokok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Borse porta computer portatile; Mouse per computer; Tappetini per mouse; Bilance elettriche; Custodie per cuffie; Auricolari; Maschere di protezione; Occhiali di protezione; Custodie per tablet; Occhiali protettivi per immersioni; Guanti per subacquei; Custodie adattate per telefoni cellulari; Cavi per trasmissione di dati; Cavalletti per apparecchi fotografici; Astucci per occhiali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Skreitinių kompiuterių krepšiai; Kompiuterių pelės; Pelės padėkliukai; Elektrinės svarstyklės; Ausinių dėklai; Ausinės; Apsauginės kaukės; Apsauginiai akiniai; Planšetinių kompiuterių dangteliai; Apsauginiai narų akiniai; Narų pirštinės; Mobiliesiems telefonams pritaikyti dėklai; Duomenų perdavimo kabeliai; Fotoaparatų stovai; Akinių įmautės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Klēpjdatoru somas; Datorpele; Peļu (datoru perifērijas ierīču) paliktņi; Elektriskie svari; Austiņu futrāļi; Ieaušu austiņas; Aizsargmaskas; Brilles acu aizsardzībai; Planšetdatoru futrāļi; Niršanas brilles; Nirēju un ūdenslīdēju cimdi; Mobilo tālruņu futrāļi; Datu pārraides kabeļi; Fotoaparātu, kinokameru un videokameru statīvi; Briļļu maki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Bagalji għall-ġarr ta' kompjuter portabbli; Maws tal-kompjuter; Mattijiet għall-maws; Mwieżen elettriċi; Kaxxetti għall-kuffji; Kuffji; Maskri protettivi; Nuċċalijiet protettivi; Kaxxetti għal kompjuters stil tablet; Nuċċalijiet tal-għaddasa; Ingwanti għall-għaddasa; Kaxxetti adattati għat-telefowns ċellulari; Linji għat-trasmissjoni ta' data; Apparat għaż-żamma ta' apparat fotografiku; Kontenituri tan-nuċċalijiet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Aangepaste tassen voor laptops; Computermuis; Muismatten; Elektrische weegschalen; Etuis voor koptelefoons; Oortelefoons; Beschermende maskers; Beschermende brillen; Hoezen voor tablets; Duikbrillen; Duikerhandschoenen; Hoesjes voor mobiele telefoons; Datatransmissiekabels; Statieven [fotografie]; Brillenkokers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Torby do noszenia komputerów; Myszki komputerowe; Podkładki pod myszy komputerowe; Wagi elektryczne; Futerały na słuchawki; Słuchawki [douszne]; Maski ochronne; Okulary ochronne; Etui do tabletów; Gogle dla nurków; Rękawice dla nurków; Futerały dopasowane do telefonów komórkowych; Kable do transmisji danych; Statywy do aparatów fotograficznych; Etui na okulary.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Sacolas adaptadas para computadores portáteis; Ratos para computador; Tapetes de rato; Balanças elétricas; Estojos para auscultadores; Auriculares; Máscaras de proteção; Óculos de proteção; Malas concebidas para computadores "tablet"; Óculos de mergulho; Luvas para mergulho; Bolsas adaptadas para telemóveis; Cabos para a transmissão de dados; Pés para aparelhos fotográficos; Estojos para óculos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Genți adaptate pentru laptopuri; Mouse-uri pentru computer; Suporturi de mouse; Cântare electrice; Cutii pentru căști; Căști auriculare; Măști de protecție; Ochelari de protecție; Huse pentru calculatoare tabletă; Ochelari pentru scufundare liberă; Mănuși de scafandru; Etuiuri pentru telefoane mobile; Cabluri pentru transmisia de date; Trepiede pentru aparate fotografice; Tocuri pentru ochelari fără brațe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Tašky na notebooky; Počítačové myši; Podložky pod myš; Elektrické váhy; Puzdrá na slúchadlá; Slúchadlá; Ochranné masky; Bezpečnostné okuliare; Puzdrá na tabletové počítače; Okuliare pre potápačov; Potápačské rukavice; Puzdrá na mobilné telefóny; Káble na prenos údajov; Statívy na fotoaparáty; Puzdrá na okuliare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Torbe, prilagojene prenašanje računalnikov; Računalniške miške; Podloge za miško; Električne tehtnice; Etuiji za slušalke; Slušalke; Zaščitne maske; Zaščitni naočniki; Etuiji za tablične računalnike; Potapljaška očala; Rokavice za potapljače; Etuiji za mobilne telefone; Kabli za prenos podatkov; Stojala za fotografske aparate; Etuiji za očala.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Väskor för bärbara datorer; Datormusar; Musmattor; Elektriska vågar; Fodral för hörlurar; Hörlurar; Skyddsmasker; Skyddsglasögon; Fodral för surfplattor; Glasögon för dykare; Handskar för dykare; Fodral anpassade för mobiltelefoner; Kablar för dataöverföring; Stativ för fotografiapparater; Glasögonfodral.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>14</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Обици; Ръчни часовници; Будилници; Калъфи за стенни часовници; Ръчни часовници; Каишки за ръчни часовници; Кутии за ръчни часовници; Части за часовници; Гривни; Бижута за глава; Огърлици [бижутерия]; Kутии за бижута и кутии за часовници; Бижута с изкуствени скъпоценни камъни; Пръстени [бижутерия].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Náušnice; Hodiny; Budíky; Pouzdra na hodinky (tvarovaná); Hodinky; Řemínky k náramkovým hodinkám; Hodinková pouzdra [součásti hodinek]; Příslušenství k hodinkám; Ozdobné kroužky a náramky; Šperky jako ozdoba hlavy; Náhrdelníky [šperky]; Pouzdra na šperky a pouzdra na hodiny a hodinky; Skleněná bižutérie (imitace drahokamů); Prsteny [šperky].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Øreringe; Ure; Vækkeure; Tilpassede etuier til ure; Ure [armbåndsure]; Remme til armbåndsure; Urkasser [dele til armbåndsure]; Tilbehør til armbåndsure; Armbånd; Smykker til hovedet; Halskæder [smykker]; Smykkekasser og urkasser; Similismykker; Ringe [smykker].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Ohrringe; Uhren; Wecker; Etuis, angepasst an Armbanduhren; Taschen-/Armbanduhren; Uhrenarmbänder; Uhrengehäuse [Taschen-/Armbanduhren]; Uhrzubehör; Armbänder; Schmuckwaren für den Kopf; Halsketten [Schmuck]; Schmuck- und Uhrenbehältnisse; Strass [Edelsteinimitation]; Ringe [Schmuck].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Σκουλαρίκια· Ρολόγια τοίχου ή επιτραπέζια, κοσμήματα· Ξυπνητήρια· Θήκες [προσαρμοσμένες] για ρολόγια χειρός· Ρολόγια τοίχου ή επιτραπέζια, κοσμήματα· Λουράκια για ωρολόγια χειρός· Θήκες ωρολογιών χειρός· Εξαρτήματα ρολογιών χειρός· Βραχιόλια· Κοσμήματα για το κεφάλι· Περιδέραια [κοσμήματα]· Κοσμηματοθήκες και κουτιά ρολογιών· Στρας κοσμηματοποιίας· Δακτυλίδια [κοσμήματα].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Earrings; Wall clocks; Alarm clocks; Cases adapted to contain watches; Watches; Bands for watches; Cases for watches; Fittings for watches; Bracelets; Jewelry for the head; Necklaces; Jewellery boxes and watch boxes; Fashion jewellery; Rings [jewelry].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pendientes; Relojes que no sean de uso personal; Despertadores; Estuches para relojes [a medida]; Relojes de uso personal; Pulseras de reloj; Carcasas de reloj de uso personal; Adornos de reloj; Brazaletes y pulseras; Joyería para la cabeza; Collares [joyería]; Joyeros y estuches para relojes; Estrás; Anillos [joyería].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kõrvarõngad; Kellad; Äratuskellad; Spetsiaalsed kellakarbid; Käe-, taskukellad; Kellarihmad; Käekellade korpused; Kellatarvikud; Käe- ja jalavõrud; Peaehted (juveeltooted); Kaelakeed; Juveeltoodete karbid ja kellakarbid; Strassist juveeltooted; Sõrmused [juveeltooted].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Korvarenkaat; Kellot; Herätyskellot; Kellorasiat [muotoon sovitetut]; Kellot; Rannekellojen hihnat; Kellon kuoret; Rannekellojen tarvikkeet; Rannerenkaat; Pääkorut; Kaulakorut [korut]; Korurasiat ja kellokotelot; Strassikorut; Sormukset [korut].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Boucles d'oreilles; Horloges; Réveille-matin; Écrins pour montres [sur mesure]; Montres; Bracelets de montres; Boîtiers de montre; Accessoires pour montres; Bracelets; Bijoux pour la tête; Colliers [bijouterie]; Coffrets à bijoux et coffrets à montres; Strass; Bagues [bijouterie].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Naušnice; Satovi, zidni; Budilice; Kućišta prilagođena za satove; Satovi, zidni; Remeni za ručne satove; Kućišta džepnih satova; Dodatci za ručne satove; Narukvice; Nakit za glavu; Ogrlice [nakit]; Kutije za nakit i kutije za satove; Nakit od bižuterije; Prstenje [nakit].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Fülbevalók; Órák; Ébresztőórák; Méretre szabott óratartó tokok; Órák; Szíjak órákhoz; Óratokok; Szerelvények órákhoz; Karperecek és karkötők; Fejre való ékszerek; Nyakláncok [ékszerek]; Ékszerdobozok és óradobozok; Strassz [drágakő utánzat]; Gyűrűk [ékszerek].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Orecchini; Orologi a pendolo; Sveglie; Custodie per orologi [attrezzate]; Orologi [da polso e da tasca]; Braccialetti per orologi [cinturini]; Casse di orologi; Accessori per orologi; Braccialetti; Articoli di gioielleria per il capo; Collane [gioielleria]; Porta gioie e porta orologi; Strass; Anelli [gioielleria].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Auskarai; Laikrodžiai [sieniniai, staliniai, bokšto]; Žadintuvai; Laikrodžių dėžutės [pritaikytos]; Laikrodžiai [kišeniniai, rankiniai]; Laikrodžių apyrankės; Laikrodžių dėžutės [laikrodžių dalys]; Laikrodžių priedai; Apyrankės; Juvelyriniai galvos papuošalai; Karoliai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Juvelyrinių dirbinių dėžutės ir laikrodžių dėžutės; Strazai; Žiedai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Auskari; Pulksteņi; Modinātājpulksteņi; Futrāļi rokas pulksteņiem; Rokas un kabatas pulksteņi; Rokas pulksteņu aproces; Rokas un kabatas pulksteņu ietvari; Piederumi pulksteņiem; Rokassprādzes; Galvasrotas (juvelierizstrādājumi); Kaklarotas (juvelierizstrādājumi); Kastītes juvelierizstrādājumiem un pulksteņiem; Strasi (stikla juvelierizstrādājumi); Gredzeni (juvelierizstrādājumi).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Imsielet tal-widnejn; Arloġġi ta' l-id; Żveljarini; Kaxxi [mgħammra] għall-arloġġi; Arloġġi ta' l-id; Ċineg tal-arloġġ tal-idejn; Kaxex għall-arloġġi; Fitings għall-arloġġi tal-idejn; Brazzuletti / Ċpiepet; Ġojjellerija għar-ras; Kullani [ġojjellerija]; Kaxex għall-ġojjelli u kaxex għall-arloġġi; Ġojjellerija falza; Ċrieket [ġojjellerija].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Oorbellen; Klokken; Wekkers; Horloges (Aangepaste doosjes voor -); Horloges; Horlogebanden; Horlogekasten; Onderdelen voor uurwerken; Arm- en enkelbanden; Juwelierswaren voor het hoofd; Halskettingen [juwelierswaren]; Juwelendoosjes en horlogedoosjes; Stras; Ringen [juwelierswaren].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kolczyki; Zegarki; Budziki; Futerały na zegary [na miarę]; Zegarki; Paski do zegarków; Koperty do zegarków; Akcesoria do zegarków; Bransolety; Biżuteria do noszenia na głowie; Naszyjniki [biżuteria]; Pudełka na biżuterię i pudełka na zegarki; Biżuteria ze szkła sztrasowego; Pierścionki [biżuteria].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Brincos para orelhas; Relógios; Relógios despertadores; Estojos para relógios feitos à medida; Relógios de pulso; Braceletes para relógios; Caixas de relógios [componentes de relógios]; Acessórios para relógios; Pulseiras; Joalharia para a cabeça; Colares [joalharia]; Caixas de joias e caixas de relógios; Strass [bijuteria]; Anéis [joalharia].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cercei; Brățară (Ceasuri cu -); Ceasuri deșteptătoare; Cutii pentru ceasuri [ajustate]; Brățară (Ceasuri cu -); Brățări de ceas; Carcase de ceasuri de mână; Accesorii pentru ceasuri; Brățări; Bijuterii pentru cap; Coliere [bijuterii]; Casete pentru bijuterii și cutii pentru ceasuri; Ștrasuri; Inele [bijuterii].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Náušnice; Hodiny; Budíky; Puzdra [upravené] pre hodinky; Hodinky; Remienky na náramkové hodinky; Hodinkové puzdrá (súčasť hodiniek); Príslušenstvo pre hodinky; Náramky; Šperky na ozdobu hlavy; Náhrdelníky (klenotnícke výrobky); Šperkovnice a kazety na hodinky; Štras (brúsené olovnaté sklo); Prstene (klenotnícke výrobky).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Uhani; Ročne ure; Budilke; Škatle za ure [po meri]; Ročne ure; Paščki za ure; Ohišja za ročne ure; Oprema za ure; Zapestnice; Naglavni nakit; Ogrlice [nakit]; Šatulje za nakit in šatulje za ure; Bižuterija; Prstani [nakit].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Örhängen; Klockor; Väckarklockor; Fodral för ur [utformade]; Ur; Remmar för armbandsur; Boetter; Klocktillbehör; Armringar; Smycken för huvudet; Halsband [smycken]; Smyckeskrin och klockaskar; Oäkta smycken; Ringar [smycken].</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>18</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Приспособления за пренос на животни [чанти]; Джобни портфейли; Плажни чанти; Нашийници за домашни любимци; Несесери за гримове; Чанти за тоалетни принадлежности; Чанти за къмпинг; Куфари, чанти, портфейли и други изделия за пренасяне на багаж; Модни ръчни чанти; Ръчни чанти, портмонета и портфейли; Куфарчета за носене на документи; Чанти за спорт.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přepravky na zvířata [tašky]; Cestovní tašky; Plážové tašky; Obojky pro domácí zvířata; Kosmetické kabelky; Toaletní tašky; Turistické batohy; Zavazadla, cestovní tašky, peněženky a ostatní tašky; Módní kabelky; Kabelky, peněženky a náprsní tašky; Přenosná pouzdra na dokumenty; Sportovní tašky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Befordring til dyr [tasker]; Rejsetasker; Strandtasker; Halsbånd til kæledyr; Kosmetikpunge; Toilettasker; Tasker til campister; Rejsetasker, tasker, tegnebøger og andre bæreposer; Modehåndtasker; Håndtasker, punge og tegnebøger; Transporttasker til dokumenter; Sportstasker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Tragevorrichtungen für Tiere [Taschen]; Reisetaschen; Badetaschen; Halsbänder für Haustiere; Kosmetikbeutel; Kulturbeutel; Campingtaschen; Gepäck, Taschen, Brieftaschen und andere Tragebehältnisse; Modehandtaschen; Handtaschen, Geldbörsen und Brieftaschen; Tragekoffer für Dokumente; Sporttaschen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Τσάντες μεταφοράς ζώων· Βαλίτσες· Παραλία (τσάντες -ας)· Περιλαίμια για κατοικίδια· Τσαντάκια για καλλυντικά· Τσαντάκια για είδη προσωπικής περιποίησης· Κατασκηνωτικοί σάκκοι· Ταξιδιωτικές αποσκευές, τσάντες, πορτοφόλια και άλλα είδη μεταφοράς· Μοντέρνες γυναικείες τσάντες· Τσάντες χειρός, πορτοφόλια για κέρματα και πορτοφόλια· Θήκες μεταφοράς εγγράφων· Τσάντες γυμναστηρίου.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Animal carriers [bags]; Bags for carrying pets; Bags for travel; Beach bags; Collars for pets; Cosmetic bags; Toiletry bags; Camping bags; Luggage, bags, wallets and other carriers; Fashion handbags; Handbags, purses and wallets; Carrying cases for documents; Bags for sports.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bolsas para transportar animales; Bolsas de viaje; Bolsas de playa; Collares para animales domésticos; Neceseres para cosméticos; Bolsas de tocador; Bolsas de campamento; Equipaje, bolsos, carteras y otros porta objetos; Bolsos de moda; Bolsos, monederos y carteras de bolsillo; Estuches para llevar documentos; Bolsas de deporte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Loomade transportimise puurid [kotid]; Reisikotid; Rannakotid; Lemmikloomade kaelarihmad; Meigitarvete kotid; Tualett-tarvete kotid; Matkakotid; Kohvrid, kotid, rahakotid ja muud sarnased kandmisvahendid; Moekäekotid; Käekotid, rahakotid, rahataskud; Dokumentide kandekohvrid; Spordikotid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Eläinten kantolaitteet [kassit]; Matkakassit; Rantalaukut; Lemmikkieläinten kaulapannat; Kosmetiikkalaukut; Toalettilaukut; Laukut retkeilijöille; Matkalaukut, laukut, lompakot ja muut kantimet; Muodikkaat käsilaukut; Käsilaukut, lompakot ja kukkarot; Asiakirjojen kantokotelot; Voimistelukassit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Dispositifs pour le transport d'animaux [sacs]; Sacs de voyage; Sacs de plage; Colliers pour animaux domestiques; Trousses à maquillage; Trousses de toilette; Sacs de campeurs; Bagages, sacs, portefeuilles et autres objets de transport; Sacs à main de mode; Sacs à main, porte-monnaie et portefeuilles; Étuis pour documents; Sacs de sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Nosači za životinje [torbe]; Prtljažni artikli; Torbe za plažu; Ovratnici za kućne ljubimce; Torbe za šminku; Neseseri; Torbe za kampiranje; Kovčezi, torbe, novčanici i drugi proizvodi za nošenje; Modne torbe; Ručne torbe, torbice i novčanici; Torbe za nošenje dokumenata; Sportske torbe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hordozók állatoknak [táskák]; Poggyász; Strandtáskák; Nyakörvek házi kedvenceknek; Neszesszerek; Piperetáskák, neszesszerek; Táskák, hátizsákok táborozóknak; Utazótáskák, bőröndök, tárcák és más hordozóeszközök; Divatos kézitáskák; Kézitáskák, pénztárcák és irattárcák; Irattáskák; Sporttáskák, tornazsákok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Trasportini per animali [borse]; Sacchi da viaggio; Borse da spiaggia; Collari per animali domestici; Borsellini per cosmetici; Astucci da toilette; Sacchi da campeggiatori; Valigie, borse, portafogli e contenitori portatili; Borse alla moda; Borsette, portamonete e portafogli; Custodie per documenti; Borse da sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Gyvūnų gabenimo krepšiai; Kelionmaišiai; Paplūdimio krepšeliai; Kambarinių gyvūnų antkakliai; Kosmetikos krepšeliai; Tualeto reikmenų krepšeliai; Turistų krepšiai; Lagaminai, rankinukai, piniginės ir kiti krepšiai; Madingos rankinės; Rankinukai, piniginės ir sulenkiamos piniginės; Nešiojamieji dokumentų dėklai; Sportiniai krepšiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Somas dzīvnieku pārnēsāšanai; Ceļasomas; Pludmales somas; Mājdzīvnieku kaklasiksnas; Kosmētikas piederumu somiņas; Kosmētikas somiņas; Tūristu somas; Bagāžas somas un čemodāni, somas, naudas maki un citi piederumi lietu pārnēsāšanai; Modernas rokassomas; Rokassomas, naudasmaki un kabatas portfeļi; Dokumentu koferi; Sporta somas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Trasportaturi tal-annimali [basktijiet]; Valiġġi; Basktijiet tal-baħar; Kullari għall-annimali domestiċi; Boroż għall-kożmetiċi; Boroż għall-oġġetti tat-twaletta; Basktijiet għal min jikkampeġġja; Bagalji, basktijiet, kartieri u oġġetti oħra li ġġor fihom; Ħendbegs tal-moda; Basktijiet tal-id, portmonijiet u kartieri; Kaxxetti għall-ġarr tad-dokumenti; Basktijiet għall-affarijiet li jintużaw fil-ġinnasju (sport).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Draagtassen voor dieren; Reistassen; Strandtassen; Halsbanden voor huisdieren; Etuis voor cosmetische middelen; Toilettassen; Kampeertassen; Bagage, tassen, knapzakken en andere draagtassen; Modehandtassen; Handtassen, portemonnees en portefeuilles; Draagkoffers voor documenten; Sporttassen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Nosidełka dla zwierząt [torby]; Bagaż; Torby plażowe; Obroże dla zwierząt domowych; Kosmetyczki; Kosmetyczki [saszetki na przybory toaletowe]; Torby turystyczne; Walizy, torby podróżne, torby, portfele i inne artykuły służące do przenoszenia; Stylowe torebki; Torebki, portmonetki i portfele; Futerały przenośne na dokumenty; Torby gimnastyczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Caixas de transporte de animais [sacos]; Sacos de viagem; Sacos de praia; Coleiras para animais de estimação; Estojos de maquilhagem; Sacos de toilette; Sacos para campistas; Bagagens, malas, carteiras e outras bolsas de transporte; Malas de senhora à moda; Malas de mão [para senhora], bolsas e carteiras; Malas para transporte de documentos; Sacos de desporto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Transportoare pentru animale [genți]; Genți; Genți de plajă; Zgărzi pentru animale de companie; Gentuțe cosmetice; Truse de toaletă (marochinărie); Rucsacuri pentru camping; Bagaje, pungi, portofele și alte accesorii; Posete la moda; Poșete, portmonee și portofele; Mape pentru transportul documentelor; Genți sportive.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Tašky na prenášanie zvierat; Cestovné tašky; Plážové tašky; Obojky pre domáce zvieratá; Kozmetické taštičky; Toaletné taštičky; Turistické plecniaky; Kufre, tašky, peňaženky a výrobky koženej galantérie; Módne kabelky; Kabelky, peňaženky a náprsné tašky; Prenosné puzdrá na dokumenty; Športové tašky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pripomočki za prenašanje živali [torbe]; Prtljaga; Torbe za plažo; Ovratnice za hišne ljubljenčke; Kozmetične torbice; Toaletne torbice; Torbe za tabornike; Kovčki, potovalne torbe, denarnice in drugi podobni proizvodi; Modne ročne torbice; Ročne torbice, torbice in denarnice; Etuiji za nošenje dokumentov; Telovadne torbe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Transportväskor för djur; Reseväskor; Strandväskor; Halsband för sällskapsdjur; Sminketuier; Necessärer; Väskor för campare; Resgods, väskor, plånböcker och andra artiklar för bärhjälp; Modehandväskor; Handväskor, plånböcker och portmonnäer; Bärväskor för dokument; Bags för sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ръкавици за велосипедисти; Ръкавици с един пръст; Костюми за маскарад и Хелоуин; Трика; Бански костюми за мъже; Бански костюми за жени; Дамско облекло; Ръкавици с чувствителни върхове на пръстите, които могат да се носят при използване на ръчни електронни устройства със сензорни екрани; Шалчета; Панделки, ленти за глава; Ръкавици за сноуборд; Зимни ръкавици; Плувни шапки; Ръкавици; Къси чорапи и дълги чорапи.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Rukavice pro cyklisty; Palčáky (rukavice); Maškarní kostýmy a kostýmy na Halloween; Punčochové kalhoty; Pánské plavky; Dámské plavky; Dámské oděvy; Rukavice s vodivým materiálem na konečcích prstů k ovládání přenosných elektronických zařízení s dotykovým displejem; Šátky a šály; Čelenky [oděvy]; Snowboardové rukavice; Zimní rukavice; Koupací čepice; Rukavice [oděvy]; Ponožky a punčochy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Handsker til cyklister; Fingerløse handsker; Karnevals- og halloweenkostumer; Trikoter; Badedragter til mænd; Badedragter til kvinder; Dametøj; Handsker med ledende fingerspidser til anvendelse ved brug af håndholdte elektroniske enheder med berøringsskærme; Tørklæder; Pandebånd [beklædning]; Snowboard-handsker; Vinterhandsker; Badehætter; Handsker [beklædning]; Strømper og sokker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Handschuhe für Radfahrer; Fingerlose Handschuhe; Faschings-, Karnevals- und Halloween-Kostüme; Strumpfhosen; Badeanzüge für Herren; Badeanzüge für Damen; Damenbekleidung; Handschuhe mit leitfähigen Fingerspitzen, die beim Verwenden von elektronischen Taschengeräten mit Berührungsbildschirm getragen werden können; Schals; Stirnbänder [Bekleidung]; Snowboard-Handschuhe; Winterhandschuhe; Bademützen; Handschuhe [Bekleidung]; Socken und Strumpfwaren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Γάντια για ποδηλάτες· Γάντια χωρίς χωρίσματα για τα δάκτυλα· Κοστούμια μεταμφίεσης και αποκριάτικα (Halloween)· Κολάν· Ανδρικά μαγιό· Γυναικεία μαγιό· Γυναικεία ενδύματα· Γάντια με αγώγιμο υλικό στις άκρες των δακτύλων κατάλληλα για χρήση ηλεκτρικών συσκευών με οθόνη αφής· Μαντήλια για το λαιμό· Περίδεμα κεφαλιού [είδη ένδυσης]· Γάντια χιονοσανίδας· Χειμερινά γάντια· Κολυμβητικά σκουφάκια· Γάντια· Καλτσάκια και λεπτές γυναικείες κάλτσες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Cycling Gloves; Fingerless gloves; Masquerade and halloween costumes; Pantyhose; Bathing suits for men; Bathing costumes for women; Ladies' clothing; Gloves with conductive fingertips that may be worn while using handheld electronic touch screen devices; Scarves; Headbands; Snowboard gloves; Winter gloves; Swimming caps [bathing caps]; Gloves; Socks and stockings.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Guantes para ciclistas; Mitones; Disfraces y trajes de Halloween (víspera de Todos los Santos); Pantis; Trajes de baño para caballeros; Trajes de baño para señora; Ropa de mujer; Guantes con puntas conductoras que pueden usarse al utilizar dispositivos electrónicos portátiles provistos de pantallas táctiles; Fulares; Bandas para la cabeza [prendas de vestir]; Guantes de snowboard; Guantes de invierno; Gorros de baño; Guantes [prendas de vestir]; Calcetines y medias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ratturikindad; Labakindad, käpikud; Maskeraadi- ja halloweenikostüümid; Sukkpüksid; Meeste ujumiskostüümid; Naiste supelkostüümid; Naisterõivad; Konduktiivsete sõrmeotstega kindad, mida saab kasutada puuteekraaniga elektrooniliste pihuseadmete kasutamisel; Sallid; Peapaelad [rõivad]; Lumelauakindad; Talvekindad; Supelmütsid; Kindad (rõivad); Sokid ja sukad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Pyöräilykäsineet; Lapaset; Naamiais- ja halloweenasut; Sukkahousut; Miesten uimapuvut; Naisten uimapuvut; Naisten vaatteet; Sähköä johtavilla sormenpäillä varustetut käsineet kosketusnäytöllä varustetun elektroniikan käyttöä varten; Huivit; Päänauhat [hikinauhat]; Lumilautakäsineet; Talvikäsineet; Uimalakit; Käsineet; Sukat ja pitkät sukat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Gants pour cyclistes; Mitaines; Costumes de carnaval et d'halloween; Collants; Maillot de bain pour hommes; Maillots de bain pour femmes; Vêtements pour femmes; Gants à doigts conducteurs pouvant être portés lors de l'utilisation de dispositifs électroniques portables à écran tactile [habillement]; Foulards; Bandeaux pour la tête [habillement]; Gants de snowboard; Gants d'hiver; Bonnets de bain; Gants [habillement]; Chaussettes et bas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Biciklističke rukavice; Narukvice, vunene [pletene]; Kostimi za maškare i Noć vještica; Bodiji; Kupaće gaćice za muškarce; Ženski kupaći kostimi; Odjeća za žene; Rukavice s provodljivim vršcima prstiju za korištenje s elektroničkim uređajima sa zaslonom na dodir; Rupci [fulari]; Trake za glavu; Rukavice za snowboard; Zimske rukavice; Kape za plivanje; Rukavice; Čarape i dokoljenke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kesztyűk kerékpárosoknak; Kétujjas kesztyűk; Álarcosbálra való és Halloween jelmezek; Harisnyanadrágok; Férfi fürdőnadrágok; Női fürdőruhák; Ruházati cikkek nők számára; Kapacitív kesztyűk érintőképernyős készülékekhez; Sálak; Fejszalagok [ruházat]; Hódeszkás kesztyűk; Téli kesztyűk; Úszósapkák; Kesztyűk; Zoknik és harisnyák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Guanti per ciclisti; Guanti a manopola; Costumi di halloween e per feste in maschera; Collants; Costumi da bagno da uomo; Costumi da bagno da donna; Abbigliamento da donna; Guanti con dita a fibre conduttive che possono essere indossati durante l'uso di dispositivi elettronici palmari con touch screen; Foulards [fazzoletti]; Fasce per la testa [abbigliamento]; Guanti per snowboard; Guanti invernali; Cuffie da bagno; Guanti [abbigliamento]; Calzini e calze.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Dviratininkų pirštinės; Puspirštinės; Maskarado ir Helovino kostiumai; Pėdkelnės; Vyriški maudymosi kostiumai; Moteriški maudymosi kostiumėliai; Moteriški drabužiai; Pirštinės su laidžiais pirštų galais, kurias galima dėvėti naudojant rankinius elektroninius prietaisus su jutikliniu ekranu; Šalikai; Galvajuostės [drabužiai]; Snieglentininkų pirštinės; Žieminės pirštinės; Maudymosi kepuraitės; Pirštinės [drabužiai]; Puskojinės ir kojinės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Velosipēdistu cimdi; Pirkstus nenosedzoši cimdi; Maskarādēm un Helovīna svētkiem paredzētie kostīmi; Triko; Vīriešu peldtērpi; Sieviešu peldkostīmi; Sieviešu apģērbi; Cimdi ar vadītspējīgiem pirkstu galiem, ko var nenovilkt, izmantojot elektroniskas skārienjutīgas ierīces; Šalles; Pieres lentes (apģērbi); Snovborda cimdi; Ziemas cimdi; Peldcepures; Cimdi; Zeķes un garās zeķes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ingwanti għaċ-ċiklisti; Ingwanti li jgħattu erba' swaba tal-id flimkien u l-behem tgħattih waħdu [mittens]; Kostumi tal-maskarati u tal-Halloween; Tajts; Malji tal-għawm għall-irġiel; Malji tal-għawm għan-nisa; Ħwejjeġ tan-nisa; Ingwanti bi swaba' konduttivi li jistgħu jintlibsu waqt li jintuża apparat elettroniku b'skrin li jinħadem billi tmissu; Xalpi; Bandò [lbies]; Ingwanti għall-isnowbord; Ingwanti tax-xitwa; Kapep tal-għawm; Ingwanti; Kalzetti li jaslu sal-għaksa u dawk li jaslu sal-koxxa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Handschoenen voor fietsers; Wanten; Verkleed- en Halloweenkostuums; Panty's; Badkleding voor heren; Badkleding voor dames; Dameskleding; Handschoenen met geleidende vingertoppen die kunnen worden gedragen tijdens het gebruik van elektronische touchscreen apparatuur; Halsdoeken; Hoofdbanden [kleding]; Snowboard handschoenen; Winterhandschoenen; Badmutsen; Handschoenen [kleding]; Sokken en kousen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Rękawiczki dla rowerzystów; Rękawiczki z jednym palcem; Kostiumy na bale maskowe i Halloween; Rajstopy; Kostiumy kąpielowe dla mężczyzn; Kostiumy kąpielowe dla kobiet; Odzież damska; Rękawiczki z materiałem przewodzącym na czubkach palców, które można nosić podczas używania podręcznych urządzeń elektronicznych z ekranem dotykowym; Szaliki; Opaski na głowę; Rękawice do snowboardu; Rękawiczki zimowe; Czepki kąpielowe; Rękawiczki; Skarpetki i pończochy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Luvas para ciclistas; Luvas sem dedos; Fatos de carnaval e de Halloween; Collants; Fatos de banho para homem; Fatos de banho para senhora; Vestuário de mulher; Luvas com pontas dos dedos condutoras para poderem ser usadas com dispositivos eletrónicos manuais com ecrã tátil; Cachecóis; Fitas para cabeça [vestuário]; Luvas de snowboard; Luvas de inverno; Toucas de banho; Luvas [vestuário]; Peúgas e meias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Mănuși pentru cicliști; Mitene; Costume de bal mascat și de Halloween; Colanți; Costume de baie pentru bărbați; Costume de baie pentru femei; Îmbrăcăminte pentru femei; Mănuși cu vârfurile degetelor din material conductiv, care por fi purtate atunci când se utilizează dispozitive electronice portabile cu ecran tactil; Eșarfe; Bentițe pentru cap; Mănuși pentru snowboard; Mănuși de iarnă; Căști de înot; Mănuși [articole de îmbrăcăminte]; Șosete și ciorapi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Rukavice pre cyklistov; Palčiaky; Maškarné kostýmy a kostýmy na Halloween; Pančuškové nohavice; Pánske plavky; Dámske plavky; Dámske odevy; Rukavice s vodivými končekmi prstov, ktoré sa môžu používať počas obsluhy zariadení s elektronickými dotykovými obrazovkami; Šatky, šály; Čelenky (oblečenie); Snoubordové rukavice; Zimné rukavice; Kúpacie čiapky; Rukavice; Ponožky a pančuchy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Rokavice za kolesarje; Palčniki (rokavice); Kostumi za maškarado in noč čarovnic; Hlačne nogavice; Kopalke za moške; Kopalke za ženske; Oblačila za ženske; Rokavice s prevodnimi prstnimi konicami, za uporabo z ročnimi elektronskimi napravami, ki imajo zaslon na dotik; Ovratne rute; Naglavni trakovi [oblačila]; Rokavice za deskanje na snegu; Zimske rokavice; Plavalne kape; Rokavice; Kratke in dolge nogavice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Handskar för cyklister; Torgvantar; Maskerad- och halloweendräkter; Strumpbyxor; Baddräkter för män; Baddräkter för damer; Damkläder; Handskar med ledande fingertoppar som kan bäras när man använder pekskärmen på handhållen elektronisk utrustning; Scarves; Pannband [kläder]; Snowboardhandskar; Vinterhandskar; Badmössor; Handskar; Sockor och strumpor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079129</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>96576</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003122958</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-06-02</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>004585295</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2005-08-10</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>004585295</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2015-02-09</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>LIFE</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>016673171</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2017-04-28</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>016673171</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2020-01-13</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>life</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>60690</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>13775</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018468515</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>96576</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-08</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018677537</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Change of name and professional address</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>96576</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-22</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
