<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T09:40:13</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224201</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224201</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>UPEASY</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Медицинско устройство, а именно, преносима възглавница за повдигане на седалка с цел подпомагане на хора при тяхното внимателно сядане и ставане от столове, дивани и други повърхности.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Lékařská zařízení, jmenovitě přenosný zvedací sedák pro pomoc osobám při pozvolném usedání a zvedání se z křesel, pohovek a jiných povrchů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Medicinsk udstyr, nemlig en bærbar siddepude, som kan hæves, der hjælper personer med at komme ned at sidde og rejse sig fra stole, sofaer og andre overflader.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Medizinische Geräte, nämlich transportable Hebesitzpolster zur Unterstützung von Personen beim vorsichtigen Hinsetzen und Aufstehen von Stühlen, Sofas und anderen Oberflächen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ιατρικές διατάξεις, συγκεκριμένα, φορητό ανυψούμενο μαξιλάρι καθίσματος ως βοήθημα για το εύκολο κάθισμα και το σήκωμα ατόμων από καρέκλες, καναπέδες, και άλλες επιφάνειες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Medical device, namely, a portable lifting seat cushion for assisting persons in gently seating and raising themselves from chairs, sofas, and other surfaces.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Dispositivo médico, en concreto, un cojín de asiento elevable para ayudar a las personas a sentarse y levantarse con suavidad de sillas, sofás y otras superficies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meditsiiniinstrumendid, nimelt kaasaskantav tõstetav istmepadi, mis aitab inimestel õrnalt istuda ja end toolidelt, diivanitelt ja muudelt pindadelt tõsta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lääketieteellinen laite, nimittäin kannettava kohotettava istuintyyny, jolla avustetaan henkilöitä varovasti istumaan ja nostamaan itsensä tuoleilta, sohvilta ja muilta tasoilta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Dispositif médical, à savoir coussin de siège de levage portable pour aider des personnes à s'asseoir dans des chaises, des sofas et d'autres surfaces et à se lever en douceur.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Medicinski uređaji, i to prenosivi jastuci za sjedala za posjedanje i podizanje osoba sa stolica, sofa i ostalih površina.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Orvosi eszköz, nevezetesen egy hordozható emelő üléspárna, amely segíti az embereket a székeken, kanapékon és más felületeken történő kényelmes ülésében és a felállásban.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Dispositivo medico, ovvero, un cuscino di seduta a sollevamento portatile per assistere le persone a sedersi e alzarsi da sedie, sofà, e altre superfici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Medicinos prietaisas, būtent nešiojamoji kėlimo sėdynės pagalvė, skirta padėti žmonėms švelniai atsisėsti ir atsikelti nuo kėdžių, sofų ir kitų paviršių.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Medicīnas ierīce, proti, pārnēsājams, paceļams sēdekļa spilvens, kas palīdz cilvēkiem viegli sēdēt un pacelt sevi no krēsliem, dīvāniem un citām virsmām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat mediku, jiġifieri, kuxxin tas-sedil tal-irfigħ li jista' jinġarr biex jgħin persuni biex b'mod ġentili dawn ipoġġu jew iqajmu lilhom infushom minn siġġijiet, sufani, u wċuħ oħra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Medische apparatuur, te weten een draagbaar stoelkussen met hefmechanisme om personen te helpen bij het makkelijk plaatsnemen op en opstaan uit stoelen, sofa's en andere oppervlakken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia medyczne, mianowicie przenośne poduszki na siedzenie umożliwiające delikatne siadanie na krzesła, kanapy i inne powierzchnie oraz wstawanie z nich.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Dispositivo médico, especificamente uma almofada de assento elevatória portátil para auxiliar as pessoas a sentarem-se e a levantarem-se suavemente em e de cadeiras, sofás e outras superfícies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Dispozitiv medical, și anume o pernă pentru un scaun mobil care se ridică pentru a ajuta persoanele să se așeze și să se ridice ușor de pe scaune, canapele și alte suprafețe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zdravotnícke pomôcky, menovite prenosné zdvíhacie sedadlo na pomoc osobám pre jemnom usádzaní a zdvíhaní zo stoličky, gauča a iných povrchov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Medicinski aparat, in sicer prenosna dvižna blazina za sedež za pomoč ljudem pri nežnem posedanju in dvigovanju s stolov, zof in drugih površin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Medicinska anordningar, nämligen en bärbar upphöjande sittkudde för att assistera personer för att sitta mjukt och för att resa sig från stolen, fåtöljer, och andra ytor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/080</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/151</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-11</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079117</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>46609</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
