<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-24T08:47:47</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224166</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224166</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-22</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>sv</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-24</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Cook IT by NORDISKA PLAST</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Контейнери за компост за домакинска употреба; Кофи за боклук; Пластмасови кошчета (кофи за боклук); Съдове за напитки; Контейнери за съхранение на храна; Купички за пиене за домашни любимци; Градинарски лейки; Дозиращи лъжички за кафе; Буркани; Фунии; Купи; Кухненски прибори; Сокоизстисквачки за плодови сокове; Уреди за мачкане на храна; Цедки; Подноси за храна; Дъски за рязане на месо; Стъклени чаши за пиене; Купи и халби; Чинии; Кошници за хляб за домакински цели; Разделители за прибори за хранене за чекмедже; Стойки/сушилници за сушене на чинии; Кошници за прибори за хранене; Ведра.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nádoby na kompost k použití v domácnosti; Nádoby na odpad; Plastové nádoby (popelnice); Nádoby na nápoje; Nádoby na ukládání potravin; Misky na pití pro domácí zvířata; Konve na zalévání; Naběračky na kávu; Nádoby ze skla; Trychtýře; Misky; Kuchyňské náčiní; Ruční odšťavňovače na ovocné šťávy; Šťouchadla na jídlo; Cedníky; Jídelní podnosy; Prkénka na krájení; Sklenice na pití; Hrnky a šálky; Stolní talíře; Košíky na chleba pro použití v domácnosti; Přihrádky na příbory; Odkapávače na nádobí; Košíky na příbory; Kbelíky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kompostbeholdere til husholdningsbrug; Skraldebøtter; Plasticspande (skraldespande); Beholdere til drikkevarer; Beholdere til opbevaring af mad; Drikkeskåle til kæledyr; Vandkander; Kaffemåleskeer; Krukker; Tragte; Spølkum; Køkkenredskaber; Frugtjuicepressere; Mosere til mad [kartoffelmoser]; Sier; Madbakker; Forskærerbrætter; Drikkeglas; Kopper og krus; Tallerkner; Brødkurve til husholdningsbrug; Bestikbakker; Opvaskestativer; Bestikkurve; Spande.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kompostbehälter für Haushaltszwecke; Mülleimer; Abfallbehälter aus Kunststoff; Trinkbehälter; Vorratsbehälter für Lebensmittel; Trinkschalen für Haustiere; Gießkannen; Kaffeemaßlöffel; Kruggefäße; Trichter; Schalen; Küchengeräte; Reiben zur Herstellung von Fruchtsäften; Nahrungsmittelstampfer; Siebe; Tabletts; Tranchierbretter; Glaswaren für Getränke; Tassen und Becher; Geschirr; Brotkörbe für den Haushalt; Bestecktabletts; Abtropfständer; Besteckkörbe; Eimer aller Art.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κάδοι κομποστοποίησης οικιακής χρήσης· Δοχεία απορριμμάτων· Πλαστικοί κάδοι (σκουπιδοτενεκέδες)· Δοχεία ποτών· Δοχεία αποθήκευσης τροφίμων· Γαβάθες πόσης για κατοικίδια ζώα· Ποτιστήρια· Κουτάλια για τον καφέ· Κανάτα· Χωνιά· Γαβάθες· Σκεύη μαγειρικής χρήσης· Στίφτες για χυμούς φρούτων· Εργαλεία πολτοποίησης τροφίμων· Σουρωτήρια· Δίσκοι φαγητού· Πλάκες κοπής· Γυαλικά είδη για ποτά· Κύπελλα και κούπες· Πιατέλες· Καλάθια για το ψωμί, για οικιακή χρήση· Δίσκοι για μαχαιροπίρουνα· Σχάρες για το στέγνωμα των πιάτων· Καλάθια για μαχαιροπήρουνα· Κάδοι.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Compost containers for household use; dust bins; plastic bins (dust bins); drinks containers; food storage containers; pet drinking bowls; watering cans; Coffee scoops; jars; funnels; bowl (basins); kitchen utensils; reamers for fruit juice; food mashers; strainers; meal trays; carving boards; drinking glasses; cups and mugs; table plates; bread baskets; cutlery trays; dish drying racks; cutlery baskets; buckets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Recipientes de uso doméstico para compost; Cubos de basura; Cubos de plástico (cubos de basura); Recipientes para bebidas; Recipientes para almacenar alimentos; Cuencos de beber para animales domésticos; Regaderas; Cucharas medidoras de café; Botes (tarros); Embudos; Tazones (cuencos); Utensilios de cocina; Exprimidores para zumo de fruta; Pasapurés; Coladores; Bandejas para la comida; Tablas para trinchar; Cristalería para bebidas; Tazas y tazones; Platos; Cestas para el pan de uso doméstico; Bandejas de cubertería; Secadores de vajilla [escurreplatos]; Cestos para cuchillería; Cubos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Majapidamises kasutatavad kompostimahutid; Prügikastid; Plastkorvid (prügikorvid); Joogimahutid, joogianumad; Anumad toidu hoidmiseks; Lemmikloomade joogikausid; Kastekannud; Kohvimõõdulusikad; Purgid; Lehtrid; Kausid, vaagnad; Köögitarbed; Käsimahlapressid; Toidupudrustajad; Kurnad; Toidukandikud; Lõikelauad; Joogiklaasid; Tassid ja kruusid; Taldrikud; Leivakorvid [majatarbed]; Söögiriistakarbid; Nõudekuivatusrestid; Söögiriistakorvid; Panged, ämbrid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kompostiastiat kotitalouskäyttöön; Roska-astiat; Muovikorit (jäteastiat); Juomasäiliöt; Elintarvikkeiden säilytysastiat; Lemmikkien juomakupit; Kastelukannut; Kahvimitat; Purkit; Suppilot; Vadit [astiat]; Keittokattilasarjat; Hedelmämehupusertimet; Elintarvikkeiden soseuttajat; Siivilät; Ateriatarjottimet; Leikkuulaudat; Lasiset juoma-astiat; Kupit ja mukit; Lautaset; Leipäkorit kotitalouskäyttöön; Ruokailuvälinelokerikot; Astiankuivaustelineet; Ruokailuvälinekorit; Sangot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bacs à compost à usage ménager; Poubelles; Corbeilles en plastique (poubelles); Récipients pour boissons; Récipients pour la conservation d'aliments; Écuelles pour la boisson pour animaux domestiques; Arrosoirs; Cuillers à café; Pots [bocaux]; Entonnoirs; Bols; Ustensiles de cuisine; Presse-fruits pour jus de fruits; Pilons à légumes; Passoires; Plateaux-repas (vaisselle); Planches à découper; Verrerie pour boissons; Tasses et chopes; Assiettes; Corbeilles à pain à usage ménager; Range-couverts; Égouttoirs à vaisselle; Paniers à couverts; Seaux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kante za kompost za uporabu u kućanstvu; Kante za smeće; Plastične kante za otpatke (kante za smeće); Posude za piće; Spremnici za hranu; Posude za pojenje kućnih ljubimaca; Kante za zalijevanje; Mjerne žličice za kavu; Tegle; Lijevci; Plitice [zdjelice]; Kuhinjski pribor; Cjedila za agrume; Gnječilice; Cjedila; Poslužavnici za jelo; Daske za rezanje; Stakleno posuđe za pića; Male i velike šalice; Tanjuri; Košare za kruh [za kućanstvo]; Držači pribora za jelo za ladice; Stalci za sušenje posuđa; Košare za pribor za jelo; Vedra [drvene posude].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Komposzttartályok háztartási használatra; Szemeteskukák; Műanyag tartályok (porzsákok); Italtartók; Tartók, dobozok élelmiszerek tárolásához; Ivótálak kedvtelésből tartott háziállatoknak; Locsolókannák, öntözőkannák; Kávéadagoló kanalak; Lekváros üvegek, befőttes üvegek; Tölcsérek; Mosdótálak, lavórok; Konyhai eszközök, kis méretű; Gyümölcsfacsarók gyümölcslé készítéséhez; Ételtörők; Szűrők [passzírozók]; Étkező tálcák; Vágódeszkák; Üvegáru italokhoz; Csészék és bögrék; Tányérok; Kenyérkosarak, háztartási célokra; Evőeszköztartók; Edényszárító állványok; Evőeszköz-tároló kosarak; Vödrök.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Contenitori per compost per uso domestico; Pattumiere; Bidoni della spazzatura in plastica; Contenitori per bibite; Contenitori per la conservazione degli alimenti; Ciotole per bere per animali domestici; Innaffiatoi; Cucchiaini da caffè; Caraffe; Imbuti; Bacinelle; Utensili da cucina; Spremifrutta per fare succhi di frutta; Utensili per schiacciare alimenti; Colini; Vassoi; Taglieri; Vetreria [bicchieri]; Bicchieri e tazze; Piatti; Cestini per il pane per uso domestico; Portaposate; Cestelli per asciugare i piatti; Cestini per coltelleria; Secchi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Buitiniai komposto konteineriai; Atliekų dėžės; Plastikiniai indai (atliekų dėžės); Gėrimų tara; Talpyklos maistui laikyti; Kambarinių gyvūnėlių geriamieji dubenėliai; Laistytuvai; Kavos samteliai; Indai plačiu kakleliu; Piltuvėliai; Katiliukai; Virtuviniai indai; Vaisių sulčių spaustuvai; Maisto grūstukai; Koštuvai; Valgių padėklai; Pjaustymo lentos; Stiklinės; Puodeliai ir bokalai; Lėkštės; Duonos krepšeliai (buities reikmėms); Valgomųjų įrankių laikymo dėklai; Indų džiovinimo grotelės; Pintinės stalo įrankiams; Kibirai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Komposta tvertnes izmantošanai mājsaimniecībā; Atkritumu tvertnes; Plastmasas atkritumu tvertnes [putekļu tvertnes]; Trauki dzērieniem; Pārtikas uzglabāšanas tvertnes; Bļodiņas mājdzīvnieku dzirdināšanai; Lejkannas; Kafijas karotes; Burkas; Piltuves; Bļodas [tvertnes]; Virtuves trauki; Augļu sulas spiedes; Pārtikas stampas; Caurduri; Ēdienu paplātes; Griežamie dēlīši; Dzērienu glāzes; Tases un krūzes; Šķīvji; Maizes groziņi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Galda piederumu kastes; Trauku žāvēšanas plaukti; Grozi ar vāku; Spaiņi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kontenituri tal-kompost għall-użu fid-djar; Landi taż-żibel; Laned tal-plastik (laned tal-iskart); Kontenituri għax-xorb; Kontenituri għall-ħażna tal-ikel; Skutelli tax-xorb għall-annimali domestiċi; Laned għat-tisqija; Sassli tal-kafè; Vażetti; Lenbut; Friskaturi [skutelli]; Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir; Għodda biex tagħsar il-meraq tal-frott; Għaffieġa tal-ikel; Passaturi; Trejs tal-ikel; Uċuħ biex tqatta' fuqhom; Tazzi tal-ħġieġ; Kikkri u maggijiet; Platti li fihom jisserva l-ikel; Basktijiet tal-ħobż għal skopijiet domestiċi; Gabarrejiet għall-pożati; Xtillieri għat-tnixxif tad-dixxijiet; Basktijiet għall-pożati; Bramel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Groencontainers voor huishoudelijke doeleinden; Vuilnisbakken; Plastic emmers (prullenbakken); Houders voor dranken; Houders voor de opslag van voedingsmiddelen; Drinkschalen voor huisdieren; Gieters; Koffiemaatschepjes; Bokalen; Trechters; Kommen; Keukengerei; Vruchtenpersen voor vruchtensap; Voedselstampers; Vergieten; Dienbladen voor maaltijden; Snijplanken; Drinkglazen; Kopjes en bekers; Borden; Broodmanden voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Bestekbakken; Vaatdroogrekken; Bestekmanden; Kuipjes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pojemniki na kompost do użytku domowego; Kosze na śmieci; Kosze z tworzyw sztucznych (kosze na śmieci); Pojemniki do napojów; Pojemniki do przechowywania żywności; Miski do picia dla zwierząt domowych; Konewki; Miarki do kawy; Słoiki; Lejki; Miseczki; Przybory kuchenne; Wyciskarki do soku z owoców; Tłuczki kuchenne; Cedzaki; Tace na posiłki; Deski do krojenia; Naczynia szklane do napojów; Filiżanki i kubki; Talerze; Kosze na chleb do użytku domowego; Pojemniki z przegrodami do przechowywania sztućców; Suszarki-ociekacze do naczyń; Koszyki na sztućce; Kubły.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Recipientes de compostagem para uso doméstico; Caixotes do lixo; Caixotes de plástico (caixotes do lixo); Recipientes para bebidas; Recipientes para o armazenamento de alimentos; Tigelas para beber para animais de estimação; Regadores; Medidores de café; Potes; Funis; Bacias [pias]; Utensílios para cozinha; Espremedores para sumos de fruta; Esmagadores de alimentos; Coadores; Bandejas para refeições; Tábuas para trinchar; Copos para bebidas; Taças e canecas; Louça; Cestos para pão, para uso doméstico; Tabuleiros para serviço de talheres; Suportes de secar louça; Cestos para cutelaria; Baldes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Recipiente pentru compost, de uz casnic; Lăzi de gunoi; Coșuri din plastic (coșuri de gunoi); Recipiente pentru băuturi; Recipiente pentru depozitarea alimentelor; Boluri pentru băut pentru animale de companie; Stropitori; Linguri de cafea; Borcane; Pâlnii; Chiuvete; Ustensile de bucătărie; Storcătoare pentru sucuri de fructe; Ustensile de zdrobit alimentele; Strecurători; Tăvi pentru servit masă; Tocătoare; Articole din sticlă pentru băuturi; Ceşti şi căni; Farfurii; Coşuri de pâine de uz casnic; Tăvi de tacâmuri; Suporturi pentru uscarea vaselor; Coșuri pentru tacâmuri; Doniţe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nádoby na kompost, určené do domácnosti; Smetné nádoby; Plastové vrecká (vrecká na smeti); Nádoby na nápoje; Skladovacie nádoby na jedlo; Misky na pitie pre domáce zvieratká; Polievacie kanvy; Naberačky na kávu; Poháre; Lieviky; Misy; Kuchynský riad; Ručné odšťavovače na citrusy; Mliaždiče na jedlo; Cedidlá; Podnosy na jedlo; Dosky na krájanie; Sklené poháre; Šálky a hrnčeky; Taniere; Košíky na chlieb pre domácnosť; Priehradky na zorganizovanie príborov; Stojany na odkvapkávanie riadu; Koše na prestieranie; Kade, putne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Posode za kompost za gospodinjske namene; Smetnjaki; Plastični koši (koši za smeti); Posode za pijačo; Posode za shranjevanje hrane; Posode za pitje za hišne ljubljenčke; Kangle za zalivanje; Zajemalke za kavo; Kozarci za shranjevanje (vlaganje); Lijaki za natakanje; Umivalniki (sklede); Kuharski pripomočki; Stiskalniki za sadni sok; Tlačilke za hrano; Cedila; Kovinski pladnji; Deske za rezanje; Kozarci za pijačo; Kozarci in skodelice; Krožniki; Košarice za kruh za gospodinjske namene; Pladnji za pribor; Stojala za sušenje posode; Košarice za pribor; Vedra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kompostbehållare för hushållsbruk; soptunnor; plasttunnor (soptunnor); behållare för drycker; behållare för förvaring av livsmedel; vattenskålar för husdjur; vattenkannor; kaffemått; burkar; trattar; bunkar (skålar); köksredskap; pressar för fruktsaft; pressredskap för livsmedel: durkslag; brickor; skärbrädor; dricksglas; koppar och muggar; tallrikar; brödkorgar; besticklådor; diskställ; bestickkorgar; hinkar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/110</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-12</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/183</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-24</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079049</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>12268</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
