<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-03T12:28:02</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224707</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224707</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-30</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>cs</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-03</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ORIGINAL WAR</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Компютърни програми, записани; Компютърни програми [софтуер, които може да бъде прехвърлян върху друг носител]; Компютърни програми, записани; Софтуер за игри; Софтуер за компютърни игри, с възможност за изтегляне от интернет; Софтуер за компютърни игри с възможност за сваляне от глобална компютърна мрежа и безжични устройства; Софтуерни програми за видеоигри; Компютърен софтуер за игри, с възможност за сваляне от глобална компютърна мрежа; Софтуер за компютърни игри за употреба в мобилни и клетъчни телефони; Софтуер за компютърни игри, записан; Компютърни игри с възможност за изтегляне; Компютърни софтуерни приложения, за сваляне; Софтуер за игри за употреба с видео игрални конзоли.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Počítačové programy (Nahrané -); Počítačové programy [stahovatelné]; Počítačový software (nahraný); Software počítačových her; Software počítačových her ke stažení; Software počítačových her ke stažení prostřednictvím celosvětové počítačové sítě a bezdrátových zařízení; Programy videoher (počítačový software); Počítačový herní software s možností stažení z celosvětové počítačové sítě; Počítačový herní software do mobilních telefonů; Nahraný počítačový herní software; Počítačové hry (Programy -); Počítačové hry ke stažení; Počítačové softwarové aplikace, ke stažení; Programy počítačových her; Herní software pro použití s videoherními konzolemi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Computerprogrammer, optagne; Downloadable computerprogrammer; Software til computere, optaget; Software til spil; Downloadable software til computerspil; Software til computerspil, der kan downloades fra et globalt computernetværk og via trådløse anordninger; Softwareprogrammer til videospil; Software til computerspil, der kan downloades fra et globalt computernetværk; Software til computerspil til brug på mobiltelefoner; Optaget computerspillesoftware; Downloadable computerspil; Softwareapplikationer til computere, downloadable; Software til spil til anvendelse sammen med konsoller til videospil.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gespeicherte Computerprogramme; Herunterladbare Computerprogramme; Gespeicherte Computersoftware; Spielsoftware; Herunterladbare Computerspielsoftware; Aus einem weltweiten Computernetz und über drahtlose Geräte herunterladbare Computerspielsoftware; Software für Videospiele; Aus einem weltweiten Computernetz herunterladbare Computerspielsoftware; Computerspielsoftware zur Verwendung in Mobil- und Funktelefonen; Gespeicherte Computerspielsoftware; Herunterladbare Computerspiele; Herunterladbare Software-Anwendungen für Computer; Spielsoftware zur Verwendung mit Videospielkonsolen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Η/Υ (Προγράμματα -) εγγεγραμμένα· Η/Υ (προγράμματα -) [τηλεμεταφερόμενο λογισμικό]· Η/Υ (Προγράμματα -) εγγεγραμμένα· Λογισµικό ηλεκτρονικών παιχνιδιών· Τηλεφορτώσιμο λογισμικό για παιχνίδια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Λογισμικό παιχνιδιών ηλεκτρονικού υπολογιστή με δυνατότητα τηλεφόρτωσης από παγκόσμιο δίκτυο ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών και ασύρματες διατάξεις· Προγράμματα λογισμικού πληροφορικής για παιχνίδια βίντεο· Λογισμικό παιχνιδιών ηλεκτρονικού υπολογιστή με δυνατότητα τηλεφόρτωσης από παγκόσμιο δίκτυο ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Λογισμικό παιχνιδιών ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για χρήση σε κινητά και κυψελοειδή τηλέφωνα· Εγγεγραμμένο λογισμικό παιχνιδιών ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Παιχνίδια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών με δυνατότητα τηλεφόρτωσης· Εφαρμογές λογισμικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών, μεταφορτώσιμες· Λογισμικό παιχνιδιών για χρήση με κονσόλες βιντεοπαιχνιδιών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Computer programs, recorded; Computer programs, downloadable; Computer software, recorded; Games software; Computer game software, downloadable; Downloadable computer game software via a global computer network and wireless devices; Software programs for video games; Computer game software downloadable from a global computer network; Computer game software for use on mobile and cellular phones; Computer game software, recorded; Downloadable computer games; Computer software applications, downloadable; Games software for use with video game consoles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Programas informáticos grabados; Programas informáticos descargables; Software [programas grabados]; Software de juegos; Software descargable de juegos informáticos; Software de juegos informáticos descargable a través de una red informática mundial y dispositivos inalámbricos; Programas de software para videojuegos; Software de juegos informáticos descargable desde una red informática global; Software de juegos informáticos para su uso en teléfonos móviles y celulares; Software de juegos de ordenador grabados; Juegos de ordenador descargables; Aplicaciones informáticas descargables; Software de juegos para su uso con consolas de videojuegos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Salvestatud arvutiprogrammid; Arvutiprogrammid [allalaaditav tarkvara]; Salvestatud arvutitarkvara; Mängude tarkvara; Allalaaditav arvutimängutarkvara; Ülemaailmse arvutivõrgu ja juhtmeta seadmete kaudu allalaaditav arvutimängutarkvara; Videomängude tarkvaraprogrammid; Ülemaailmsest arvutivõrgust allalaaditav arvutimängutarkvara; Mobiiltelefonide ja kärgtelefonidega kasutatav arvutimängutarkvara; Salvestatud arvutimängutarkvara; Allalaaditavad arvutimängud; Allalaaditavad arvutitarkvararakendused; Videomängukonsoolidega kasutatav mängutarkvara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tietokoneohjelmat, tallennetut; Ohjelmistot (tietokone -) [järjestelmästä toiseen poimittavat]; Tietokoneohjelmat [tallennetut]; Peliohjelmistot; Ladattavat tietokonepeliohjelmistot; Maailmanlaajuisesta tietokoneverkosta ja langattomista laitteista ladattavat tietokonepeliohjelmistot; Ohjelmistot videopeleihin; Maailmanlaajuisesta tietokoneverkosta ladattavat tietokonepeliohjelmistot; Matkapuhelimissa käytettävät tietokonepeliohjelmistot; Tallennetut tietokonepeliohjelmistot; Ladattavat tietokonepelit; Ladattavat tietokoneohjelmistosovellukset; Videopelikonsolien kanssa käytettävät peliohjelmistot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Programmes d'ordinateurs enregistrés; Programmes d'ordinateurs téléchargeables; Logiciels [programmes enregistrés]; Logiciels de jeux enregistrés; Logiciels de jeux téléchargeables; Logiciels de jeux informatiques téléchargeables via un réseau informatique mondial et des dispositifs sans fil; Logiciels pour jeux vidéo; Logiciels de jeux téléchargeables via un réseau informatique mondial; Logiciels de jeux informatiques pour téléphones mobiles et cellulaires; Ludiciels enregistrés; Jeux informatiques téléchargeables; Applications logicielles informatiques téléchargeables; Logiciels pour consoles de jeux vidéo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Računalni programi [snimljeni]; Programi (računalni -) [koji se mogu preuzeti]; Računalni programi [snimljeni]; Softver za igrice; Softver za računalne igre koji se može preuzeti; Programi za računalne igre koji se mogu preuzeti putem interneta i bežičnih uređaja; Računalni programi za video igre; Programi za računalne igre koji se mogu preuzeti s globalne računalne mreže; Programi za računalne igre za uporabu na mobilnim telefonima; Snimljeni softver za računalne igre; Računalne igrice koje se mogu preuzimati; Aplikacije za računalne programe koje se mogu preuzeti s Interneta; Softver za igre za uporabu s konzolama za videoigre.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Számítógépes programok, rögzített; Számítógépes programok [letölthető szoftverek]; Számítógépes programok, rögzített; Játékszoftverek; Letölthető számítógépes játékszoftverek; Globális számítógépes hálózaton és vezeték nélküli készülékeken keresztül letölthető számítógépes játékszoftverek; Szoftverek videojátékokhoz; Globális számítógépes hálózatról letölthető számítógépes játékszoftverek; Mobiltelefonokon használt számítógépes játékszoftverek; Számítógépes játékszoftverek, rögzített; Letölthető számítógépes játékok; Számítógépes szoftveralkalmazások, letölthető; Játékszoftverek videojáték-konzolokhoz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Programmi informatici, registrati; Programmi per computer, scaricabili; Software [programmi registrati]; Software per giochi; Software di videogiochi scaricabili; Software scaricabili per giochi per computer disponibili mediante una rete informatica globale e dispositivi senza fili; Software per videogiochi; Software per giochi per computer scaricabili da una rete informatica globale; Software per giochi per computer da utilizzare su telefoni cellulari; Software di giochi registrati; Giochi scaricabili per elaboratori elettronici; Applicazioni per computer software, scaricabili; Software per giochi da utilizzare con console per videogiochi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Įrašytos kompiuterių programos; Parsisiunčiamosios kompiuterių programos; Kompiuterių programinė įranga [įrašyta]; Kompiuterinių žaidimų programinė įranga; Parsisiunčiamoji kompiuterinių žaidimų programinė įranga; Visuotiniu kompiuterių tinklu ir belaide įranga parsisiunčiamoji kompiuterinių žaidimų programinė įranga; Vaizdo žaidimų programinė įranga; Visuotiniu kompiuterių tinklu parsisiunčiamoji kompiuterinių žaidimų programinė įranga; Kompiuterinių žaidimų programinė įranga mobiliesiems telefonams; Įrašyta kompiuterinių žaidimų programinė įranga; Parsisiunčiamieji kompiuteriniai žaidimai; Parsisiunčiamoji kompiuterių programinė įranga; Kompiuterių programinė įranga, naudojama su vaizdo žaidimų valdymo pultais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ierakstītas datorprogrammas; Lejupielādējamas datorprogrammas; Ierakstīta programmatūra; Spēļu programmatūra; Lejupielādējama datoru spēļu programmatūra; No globālā datortīkla un bezvadu ierīcēm lejupielādējama datorspēļu programmatūra; Videospēļu programmas (datoru programmatūra); No globālā datortīkla lejupielādējama datorspēļu programmatūra; Datorspēļu programmatūra izmantošanai ar mobilajiem tālruņiem; Ierakstīta datorspēļu programmatūra; Lejuplādējamas datorspēles; Lejupielādējamas datorprogrammu lietotnes; Datoru programmatūra izmantošanai ar videospēļu konsolēm.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Programmi tal-kompjuter irrekordjati; Programmi tal-kompjuter [softwer li jista' jitniżżel]; Programmi tal-kompjuter irrekordjati; Softwer tal-logħbiet; Softwer tal-logħob tal-kompjuter li jista' jitniżżel; Softwer tal-logħob tal-kompjuter li jista' jitniżżel permezz ta' netwerk tal-kompjuter globali u tagħmir mingħajr fili; Softwer tal-logħob tal-vidjo; Softwer tal-logħob tal-kompjuter li jista' jitniżżel permezz ta' netwerk informatiku globali; Softwer tal-logħob tal-kompjuter għall-użu fuq telefons ċellulari u mowbajls; Softwer tal-logħob tal-kompjuter, irrekordjat; Logħob tal-kompjuter li jistgħu jitniżżlu; Applikazzjonijiet ta' softwer tal-kompjuter, li jitniżżlu; Softwer tal-logħob għall-użu ma' konsowls tal-vidjowgejm.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Geregistreerde computerprogramma's; Computerprogramma's, downloadable; Software [geregistreerde programma's]; Spelsoftware; Downloadbare computerspelsoftware; Computerspelsoftware, te downloaden via een wereldwijd computernetwerk en draadloze apparaten; Softwareprogramma's voor videospellen; Computerspelsoftware, te downloaden van een wereldwijd computernetwerk; Computerspelsoftware voor gebruik op mobiele en draagbare telefoons; Opgenomen software voor computerspellen; Downloadbare computerspellen; Downloadbare computersoftware-applicaties; Spelsoftware voor gebruik met videospelconsoles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Programy komputerowe nagrane; Programy komputerowe [oprogramowanie do pobrania]; Programy komputerowe nagrane; Oprogramowanie gier; Oprogramowanie gier komputerowych do pobrania; Oprogramowane gier komputerowych do pobrania za pośrednictwem globalnej sieci komputerowej i urządzeń bezprzewodowych; Oprogramowanie do gier wideo; Oprogramowane gier komputerowych do pobrania za pośrednictwem globalnej sieci komputerowej; Oprogramowanie gier komputerowych do użytku na telefonach komórkowych; Oprogramowanie gier komputerowych, nagrane; Pobieralne gry komputerowe; Aplikacje komputerowe do pobrania; Oprogramowanie do gier do użytku z konsolami do gier wideo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Programas de computador gravados; Programas de computador descarregáveis; Software [programas de computador gravados]; Software de jogos; Software de jogos de computador para download; Software de jogos descarregável via rede informática mundial e dispositivos sem fios; Programas de software para jogos de vídeo; Software de jogos de computador descarregável de uma rede informática mundial; Software de jogos de computador para utilizar em telemóveis e telefones celulares; Software de jogos de computador gravados; Jogos de computador descarregáveis; Aplicações de software informático descarregáveis; Software de jogos para uso com consolas de jogos de vídeo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Programe de calculator înregistrate; Programe de calculatoare [software descărcabil]; Programe de calculator înregistrate; Software pentru jocuri; Software pentru jocuri de calculator, descărcabil; Software descărcabil pentru jocuri de calculator într-o rețea informatică mondială și de pe dispozitive fără fir; Programe pentru jocuri de calculator [software de calculator]; Software pentru jocuri pe calculator, descărcabil dintr-o rețea globală de calculatoare; Software pentru jocuri pe calculator destinate utilizării pe telefoanele mobile și celulare; Software pentru jocuri de calculator, înregistrat; Jocuri de calculator descărcabile; Aplicații software de calculator, descărcabile; Software pentru jocuri folosit împreună cu consolele de jocuri video.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nahraté počítačové programy; Počítačové programy (sťahovateľné); Počítačový softvér (nahraté počítačové programy); Počítačové hry (softvér); Stiahnuteľný počítačový herný softvér; Počítačový herný softvér s možnosťou prevzatia prostredníctvom svetovej počítačovej siete a bezdrôtových zariadení; Softvérové programy pre video hry; Počítačový herný softvér, ktorý možno prevziať prostredníctvom globálnej počítačovej siete; Počítačový herný softvér pre mobilné telefóny; Nahraný počítačový herný softvér; Stiahnuteľné počítačové hry; Počítačové softvérové aplikácie (sťahovateľné); Herný softvér na použitie s videohernými konzolami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Računalniški programi, posneti; Računalniški programi [naložljiva programska oprema]; Računalniški programi, posneti; Programska oprema za igrice; Naložljiva programska oprema za računalniške igre; Programska oprema za računalniške igre, naložljiva prek globalne računalniške mreže in brezžičnih naprav; Programska oprema za video igre; Programska oprema za računalniške igre, naložljiva s svetovnega računalniškega omrežja; Programska oprema za računalniške igre za uporabo na mobilnih telefonih; Posneta programska oprema za računalniške igre; Naložljive računalniške igre; Računalniška programska oprema, naložljiva preko računalniške mreže; Programska oprema za igre za uporabo s konzolami za video igre.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Registrerade datorprogram; Datorprogram, nedladdningsbara; Registrerade datormjukvaror; Programvara för spel; Nedladdningsbar programvara för dataspel; Datorspelsprogramvara som kan laddas ned från ett globalt datornät och trådlösa anordningar; Programvara för videospel; Datorspelprogramvara som kan laddas ned från ett globalt datornät; Datorspelprogramvara för användning med mobila telefoner och mobiltelefoner; Datorprogram för spel, inspelade; Nedladdningsbara datorspel; Softwareapplikationer för datorer, nedladdningsbara; Spelprogramvara för användning med videospelkonsoler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Осигуряване на он-лайн компютърни игри; Осигуряване на компютърна игра, която да е достъпна от цялата мрежа от потребители на мрежата; Услуги свързани с електронни игри, включително осигуряване на компютърни игри он-лайн или посредством глобалната компютърна мрежа; Осигуряване онлайн на информация в сферата на компютърните развлекателни игри; Услуги, свързани с провеждане на онлайн игри [от мрежа].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Poskytování online počítačových her; Poskytování počítačových her přístupných pro uživatele sítě; Služby v oblasti elektronických her, včetně poskytování počítačových her on-line nebo prostřednictvím globální počítačové sítě; Poskytování online informací v oblasti zábavy týkající se počítačových her; Provozování her on-line z počítačové sítě.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tilvejebringelse af online computerspil; Computerspil, hvortil netværksbrugere kan få adgang på hele netværket; Elektroniske spiltjenester, inklusive tilvejebringelse af onlinespil eller spil tilvejebragt via et globalt computernetværk; Onlineinformation vedrørende computerspil; Spiltjenester tilvejebragt online fra et computernetværk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Online angebotene Spieldienstleistungen; Bereitstellen eines Computerspiels, zu dem Netzbenutzer netzweiten Zugang haben; Durchführung elektronischer Spiele einschließlich Computerspiele, online oder mittels eines globalen Computernetzes; Erteilen von Online-Auskünften im Bereich Computerspielunterhaltung; Über ein Computernetzwerk online angebotene Spieldienstleistungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">On line παροχή ηλεκτρονικών παιχνιδιών· Παροχή παιχνιδιών ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών με δυνατότητα πρόσβασης μέσω δικτύου από χρήστες δικτύων· Υπηρεσίες ηλεκτρονικών παιχνιδιών,συμπεραμβανομένης της παροχής παιχνιδιών ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Παροχή πληροφοριών μέσω διαδικτυακής σύνδεσης (on-line) στον τομέα της ψυχαγωγίας μέσω παιχνιδιών ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Παιχνιδιού (υπηρεσίες -) που παρέχονται on-line [από δίκτυο πληροφορικής].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Provision of on-line computer games; Providing a computer game that may be accessed network-wide by network users; Electronic games services, including provision of computer games on-line or by means of a global computer network; Providing on-line information in the field of computer gaming entertainment; Game services provided online from a computer network.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Facilitación de juegos informáticos en línea (online); Facilitación de un juego de ordenador al que se pueda acceder en toda la red por usuarios de la red; Servicios de juegos electrónicos, incluyendo juegos de ordenador prestados en línea o por medio de una red informática global; Facilitación de información en línea en materia de entretenimiento de juegos informáticos; Servicios de juegos disponibles en línea por una red informática.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Veebis arvutimängude pakkumine; Arvutimängu pakkumine, millele on võrgukasutajatel juurdepääs kogu võrgu ulatuses; Elektroonilised mänguteenused, sh arvutimängude pakkumine veebis või globaalse arvutivõrgu kaudu; Arvutimängumeelelahutuse alase info pakkumine veebis; Mänguteenused arvutivõrgus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Online-tietokonepelien tarjoaminen; Sellaisen tietokonepelin tarjoaminen, joka on verkonkäyttäjien käytettävissä koko verkon alueella; Elektroniset pelipalvelut, mukaan lukien tietokonepelien tarjoaminen online-muodossa tai maailmanlaajuisen tietokoneverkon välityksellä; Tietokonepeliviihdettä koskevien online-tietojen tarjoaminen; Pelipalveluiden tarjoaminen [suoraan tietoverkoissa].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Mise à disposition de jeux informatiques en ligne; Service de jeux informatiques accessibles sur réseau par les utilisateurs; Services de jeux électroniques, y compris jeux d'ordinateur fournis en ligne ou par un réseau informatique mondial; Information en ligne dans le domaine des jeux et du divertissement informatiques; Services de jeu proposés en ligne à partir d'un réseau informatique.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pružanje online računalnih igara; Pružanje računalne igre kojoj mogu pristupiti korisnici širom mreže; Usluge elektroničkih igara, uključujući pribavljanje računalnih igara online putem ili posredstvom globalne računalne mreže; Pružanje online informacija u svezi sa opremom za računalne igre; Online igre na računalnoj mreži.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Online számítógépes játékok szolgáltatása; Hálózati felhasználók számára hálózat-szerte hozzáférhető számítógépes játék biztosítása; Elektronikus játék szolgáltatások, beleértve az online vagy globális számítógépes hálózat segítségével biztosítottakat is; Számítógépes játékokkal kapcsolatos szórakoztatásról nyújtott online információk; Számítógépes hálózatról online biztosított játékszolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Fornitura di giochi per computer on-line; Servizi di giochi per computer accessibili da utenti di reti; Servizi relativi a giochi elettronici, compresa l'offerta di giochi per computer on-line o mediante una rete informatica globale; Fornitura di informazioni on-line relative all'intrattenimento mediante giochi per computer; Servizi di giochi proposti online [partendo da una rete informatica].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Internetinių kompiuterinių žaidimų parūpinimas; Kompiuterinių žaidimų, prie kurių vartotojai gali prisijungti tinkle, paslaugos; Elektroninių žaidimų paslaugos, įskaitant kompiuterinių žaidimų paslaugas, teikiamas tiesioginiu ryšiu arba visuotiniu kompiuterių tinklu; Tiesioginės informacijos teikimas apie kompiuterinių žaidimų pramogas; Žaidimų paslaugos, teikiamos tiesiogiai per kompiuterių tinklą.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Nodrošināšana ar tiešsaistes datorspēlēm; Tīkla lietotājiem tīklā pieejamu datorspēļu nodrošināšana; Elektronisko spēļu pakalpojumi, arī datorspēļu nodrošināšana tiešsaistē vai pasaules datortīklā; Tiešsaistes informācijas nodrošināšana attiecībā uz datorspēļu izklaidi; Spēļu pakalpojumu nodrošināšana tiešsaistē ar datortīklu starpniecību.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Il-provvista ta' logħob tal-kompjuter onlajn; Provvista ta' logħba tal-kompjuter aċċessibbli minn netwerk kollu mill-utenti tan-netwerk; Servizzi ta' logħob elettroniku, li jinkludu l-provvista ta' logħob tal-kompjuter onlajn jew permezz ta' netwerk globali tal-kompjuter; Il-provvista ta' informazzjoni onlajn fil-qasam tad-divertiment tal-logħob bil-kompjuter; Servizzi ta' logħob provduti fuq l-internet (minn netwerk tal-kompjuter).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verstrekking van on line computerspellen; Het leveren van een computerspel met toegang over het hele netwerk voor netwerkgebruikers; Spellen (Elektronische -) via internet of via een wereldwijd computernetwerk; Informatie op het gebied van amusement in de vorm van computerspellen (Ter beschikking stellen van -); Ter beschikking stellen van online spellen via een computernetwerk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Udostępnianie gier komputerowych on-line; Udostępnianie gry komputerowej dostępnej w sieci dla użytkowników sieci; Usługi w zakresie gier elektronicznych, w tym udostępnianie gier online lub za pośrednictwem globalnej sieci komputerowej; Informacje online z dziedziny rozrywki z zakresu gier komputerowych; Usługi gier oferowane w systemie on-line za pośrednictwem sieci komputerowej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Fornecimento de jogos de computador on-line; Fornecimento de um jogo de computador ao qual podem ter acesso em toda a rede os utilizadores de redes informáticas; Serviços de jogos eletrónicos, incluindo o fornecimento de jogos de computador on-line ou por meio de uma rede informática mundial; Prestação de informações on-line no domínio do entretenimento por jogos de computador; Serviços de jogo prestados online a partir de uma rede de computadores.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Furnizare de jocuri de calculator on-line; Furnizarea unui joc pe calculator care poate fi accesat în toată rețeaua de către utilizatorii rețelei; Servicii în domeniul jocurilor electronice, care includ jocuri de calculator furnizate on-line sau printr-o rețea globală de calculatoare; Furnizare de informații online în domeniul divertismentului cu jocuri pe calculator; Jocuri on-line printr-o rețea de calculatoare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Poskytovanie on-line počítačových hier; Poskytovanie počítačových hier, ktoré sú prístupné v celej sieti pre užívateľov siete; Služby v oblasti elektronických hier, vrátane poskytovania počítačových hier on-line alebo globálnou počítačovou sieťou; Poskytovanie on-line informácií v oblasti počítačovej hernej zábavy; Online poskytovanie počítačových hier (z počítačových sietí).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Nudenje spletnih računalniških iger; Nudenje računalniških iger, ki so dostopne uporabnikom na celotnem omrežju; Storitve elektronskih iger, vključno z nudenjem računalniških iger preko spleta ali globalnega računalniškega omrežja; Zagotavljanje spletnih informacij na področju zabave z računalniškimi igrami; Storitev nudenja spletnih iger (preko računalniškega omrežja).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tillhandahållande av direktanslutna datorspel; Tillhandahållande av ett datorspel för åtkomst över ett helt nätverk av nätverksanvändare; Elektroniska speltjänster, inkluderande tillhandahållande av datorspel genom direktanslutning eller genom ett globalt datornätverk; Direktansluten information rörande datorspelunderhållning; Speltjänster online via datornätverk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Проектиране на софтуер за компютърни игри; Услуги за инсталиране и поддръжка на софтуер; Презапис на компютърни програми; Компютърно програмиране на компютърни игри; Компютърно програмиране на видео игри; Проектиране на софтуер.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Navrhování softwaru počítačových her; Údržba a instalace počítačových programů; Kopírování počítačových programů; Programování počítačových her; Počítačové programování videoher; Tvorba software (počítačových programů).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Design af software til computerspil; Installering og vedligeholdelse af computersoftware; Duplikering af computerprogrammer; Computerprogrammering af computerspil; Computerprogrammering af videospil; Design af computerprogrammer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Konzeption von Software für Computerspiele; Computersoftwareinstallation und -wartung; Kopieren von Computerprogrammen; Computerprogrammierung von Computerspielen; Computerprogrammierung von Videospielen; Design von Computer-Software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Σχεδιασμός λογισμικού για παιχνίδια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Δημιουργία, εγκατάσταση και συντήρηση προγραμμάτων επεξεργασίας δεδομένων· Αντιγραφή προγραμμάτων πληροφορικής· Προγράμματα ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για παιχνίδια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Προγράμματα ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών για βιντεοπαιχνίδια· Σχεδιασμός λογισμικού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Design of computer game software; Installation and maintenance of computer programs; Duplication of computer programs; Computer programming of computer games; Computer programming of video games; Computer software design.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Diseño de software de juegos de ordenador; Instalación y mantenimiento de software; Duplicación de programas informáticos; Programación de juegos de ordenador; Programación de videojuegos; Diseño de software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arvutimängutarkvara projekteerimine; Arvutitarkvara installeerimine ja hooldus; Arvutiprogrammide dubleerimine; Arvutimängude programmeerimine; Videomängude programmeerimine; Tarkvara projekteerimine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tietokonepeliohjelmistojen suunnittelu; Tietokoneohjelmistojen asennus ja huolto; Tietokoneohjelmistojen monistus; Tietokonepelien ohjelmointi; Videopelien ohjelmointi; Ohjelmistosuunnittelu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Conception de logiciels de jeux d'ordinateurs; Installation et maintenance de logiciels; Duplication de programmes informatiques; Programmation informatique de jeux d'ordinateurs; Programmation informatique de jeux vidéo; Élaboration [conception] de logiciels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Dizajn softvera računalnih igara; Instalacija i održavanje računalnih programa; Umnožavanje računalnih programa; Računalno programiranje računalnih igara; Računalno programiranje video igara; Izrada [koncipiranje] računalnih progama.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Számítógépes játékszoftverek tervezése; Számítógépes szoftver telepítése és karbantartása; Számítógépes programok másolása; Számítógépes játékok programozása; Videojátékok számítógépes programozása; Szoftvertervezés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Progettazione di software per giochi per computer; Installazione e manutenzione di programmi per computer; Duplicazione di programmi informatici; Programmazione di giochi per computer; Programmazione di videogame; Elaborazione [ideazione] di software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kompiuterinių žaidimų programinės įrangos projektavimas; Kompiuterių programinės įrangos instaliavimas ir techninė priežiūra; Kompiuterių programų dubliavimas; Kompiuterinių žaidimų programavimas; Vaizdo žaidimų kompiuterinis programavimas; Kompiuterių programinės įrangos projektavimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Datorspēļu programmatūras dizains; Datoru programmu instalēšana un uzturēšana; Datorprogrammu pavairošana; Datorspēļu datorprogrammēšana; Videospēļu datorprogrammēšana; Datorprogrammu projektēšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Disinn ta' softwer tal-logħob tal-kompjuter; Installazzjoni u manutenzjoni ta' softwer tal-kompjuter; Duplikazzjoni ta' programmi tal-kompjuter; Ipprogrammar ta' logħob tal-kompjuter; Ipprogrammar ta' logħob tal-vidjo; L-iżvilupp ta' softwer tal-kompjuter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Softwareontwerp voor computerspellen; Installatie en onderhoud van computerprogramma' s; Kopiëren van computerprogramma's; Computerprogrammering van computerspellen; Computerprogrammering van videospellen; Software-ontwikkeling.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Projektowanie oprogramowania do gier komputerowych; Instalacja i utrzymanie programów komputerowych; Powielanie programów komputerowych; Programowanie komputerowe w zakresie gier komputerowych; Programowanie komputerowe w zakresie gier wideo; Projektowanie oprogramowania komputerowego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Design de software para jogos de computador; Instalação e manutenção de programas informáticos; Duplicação de programas de computador; Programação para jogos de computador; Programação informática de jogos de vídeo; Design de software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Proiectare de software pentru jocuri pe calculator; Servicii de instalare și întreținere de software; Copierea programelor informatice; Elaborare de programe de calculator pentru jocuri pe calculator; Elaborare de programe de calculator pentru jocuri video; Proiectare de software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Navrhovanie softvéru počítačových hier; Inštalovanie a údržba počítačových programov; Zhotovovanie kópií počítačových programov; Počítačové programovanie počítačových hier; Počítačové programovanie videohier; Tvorba softvéru.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Oblikovanje programske opreme za računalniške igre; Namestitev in vzdrževanje računalniške programske opreme; Kopiranje računalniških programov; Računalniško programiranje računalniških iger; Računalniško programiranje video iger; Oblikovanje programske opreme.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Utformning av datorspelprogramvara; Installation och underhåll av datorprogramvara; Duplicering av datorprogram; Datorprogrammering av dataspel; Datorprogrammering av videospel; Utformning av programvara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/075</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-21</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/144</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-31</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>325064</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
