<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:43</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224165</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224165</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Messen</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>26</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ленти за коса; Ширити; Фиби за коса; Брошки [аксесоари за дрехи]; Украшения, орнаменти за коса; Фуркети, фиби за къдрене на коса; Фуркети, фиби за коса; Мрежи за коса; Карфици [с изключение на бижута]; Панделки за коса; Шапки за боядисване на коса; Маши за навиване на коса; Мъниста, с изключение на тези за бижута; Куки за килими; Перуки; Коса за удължаване; Човешка коса; Игли за замрежване; Коса за удължаване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Čelenky do vlasů; Prýmky; Pinetky; Brože [oděvní doplňky]; Ozdoby do vlasů; Klipsy pro natáčení vlasů; Vlásenky; Síťky na vlasy; Špendlíky, ne šperky; Mašle do vlasů; Čepice na barvení vlasů; Papírové natáčky; Korálky, ne pro výrobu šperků; Háčky na koberce; Paruky; Příčesky na prodloužení vlasů; Lidské vlasy; Látací jehly; Umělé vlasy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Hårbånd; Kantebånd; Hårklemmer; Brocher [tilbehør til beklædningsgenstande]; Pyntegenstande til håret; Hårkrøllenåle; Hårnåle; Hårnet; Nåle, undtagen smykker; Hårsløjfer; Lysningshætter; Papilotter af papir; Perler, andre end til fremstilling af smykker; Tæppekroge; Parykker; Hair extensions; Hår fra mennesker; Stoppenåle; Kunstigt hår.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Haarbänder; Tressen, Soutachen, Litzen, Borten [Besatzwaren]; Haarklemmen; Broschen [Kleidungszubehör]; Haarschmuck; Onduliernadeln; Haarnadeln; Haarnetze; Stecknadeln, ausgenommen Schmuckwaren; Haarreifen; Haarfärbehauben; Lockenwickler-Papier; Künstliche Perlen, ausgenommen zur Fertigung von Schmuck; Knüpfhaken für Teppiche; Perücken; Haarverlängerungen; Menschliches Haar; Stopfnadeln; Perücken [Haarteile].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ελαστικές κορδέλες για μάζεμα των μαλλιών· Γαλόνια· Τσιμπιδάκια μαλλιών· Πόρπες [αξεσουάρ ένδυσης]· Διακοσμητικά είδη για τα μαλλιά· Μαλλιά (Φουρκέτες για κυματιστά -)· Μαλλιά (Φουρκέτες για -)· Δίχτυα για τα μαλλιά· Καρφίτσες, εκτός από κοσμήματα· Φιόγκοι για τα μαλλιά· Σκουφάκια βαφής μαλλιών· Ρολά για τα μαλλιά· Χάντρες, εκτός από αυτές που προορίζονται για την κατασκευή κοσμημάτων· Άγκιστρα για τάπητες· Περούκες· Περουκίνια· Ανθρώπινα μαλλιά· Βελόνες μανταρίσματος· Περουκίνια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hair bands; Braids; Hair grips [slides]; Slides [hair grips]; Brooches [clothing accessories]; Hair ornaments; Hair curling pins; Hair pins; Hair nets; Pins, other than jewellery [jewelry (Am.)]; Bows for the hair; Hair coloring caps; Hair curling papers; Beads, other than for making jewelry; Rug hooks; Wigs; Hair extensions; Human hair; Darning needles; False hair.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bandas para el cabello; Cordones; Pinzas para el cabello; Broches [complementos de vestir]; Artículos de adorno para el cabello; Horquillas para ondular el cabello; Horquillas para recogidos; Redecillas para el cabello; Alfileres que no sean artículos de joyería; Lazos para el cabello; Gorros para hacer mechas; Tiras de papel para rizar el cabello; Cuentas que no sean para confeccionar joyas; Ganchos para tejer alfombras; Pelucas; Extensiones de cabello; Cabello; Agujas de zurcir; Cabello postizo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Juuksepaelad, juukselindid; Punutised; Juuksenõelad; Prossid, preesid, sõled, rinnanõelad [rõivamanused]; Juukseehted; Lokirullinõelad; Krunninõelad, juuksenõelad; Juuksevõrgud; Nõelad, v.a juveeltooted; Juukselipsud; Juuste värvimisel kasutatavad mütsid; Lokirullipaberid; Helmed, v.a ehete valmistamiseks; Vaibakonksud; Parukad; Juuksepikendused; Juuksed; Sukanõelad; Valejuuksed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Hiusnauhat; Punokset; Hiuspinnit; Rintaneulat vaatetukseen; Hiuskoristeet; Hiuskäherrinpuikot; Hiusneulat; Hiusverkot; Pinssit [muut kuin korut]; Rusetit hiuksia varten; Hiustenvärjäysmyssyt; Hiuskähertimet; Helmet, muut kuin korujen tekemiseen tarkoitetut; Mattokoukut; Peruukit; Tupeet; Luonnonhiukset; Parsinneulat; Tupeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bandeaux pour les cheveux; Lacets [cordons]; Pinces à cheveux; Broches [accessoires d'habillement]; Articles décoratifs pour la chevelure; Épingles à onduler les cheveux; Épingles à cheveux; Filets pour les cheveux; Épingles autres qu'articles de bijouterie; Nœuds pour les cheveux; Bonnets à mèches; Papillotes [bigoudis]; Perles autres que pour la confection de bijoux; Crochets à tapis; Perruques; Extensions capillaires; Cheveux; Aiguilles à repriser; Cheveux postiches.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Gumice za kosu; Uzice [konopčići]; Ukosnice; Broševi [odjevni pribor]; Ukrasni predmeti za kosu; Ukosnice za kovrčanje kose; Ukosnice za kosu; Mreže za kosu; Pribadače [osim nakita]; Mašne za kosu; Kape za bojenje pramenova; Uvijači za kosu; Perlice, osim za izradu nakita; Kukice za sagove; Vlasulje; Umjetna kosa; Ljudska kosa; Igle za krpanje; Umjetna kosa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hajpántok; Szalagok, fonatok, zsinórok; Hajcsatok; Melltűk [ruhakiegészítők]; Hajdíszek; Tűcsipeszek; Hajtűk; Hajhálók; Gombostűk, nem ékszerészeti cikkek; Masnik hajba; Sapkák melírozáshoz; Elektromos hajsütővasak; Gyöngyszemek, nem ékszerkészítéshez; Kampós tűk szőnyegkészítéshez; Parókák; Hajhosszabbítások; Haj; Stoppolótűk; Hajhosszabbítások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Fasce per i capelli; Cordoni trecciati; Mollette per capelli; Spille [accessori di abbigliamento]; Articoli d'ornamento per la capigliatura; Forcine per ondulare i capelli; Spilli per capelli; Retine o reticelle per i capelli; Spille eccetto gli articoli di gioielleria; Cerchietti per capelli; Cuffiette per meches; Bigodini; Perle non per confezionare gioielleria; Uncinetti per tappeti; Parrucche; Extension per capelli; Capelli veri; Aghi per rammendare; Capelli posticci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Plaukų juostos; Juostelės; Plaukų segtukai; Sagės [drabužių papuošalai]; Plaukų papuošalai; Plaukų sukimo segtukai; Plaukų smeigtukai; Plaukų tinkleliai; Sagės [išskyrus juvelyrinius dirbinius]; Plaukų lankeliai; Plaukų dažymo kepuraitės; Popieriniai plaukų suktukai; Karoliukai (ne juvelyriniams dirbiniams gaminti); Kilimėlių kabliukai; Perukai; Plaukų sruogos; Žmonių plaukai; Adymo adatos; Netikri plaukai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Matu stīpas; Pītas lentes; Matu saspraudes; Piespraudes (apģērbu aksesuāri); Dekoratīvas matu rotas; Spraudītes matu cirtošanai; Matadatas; Matu tīkliņi; Spraudītes, izņemot juvelierizstrādājumus; Matu lenšu pušķi; Cepurītes matu šķipsnu iekrāsošanai; Papīra rullīši matu uztīšanai; Pērlītes, kas nav paredzētas rotaslietu darināšanai; Āķi ar cilpu paklāju āķošanai; Parūkas; Mati pieaudzēšanai; Cilvēku mati; Lāpāmadatas; Mākslīgie mati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Faxex għaż-żamma lura tax-xagħar; Tberfil; Furfiċetti tax-xagħar; Labar [aċċessorji tal-ilbies]; Oġġetti dekorattivi għax-xagħar; Labar għall-innukklar tax-xagħar; Furfiċetti; Xbieki għax-xagħar; Labar, minbarra ġojjellerija; Ċfuf għax-xagħar; Brieret bit-toqob użati għall-għoti ta' kulur lix-xagħar; Tagħmir li jinnokkla x-xagħar; Żibeġ, minbarra dawk biex issir il-ġojjellerija; Ganċijiet tat-twapet; Parrokki; Estensjonijiet tax-xagħar; Xagħar uman; Labar għas-sarsir; Estensjonijiet tax-xagħar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Haarbanden; Boordsel; Haarpennen; Spelden [kledingtoebehoren]; Versiersels voor het haar; Haarkrulspelden; Haarspelden; Haarnetjes; Spelden, anders dan juwelierswaren; Diademen; Mutsen voor haarkleuring; Papillotten [papieren haarkrullers]; Kralen, anders dan voor het maken van sieraden; Tapijthaken; Pruiken; Haar-extensies; Menselijk haar; Stopnaalden; Vals haar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przepaski do włosów; Galony; Spinki do włosów; Broszki [dodatki do ubrań]; Dekoracyjne akcesoria do włosów; Wsuwki do kręcenia włosów; Szpilki do włosów; Siatki na włosy; Szpilki, inne niż biżuteria; Kokardy do włosów; Czepki do farbowania włosów; Wałki do włosów; Koraliki, inne niż do wyrobu biżuterii; Szydła do tkania kilimów i dywaników; Peruki; Włosy do przedłużania; Ludzkie włosy; Igły do cerowania; Włosy do przedłużania.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Bandoletes; Cordões [laços]; Ganchos invisíveis para o cabelo; Broches [acessórios de vestuário]; Artigos decorativos para o cabelo; Alfinetes para enrolar o cabelo; Alfinetes para o cabelo; Redes para o cabelo; Alfinetes, sem ser joalharia; Diademas [bandoletes]; Gorros para madeixas; Papelotes [rolos de cabelo]; Missangas, não sendo para fazer joalharia; Ganchos para tapetes; Perucas; Extensões capilares; Cabelo; Agulhas para passajar; Cabelo postiço.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Benzi pentru păr; Trese; Agrafe pentru păr; Broșe [accesorii de îmbrăcăminte]; Articole decorative pentru păr; Ace de ondulat părul; Ace de păr; Fileuri de păr; Ace cu gămălie, altele decât articolele de bijuterie; Funde pentru păr; Bonete pentru vopsirea părului; Ondulatoare de păr, altele decât articolele manuale; Mărgele, altele decât pentru crearea de bijuterii; Croșete pentru covoare; Peruci; Meșe (de păr); Păr uman; Ace de stopat; Meșe (de păr).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Stuhy do vlasov; Pletené šnúry; Sponky do vlasov; Brošne (doplnky oblečenia); Ozdoby do vlasov; Vlásenky na tvarovanie účesov; Ihlice do vlasov; Sieťky na vlasy; Špendlíky, ihlice okrem šperkov; Mašle do vlasov; Čiapky na melírovanie vlasov; Papierové natáčky; Korálky, nie na výrobu šperkov; Háčiky na koberce; Parochne; Pramienky na predlžovanie vlasov; Ľudské vlasy; Plátacie ihly; Umelé vlasy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Trakovi za lase; Okrasne vrvice; Lasnice; Broške [dodatki za oblačila]; Dekorativni izdelki za lase; Igle za kodranje las; Igle za lase; Mrežice za lase; Bucike, ne kot nakit; Pentlje za lase; Kape za barvanje las; Navijalke; Kroglice, ne za izdelavo nakita (perle); Kaveljčki za preproge; Lasulje; Lasni podaljški; Človeški lasje; Igle za krpanje; Lasni podaljški.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hårband; Tränsar; Hårklämmor; Broscher [beklädnadsaccessoarer]; Dekorativa artiklar för håret; Hårlockningsnålar; Hårnålar; Hårnät; Nålar (inte juvelerarvaror); Hårrosetter; Hårfärgningsmössor; Hårlockningspapper; Kulor, andra än för smyckestillverkning; Mattkrokar; Peruker; Hårförlängningar; Människohår; Stoppnålar; Löshår.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079048</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>71845</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
