<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-07T08:44:51</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224194</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224194</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-03</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>cs</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-07</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>TIKARO</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162205370</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/224/018224194/000162205370.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>01.15.15</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.05.19</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.05.20</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.05.21</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.07.11</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.07.22</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>25.05.99</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.03.11</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.05</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>1</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Чаени екстракти за хранителната промишленост; Сол за използване в промишлеността; Витамини за хранителната промишленост.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Čajové extrakty pro potravinářský průmysl; sůl pro použití v průmyslu; vitaminy pro potravinářský průmysl.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Teekstrakter til fødevareindustrien; Salt til brug i industrien; Vitaminer til fødevareindustrien.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Tee-Extrakte für die Lebensmittelindustrie; Salze für die Industrie; Vitamine für die Lebensmittelindustrie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εκχυλίσματα τσαγιού για τη βιομηχανία τροφίμων· Αλάτι για χρήση στη βιομηχανία· Βιταμίνες για τη βιομηχανία τροφίμων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Tea extracts for the food industry; Salt for use in industry; Vitamins for the food industry.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Extractos de té para la industria alimentaria; Sal para uso industrial; Vitaminas para la industria alimentaria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tee-ekstraktid toiduainetööstuses kasutamiseks; Tööstuslik sool; Vitamiinid toiduainetööstusele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Teeuutteet elintarviketeollisuudelle; Suola teollisuuskäyttöön; Vitamiinit elintarviketeollisuudelle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Extraits de thé pour l'industrie alimentaire; Sel destiné à l'industrie; Vitamines destinées à l'industrie alimentaire.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Ekstrakti čaja za prehrambenu industriju; Sol za uporabu u industriji; Vitamini za prehrambenu industriju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Teakivonatok az élelmiszeripar számára; Ipari felhasználású sók; Vitaminok az élelmiszeripar számára.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Estratti di tè per l'industria alimentare; Sale per uso industriale; Vitamine per l'industria alimentare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Arbatos ekstraktai (maisto pramonei); Druska pramonės reikmėms; Vitaminai (maisto pramonei).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tējas ekstrakti izmantošanai pārtikas nozarē; Sāls izmantošanai rūpniecībā; Vitamīni izmantošanai pārtikas nozarē.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Estratti tal-pjanta tat-te għall-industrija tal-ikel; Melħ għal skopijiet industrijali; Vitamini għall-industrija tal-ikel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Thee-extracten voor de voedingsindustrie; Zout voor gebruik in de industrie; Vitamines voor de voedingsindustrie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Ekstrakty z herbaty dla przemysłu spożywczego; Sól do stosowania w przemyśle; Witaminy dla przemysłu spożywczego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Extratos de chá para a indústria alimentar; Sal destinado à indústria; Vitaminas para a indústria alimentar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Extracte de ceai pentru industria alimentară; Sare de uz industrial; Vitamine pentru industria alimentară.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Čajové výťažky pre potravinársky priemysel; Soľ na použitie v priemysle; Vitamíny pre potravinársky priemysel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Čajni izvlečki za uporabo v živilski industriji; Sol za industrijsko uporabo; Vitamini za uporabo v živilski industriji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Teextrakt för livsmedelsindustrin; Salt för bruk inom industrin; Vitaminer för livmedelsindustrin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Билкови чайове за лечебни цели; Лечебни билки; Астматичен чай; Лечебен чай; Диетични напитки за медицински цели; Медицински корени; Диетични напитки за медицински цели; Медицински напитки; Отвари от билки за фармацевтични цели; Усилващи препарати; Тонизиращи средства; Храна за бебета; Лаксативи [разхлабителни средства]; Хранителни добавки от прополис; Протеинови хранителни добавки; Средства, потискащи апетита, за медицински цели; Хранителни добавки от полени; Сиропи за фармацевтични цели; Напитка от малцово мляко за лечебни цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Bylinné čaje pro lékařské účely; byliny (léčivé -); čaj astmatický; čaje léčivé; dietetické nápoje upravené pro lékařské účely; kořeny (léčivé -); nápoje dietetické, upravené pro lékařské účely; nápoje léčivé; odvary pro farmaceutické účely; posilující přípravky; tonika; potrava pro kojence; pročišťující přípravky; propolisové potravinové doplňky; proteinové potravinové doplňky; přípravky potlačující chuť k jídlu pro lékařské účely; pylové potravinové doplňky; sirupy pro farmaceutické účely; sladové mléčné nápoje pro lékařské účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Urteteer til medicinsk brug; Lægeurter; Te imod astma; Medicinsk te; Diætetiske drikke tilpasset medicinske formål; Rødder til medicinsk brug; Diætetiske drikke tilpasset medicinske formål; Miksturer [medicinske drikke]; Dekokter til farmaceutiske formål; Styrkende præparater; Tonicvand; Mad til spædbørn; Udtømningsmidler; Propolis til brug som kosttilskud; Protein til brug som kosttilskud; Appetitdæmpende midler til medicinsk brug; Pollen til brug som kosttilskud; Sirup til farmaceutiske formål; Mælkedrikke med malt til medicinske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kräutertees für medizinische Zwecke; Medizinische Kräuter; Asthmatee; Medizinische Tees; Diätgetränke für medizinische Zwecke; Wurzeln mit medizinischer Wirkung; Diätgetränke für medizinische Zwecke; Medizinische Getränke; Dekokte für pharmazeutische Zwecke; Stärkungsmittel; Tonika; Babykost; Blutreinigende Mittel; Nahrungsergänzungsmittel aus Propolis; Nahrungsergänzungsmittel aus Proteinen; Appetitzügler für medizinische Zwecke; Nahrungsergänzungsmittel aus Pollen; Sirupe für pharmazeutische Zwecke; Malzmilchgetränke für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Τσάι με βότανα για φαρμακευτική χρήση· Βότανα φαρμακευτικά· Αντιασθματικό τσάι· Τσάι ιατρικό· Ποτά διαιτητικά για χρήση ιατρική· Ιατρικές ρίζες· Ποτά διαιτητικά για χρήση ιατρική· Ιατρικά ποτά· Αφεψήματα για φαρμακευτική χρήση· Δυναμωτικά παρασκευάσματα· Τονωτικά σκευάσματα· Βρεφικές/Παιδικές τροφές· Καθαρτικά· Συμπληρώματα διατροφής με πρόπολη· Πρωτεϊνούχα συμπληρώματα διατροφής· Αντιορεξιογόνα παρασκευάσματα για χρήση ιατρική· Συμπληρώματα διατροφής με γύρη· Σιρόπια για χρήση φαρμακευτική· Γάλα βύνης ιατρικής χρήσης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Herbal teas for medicinal purposes; Medicinal herbs; Asthmatic tea; Medicinal tea; Dietetic beverages adapted for medical purposes; Medicinal roots; Dietetic beverages adapted for medical purposes; Medicinal drinks; Decoctions for pharmaceutical purposes; Energising preparations; Tonics; Infant formula; Depuratives; Propolis dietary supplements; Protein dietary supplements; Appetite suppressants for medical purposes; Pollen dietary supplements; Syrups for pharmaceutical purposes; Malted milk beverages for medical purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Tisanas; Hierbas medicinales; Antiasmático (Té -); Té medicinal; Bebidas dietéticas para uso médico; Raíces medicinales; Bebidas dietéticas para uso médico; Pociones medicinales; Decocciones para uso farmacéutico; Preparaciones reforzantes; Tónicos reconstituyentes; Preparaciones para lactantes; Depurativos; Suplementos alimenticios a base de propóleos; Suplementos alimenticios a base de proteínas; Supresores del apetito para uso médico; Suplementos alimenticios a base de polen; Jarabes para uso farmacéutico; Leche malteada para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Taimeteed (Meditsiinilised); Ravimtaimed; Astmatee; Ravimteed; Meditsiinilised dieetjoogid; Ravimjuured; Dieetjoogid (Meditsiinilised); Ravimjoogid; Farmatseutilised dekoktid, droogikeedised; Üldtugevdavad preparaadid; Toonikud; Imikutoit; Verepuhastid; Proopolis toidulisandina; Valk toidulisandina; Meditsiiniotstarbelised söögiisuvähendajad; Õietolm toidulisandina; Farmatseutilised siirupid; Meditsiinilised linnasepiimajoogid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Yrttiteet lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Lääkeyrtit; Astmatee; Lääketee; Dieettijuomat lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Lääkinnälliset juuret; Dieettijuomat lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Lääkejuomat; Dekoktit [keitteet] lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Vahvistavat valmisteet; Hoitoaineet; Äidinmaidonvastikkeet; Ulostusaineet; Mehiläisliima (propolis) lisäravinteena; Proteiinit lisäravinteena; Ruokahalua heikentävät valmisteet lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Siitepöly lisäravinteena; Siirappi lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Imelletyt maitojuomat lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Tisanes; Herbes médicinales; Thé antiasthmatique; Thé médicinal; Boissons diététiques à usage médical; Racines médicinales; Boissons diététiques à usage médical; Potions médicinales; Décoctions à usage pharmaceutique; Préparations fortifiantes; Préparations toniques; Préparations alimentaires pour nourrissons; Dépuratifs; Compléments alimentaires de propolis; Compléments alimentaires protéinés; Coupe-faim à usage médical; Compléments alimentaires de pollen; Sirops à usage pharmaceutique; Boissons au lait malté à usage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Ljekoviti čajevi za medicinske svrhe; Ljekovite trave; Antiasmatski čaj; Medicinski čaj; Dijetni napici za medicinske potrebe; Ljekovito korijenje; Dijetni napici za medicinske potrebe; Medicinski napici; Dekokti za farmaceutske potrebe; Preparati za jačanje organizma; Tonici; Hrana za bebe; Depurativna sredstva; Propolis kao prehrambeni dodatak; Proteinski prehrambeni dodaci; Sredstva za suzbijanje apetita za medicinske svrhe; Pelud kao prehrambeni dodatak; Sirup za farmaceutske potrebe; Sladovo mlijeko za meidcinske potrebe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Herbateák gyógyászati használatra; Gyógynövények; Asztma elleni tea; Gyógyteák; Diétás italok gyógyászati célokra; Növényi gyökerek, orvosi használatra; Diétás italok gyógyászati használatra; Gyógyitalok; Főzetek gyógyszerészeti célokra; Erősítő preparátumok; Tonikok; Bébiételek; Hashajtók; Propolisz étrend-kiegészítők; Protein étrend-kiegészítők; Étvágycsökkentők orvosi, gyógyászati használatra; Pollen étrend-kiegészítők; Szirupok gyógyszerészeti használatra; Malátás tejitalok gyógyászati használatra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Tisane per uso medico; Erbe medicinali; Tè antiasmatico; Tè medicinale; Bevande dietetiche per uso medico; Radici medicinali; Bevande dietetiche per uso medico; Pozioni medicinali; Decotti per uso farmaceutico; Preparati ricostituenti; Ricostituenti; Alimenti per neonati; Depurativi; Integratori alimentari di propoli; Integratori alimentari di proteine; Farmaci anoressizzanti; Integratori alimentari di polline; Sciroppi per uso farmaceutico; Latte maltato per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Žolių arbatos (medicinos reikmėms); Vaistažolės; Arbata nuo astmos; Gydomosios arbatos; Dietiniai gėrimai (medicinos reikmėms); Gydomosios šaknelės; Dietiniai gėrimai (medicinos reikmėms); Gydomieji gėrimai; Nuovirai (farmacijos reikmėms); Stiprinamieji preparatai; Tonizuojamosios priemonės; Kūdikių maistas; Laksantai [vidurius paleidžiantys vaistai]; Bičių pikio maisto papildai; Baltymų maisto papildai; Apetito slopinamieji preparatai (preparatai nuo valgumo) (medicinos reikmėms); Žiedadulkių maisto papildai; Sirupai (farmacijos reikmėms); Pieno gėrimai su salyklu (medicinos reikmėms).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Augu tējas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Ārstniecības augi; Tēja pret astmu; Ārstnieciskās tējas; Diētiskie dzērieni medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Saknes farmaceitiskiem nolūkiem; Diētiskie dzērieni medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Ārstnieciski dzērieni; Novārījumi farmaceitiskiem nolūkiem; Spēcinoši preparāti; Ādu tonizējoši līdzekļi; Uzturs zīdaiņiem un maziem bērniem; Caurejas līdzekļi; Propolisa uztura bagātinātāji; Proteīns kā uztura bagātinātājs; Apetīti samazinoši līdzekļi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Ziedputekšņu uztura bagātinātāji; Sīrupi farmaceitiskiem nolūkiem; Iesala piena dzērieni medicīniskiem nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tejiet tal-ħwawar għal skopijiet mediċinali; Ħxejjex mediċinali; Te għall-ażżma; Te mediċinali; Xorb djetetiku adattat għal skopijiet mediċi; Għeruq mediċinali; Xorb djetetiku adattat għal skopijiet mediċi; Xorb mediċinali; Dekozzjonijiet għal skopijiet farmaċewtiċi; Preparazzjonijiet restorativi; Toniċi; Ikel għat-trabi; Purganti; Supplimenti tad-dieta biż-żaftura; Supplimenti tad-dieta bil-proteini; Mediċina li taqta' l-aptit għal skopijiet mediċi; Supplimenti tad-dieta bil-polline; Ġulepp għal skopijiet farmaċewtiċi; Xorb tal-ħalib bix-xgħir għal skopijiet mediċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kruidenaftreksels [tisanes]; Geneeskrachtige kruiden; Thee tegen astma; Medicinale thee; Dieetdranken voor medisch gebruik; Medicinale wortels; Dieetdranken voor medisch gebruik; Medicinale drankjes; Aftreksels voor farmaceutisch gebruik; Versterkende preparaten; Tonics; Voedingsmiddelen voor baby's; Bloedzuiverende middelen; Voedingssupplementen op basis van propolis; Voedingssupplementen op basis van proteïne; Eetlustremmers voor medisch gebruik; Voedingssupplementen op basis van pollen; Siropen voor farmaceutisch gebruik; Moutmelk voor medisch gebruik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Herbaty ziołowe do celów medycznych; Zioła lecznicze; Astmatycy (Herbata dla -); Herbata lecznicza; Dietetyczne napoje przystosowane do celów medycznych; Korzenie lekarskie; Dietetyczne napoje przystosowane do celów medycznych; Napoje lecznicze; Wywary do celów farmaceutycznych; Preparaty wzmacniające; Toniki; Żywność dla niemowląt; Środki przeczyszczające; Suplementy diety zawierające propolis; Suplementy diety zawierające białko; Środki zmniejszające apetyt do celów medycznych; Suplementy diety zawierające pyłek kwiatowy; Syropy do użytku farmaceutycznego; Napoje z mleka słodowego do celów medycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Tisanas para fins medicinais; Ervas medicinais; Chá antiasmático; Chá medicinal; Bebidas dietéticas para uso medicinal; Raízes medicinais; Bebidas dietéticas para uso medicinal; Poções medicinais; Decocções para uso farmacêutico; Produtos fortificantes; Tónicos; Preparações alimentares para bebés; Depurativos; Suplementos dietéticos de própolis; Suplementos dietéticos de proteína; Supressores de apetite para uso médico; Suplementos dietéticos de pólen; Xaropes para uso farmacêutico; Leite maltado [leite de malte] para uso medicinal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ceaiuri din plante pentru uz medicinal; Ierburi medicinale; Antiasmatice (Ceaiuri -); Ceai medicinal; Băuturi dietetice de uz medical; Rădăcini medicinale; Băuturi dietetice de uz medical; Poţiuni medicinale; Decocturi de uz farmaceutic; Preparate tonice; Tonice; Alimente pentru bebeluşi; Laxative; Suplimente alimentare pe bază de propolis; Suplimente alimentare proteice; Preparate de uz medical pentru inhibarea apetitului; Suplimente alimentare pe bază de polen; Siropuri de uz farmaceutic; Băuturi din lapte de malţ de uz medical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Bylinkové čaje na lekárske použitie; Liečivé rastliny; Astma (Čaj proti -); Liečivé čaje; Diétne nápoje na lekárske použitie; Liečivé korene; Diétne nápoje na lekárske účely; Liečivé nápoje; Zápary na farmaceutické použitie; Posilňujúce prípravky; Toniká; Potraviny pre batoľatá; Preháňadlá; Propolisové výživové doplnky; Proteínové výživové doplnky; Prípravky na zníženie chuti do jedla na lekárske použitie; Peľové výživové doplnky; Sirupy na farmaceutické použitie; Sladové mliečne nápoje na lekárske použitie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zeliščni čaji za medicinske namene; Zdravilna zelišča; Čaj za astmatike; Zdravilni čaji; Dietetične pijače, prirejene za medicinske namene; Zdravilne koreninice; Dietetične pijače prirejene za medicinske namene; Zdravilne pijače; Zvarki za farmacevtske namene; Preparati za okrepitev; Losjoni; Hrana za dojenčke; Laksativi; Propolis kot prehranski dodatek; Proteini kot prehranski dodatki; Sredstva za zmanjševanje apetita za medicinske namene; Pelod kot prehranski dodatek; Sirupi za farmacevtske namene; Mlečne pijače s sladom za medicinske namene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Örtteer för medicinska ändamål; Medicinalörter; Astmatéer; Medicinalte; Dietiska drycker för medicinska ändamål; Medicinalrötter; Dietiska drycker för medicinska ändamål; Medicinaldrycker; Dekokter för farmaceutiska ändamål; Stärkande preparat; Tonikum; Spädbarnsmat; Laxativ; Kosttillskott av honung; Kosttillskott av protein; Aptitreducerande preparat för medicinska ändamål; Kosttillskott av frömjöl [pollen]; Sirap för farmaceutiska ändamål; Malthaltiga mjölkdrycker för medicinska ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Данни, бази данни и други информационни продукти върху носители на данни и в електронните мрежи за бази данни, информационните или телекомуникационните мрежи от всякакъв вид; Софтуер за обратно търсене; Софтуер с възможност за изтегляне от рода на мобилно приложение.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Data, databáze a jiné informační produkty na nosičích dat a v elektronických datových, informačních a telekomunikačních sítích všeho druhu; software pro zpětné vyhledávaní; software ke stažení ve formě mobilní aplikace.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Data, databaser og andre informationsprodukter på databærere og i elektroniske data-, informations- eller telekommunikationsnetværk af enhver art; Software til omvendt billedsøgning; Software, der kan downloades, i form af en mobil applikation.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Daten, Datenbanken und andere Informationsprodukte auf Datenträgern und in elektronischen Daten-, Informations- oder Telekommunikationsnetzen aller Art; Software für die Rückwärtssuche; Herunterladbare Software in Form von mobilen Anwendungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δεδομένα, βάσεις δεδομένων και άλλα πληροφοριακά προϊόντα σε μέσα αποθήκευσης δεδομένων και σε ηλεκτρονικά δίκτυα, δίκτυα δεδομένων, πληροφοριών ή τηλεπικοινωνιακά δίκτυα κάθε είδους· Λογισμικό για αντίστροφη αναζήτηση· Τηλεφορτώσιμο λογισμικό με τη μορφή κινητών εφαρμογών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Data, databases and other information products on data carriers and in electronic data, information or telecommunications networks of all kinds; Software for traceability; downloadable software in the nature of a mobile application.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Datos, bases de datos y otros productos de información en soportes de datos y en redes electrónicas de datos, informáticas o de telecomunicación de todo tipo; Software de búsqueda inversa; Software descargable del tipo de una aplicación móvil.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Andmed, andmekogud ja muud infotooted andmekandjatel ja igat liiki elektroonilistes andme-, teabe-, kaugsidevõrkudes; Pöördotsingu tarkvara; Allalaaditav tarkvara mobiilirakenduse kujul.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Data, tietokannat ja muut tiedot tietovälineillä ja kaikenlaisissa sähköisissä data-, tieto- tai tietoliikenneverkoissa; Ohjelmistot peruuttavaan hakuun; Ladattavat ohjelmistot mobiilisovellusten muodossa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Données, bases de données et autres produits d'information sur supports de données et sur réseaux électroniques de données, d'informations ou de télécommunications de tous types; Logiciels pour la recherche inversée; Logiciels téléchargeables sous forme d'une application mobile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Podatci, baze podataka i drugi informacijski proizvodi na nosačima podataka i elektronički podatci, informacijske ili telekomunikacijske mreže svih vrsta; Softver za obrnuto pretraživanje; Softver koji se može preuzimati poput mobilne aplikacije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Adatok, adatbázisok és egyéb informatikai termékek adathordozókon és elektronikus adat, információs és telekommunikációs hálózatok minden típusán; Fordított keresési szoftverek; Letölthető szoftverek mobil alkalmazás formájában.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Dati, banche dati e altri prodotti di informazione su supporti dati in reti dati, informazione o telecomunicazione elettroniche di tutti i tipi; Software per tracciabilità; Software scaricabili in forma d'applicazioni cellulari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Duomenys, duomenų bazės ir kiti informacijos produktai duomenų laikmenose ir visų rūšių elektroniniuose duomenų, informacijos, telekomunikacijos tinkluose; Atsekamumo programinė įranga; Parsisiunčiamoji programinė įranga, būtent mobiliosios taikomosios programos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Dati, datubāzes un citi informācijas produkti dažādos datu nesējos un dažādos elektroniskajos datu, informācijas vai telekomunikācijas tīklos; Datu izguves programmatūra; Lejupielādējama programmatūra mobilo lietotņu veidā.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Data, bażijiet tad-data u prodotti oħra ta' informazzjoni fuq ġarriera tad-data u f'netwerks tad-data elettronika, tal-informazzjoni jew tat-telekomunikazzjoni ta' kull tip; Software għar-riċerka bil-maqlub; Softwer li jista' jitniżżel fl-għamla ta' applikazzjoni mobbli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Data, databanken en andere informatieproducten op gegevensdragers en in alle soorten elektronische, data-, informatie- of telecommunicatienetwerken; Software voor research; Downloadbare software in de vorm van een mobiele applicatie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dane, bazy danych i inne produkty informatyczne na nośnikach danych i w sieciach elektronicznych, w sieciach danych i w sieciach informatycznych lub telekomunikacyjnych wszelkiego rodzaju; Oprogramowanie do wyszukiwania wstecznego; Pobieralne oprogramowanie w postaci mobilnej aplikacji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Dados, bases de dados e outros produtos de informação em suportes de dados e em todo o tipo de redes eletrónicas, de dados, informáticas ou de telecomunicações; Software que permite ligações para outros recursos Web ("backlinks"); Software descarregável sob a forma de uma aplicação móvel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Date, baze de date și alte produse informatice pe suporturi de date și în rețele de date electronice, informatice sau de telecomunicații de orice fel; Software pentru căutare inversă; Software descărcabil sub forma unei aplicaţii mobile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Údaje, databázy a iné informačné produkty na nosičoch údajov a v elektronických dátových, informačných alebo telekomunikačných sieťach všetkých druhov; Softvér na spätné vyhľadávanie; Stiahnuteľný softvér v podobe mobilných aplikácií.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Podatki, baze podatkov in drugi informacijski izdelki na nosilcih podatkov in v elektronskih podatkovnih, informacijskih ali telekomunikacijskih omrežjih vseh vrst; Programska oprema za povratno iskanje; Naložljiva programska oprema v obliki mobilne aplikacije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Data, databaser och andra informationsprodukter på databärare och på elektroniska data-, informations- eller telekommunikationsnät av alla slag; Programvara för bakåtsökning; Nerladdningsbar programvara i form av en mobil tillämpning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>29</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Напитки, приготвени от или съдържащи мляко; Суроватка; Сушено мляко; Напитки на основата на бадемово мляко; Фъстъчено мляко [безалкохолна напитка].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nápoje vyrobené z mléka nebo obsahující mléko; syrovátka; sušené mléko; mandlové mléko (jako nápoj); mléko arašídové (nápoje nealkoholické).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Drikke fremstillet af eller indeholdende mælk; Valle; Mælkepulver; Drikke baseret på mandelmælk; Jordnøddemælk [ikke-alkoholholdige drikke].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Getränke aus Milch oder Milch enthaltende Getränke; Molke; Milchpulver; Getränke auf der Basis von Mandelmilch; Erdnussmilch [alkoholfrei].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ροφήματα από ή που περιέχουν γάλα· Τυρόγαλα· Σκόνη γάλακτος· Ροφήματα με βάση το γάλα αμυγδάλου· Γάλα με αραχίδα [μη οινοπνευματώδες ποτό].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Beverages made from or containing milk; Whey; Dried milk; Almond milk-based beverages; Peanut milk [non-alcoholic beverage].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bebidas hechas de o que contienen leche; Suero de leche; Leche deshidratada; Bebidas a base de leche de almendras; Leche de maní [bebida sin alcohol].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Piimast valmistatud või seda sisaldavad joogid; Piimavadak; Piimapulbrid; Mandlipiimajoogid; Maapähklipiim [alkoholivaba jook].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Maidosta valmistetut tai maitoa sisältävät juomat; Hera; Maitojauhe; Mantelimaitopohjaiset juomat; Maapähkinämaito [alkoholiton juoma].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Boissons à base de lait ou contenant du lait; Petit-lait; Lait déshydraté; Boissons à base de lait d'amandes; Lait d'arachides [boisson sans alcool].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pića napravljena od mlijeka ili koja sadrže mlijeko; Surutka; Mlijeko u prahu; Pića na bazi bademovog mlijeka; Mlijeko od kikirikija [bezalkoholni napitak].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tejből készült vagy tejtartalmú italok; Tejsavó; Tejpor; Mandulatej-alapú italok; Földimogyoró tej [alkoholmentes ital].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Bevande a base di o contenenti latte; Siero di latte; Latte disidratata; Bevande a base di latte di mandorle; Latte d'arachidi [bevande non alcooliche].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Gėrimai iš pieno ar kurių sudėtyje yra pieno; Pieno išrūgos; Pieno milteliai; Migdolų pieno gėrimai; Žemės riešutų pienas [gaivusis gėrimas].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Dzērieni, kas izgatavoti no piena vai satur to; Sūkalas; Piena pulveris; Dzērieni uz mandeļu piena bāzes; Zemesriekstu piens.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Xarbiet magħmulin minn jew li fihom il-ħalib; Xorrox; Trab tal-ħalib; Xarbiet ibbażati fuq il-ħalib tal-lewż; Ħalib tal-karawett [xarba mhux alkoħolika].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Dranken gemaakt van melk of melk bevattend; Melkwei; Gedroogde melk; Dranken op basis van amandelmelk; Pindamelk [alcoholvrije dranken].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Napoje przyrządzone z mleka lub zawierające mleko; Serwatka; Mleko w proszku; Napoje na bazie mleka migdałowego; Mleko orzechowe (Napoje bezalkoholowe -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Bebidas feitas de ou contendo leite; Soro de leite; Leite desidratado; Bebidas à base de leite de amêndoa; Leite de amendoins [bebida não-alcoólica].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Băuturi preparate din lapte sau care conţin lapte; Zer; Lapte praf; Băuturi pe bază de lapte de migdale; Lapte de arahide [băutură nealcoolică].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nápoje vyrobené z mlieka alebo s obsahom mlieka; Srvátka; Sušené mlieko; Nápoje z mandľového mlieka; Arašidové mlieko [nealkoholický nápoj].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pijače, pripravljene iz mleka ali ki vsebujejo mleko; Sirotka; Mleko v prahu; Pijače na osnovi mandljevega mleka; Kikirikijevo mleko [brezalkoholna pijača].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Drycker tillverkade av eller innehållande mjölk; Vassla; Mjölkpulver; Drycker baserade på mandelmjölk; Jordnötsmjölk (icke-alkoholhaltig dryck).</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>30</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Чай; Студен чай; Какао; Какаови напитки; Какаови напитки с мляко; Кафе; Заместители на кафе; Растителни продукти, използвани като заместители на кафе; Напитки, съдържащи кафе; Напитки от кафе с мляко; Шоколадови напитки; Чаени напитки; Кафе (Неизпечено -); Растителни продукти, използвани като заместители на кафе; Зърнени и енергийни десертни блокчета; Сладкарски блокчета; Високо-протеинови зърнени десертни блокчета; Десертни блокчета, съдържащи смес от зърнени култури, ядки и сушени плодове [захарни изделия]; Шейкове с намалени калории; Сладкарски изделия; Сладкарски изделия; Хранителни сладкиши; Шоколади; Сладкарски изделия; Смес за сладкиши; Сухари; Петифури [пасти, торти, кексове и др.]; Bафли; Бонбони с карамел; Бисквити; Сладки и солени сладкиши; Пирожки с пълнеж [пай, пирог]; Зърнени храни (обработени) с ниско съдържание на въглехидрати; Зърнени продукти; Сладкиши с ниско съдържание на въглехидрати; Готови хранителни смеси, включени в този клас; Екстракти от кафе; Екстракти от неестествено кафе; Цикория; Чай; Чаени екстракти; Какао и заместители; Прахообразни препарати, съдържащи какао за употреба в приготвяне на напитки; Кокос на прах; Тапиока; Смес за сладкиши; Шоколади и десерти; Шоколадови продукти; Шоколад за мазане; Шоколадови продукти за мазане, съдържащи ядки; Охладени десерти; Готови десерти; Сладоледени десерти; Сладоледи; Фунийки за сладоледи; Замразени кисели млека и сорбета; Сиропи и меласи; Мед; Захар; Лед, натурален или изкуствен; Обработени зърнени храни, нишесте и продукти, произведени от тях; Препарати за печене и мая; Хляб и козуначени кифли със стафиди; Хлебни изделия; Подправки; Пици; Киш [ястие от Лотарингия]; Изделия от пчелни продукти; Ястия на основата на ориз; Оризови бисквити; Хрупкави бисквити, приготвени от зърнени храни.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Čaje; čaje ledové; kakao; kakaové nápoje; kakaové nápoje s mlékem; káva; kávové náhražky; kávové náhražky rostlinného původu; kávové nápoje; kávové nápoje s mlékem; čokoládové nápoje; nápoje na bázi čaje; nepražená káva; rostlinné přípravky jako kávové náhražky; cereální tyčinky a energetické tyčinky; tyčinky (cukrovinky); cereální tyčinky s vysokým obsahem proteinů; tyčinky obsahující směs cereálií, ořechů a sušeného ovoce (cukrovinky); svačinky se sníženým obsahem uhlovodanů; cukrovinky; cukroví; výživné cukrovinky; čokolády; bonbóny; sušenky; suchary; keksy; oplatky; karamely; biskvity; sladké a slané pečivo; koláče; obilniny (zpracované) se sníženým obsahem uhlovodanů; výrobky z obilnin; cukrovinky se sníženým obsahem uhlovodanů; hotové potravinové směsi v rámci této třídy; kávové výtažky; výtažky kávových náhražek; cikorka; čaj; čajové výtažky; kakao a jejich náhražky; práškové přípravky obsahující kakao pro použití při výrobě nápojů; kakaový prášek; tapioka; dorty; čokoláda a zákusky; čokoládové výrobky; čokoládové pomazánky; čokoládové pomazánky obsahující ořechy; chlazené dezerty; hotové dezerty; zmrzlinové dezerty; zmrzlina; kornoutky na zmrzliny; mražené jogurty a sorbety; sirupy a melasa; med; cukr; led (přírodní nebo umělý); zpracované obilí, škrob a produkty z nich vyrobené; pečicí přípravky a droždí; chléb a pečivo; pekárenské výrobky; chuťové přísady; pizzy; quiche (slané koláče); výrobky z včelích produktů; rýžové pokrmy; rýžové sušenky; cereální lupínky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Te; Iste; Kakao; Kakaodrikke; Kakaodrikke med mælk; Kaffe; Kaffeerstatning; Kaffeerstatning (Plantepræparater til brug som -); Drikke på basis af kaffe; Kaffedrikke med mælk; Chokoladebaserede drikke; Tebaserede drikkevarer; Ubrændt kaffe; Vegetabilske præparater til brug som kaffeerstatninger; Myslibarer og energibarer; Konfekturestænger; Høj-protein barer baseret på korn; Snackbarer med en blanding af korn, nødder, tørrede frugter [konfekturevarer]; I form af smoothies med lavt kalorieindhold; Bolsjer; Sukkervarer; Konfekturevarer til ernæring; Chokolader; Bolsjer; Biscuits [søde kiks og småkager]; Tvebakker; Petits-four [kager]; Vaffelkiks; Slik med karamel; Biscuits; Søde og salte konditorivarer; Indbagte dejretter; Kulhydratfattige kornprodukter (forarbejdede); Kornpræparater; Kulhydratfattige konfekturevarer; Færdiglavede fødevareblandinger indeholdt i denne klasse; Kaffeekstrakter; Ekstrakter af kaffeerstatning; Cikorie; Te; Teekstrakter; Kakao og erstatninger herfor; Præparater i pulverform med kakao til fremstilling af drikke; Kakaopulver; Tapioka; Kager; Chokolader og desserter; Chokoladeprodukter; Chokoladesmørepålæg; Chokoladesmørepålæg med nødder; Nedkølede desserter; Tilberedte desserter; Iscremedesserter; Spiseis; Vafler til is; Yoghurtis og sorbetis; Lys sirup; Honning; Sukker; Råis, naturlig eller kunstig; Forarbejdet korn, stivelse og produkter fremstillet deraf; Præparater til bagning og gær; Brød og boller; Bagerivarer; Smagsstoffer [krydderier]; Pizzaer; Quiches [tærter]; Varer fremstillet af produkter fra bier; Risbaserede retter; Riskiks; Chips fremstillet af korn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Tee; Eistee; Kakao; Kakaogetränke; Milchkakao; Kaffee; Kaffee-Ersatz; Kaffee-Ersatzstoffe auf pflanzlicher Grundlage; Kaffeegetränke; Milchkaffee; Schokoladegetränke; Getränke auf der Basis von Tee; Rohkaffee; Kaffee-Ersatzstoffe auf pflanzlicher Grundlage; Müsliriegel und Energieriegel; Süßwarenriegel; Proteinreiche Getreideriegel; Snackriegel mit einer Mischung aus Getreidekörnern, Nüssen und getrocknetem Obst [Süßwaren]; In Form von kalorienreduzierten Smoothies; Bonbons; Zuckerwaren, Konfekt; Nährstoffhaltige Konditorwaren; Pralinen; Bonbons; Kekse; Zwieback; Petits Fours [Gebäck]; Oblaten; Karamellstücke; Biskuits; Süße oder herzhafte feine Backwaren; Pasteten im Teigmantel; Kohlenhydratarme Zerealien (bearbeitete); Getreidepräparate; Kohlenhydratarme Konditorwaren; Nahrungsmittelfertigmischungen, soweit sie in dieser Klasse enthalten sind; Kaffeeextrakte; Extrakte von Kaffeeersatzmitteln; Zichorie; Tee; Teeextrakte; Kakao und Ersatzstoffe hierfür; Pulverförmige kakaohaltige Präparate zur Verwendung bei der Zubereitung von Getränken; Kakaopulver; Tapioca; Kuchen; Schokoladen und Desserts; Schokoladeprodukte; Schokoladenaufstriche; Schokoladen-Brotaufstriche mit Nüssen; Gekühlte Desserts; Fertigesserts; Eiscremedesserts; Speiseeis; Eistüten; Gefrorener Joghurt und Sorbets; Melassesirup; Honig; Zucker; Roheis [natürlich oder künstlich gefroren]; Verarbeitetes Getreide und Stärken für Nahrungsmittel sowie Waren hieraus; Backpräparate und Hefe; Brot und Brötchen; Backwaren; Gewürzmischungen; Pizzas; Quiches; Waren aus Bienenprodukten; Gerichte auf Reisbasis; Reisplätzchen; Chips aus Getreide.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Τσάι· Παγωμένο τσάι· Κακάο· Ποτά με βάση το κακάο· Γάλα (Κακάο με -)· Καφές· Υποκατάστατα καφέ· Παρασκευάσματα φυτικά υποκατάστατα του καφέ· Ποτά με βάση τον καφέ· Γάλα (Καφές με -)· Ρόφημα σοκολάτας· Ποτά με βάση το τσάι· Καφές [ακαβούρντιστος]· Παρασκευάσματα φυτικά υποκατάστατα του καφέ· Μπάρες δημητριακών και μπάρες ενέργειας· Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής σε μορφή ράβδου· Ράβδοι δημητριακών υψηλής περιεκτικότητας σε πρωτεΐνες· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) σε μορφή ράβδου τα οποία περιέχουν μείγμα σπόρων, ξηρών καρπών και αποξηραμένων φρούτων [είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής]· Ως ελαφρά παχύρρευστα ποτά φρούτων με μειωμένη περιεκτικότητα σε θερμίδες· Ζαχαρώδη· Ζαχαρωτών είδη· Θρεπτικά είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής· Σοκολάτες, σοκολάτα· Ζαχαρώδη· Γλυκά· Φρυγανιές· Πτιφούρ [είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής]· Γκοφρέτες· Ζαχαρωτά με καραμέλα· Μπισκότα· Ζύμες, γλυκές και αλμυρές· Πίτες· Δημητριακά χαμηλής περιεκτικότητας σε υδατάνθρακες (επεξεργασμένα)· Δημητριακών (Παρασκευάσματα -)· Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής χαμηλής περιεκτικότητας σε υδατάνθρακες· Έτοιμα μείγματα τροφίμων στα πλαίσια της παρούσας κλάσης· Εκχυλίσματα καφέ· Εκχυλίσματα υποκατάστατων καφέ· Κιχώριο· Τσάι· Εκχυλίσματα τσαγιού· Κακάο και υποκατάστατα αυτού· Παρασκευάσματα σε μορφή σκόνης που περιέχουν κακάο για χρήση στην παρασκευή ροφημάτων· Κακάο σε σκόνη· Ταπιόκα· Γλυκά· Σοκολάτες και επιδόρπια· Προϊόντα σοκολάτας· Παρασκευάσματα σοκολάτας σε μορφή κρέμας· Επαλείμματα σοκολάτας με ξηρούς καρπούς· Παγωμένα επιδόρπια· Έτοιμα επιδόρπια· Επιδόρπια παγωτού· Παγωτά· Χωνάκια παγωτού· Παγωμένο γιαούρτι και παγωτά νερού· Σιρόπια και μελάσες· Μέλι· Ζάχαρη· Πάγος ακατέργαστος, φυσικός ή τεχνητός· Επεξεργασμένα σιτηρά, άμυλο και προϊόντα παραγόμενα από αυτά· Παρασκευάσματα για ψήσιμο καθώς και μαγιά· Ψωμί και ψωμάκια· Είδη αρτοποιίας· Καρυκεύματα· Πίτσες· Κις· Είδη από μελισσοκομικά προϊόντα· Πιάτα (γεύματα) με βάση το ρύζι· Ρυζιού κέικ· Τραγανά τεμάχια (κρισπς) από δημητριακά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Tea; Ices tea; Cocoa; Cocoa-based beverages; Cocoa beverages with milk; Coffee; Artificial coffee; Vegetal preparations for use as coffee substitutes; Coffee-based beverages; Coffee beverages with milk; Drinking chocolate; Tea-based beverages; Coffee (Unroasted -); Vegetal preparations for use as coffee substitutes; Cereal bars and energy bars; Confectionery bars; High-protein cereal bars; Snack bars containing a mixture of grains, nuts and dried fruit [confectionery]; being reduced calorie smoothies; Sweetmeats [candy]; Confectionery; nutritional confectionery; Chocolates; Sweetmeats [candy]; Cookies; Rusks; Petits fours [cakes]; Wafers; Candy with caramel; Biscuits; Sweet and savoury pastries; Pies; Processed cereals with reduced carbohydrate content; Cereal preparations; Low carbohydrate confectionery; Ready-mixed foodstuffs included in this class; Coffee extracts; artificial coffee extracts; Chicory; Tea; Tea extracts; Cocoa and substitutes therefor; Powdered preparations containing cocoa for use in making beverages; Cocoa powder; Tapioca; Cakes; Chocolates and desserts; Chocolate products; Chocolate spreads; Chocolate spreads containing nuts; chilled desserts; Prepared desserts; Ice cream desserts; Edible ices; Cones for ice cream; Frozen yoghurts and sorbets; Golden syrup; Honey; Sugar; Ice, natural or artificial; Processed grain, starch and goods made therefrom; Baking preparations and yeasts; Bread and buns; Bakery goods; Condiments; Pizza; Quiches; Goods made from bee products; Rice based dishes; Rice biscuits; Crisps made of cereals.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Té; Té helado; Cacao; Bebidas a base de cacao; Cacao con leche; Café; Sucedáneos del café; Café (Preparaciones vegetales utilizadas como sucedáneos del -); Bebidas a base de café; Café con leche; Chocolate para beber; Bebidas a base de té; Café sin tostar; Preparaciones vegetales utilizadas como sucedáneos del café; Barritas de cereales y barritas energéticas; Barras de golosina; Barritas de cereales ricas en proteínas; Barritas tentempié que contienen una mezcla de granos, nueces y frutas secas [confitería]; Smoothies (bebidas cremosas a base de fruta) con pocas reducidas; Caramelos; Dulces; Artículos de confitería nutritivos; Bombones; Caramelos; Galletas; Biscotes; Pastelitos dulces y salados [productos de pastelería]; Barquillos [obleas]; Caramelos de azúcar; Pastas (galletas); Repostería dulce y salada; Tartas saladas; Cereales (procesados) con bajo contenido en hidratos de carbono; Cereales (Preparaciones a base de -); Confitería con bajo contenido en hidratos de carbono; Mezclas alimenticias preparadas en el marco de esta clase; Extracto de café; Extractos de sucedáneos del café; Achicoria; Té; Extractos de té; Cacao y sus sucedáneos; Preparaciones en polvo que contienen cacao para la confección de bebidas; Cacao en polvo; Tapioca; Tortas [pasteles]; Chocolates y postres; Productos de chocolate; Cremas de chocolate para untar; Pastas para untar a base de chocolate con frutos secos; Postres refrigerados; Postres preparados; Postres a base de helado; Helados comestibles; Cucuruchos para helados; Yogures helados y sorbetes; Jarabe de melaza; Miel; Azúcar; Hielo natural o artificial; Cereal procesado, almidón y productos a base de los mismos; Productos para hornear y levadura; Panes y bollos; Productos de panadería; Condimentos; Pizza; Quiches; Artícultos que contienen productos de abejas; Platos a base de arroz; Galletas de arroz; Aperitivos crujientes hechos de cereales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tee; Jäätee; Kakao; Kakaojoogid; Kakaojoogid piimaga; Kohv; Kohvi aseained; Taimsed kohvi aseained; Kohvijoogid; Kohvi-piimajoogid; Šokolaadijoogid; Teejoogid; Röstimata roheline kohv; Taimsed kohvi aseained; Teraviljabatoonid, energiabatoonid; Maiustusetahvlid; Valgurikkad teraviljabatoonid; Suupistebatoonid, mis sisaldavad teraviljade, pähklite ja kuivatatud puuviljade segu [maiustused]; Madala kalorisisaldusega smuutid; Kompvekid; Maiustused, kondiitritooted; Toitvad maiustused; Šokolaadid ja šokolaadikommid; Kompvekid; Biskviidid, küpsised; Kuivikud; Kondiitrikoogid [Väikesed]; Vahvliküpsised; Karamelliga kommid; Biskviidid; Magusad ja soolased kondiitritooted; Pirukad; Madala süsivesikusisaldusega teraviljad (töödeldud); Teraviljasaadused; Madala süsivesikusisaldusega maiustused; Valmis toiduainesegud, mis kuuluvad sellesse klassi; Kohviekstraktid; Sünteetilised kohviekstraktid; Sigurid; Tee; Tee-ekstraktid; Kakao ja kakao aseained; Kakaod sisaldavad pulberpreparaadid jookide valmistamiseks; Kakaopulber; Tapiokk, maniokitärklis; Koogid, keeksid, tordid; Šokolaadid, desserdid; Šokolaaditooted; Šokolaadivõided; Pähkleid sisaldavad šokolaadivõided; Külmad magustoidud; Valmisdesserdid; Piima- või koorejäätisest magustoidud; Jäätis; Jäätisetorbikud; Külmutatud jogurtid ja šerbetid; Kuldsiirup, melass; Mesi; Suhkur; Looduslik või tehisjää; Töödeldud teravili, tärklis ja nendest valmistatud tooted; Küpsetusained ja pärm; Leivad ja kuklid; Pagaritooted; Maitseained; Pitsad; Quiche'id [lahtised munapiimaga pirukad]; Mesindussaadused; Riisitoidud; Riisiküpsised; Teraviljakrõpsud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tee; Jääteet; Kaakao; Juomat, kaakaopohjaiset; Kaakaojuomat maidon kanssa; Kahvi; Kahvinkorvike; Kasvisvalmisteet kahvin korvikkeena; Juomat, kahvipohjaiset; Kahvijuomat maidon kanssa; Suklaapohjaiset juomat; Teepohjaiset juomat; Kahvi, paahtamaton; Kasvisvalmisteet kahvin korvikkeena; Vilja- ja energiapatukat; Makeispatukat; Proteiinipitoiset viljapatukat; Viljatuotteita, pähkinöitä ja kuivattuja hedelmiä sekoituksina sisältävät välipalapatukat [makeisina]; Vähäkalorisina pirtelöjuomina; Sokerimakeiset; Makeiset; Ravitsevat makeiset; Suklaat; Sokerimakeiset; Keksit; Korput; Leivät (Pikku -); Vohvelikeksit; Kinuskikaramellit; Keksit; Makeat ja suolaiset leivonnaiset; Piirakat; Vähän hiilihydraatteja sisältävät viljat (käsiteltynä); Viljavalmisteet; Vähän hiilihydraatteja sisältävät makeiset; Valmiit elintarvikeseokset tässä luokassa; Kahviuutteet; Keinotekoiset kahviuutteet; Sikuri; Tee; Teeuutteet; Kaakao ja sen korvikkeet; Kaakaota sisältävät jauhetut valmisteet juomien valmistukseen; Kaakaojauhe; Tapioka; Kakut; Suklaat ja jälkiruoat; Suklaatuotteet; Suklaalevitteet; Suklaalevitteet, jotka sisältävät pähkinöitä; Jäähdytetyt jälkiruoat; Valmiit jälkiruoat; Jäätelöjälkiruoat; Jäätelöt; Jäätelötuutit; Jogurttijäätelöt ja sorbetit; Siirapit ja melassit; Hunaja; Sokeri; Jää, luonnollinen tai keinotekoinen; Viljan, tärkkelyksen ja niistä valmistettujen tuotteiden käsittely; Leivontavalmisteet sekä hiiva; Leivät ja pullat; Leipomotuotteet; Mausteet; Pizza; Quiche-piirakat; Mehiläistuotteista tehdyt valmisteet; Riisipohjaiset ateriat; Riisikeksit; Viljasta valmistetut lastut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Thé; Glaces comestibles, thé; Cacao; Boissons à base de cacao; Boissons à base de cacao et de lait; Café; Succédanés du café; Préparations végétales remplaçant le café; Boissons à base de café; Café au lait; Cacao soluble; Boissons à base de thé; Café vert; Préparations végétales remplaçant le café; Barres de céréales et barres énergétiques; Confiseries en barre; Barres de céréales hyperprotéinées; En-cas contenant un mélange de céréales, de fruits à coque et de fruits séchés [confiseries]; En tant que smoothies [boissons de fruits ou de légumes mixés] pauvres en calories; Bonbons; Sucreries; Confiserie nutritionnelle; Chocolats; Bonbons; Biscuits; Biscottes; Petits fours [pâtisserie]; Gaufrettes; Bonbons au caramel; Biscuits; pâtisserie sucrée et salée; Tourtes; Céréales (traitées) à faible teneur en hydrates de carbone; Préparations faites de céréales; Confiserie à faible teneur en glucides; Mélanges alimentaires prêts à consommer compris dans cette classe; Extraits de café; Extraits de succédanés du café; chicoré; Thé; Extraits de thé; Cacao et ses succédanés; Préparations en poudre contenant du cacao destinées à faire des boissons; Cacao en poudre; Tapioca; Gâteaux; Chocolats et desserts; Produits à base de chocolat; Pâtes à tartiner au chocolat; Pâtes à tartiner au chocolat contenant des fruits à coque; Desserts glacés; Desserts préparés; Crèmes glacées [desserts]; Glaces alimentaires; Cornets pour crème glacée; Yaourts glacés et sorbets; Sirop de mélasse; Miel; Sucre; Glace brute, naturelle ou artificielle; Céréales transformées, fécule et produits à base de ces dernières; Préparations pour la panification et levures; Pain et petits pains; Produits de boulangerie; Condiments; Pizzas; Quiches; Produits fabriqués à partir des substances créées par les abeilles; Plats à base de riz; Biscuits de riz; Chips à base de céréales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Čaj; Ledeni čaj; Kakao; Pića na bazi kakaa; Kakao pića s mlijekom; Kava; Nadomjesci kave; Kava (biljni pripravci kao nadomjesci kave); Pića na bazi kave; Pića od kave s mlijekom; Čokoladna pića; Napitci na bazi čaja; Nepržena kava; Biljni pripravci kao nadomjesci kave; Pločice od žitarica i energetske pločice; Konditorske pločice; Visokoproteinske pločice od žitarica; Čokoladice koje sadrže mješavinu žitarica, oraščića i osušenog voća [konditorske]; Frapei sa smanjenim udjelom kalorija; Konditorski proizvodi; Slatkiši; Prehrambeni slatkiši; Čokoladne praline; Konditorski proizvodi; Tijesto za kolače; Dvopek; Čajni kolačići [minjoni]; Oblatne; Bomboni s karamelom; Kremasta juha; Slani i slatki proizvodi od tijesta; Slane ili slatke pite; Žitarice (prerađene) s niskom razinom ugljikohidrata; Žitarice (pripravci od žitarica); Slatkiši s niskom razinom ugljikohidrata; Pripremljena miješana hrana obuhvaćena ovim razredom; Ekstrakti kave; Ekstrakti umjetne kave; Cikorija; Čaj; Čajni ekstrakti; Kakao i zamjena za njega; Pripravci u prahu koji sadržavaju kakao za pripremu pića; Kakao u prahu; Tapioka; Tijesto za kolače; Čokolade i deserti; Čokoladni proizvodi; Čokoladni namazi; Čokoladni namazi s orašastim plodovima; Hladni deserti; Gotovi deserti; Sladoledni deserti; Sladoledi; Korneti za sladoled; Zamrznuti jogurti i šerbeti; Sirupi i melase; Med; Šećer; Led, prirodni ili umjetni; Obrađene žitarice, škrob i proizvodi od njih; Proizvodi za pečenje i kvasac; Kruh i peciva; Pekarski proizvodi; Začinski dodaci; Pizza; Quiche [vrsta slane torte]; Proizvodi od pčelinjih proizvoda; Jela na bazi riže; Keksi od riže; Čips od žitarica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tea; Jeges tea; Kakaó; Kakaóalapú italok; Kakaóitalok tejjel; Kávé; Pótkávé; Növényi készítmények pótkávéként való használatra; Kávé alapú italok; Kávé tejjel; Csokoládés italporok; Tea alapú italok; Kávé, pörköletlen; Növényi készítmények pótkávéként való használatra; Müzliszeletek, energiaszeletek; Édesség szeletek; Magas protein tartalmú gabonaszeletek; Magvak, diófélék és szárított gyümölcsök keverékét tartalmazó rágcsálnivaló szeletek [édességek]; Azaz csökkentett kalóriatartalmú smoothie-k; Kandiscukor; Cukorkaáruk; Tápláló édességek; Csokoládék; Kandiscukor; Süteménytészta; Kétszersültek; Aprósütemény, teasütemény; Ostyák; Karamellás cukorkák; Kekszek; Édes és sós sütemények; Gyümölcsös sütemények/torták; Csökkentett szénhidráttartalmú gabonafélék (feldolgozott); Gabonakészítmények; Alacsony szénhidráttartalmú cukrászáruk; Készétel keverékek ebben az osztályban; Kávékivonatok; Pótkávékivonatok; Cikória; Tea; Teakivonatok; Kakaó és annak helyettesítő anyagai; Kakaótartalmú porkészítmények italok készítéséhez; Kakaóporok; Tápióka; Süteménytészta; Csokoládék és desszertek; Csokoládétermékek; Mogyorókrémek; Dióféléket tartalmazó kenhető csokoládék; Fagyasztott desszertek; Kész desszertek; Fagylalt desszertek, jégkrémek; Fagylaltok; Fagylalttölcsérek; Fagyasztott joghurtok és sörbetek; Szirupok és melasz; Méz; Cukor; Jég, természetes vagy mesterséges; Feldolgozott gabonák, keményítő és az ezekből származó áruk; Sütéshez való készítmények és élesztő; Kenyerek és zsemlék; Pékáruk; Fűszerek, ízesítők; Pizza; Quiche [tésztában sült sós sodó]; Méhészeti termékekből készült áruk; Rizs alapú ételek; Puffasztott rizs szelet; Gabonából készült ropogtatnivalók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Tè; Tè freddo; Cacao; Bevande a base di cacao; Bevande al cacao con latte; Caffè; Succedanei del caffè; Preparati vegetali succedanei del caffè; Bevande a base di caffè; Caffè e latte; Bevande a base di cioccolato; Bevande a base di tè; Caffè verde; Preparati vegetali succedanei del caffè; Barrette ai cereali e barrette energetiche; Prodotti dolciari in barrette; Barrette ai cereali ad alto contenuto proteico; Snack in barrette contenenti miscele di cereali, noci e frutta secca [confetteria]; Bibite ipocaloriche; Bonbons; Confetteria; Confetteria nutrizionale; Cioccolatini; Bonbons; Biscotti; Pane biscottato; Pasticcini [pasticceria]; Wafer; Zucchero candito al caramello; Biscotti; Pasticceria dolce e salata; Focacce; Cereali (lavorati) a basso contenuto di carboidrati; Preparati fatti di cereali; Confetteria a basso contenuto di carboidrati; Miscele alimentari pronte nell'ambito di questa classe; Estratti di caffè; Estratti di succedanei del caffè; Cicoria; Tè; Estratti di tè; Cacao e relativi succedanei; Prodotti in polvere contenenti cacao per preparare bevande; Cacao in polvere; Tapioca; Dolci; Cioccolatini e dessert; Prodotti a base di cioccolato; Creme da spalmare a base di cioccolato; Cioccolato spalmabile contenente nocciole; Dessert freddi; Dessert pronti; Dessert al gelato; Gelati; Coni per gelati; Yogurt gelato e sorbetti; Sciroppo di melassa; Miele; Zucchero; Ghiaccio, naturale o artificiale; Amido e cereali lavorati e prodotti a base di questi ultimi; Prodotti per la cottura e lieviti; Pane e panini; Prodotti da forno; Condimenti; Pizze; Quiche; Miele; Piatti a base di riso; Biscotti di riso; Sfogliatine a base di cereali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Arbata; Šaltoji arbata; Kakava; Kakavos gėrimai; Kakavos gėrimai su pienu; Kava; Kavos pakaitalai; Augaliniai preparatai, naudojami kaip kavos pakaitalai; Kavos gėrimai; Kavos gėrimai su pienu; Šokolado gėrimai; Arbatžolių gėrimai; Kava (Neskrudinta -); Augaliniai preparatai, naudojami kaip kavos pakaitalai; Javainių ir energiniai batonėliai; Konditeriniai batonėliai; Baltymingieji javainių batonėliai; Užkandžių batonėliai su grūdais, riešutais ir džiovintais vaisiais [konditerijos gaminiai]; Mažai kaloringi tirštieji kokteiliai; Saldainiai [ledinukai]; Konditerijos gaminiai; Mitybiniai konditerijos gaminiai; Šokoladai; Saldainiai [ledinukai]; Biskvitai; Džiūvėsiai; Pyragaičiai su įdaru [kepiniai]; Vafliai [sausainiai]; Saldainiai su karamele; Biskvitai; Saldūs ir sūrūs kepiniai; Pyragai; Mažo angliavandenių kiekio javainiai (apdirbti); Grūdų produktai; Mažo angliavandenių kiekio konditerijos gaminiai; Paruošti maisto mišiniai, priskirti šiai klasei; Kavos ekstraktai; Kavos pakaitalų ekstraktai; Cikorija; Arbata; Arbatos ekstraktai; Kakava ir ją pakeičiančios medžiagos; Miltelių preparatai, kurių sudėtyje yra kakavos, skirti naudoti gaminant gėrimus; Kakavos milteliai; Tapijoka; Kepiniai; Šokoladai ir desertai; Šokolado produktai; Šokoladiniai užtepai; Šokoladiniai užtepai su riešutais; Šaldyti desertai; Paruošti desertai; Ledų desertai; Ledai; Vafliniai indeliai ledams; Šaldyti jogurtai ir šerbetas; Melasos sirupas; Medus; Cukrus; Natūralus ar dirbtinis ledas; Apdorotų sėklų, krakmolo ir iš jų pagaminti produktai; Kepimo preparatai ir mielės; Duona ir saldžios bandelės; Kepiniai; Prieskoniai; Picos; Pyragai su aštriu vaisių įdaru [quiches]; Bičių produktų gaminiai; Ryžių patiekalai; Ryžių sausainiai; Javainiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tēja; Ledus tēja; Kakao; Dzērieni uz kakao bāzes; Kakao dzērieni ar pienu; Kafija; Kafijas aizstājēji; Kafijas aizstājēji no augiem; Kafijas dzērieni; Kafijas dzērieni ar pienu; Dzeramā šokolāde; No tējas gatavoti dzērieni; Kafija (negrauzdēta); Kafijas aizstājēji no augiem; Graudu batoniņi un enerģijas batoniņi; Saldumu tāfelītes; Graudaugu batoniņi ar augstu olbaltumvielu saturu; Uzkodu batoniņi, kas sastāv no graudu, riekstu un žāvētu augļu maisījuma (konditorejas izstrādājumi); Augļu kokteiļi ar samazinātu kaloriju daudzumu; Konditorejas izstrādājumi; Konditorejas izstrādājumi; Barojoši konditorejas izstrādājumi; Šokolādes; Konditorejas izstrādājumi; Toršu mīkla; Sausiņi; Mazas kūciņas; Vafeļu cepumi; Karameļu konfektes; Biskvīti; Saldā un sāļā mīkla; Pīrāgs; (apstrādāti) graudaugi ar zemu ogļhidrātu saturu; Graudaugu pusfabrikāti; Konditorejas izstrādājumi ar zemu ogļhidrātu saturu; Gatavi pārtikas maisījumi šīs klases ietvaros; Kafijas ekstrakti; Mākslīgās kafijas ekstrakti; Cigoriņi; Tēja; Tējas ekstrakti; Kakao un tā aizvietotāji; Pulverveida līdzekļi ar kakao, kurus izmanto dzērienu pagatavošanā; Kakao pulveris; Tapioka; Toršu mīkla; Šokolāde un deserti; Šokolādes produkti; Šokolādes ziežamā masa; Šokolādes ziežamās masas, kas satur riekstus; Atdzesēti deserta ēdieni; Gatavi saldie ēdieni; Saldējuma saldie ēdieni; Saldējums; Vafeļu konusi saldējumam; Saldēti jogurti un sorbeti; Sīrupi (ēdieni); Medus; Cukurs; Dabīgs vai mākslīgs ledus; Apstrādāti graudi, ciete un no tiem izgatavoti produkti; Cepšanai paredzētas vielas, arī raugs; Maize un smalkmaizītes; Maizes produkti; Garšvielu mērces; Picas; Kišs (pīrāgs ar sāļo pildījumu); Preces no biškopības produktiem; Rīsu ēdieni; Rīsu cepumi; Čipsi no graudaugiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Tè; Te kiesaħ; Kawkaw; Xorb ibbażat fuq il-kawkaw; Xorb tal-kawkaw bil-ħalib; Kafè; Kafè artifiċjali; Preparazzjonijiet veġetali għal użu bħala sostituti tal-kafè; Xorb ibbażat fuq il-kafè; Xorb tal-kafè bil-ħalib; Ċikkulata tax-xorb; Xorb ibbażat fuq it-te; Kafè (Mhux mixwi -); Preparazzjonijiet veġetali għall-użu bħala sostituti tal-kafè; Bars taċ-ċereali u bars li jagħtuk l-enerġija; Biċċiet solidi tal-ħelu; Biċċiet sħaħ tal-ikel taċ-ċereali b'livell għoli ta' proteini; Bars li fihom taħlita ta' ċereali, ġewż u frott imnixxef [ħelu], bħala ikel ħafif; Li jkunu smoothies bil-kaloriji mnaqqsa; Ħelu; Ħelu; Ħelu sustanzjuż; Ċikkulati; Ħelu; Għaġina tal-kejk; Panini jqarmċu; Kejk żgħir ta' l-intrita; Wejfers; Zokkor-kandju bil-karamella; Gallettini; Għaġina tal-ħelu biz-zokkor u bil-melħ; Torti; Ċereali bil-livell ta' karboidrati baxx (proċessati); Preparazzjonijiet magħmula miċ-ċereali; Ħelu bil-karboidrat baxx; Taħlitiet tal-ikel lesti, inklużi f'din il-Klassi; Estratti tal-kafè; Estratti tal-kafè artifiċjali; Ċikwejra; Tè; Estratti tat-tè; Kawkaw u sostituti għalih; Preparazzjonijiet tat-trab li fihom l-kawkaw għall-użu biex isir ix-xorb; Trab tal-kawkaw; Tapjoka; Għaġina tal-kejk; Ċikkulati u deżerti; Prodotti taċ-ċikkulata; Spreds taċ-ċikkulata; Ċikkulata li tindilek li fiha l-ġewż; Deżerti mkessħa; Deżerti lesti; Deżerti tal-ġelat; Ġelati; Koni tal-ġelati; Jogurts tal-friża u sorbetti; Xiropp u għasel iswed; Għasel; Zokkor; Silġ, naturali jew artifiċjali; Ċereali pproċessati, lamtu u prodotti tagħhom; Preparazzjonijiet għall-ħami u ħmira; Ħobż u panini; Prodotti tal-ħami; Kondimenti; Pizez; Kixx; Prodotti magħmula minn prodotti tan-naħal; Ikliet ibbażati fuq ir-ross; Gallettini tar-ross; Krisps magħmul miċ-ċereali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Thee; Ijsthee; Cacao; Dranken op basis van cacao; Cacaodranken met melk; Koffie; Koffiesurrogaten; Plantaardige preparaten als vervangingsmiddel van koffie; Dranken op basis van koffie; Koffiedranken met melk; Dranken op basis van chocolade; Dranken op basis van thee; Ongebrande koffie; Plantaardige preparaten als vervangingsmiddel van koffie; Graan- en energierepen; Snoepgoedrepen; Graanrepen met verhoogd eiwitgehalte; Snackrepen bestaande uit een mengsel van granen, noten en gedroogde vruchten [suikergoed]; In de vorm van caloriearme smoothies; Snoepgoed; Suikergoed; Voedzame suikerbakkerswaren; Chocolaatjes; Snoepgoed; Koekjes; Beschuit; Petit-fours [gebak]; Wafeltjes; Snoepgoed met karamel; Biscuits; Zoete en hartige banketbakkerswaren; Pasteien [hartige taarten]; Graanproducten (bewerkt) met een laag gehalte aan koolhydraten; Graanpreparaten; Suikerbakkerswaren met een laag gehalte aan koolhydraten; Kant-en-klare levensmiddelenmengsels, voor zover begrepen in deze klasse; Koffie-extracten; Extracten van koffiesurrogaten; Cichorei; Thee; Thee extracten; Cacao en vervangingsmiddelen hiervoor; Poederpreparaten met cacao voor de bereiding van dranken; Cacaopoeder; Tapioca; Taarten; Chocolade en nagerechten; Chocoladeproducten; Chocoladesmeersels; Chocolademengsels die noten bevatten; Gekoelde nagerechten; Kant-en-klare desserts; IJsdesserten; Consumptie-ijs; Hoorntjes voor roomijs; Yoghurtijs en waterijs; Melassestroop; Honing; Suiker; Ijs, natuurlijk of kunstmatig vervaardigd; Bewerkte granen, zetmeel en hiervan vervaardigde producten; Bakpreparaten en gist; Brood en bolletjes; Bakkerijproducten; Kruiden [specerijen]; Pizza's; Quiches; Artikelen van imkerijproducten; Rijstschotels; Rijstkoekjes; Chips van granen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Herbata; Herbata mrożona; Kakao; Napoje na bazie kakao; Napoje kakaowe z mlekiem; Kawa; Kawa nienaturalna; Kawa (Preparaty roślinne zastępujące -); Napoje na bazie kawy; Napoje kawowe z mlekiem; Czekolada pitna; Nielecznicze napoje na bazie herbaty; Kawa niepalona; Preparaty roślinne zastępujące kawę; Batony zbożowe i energetyczne; Batoniki cukiernicze; Wysokoproteinowe batoniki zbożowe; Batoniki zawierające mieszankę ziaren, orzechów i suszonych owoców [wyroby cukiernicze]; Będące napojami typu smoothie o zmniejszonej zawartości kalorycznej; Wyroby cukiernicze; Słodycze; Odżywcze wyroby cukiernicze; Czekoladki; Wyroby cukiernicze; Ciasto na wypieki; Suchary; Ptifurki [ciasteczka]; Wafelki; Cukierki z karmelem; Biszkopty; Słodkie i słone wyroby cukiernicze; Placki; Zboża (przetworzone) o obniżonej zawartości węglowodanów; Zbożowe (Preparaty -); Wyroby cukiernicze niskocukrowe; Gotowe mieszanki spożywcze, ujęte w tej klasie; Ekstrakty z kawy; Ekstrakty kawy nienaturalnej; Cykoria; Herbata; Wyciągi z herbaty; Kakao i jego zamienniki; Preparaty w proszku zawierające kakao do sporządzania napojów; Kakao w proszku; Tapioka; Ciasto na wypieki; Czekolady i desery; Wyroby z czekolady; Pasty czekoladowe [do smarowania]; Pasty czekoladowe do smarowania zawierające orzechy; Zimne desery; Gotowe desery; Desery lodowe; Lody; Rożki do lodów; Mrożone jogurty i sorbety; Syropy i melasa; Miód; Cukier; Lód naturalny lub sztuczny; Przetworzone ziarna, skrobia i produkty z nich wytworzone; Preparaty do pieczenia oraz drożdże; Chleb i bułki; Wyroby piekarnicze; Przyprawy; Pizza; Quiche; Produkty pszczele; Dania na bazie ryżu; Ciasteczka ryżowe; Chrupki zbożowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Chá; Chá gelado; Cacau; Bebidas à base de cacau; Bebidas de cacau com leite; Café; Sucedâneos do café; Preparações vegetais para substitutos do café; Bebidas à base de café; Bebidas de café com leite; Pós de chocolate para fazer bebidas; Bebida à base de chá; Café verde; Preparações vegetais para substitutos do café; Barras de cereais e barras energéticas; Barras de confeitaria; Barras de cereais com alto teor de proteína; Barras alimentares contendo grãos de cereais e frutos secos [confeitaria]; Sendo batidos de baixo teor calórico; Bombons [doçaria]; Confeitaria; Confeitaria nutritiva; Chocolates; Bombons [doçaria]; Biscoitos [bolinhos]; Tostas; Petits four [pastelaria]; Wafers; Rebuçados de caramelo; Biscoitos; Pastelaria doce e salgada; Tartes [empadas]; Cereais (transformados) com baixo teor de hidratos de carbono; Preparações à base de cereais; Confeitaria com baixo teor de hidratos de carbono; Misturas alimentares pré-confecionadas incluídas nesta classe; Extratos de café; Extractos de sucedâneos do café; Chicória; Chá; Extratos de chá; Cacau e respetivos sucedâneos; Produtos em pó contendo cacau para a preparação de bebidas; Cacau em pó; Tapioca; Bolos; Chocolates e sobremesas; Produtos de chocolate; Cremes de chocolate para barrar; Produtos para barrar, de chocolate, contendo oleaginosas; Sobremesas geladas; Sobremesas preparadas; Sobremesas de gelados; Gelados comestíveis; Cones para gelados; Iogurtes gelados e sorvetes; Xarope de melaço; Mel; Açúcar; Gelo, natural ou artificial; Cereais transformados, amido e produtos fabricados a partir dos mesmos; Preparações para cozedura no forno, bem como fermento; Pão e brioches; Produtos de padaria; Condimentos; Pizzas; Quiches; Produtos à base de produtos apícolas; Pratos à base de arroz; Bolachas de arroz; Produtos estaladiços feitos de cereais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ceai; Ceai rece; Cacao; Băuturi pe bază de cacao; Lapte (Cacao cu -); Cafea; Înlocuitori de cafea; Cafea (preparate vegetale care înlocuiesc -ua); Băuturi pe bază de cafea; Lapte (Cafea cu -); Ciocolată de băut; Băuturi pe bază de ceai (nemedicamentoase); Cafea verde; Cafea (preparate vegetale care înlocuiesc -ua); Batoane de cereale şi batoane energizante; Batoane dulci; Batoane de cereale bogate în proteine; Batoane pentru gustări conţinând un amestec de cereale, nuci şi fructe uscate [produse de cofetărie]; Fiind băuturi răcoritoare cu conţinut caloric redus; Dulciuri; Dulciuri; Produse de cofetărie nutritive; Bomboane cu ciocolată; Dulciuri; Torturi; Pişcoturi; Prăjiturici uscate [patiserie]; Napolitane; Dulciuri cu caramel; Biscuiţi; Produse de patiserie dulci şi sărate; Plăcinte; Cereale (prelucrate) cu conţinut mic de carbohidraţi; Cereale (Preparate din -); Produse de cofetărie cu conţinut mic de carbohidraţi; Amestecuri alimentare preparate cuprinse în această clasă; Extracte de cafea; Extracte de cafea artificială; Cicoare; Ceai; Extracte de ceai; Cacao şi înlocuitori pentru aceasta; Preparate sub forma de pudra continand cacao utilizate pentru prepararea bauturilor; Pudră de cacao; Tapioca; Torturi; Produse de ciocolată şi deserturi; Produse de ciocolată; Ciocolată tartinabilă; Ciocolată tartinabilă conţinând nuci; Deserturi reci; Deserturi gata preparate; Deserturi cu îngheţată; Îngheţată comestibilă; Cornete pentru îngheţată; Îngheţată de iaurt şi sorbete; Siropuri şi melasă; Miere; Zahăr; Gheaţă naturală sau artificială; Cereale prelucrate, amidon și produse fabricate din acestea; Preparate pentru copt precum drojdia; Pâine şi chifle; Produse de brutărie; Condimente; Pizza; Quiche [tarte sărate]; Preparate din produse apicole; Mâncăruri pe bază de orez; Biscuiţi de orez; Chipsuri din cereale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Čaj; Ľadový čaj; Kakao; Kakaové nápoje; Mliečne kakaové nápoje; Káva; Kávové náhradky; Kávové náhradky na báze rastlín; Kávové nápoje; Mliečne kávové nápoje; Čokoládové nápoje; Čajové nápoje; Nepražená káva; Rastlinné prípravky (kávové náhradky); Cereálne tyčinky a energetické tyčinky; Cukrovinky vo forme tyčiniek; Cereálne tyčinky s vysokým obsahom proteínov; Tyčinky obsahujúce zmes obilnín, orieškov a sušeného ovocia [cukrovinky]; V podobe koktailov s obmedzeným obsahom kalórií; Cukríky; Cukríky; Výživové cukrovinky; Čokolády; Cukríky; Jemné pečivárske výrobky; Sucháre; Keksy; Oblátky; Cukríky s karamelom; Biskvity; Sladké a slané pekárske výrobky; Plnené koláče; Obilniny (spracované) so zníženým obsahom uhľovodíkov; Obilniny (Prípravky z -); Sladkosti s nízkym obsahom uhľovodíkov; Hotové potravinové zmesi v rámci tejto triedy; Kávové výťažky; Výťažky z umelej kávy; Cigória; Čaj; Čajové výťažky; Kakao a náhradné látky pre ne; Práškové prípravky obsahujúce kakao na výrobu nápojov; Kakaový prášok; Tapioka; Jemné pečivárske výrobky; Čokolády a dezerty; Čokoládové výrobky; Čokoládové nátierky; Čokoládovo-orieškové nátierky; Chladené dezerty; Hotové dezerty; Zmrzlinové dezerty; Zmrzliny; Zmrzlinové kornútiky; Mrazené jogurty a vodová zmrzlina; Melasový sirup; Med; Cukor; Ľad (prírodný alebo umelý); Spracované obilie, škrob a výrobky z nich vyrobené; Prípravky na pečenie, kvasnice; Chlieb a žemle; Pekárske výrobky; Chuťové prísady; Pizza; Quiches (slaný koláč); Výrobky z včelích produktov; Jedlá na báze ryže; Ryžové sušienky; Cereálne lupienky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Čaj; Ledeni čaj; Kakav; Pijače na osnovi kakava; Kakavovi napitki z mlekom; Kava; Kavni nadomestki; Rastlinski preparati kot kavni nadomestki; Pijače na osnovi kave; Kavni napitki z mlekom; Pijače na bazi čokolade; Pijače na osnovi čaja (ne za medicinske namene); Kava, nepražena; Rastlinski preparati kot kavni nadomestki; Žitne ploščice in energijske ploščice; Slaščice v obliki ploščic; Žitne ploščice z veliko vsebnostjo beljakovin; Rezine za prigrizek, ki vsebujejo mešanico žitnih zrn, oreščkov in suhega sadja [slaščice]; Ki so smoothie napitki z zmanjšanim številom kalorij; Slaščice; Slaščice; Hranljive sladkarije; Čokolade; Slaščice; Testo za torte; Prepečenec; Čajno pecivo; Napolitanke; Karamelni bomboni; Piškoti; Sladko in slano pecivo; Pite; Žita (predelana) z znižano vsebnostjo ogljikovih hidratov; Proizvodi iz žitaric; Sladkarije z nizko vsebnostjo ogljikovih hidratov; Pripravljene mešanice hrane, ki jih obsega ta razred; Kavni ekstrakti; Ekstrakti za kavne nadomestke; Cikorija; Čaj; Čajni ekstrakti; Kakav in njegovi nadomestki; Pripravki v prahu s kakavom za proizvodnjo pijač; Kakav v prahu; Tapioka; Testo za torte; Čokolade in desertne ploščice; Čokoladni izdelki; Čokoladni namazi; Čokoladni namazi z oreščki; Ohlajeni deserti; Pripravljene sladice; Sladoledne sladice; Sladoled; Korneti za sladoled; Zamrznjeni jogurti in sorbeti; Sirupi, melasni sirupi; Med; Sladkor; Led, naraven ali umeten; Predelana žit, škrob in izdelki, pridobljeni iz njih; Pripravki za peko ter kvas; Kruh in pekovsko pecivo; Pekovski izdelki; Začimbni dodatki jedem (sol, kis, gorčica); Pice; Quiche (vrsta slane pite); Izdelki iz čebeljih proizvodov; Jedi na osnovi riža; Riževi piškoti; Hrustavci iz žitaric.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Te; Iste; Kakao; Kakaobaserade drycker; Kakaodrycker med mjölk; Kaffe; Kaffeersättning; Vegetabiliska preparat för användning som kaffeersättning; Kaffebaserade drycker; Kaffedrycker med mjölk; Chokladbaserade drycker; Te-baserade drycker; Orostat kaffe; Vegetabiliska preparat för användning som kaffeersättning; Spannmålskakor och energikakor; Godisbitar; Proteinrika spannmålsstänger; Snackstänger innehållande en blandning av spannmål, nötter och torkade frukter [godsaker]; Utgörande smoothies med reducerat kaloriinnehåll; Konfekt; Konfekt; Näringsgodsaker; Chokladprodukter; Konfekt; Kakdeg; Skorpor; Petits fours [bakverk]; Rån; Godis med kola; Biskvier; Sötade och saltade konditorivaror; Pajer; Spannmål (bearbetat) med sänkt innehåll av kalorier; Preparerade spannmålsprodukter; Godsaker med låg kalorihalt; Färdiga livsmedelsblandningar ingående i denna klass; Kaffeextrakt; Artificiellt kaffeextrakt; Cikoria; Te; Teextrakt; Kakao och ersättningsmaterial för detta; Pulverpreparat med innehåll av kakao för tillverkning av drycker; Kakaopulver; Tapioka; Kakdeg; Chokladprodukter och dessertbitar; Chokladprodukter; Bredbara chokladpålägg; Bredbara chokladpålägg med nötter; Kylda efterrätter; Tillagade desserter; Glassefterrätter; Glass; Strutar för glass; Yoghurtglass och sorbetglass; Sirap; Honung; Socker; Naturlig eller konstgjord is; Behandlat spannmål, stärkelse och produkter tillverkade av dessa; Preparat för bakning samt jäst; Bröd och bullar; Bagerivaror; Smaktillsatser (såser); Pizzor; Quiche (ostpaj); Varor av biprodukter; Risbaserade rätter; Kakor (Ris- -); Chips framställda av spannmål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>32</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Аперитиви, безалкохолни; Лимонади; Коктейли, безалкохолни; Квас [безалкохолни напитки]; Мъст; Безалкохолни напитки; Безалкохолни плодови напитки; Безалкохолни плодови екстракти; Нектари (Плодови -) [безалкохолни]; Есенции за приготвяне на напитки; Препарати за приготвяне на напитки; Газирана вода (Суровини за приготвяне на -); Сиропи за приготвяне на напитки; Сиропи за лимонади; Сода [газирана вода]; Трапезни минерални води; Шербети [напитки]; Газирана вода; Води [напитки]; Зеленчукови сокове [напитки]; Захарни сокове.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Aperitivy nealkoholické; citronády; koktejly nealkoholické; kvas (nealkoholické nápoje); mošty; nealkoholické nápoje; nealkoholické šťávy (nápoje z -); nealkoholické výtažky z ovoce; nektar (ovocný -) (nealkoholický); příchutě na výrobu nápojů; přípravky na výrobu nápojů; přípravky na výrobu sodovky; sirupy na výrobu nápojů; sirupy pro limonády; soda; stolové vody; šerbety (nápoje); šumivá voda; vody (nápoje); zeleninové šťávy (nápoje); cukerné šťávy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Aperitifs, ikke-alkoholholdige; Limonade; Cocktails, ikke-alkoholholdige; Kvass [ikke-alkoholholdige drikke]; Most; Ikke-alkoholholdige drikke; Ikke-alkoholiske frugtdrikke; Ikke-alkoholiske frugtekstrakter; Frugtnektar, ikke-alkoholholdig; Essenser til fremstilling af drikke; Præparater til fremstilling af drikke; Præparater til fremstilling af kulsyreholdige vande; Sukkerholdig saft [sirup] til drikke; Sukkerholdig frugtsaft [sirup] til limonade; Sodavand; Bordvande; Sorbets [drikke]; Kulsyreholdige vande; Vande [drikkevarer]; Grøntsagssafter [drikke]; Sukkersaft.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Aperitifs, alkoholfrei; Limonaden; Cocktails, alkoholfrei; Kwass [alkoholfreies Getränk]; Most [unvergoren]; Nichtalkoholische Getränke; Alkoholfreie Fruchtgetränke; Alkoholfreie Fruchtextrakte; Alkoholfreie Fruchtnektare; Essenzen für die Zubereitung von Getränken; Präparate für die Zubereitung von Getränken; Erzeugnisse zur Herstellung kohlensäurehaltiger Wässer; Sirupe für die Zubereitung von Getränken; Limonadensirupe; Sodawasser; Tafelwässer; Sorbets [Getränke]; Kohlensäurehaltige Wässer; Wässer [Getränke]; Gemüsesäfte [Getränke]; Zuckersäfte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Απεριτίφ μη οινοπνευματώδη· Λεμονάδες· Κοκταίηλ μη οινοπνευματώδη· Κβας [μη οινοπνευματώδες ποτό]· Μούστος· Μη αλκοολούχα ποτά· Μη αλκοολούχα μη αλκοολούχα φρούτων· Εκχυλίσματα φρούτων μη αλκοολούχα· Μη οινοπνευματώδη νέκταρ φρούτων· Ποτών (Εκχυλίσματα για την παραγωγή -)· Παρασκευάσματα ποτοποιίας· Ύδατα αεριούχα (προϊόντα παρασκευής -ων -ών)· Σιρόπια για την παρασκευή ποτών· Λεμονάδες (Σιρόπια για -)· Σόδα· Επιτραπέζιο ύδωρ· Γρανίτες [ποτά]· Ύδωρ αεριούχο· Ύδατα [ποτά]· Ποτά και χυμοί φρούτων, χυμοί λαχανικών· Χυμοί από ζάχαρη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Aperitifs, non-alcoholic; Lemonades; Cocktails, non-alcoholic; Kvass [non-alcoholic beverage]; Must; Non-alcoholic beverages; Non-alcoholic fruit juice beverages; Non-alcoholic fruit extracts; Fruit nectars, non-alcoholic; Essences for making beverages; Preparations for making beverages; Aerated water (Preparations for making -); Syrups for making beverages; Syrups for lemonade; Soda water; Table waters; Sherbets [beverages]; Aerated water; Waters [beverages]; Vegetable juices [beverages]; Sugar juices.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aperitivos sin alcohol; Limonadas; Cocteles sin alcohol; Kvas [bebida sin alcohol]; Mostos; Bebidas no alcohólicas; Bebidas de frutas sin alcohol; Extractos de frutas sin alcohol; Néctares de frutas sin alcohol; Esencias para elaborar bebidas; Preparados para la elaboración de bebidas; Productos para elaborar aguas gaseosas; Siropes para elaborar bebidas; Limonadas (Siropes para -); Sodas [aguas]; Aguas de mesa; Sorbetes [bebidas]; Aguas gaseosas; Aguas [bebidas]; Zumos vegetales [bebidas]; Siropes de azúcar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Aperitiivid (Alkoholivabad); Limonaadid; Kokteilid (Alkoholivabad); Kali [alkoholivaba jook]; Veinivirre; Alkoholivabad joogid; Alkoholivabad puuviljamahlajoogid; Alkoholivabad puuviljaekstraktid; Alkoholivabad puuviljanektarid; Essentsid (Joogi -), joogiessentsid; Joogivalmistuspreparaadid; Gaseerveevalmistusained; Siirupid jookide valmistamiseks; Siirupid (Limonaadi -), limonaadisiirupid; Soodavesi; Lauaveed; Šerbett [jook]; Gaseeritud vesi, gaseervesi; Veed [joogid]; Köögiviljamahlad [joogid]; Suhkrumahlad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Aperitiivit, alkoholittomat; Limonadit; Cocktailit, alkoholittomat; Kvassi [alkoholiton juoma]; Rypälemehu; Alkoholittomat juomat; Alkoholittomat hedelmämehujuomat; Alkoholittomat hedelmäuutteet; Nektarit (hedelmä -) [alkoholittomat]; Uutteet juomien valmistukseen; Juomien valmistusaineet; Hiilihappoveden valmistukseen käytettävät aineet; Siirappi juomien valmistukseen; Siirappi limonadin valmistukseen; Soodavesi; Pöytävedet; Kylmämehujuomat [sorbetit]; Hiilihappovesi; Vedet [juomina]; Vihannesmehut (juomat); Sokerimehu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Apéritifs sans alcool; Limonades; Cocktails sans alcool; Kwas [boisson sans alcool]; Moûts; Boissons sans alcool; Boissons de fruits sans alcool; Extraits de fruits sans alcool; Nectars de fruits; Essences pour la préparation de boissons; Préparations pour faire des boissons; Produits pour la fabrication des eaux gazeuses; Sirops pour la fabrication de boissons; Sirops pour limonades; Sodas; Eaux de table; Sorbets [boissons]; Eaux gazeuses; Eaux [boissons]; Jus végétaux [boissons]; Jus de betterave sucrière.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Aperitivi bez alkohola; Limunade; Kokteli bez alkohola; Kvas [bezalkoholno piće]; Mošt; Bezalkoholna pića; Voćni napici bez alkohola; Bezalkoholni voćni ekstrakti; Voćni nektar, bezalkoholni; Ekstrakti [koncentrati] za pripremu napitaka; Pripravci za pripremu pića; Proizvodi za pripremanje gazirane vode; Sirup za pripremu napitaka; Limunada (sirup za limunadu); Soda-voda; Stolna voda [voda za piće]; Šerbeti [slatki napitci]; Gazirane vode; Voda za piće; Povrtni sokovi (napitci); Šećerni sok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Alkoholmentes aperitifek; Limonádék; Alkoholmentes koktélok; Kvasz [alkoholmentes ital]; Mustok; Alkoholmentes italok; Alkoholmentes gyümölcsitalok; Alkoholmentes gyümölcskivonatok; Gyümölcsnektárok, alkoholmentes; Eszenciák italok előállításához; Készítmények italokhoz; Termékek szénsavas vizek előállításához; Szörpök/szirupok italok készítéséhez; Szörpök limonádékhoz; Szódavizek; Ásványvizek; Sörbetek [italok]; Szénsavas italok; Vizek [italok]; Zöldséglevek [italok]; Cukorszirupok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Aperitivi analcolici; Limonate; Cocktails analcolici; Kvas [bevande non alcooliche]; Mosti; Bevande non alcoliche; Bevande di frutta non alcooliche; Estratti di frutta senza alcool; Nettari di frutta; Essenze per la preparazione di bevande; Preparati per fare bevande; Prodotti per la fabbricazione di acque gassate; Sciroppi per la preparazione di bevande; Sciroppi per limonate; Sode; Acque da tavola; Sorbetti [bevande]; Acque gassate; Acque [bevande]; Succhi vegetali [bevande]; Succhi zuccherini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Aperityvai (Gaivieji -); Limonadai; Kokteiliai (Gaivieji -); Gira [gaivusis gėrimas]; Misa; Gaivieji gėrimai; Gaivieji vaisių sulčių gėrimai; Gaivieji vaisių ekstraktai; Vaisių nektarai [gaivieji]; Esencijos (gėrimams gaminti); Gėrimų gaminimo preparatai; Gazuoto vandens gaminimo preparatai; Sirupai gėrimams gaminti; Sirupai (limonadui); Sodos vanduo; Geriamas vanduo (buteliuose); Šerbetas [gėrimas]; Gazuotas vanduo; Vandenys [gėrimai]; Daržovių sultys [gėrimai]; Cukrinių runkelių sultys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Bezalkoholiskie aperitīvi; Limonāde; Bezalkoholiskie kokteiļi; Kvass [bezalkoholisks dzēriens]; Nenorūdzis vīnogu vīns; Bezalkoholiskie dzērieni; Bezalkoholiskie augļu sulas dzērieni; Bezalkoholiskie augļu ekstrakti; Bezalkoholiskie augļu nektāri; Ekstrakti dzērienu pagatavošanai; Sastāvdaļas dzērienu pagatavošanai; Sastāvdaļas gāzēta ūdens pagatavošanai; Sīrupi dzērienu pagatavošanai; Limonāžu sīrupi; Gāzēts ūdens; Galda ūdens; Šerbeti [dzērieni]; Gāzēti ūdeņi; Dzeramais ūdens; Dārzeņu sulas [dzērieni]; Cukura jēlsula.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Aperittivi mingħajr alkoħol; Luminati; Koktejls, mhux alkoħoliċi; Kvass [xarba mhux alkoħolika]; Għeneb magħsur; Xarbiet mhux alkoħoliċi; Xorb mhux alkoħoliku magħmul mill-meraq tal-frott; Estratti tal-frott mhux alkoħoliċi; Nettari tal-frott (mingħajr alkoħol); Essenza għat-tħejjija tax-xorb; Preparazzjonijiet biex isiru x-xarbiet; Ilma effervexxenti (Preparazzjonijiet għall-għamla ta' -); Ġulepp għall-produzzjoni ta' xarbiet; Xroppi għal-luminata; Ilma tat-tip soda; Ilma tal-mejda; Xorb ħelu fexfiexi [xorb]; Ilma effervexxenti; Ilma [xorb]; Meraq tal-ħaxix (xarbiet); Xropp taz-zokkor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Aperitieven zonder alcohol; Limonades; Cocktails zonder alcohol; Kwass [niet-alcoholische drank]; Most; Niet-alcoholische dranken; Alcoholvrije vruchtendranken; Alcoholvrije vruchtenextracten; Vruchtennectar; Essences voor de bereiding van dranken; Preparaten voor het bereiden van dranken; Producten voor het bereiden van spuitwater; Siropen voor de bereiding van dranken; Limonadesiropen; Priklimonade; Tafelwater; Sorbets [dranken]; Spuitwater; Waters [dranken]; Groentensappen [dranken]; Suikerrietsappen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Aperitify bezalkoholowe; Lemoniada; Koktajle bezalkoholowe; Kwas chlebowy [napoje bezalkoholowe]; Moszcz; Napoje bezalkoholowe; Napoje owocowe (Bezalkoholowe -); Bezalkoholowe wyciągi z owoców; Owocowe nektary, bezalkoholowe; Esencje do produkcji napojów; Preparaty do produkcji napojów; Woda gazowana (Preparaty do produkcji -); Syropy do wyrobu napojów; Lemoniady (Syropy do -); Woda sodowa; Woda stołowa; Sorbety [napoje]; Woda gazowana; Woda [napoje]; Soki warzywne [napoje]; Sok cukrowy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aperitivos sem álcool; Limonadas; Cocktails sem álcool; Kvas [bebidas sem alcoól]; Mostos; Bebidas sem álcool; Bebidas de frutas, não alcoólicas; Extratos de frutos sem álcool; Néctares de frutas, sem alcoól; Essências para a preparação de bebidas; Preparações para fazer bebidas; Preparações para o fabrico de àguas gasosas; Xarope para fazer bebidas; Xaropes para limonada; Sodas [águas]; Àguas de mesa; Refrescos à base de sumos de frutas [Sherbets]; Águas gasosas; Águas [bebidas]; Sumos vegetais [bebidas]; Sumos de açúcares.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aperitive fără alcool; Limonade; Cocteiluri fără alcool; Kvass [băutură non-alcoolică]; Musturi; Băuturi nealcoolice; Fructe (băuturi din -, fără alcool); Extracte din fructe fără alcool; Nectaruri de fructe, nealcoolice; Esenţe pentru fabricarea băuturilor; Băuturi [preparate pentru fabricarea -lor]; Sifon (Produse pentru fabricarea de -); Siropuri pentru prepararea băuturilor; Limonade (Siropuri pentru -); Sifon; Apă de masă; Sorbeturi [băuturi]; Apă gazoasă [sifon]; Apă [băuturi]; Sucuri de legume [băuturi]; Sucuri de zahăr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Aperitív (Nealkoholický -); Citronády; Koktail (Nealkoholický -); Kvas [nealkoholický nápoj]; Mušty; Nealkoholické nápoje; Nealkoholické ovocné nápoje; Nealkoholické ovocné výťažky; Ovocné nektáre; Príchute na výrobu nápojov; Prípravky na výrobu nápojov; Prípravky na výrobu sýtenej vody; Sirupy na výrobu nápojov; Sirupy na výrobu limonád; Sóda; Stolové vody; Šerbety [ovocné nápoje]; Sýtené vody; Vody (nápoje); Zeleninové džúsy (nápoje); Cukrové šťavy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Aperitivi, brezalkoholni; Limonade; Koktajli, brezalkoholni; Rženo žganje (kvass - nealkoholna pijača); Mošt; Brezalkoholne pijače; Nealkoholne pijače iz sadnih sokov; Nealkoholni sadni ekstrakti; Sadni nektar (brezalkoholni); Esence za izdelavo pijač; Preparati za izdelavo pijač; Gazirana voda, pripravki za izdelavo; Sirupi za proizvodnjo pijač; Sirupi za limonado; Sodavica; Namizne vode; Šerbeti [osvežujoča orientalska pijača iz razredčenega soka, sladkorja in dišav]; Gazirana voda; Vode [pijače]; Zelenjavni sokovi [pijače]; Sladkorni sokovi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Icke alkoholhaltiga aperitifer; Lemonad; Icke alkoholhaltiga cocktailar; Kvass [icke alkoholhaltiga drycker]; Muster; Icke alkoholhaltiga drycker; Icke-alkoholhaltiga fruktdrycker; Icke-alkoholhaltiga fruktextrakt; Nektar (frukt- -) [icke-alkoholhaltig]; Essenser för tillverkning av drycker; Preparat för tillverkning av drycker; Preparat för tillverkning av kolsyrat vatten; Koncentrat för framställning av drycker; Koncentrat för framställning av läskedrycker; Sodavatten; Bordsvatten; Sorbet [dryck]; Kolsyrat vatten; Vatten [dryck]; Grönsakssafter [drycker]; Sockersafter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Реклама и пазарна реализация; Рекламни и промоционални услуги, свързани с търговия, предоставяна онлайн по интернет; Демонстриране на стоки по интернет; Посредническа дейност в областта на търговията с чай, Чаени екстракти, Кафе, Напитки (на основата на какао), Хранителни добавки, Стикове, Енергийни и протеинови блокчета, Захарни изделия, Шоколадови изделия, Карамелени бонбони, Бисквити, Сухари, Вафли, Бонбони, Бисквити, Сладки и солени тестени продукти, Овкусители за приготвяне на напитки и Препарати за приготвяне на напитки, Плодови пити, пайове, Пасти, Шоколадови изделия, Хранителни продукти с пастообразна консистенция, Сладоледени десерти, Сладоледени сладкарски изделия, Замразени йогурти и сорбета, Мед,захарен петмез, Сладкарски изделия, Лед и Хляб; Посредническа дейност в областта на сладкарската търговия, Пекарски изделия, Подправки, Пици, Кишове, Изделия от пчелни продукти, Оризови ястия, Оризови бисквити и зърнен чипс; Търговия на дребно, на едро с чай, Чаени екстракти, Кафе, Напитки (на основата на какао), Хранителни добавки, Стикове, Енергийни и протеинови блокчета, Захарни изделия, Шоколадови изделия, Карамелени бонбони, Бисквити, Сухари, Вафли, Бонбони, Бисквити, Сладки и солени тестени продукти, Овкусители за приготвяне на напитки и Препарати за приготвяне на напитки, Плодови пити, пайове, Пасти, Шоколадови изделия, Хранителни продукти с пастообразна консистенция, Сладоледени десерти, Сладоледени сладкарски изделия, Замразени йогурти и сорбета, Мед,захарен петмез, Сладкарски изделия, Лед, Хляб и Сладкарски; Продажба на дребно и едро на хлебни изделия, Подправки, Пици, Кишове, Изделия от пчелни продукти, Оризови ястия, Оризови бисквити и зърнен чипс; Износ-внос на чай, Чаени екстракти, Кафе, Напитки (на основата на какао), Хранителни добавки, Стикове, Енергийни и протеинови блокчета, Захарни изделия, Шоколадови изделия, Карамелени бонбони, Бисквити, Сухари, Вафли, Бонбони, Бисквити, Сладки и солени тестени продукти, Овкусители за приготвяне на напитки и Препарати за приготвяне на напитки, Плодови пити, пайове, Пасти, Шоколадови изделия, Хранителни продукти с пастообразна консистенция, Сладоледени десерти, Сладоледени сладкарски изделия, Замразени йогурти и сорбета, Мед,захарен петмез, Сладкарски изделия, Лед, Хляб, Сладкиши и хлебни изделия; Износ-внос на ароматизанти, Пици, Кишове, Изделия от пчелни продукти, Оризови ястия, Оризови бисквити и зърнен чипс; Интернет търговия (електронен магазин) с чай, Чаени екстракти, Кафе, Напитки (на основата на какао), Хранителни добавки, Стикове, Енергийни и протеинови блокчета, Захарни изделия, Шоколадови изделия, Карамелени бонбони, Бисквити, Сухари, Вафли, Бонбони, Бисквити, Сладки и солени тестени продукти, Овкусители за приготвяне на напитки и Препарати за приготвяне на напитки, Плодови пити, пайове, Пасти, Шоколадови изделия, Хранителни продукти с пастообразна консистенция, Сладоледени десерти, Сладоледени сладкарски изделия, Замразени йогурти и сорбета, Мед,захарен петмез, Сладкарски изделия, Лед, Хляб, Сладкарски; Интернет търговия (електронен магазин) с хлебни изделия, Подправки, Пици, Кишове, Изделия от пчелни продукти, Оризови ястия, Оризови бисквити и зърнен чипс; Телевизионен маркетинг (услуги за телепродажби) с чай, Чаени екстракти, Кафе, Напитки (на основата на какао), Хранителни добавки, Стикове, Енергийни и протеинови блокчета, Захарни изделия, Шоколадови изделия, Карамелени бонбони, Бисквити, Сухари, Вафли, Бонбони, Бисквити, Сладки и солени тестени продукти, Овкусители за приготвяне на напитки и Препарати за приготвяне на напитки, Плодови пити, пайове, Пасти, Шоколадови изделия, Хранителни продукти с пастообразна консистенция, Сладоледени десерти, Сладоледени сладкарски изделия, Замразени йогурти и сорбета, Мед,захарен петмез, Сладкарски изделия, Лед, Хляб и Сладкарски; Телемаркетинг (продажба по телефон) с хлебни изделия, Подправки, Пици, Кишове, Изделия от пчелни продукти, Оризови ястия, Оризови бисквити и зърнен чипс; Продажба на стоки за трети лица с чай, Чаени екстракти, Кафе, Напитки (на основата на какао), Хранителни добавки, Стикове, Енергийни и протеинови блокчета, Захарни изделия, Шоколадови изделия, Карамелени бонбони, Бисквити, Сухари, Вафли, Бонбони, Бисквити, Сладки и солени тестени продукти, Овкусители за приготвяне на напитки и Препарати за приготвяне на напитки, Плодови пити, пайове, Пасти, Шоколадови изделия, Хранителни продукти с пастообразна консистенция, Сладоледени десерти, Сладоледени сладкарски изделия, Замразени йогурти и сорбета, Мед,захарен петмез, Сладкарски изделия, Лед, Хляб и Сладкарски; Продажба на стоки на трети лица с хлебни изделия, Подправки, Пици, Кишове, Изделия от пчелни продукти, Оризови ястия, Оризови бисквити и зърнен чипс; Маркетингови услуги; Разпространение (дистрибуция) на рекламни мостри; Представяне на стоки; Акции за намаления; Реклама; Пропаганда и агитация посредством всякакви видове медии; Изследване и анализ на пазара; КОНСУЛТАНТСКА ДЕЙНОСТ; Прилагане на система за подпомагане на продажби на дребно, основаваща се на преференции за редовни клиенти; Търговски услуги за програма за лоялни клиенти с нарастване; Търговски мениджмънт; Търговска администрация; Търговско управление и администрация; Онлайн реклама; Рекламни услуги; Представяне на бизнес; Услуги за художествено оформление за рекламни цели; Промоционални маркетингови услуги чрез използването на аудиовизуални медии; Маркетинг по интернет; Разпространение на реклами чрез интернет; Рекламни услуги, предоставяни чрез интернет; Отдаване под наем на рекламно пространство в интернет; Реклама в Интернет за трети лица; Разпространяване на реклама за други лица по интернет; Рекламиране на стоки и услуги на други чрез интернет; Разпространение на реклами; Разпространяване на рекламни материали онлайн; Онлайн рекламни и маркетингови услуги; Рекламиране, включително онлайн рекламиране в компютърна мрежа.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Propagační činnost a reklama; inzertní a propagační služby tykající se obchodu poskytované on-line z internetu; předvádění zboží prostřednictvím Internetu; zprostředkovatelská činnost v oblasti obchodu s čaji, čajovými extrakty, kávou, kakaem, nápoji, potravinovými doplňky, tyčinkami, energetickými a proteinovými tyčinkami, cukrovinkami, čokoládami, bonbóny, sušenkami, suchary, oplatky, karamely, biskvity, sladkým a slaným pečivem, příchutěmi na výrobu nápojů a přípravky na výrobu nápojů, dorty, zákusky, čokoládovými výrobky, pomazánkami, dezerty, zmrzlinou, kornoutky na zmrzliny, mraženými jogurty a sorbety, sirupy, melasou, medem, cukrem, ledem a chlebem; zprostředkovatelská činnost v oblasti obchodu s pečivem, pekárenskými výrobky, chuťovými přísadami, pizzou, quichem, výrobky z včelích produktů, rýžovými pokrmy, rýžovými sušenkami a cereálními lupínky; maloobchod-velkoobchod s čaji, čajovými extrakty, kávou, kakaem, nápoji, potravinovými doplňky, tyčinkami, energetickými a proteinovými tyčinkami, cukrovinkami, čokoládami, bonbóny, sušenkami, suchary, oplatky, karamely, biskvity, sladkým a slaným pečivem, příchutěmi na výrobu nápojů a přípravky na výrobu nápojů, dorty, zákusky, čokoládovými výrobky, pomazánkami, dezerty, zmrzlinou, kornoutky na zmrzliny, mraženými jogurty a sorbety, sirupy, melasou, medem, cukrem, ledem, chlebem a pečivem; maloobchod-velkoobchod s pekárenskými výrobky, chuťovými přísadami, pizzou, quichem, výrobky z včelích produktů, rýžovými pokrmy, rýžovými sušenkami a cereálními lupínky; export-import s čaji, čajovými extrakty, kávou, kakaem, nápoji, potravinovými doplňky, tyčinkami, energetickými a proteinovými tyčinkami, cukrovinkami, čokoládami, bonbóny, sušenkami, suchary, oplatky, karamely, biskvity, sladkým a slaným pečivem, příchutěmi na výrobu nápojů a přípravky na výrobu nápojů, dorty, zákusky, čokoládovými výrobky, pomazánkami, dezerty, zmrzlinou, kornoutky na zmrzliny, mraženými jogurty a sorbety, sirupy, melasou, medem, cukrem, ledem, chlebem, pečivem a pekárenskými výrobky; export-import s chuťovými přísadami, pizzou, quichem, výrobky z včelích produktů, rýžovými pokrmy, rýžovými sušenkami a cereálními lupínky; internetový obchod (e-shop) s čaji, čajovými extrakty, kávou, kakaem, nápoji, potravinovými doplňky, tyčinkami, energetickými a proteinovými tyčinkami, cukrovinkami, čokoládami, bonbóny, sušenkami, suchary, oplatky, karamely, biskvity, sladkým a slaným pečivem, příchutěmi na výrobu nápojů a přípravky na výrobu nápojů, dorty, zákusky, čokoládovými výrobky, pomazánkami, dezerty, zmrzlinou, kornoutky na zmrzliny, mraženými jogurty a sorbety, sirupy, melasou, medem, cukrem,ledem, chlebem, pečivem; internetový obchod (e-shop) s pekárenskými výrobky, chuťovými přísadami, pizzou, quichem, výrobky z včelích produktů, rýžovými pokrmy, rýžovými sušenkami a cereálními lupínky; telemarketing (prodej po telefonu) s čaji, čajovými extrakty, kávou, kakaem, nápoji, potravinovými doplňky, tyčinkami, energetickými a proteinovými tyčinkami, cukrovinkami, čokoládami, bonbóny, sušenkami, suchary, oplatky, karamely, biskvity, sladkým a slaným pečivem, příchutěmi na výrobu nápojů a přípravky na výrobu nápojů, dorty, zákusky, čokoládovými výrobky, pomazánkami, dezerty, zmrzlinou, kornoutky na zmrzliny, mraženými jogurty a sorbety, sirupy, melasou, medem, cukrem, ledem, chlebem a pečivem; telemarketing (prodej po telefonu) s pekárenskými výrobky, chuťovými přísadami, pizzou, quichem, výrobky z včelích produktů, rýžovými pokrmy, rýžovými sušenkami a cereálními lupínky; prodej zboží pro třetí osoby s čaji, čajovými extrakty, kávou, kakaem, nápoji, potravinovými doplňky, tyčinkami, energetickými a proteinovými tyčinkami, cukrovinkami, čokoládami, bonbóny, sušenkami, suchary, oplatky, karamely, biskvity, sladkým a slaným pečivem, příchutěmi na výrobu nápojů a přípravky na výrobu nápojů, dorty, zákusky, čokoládovými výrobky, pomazánkami, dezerty, zmrzlinou, kornoutky na zmrzliny, mraženými jogurty a sorbety, sirupy, melasou, medem, cukrem, ledem, chlebem a pečivem; prodej zboží pro třetí osoby s pekárenskými výrobky, chuťovými přísadami, pizzou, quichem, výrobky z včelích produktů, rýžovými pokrmy, rýžovými sušenkami a cereálními lupínky; marketing; šíření a distribuce vzorků a reklamních předmětů; předvádění zboží; slevové akce; reklama; propagace a inzerce všemi druhy médií; průzkum a analýza trhů; konzultační činnost; uplatňování systému na podporu maloobchodního prodeje založeného na zvýhodnění stálých zákazníků; obchodní služby nadstavbového věrnostního zákaznického programu; řízení obchodní činnosti; obchodní administrativa; řízení obchodní činnosti a obchodní administrativa; reklama on-line; reklamní a inzertní služby; obchodní propagace; grafická úprava pro reklamní účely; propagační marketingové služby využívající audiovizuální média; internetový marketing; šíření reklamy prostřednictvím internetu; reklamní služby poskytované přes internet; pronájem reklamního prostoru na internetu; reklama na internetu pro třetí osoby; rozšiřování reklamy pro třetí osoby prostřednictvím internetu; propagace zboží a služeb pro třetí osoby prostřednictvím internetu; šíření reklam; šíření reklamních materiálů on-line; on-line reklamní a marketingové služby; reklama, včetně online reklamy na počítačové síti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Salgsfremmende virksomhed og markedsføring; Annoncering og promovering vedrørende handel leveret online via internettet; Internetbaseret varedemonstration; Mæglervirksomhed inden for handel med te, Teekstrakter, Kaffe, Drikke (fremstillet på basis af kakao), Næringsmiddeltilskud, Pinde, Energi- og proteinbarer, Slik, sukkervarer, konfekt, Chokoladevarer, Slik, Kiks, Ristet brød, Vafler, Slik, Biscuits [søde kiks og småkager], Sødt og salt bagværk, Smagstilsætninger til fremstilling af drikke og Præparater til fremstilling af drikke, Tærter, Konditorkager, Chokoladeprodukter, Smørepålæg, Isdesserter, Isvafler, Frossen yoghurt og sorbet, Honning, sirup, Konfekturevarer, Is og Brød; Mæglervirksomhed inden for handel med bagværk, Bagerivarer, Smagstilsætninger, Pizzaer, Quiches (tærter), Varer fremstillet af produkter fra bier, Næringsmidler på basis af ris, Riskiks og chips fremstillet af korn; Detailhandel og engroshandel med te, Teekstrakter, Kaffe, Drikke (fremstillet på basis af kakao), Næringsmiddeltilskud, Pinde, Energi- og proteinbarer, Slik, sukkervarer, konfekt, Chokoladevarer, Slik, Kiks, Ristet brød, Vafler, Slik, Biscuits [søde kiks og småkager], Sødt og salt bagværk, Smagstilsætninger til fremstilling af drikke og Præparater til fremstilling af drikke, Tærter, Konditorkager, Chokoladeprodukter, Smørepålæg, Isdesserter, Isvafler, Frossen yoghurt og sorbet, Honning, sirup, Konfekturevarer, Is, Brød og Konditorivarer; Detail- og engroshandel med bagervarer, Smagstilsætninger, Pizzaer, Quiches (tærter), Varer fremstillet af produkter fra bier, Næringsmidler på basis af ris, Riskiks og chips fremstillet af korn; Eksport og import af te, Teekstrakter, Kaffe, Drikke (fremstillet på basis af kakao), Næringsmiddeltilskud, Pinde, Energi- og proteinbarer, Slik, sukkervarer, konfekt, Chokoladevarer, Slik, Kiks, Ristet brød, Vafler, Slik, Biscuits [søde kiks og småkager], Sødt og salt bagværk, Smagstilsætninger til fremstilling af drikke og Præparater til fremstilling af drikke, Tærter, Konditorkager, Chokoladeprodukter, Smørepålæg, Isdesserter, Isvafler, Frossen yoghurt og sorbet, Honning, sirup, Konfekturevarer, Is, Brød, Bagværk og bagervarer; Import og eksport af smagstilsætningsstoffer, Pizzaer, Quiches (tærter), Varer fremstillet af produkter fra bier, Næringsmidler på basis af ris, Riskiks og chips fremstillet af korn; Internetbutik med te, Teekstrakter, Kaffe, Drikke (fremstillet på basis af kakao), Næringsmiddeltilskud, Pinde, Energi- og proteinbarer, Slik, sukkervarer, konfekt, Chokoladevarer, Slik, Kiks, Ristet brød, Vafler, Slik, Biscuits [søde kiks og småkager], Sødt og salt bagværk, Smagstilsætninger til fremstilling af drikke og Præparater til fremstilling af drikke, Tærter, Konditorkager, Chokoladeprodukter, Smørepålæg, Isdesserter, Isvafler, Frossen yoghurt og sorbet, Honning, sirup, Konfekturevarer, Is, Brød, Konditorivarer; Internetbutik med bagervarer, Smagstilsætninger, Pizzaer, Quiches (tærter), Varer fremstillet af produkter fra bier, Næringsmidler på basis af ris, Riskiks og chips fremstillet af korn; Telemarketing (telefonsalg) vedrørende te, Teekstrakter, Kaffe, Drikke (fremstillet på basis af kakao), Næringsmiddeltilskud, Pinde, Energi- og proteinbarer, Slik, sukkervarer, konfekt, Chokoladevarer, Slik, Kiks, Ristet brød, Vafler, Slik, Biscuits [søde kiks og småkager], Sødt og salt bagværk, Smagstilsætninger til fremstilling af drikke og Præparater til fremstilling af drikke, Tærter, Konditorkager, Chokoladeprodukter, Smørepålæg, Isdesserter, Isvafler, Frossen yoghurt og sorbet, Honning, sirup, Konfekturevarer, Is, Brød og Konditorivarer; Telemarketing (telefonsalg) vedrørende bagervarer, Smagstilsætninger, Pizzaer, Quiches (tærter), Varer fremstillet af produkter fra bier, Næringsmidler på basis af ris, Riskiks og chips fremstillet af korn; Salg af te for tredjepart, Teekstrakter, Kaffe, Drikke (fremstillet på basis af kakao), Næringsmiddeltilskud, Pinde, Energi- og proteinbarer, Slik, sukkervarer, konfekt, Chokoladevarer, Slik, Kiks, Ristet brød, Vafler, Slik, Biscuits [søde kiks og småkager], Sødt og salt bagværk, Smagstilsætninger til fremstilling af drikke og Præparater til fremstilling af drikke, Tærter, Konditorkager, Chokoladeprodukter, Smørepålæg, Isdesserter, Isvafler, Frossen yoghurt og sorbet, Honning, sirup, Konfekturevarer, Is, Brød og Konditorivarer; Salg af varer for tredjepart i forbindelse med bagervarer, Smagstilsætninger, Pizzaer, Quiches (tærter), Varer fremstillet af produkter fra bier, Næringsmidler på basis af ris, Riskiks og chips fremstillet af korn; Marketing; Uddeling af vareprøver; Demonstration af varer; Rabattilbud; Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed; Markedsføring og annoncering via alle slags medier; Markedsundersøgelser og -analyser; Konsulentvirksomhed; Implementering af systemer til fremme af detailhandel på basis af fordele til faste kunder; Kommercielle tjenesteydelser vedrørende overordnede kundeloyalitetsordninger; Kommerciel ledelse; Forretningsadministration; Bistand ved forretningsledelse og forretningsadministration; Online reklame; Reklameservice; Forretningsmæssig promovering; Layout til reklamemæssige formål; Salgsfremmende markedsføringstjenester ved brug af audiovisuelle medier; Markedsføring via internettet; Spredning af reklamer via internettet; Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed tilvejebragt via internettet; Udlejning af reklameplads på internettet; Annonce- og reklamevirksomhed på internettet for andre; Reklameomdeling for andre via internettet; Markedsføring af produkter og tjenesteydelser for andre på internettet; Udsendelse af reklamer og annoncer; Online uddeling af reklamemateriale; Onlinereklame og -markedsføring; Reklame- og annoncevirksomhed, herunder online reklamevirksomhed på et computernetværk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Verkaufsförderung und Merchandising; Online-Werbung über das Internet in Bezug auf Handel; Präsentation von Waren im Internet; Vermittlungsdienste in Bezug auf den Handel mit Tee, Mit Teeextrakten, Von Kaffee, Getränke (auf Kakao basierend), Ernährungsergänzungen, Stiele, Mit Energie- und Proteinriegeln, Süßwaren, Zuckerwaren, Konfekt, Schokoladewaren, Bonbons, Butterkekse, Zwieback, Oblaten, Bonbons, Biskuits, Mit süßem und pikantem Gebäck, Mit Aromawürzstoffen zur Verwendung bei der Zubereitung von Getränken und Präparate für die Zubereitung von Getränken, Torten, Patisserie, Mit Waren aus Schokolade, Brotauftstriche, Eisdesserts, Waffeltüten für Eiscreme, Mit gefrorenem Jogurt und Sorbets, Honig, Melassesirup, Zuckerwaren, Mit Kühleis und Brot; Vermittlungsdienste in Bezug auf den Handel mit Gebäck, Mit Backwaren, Mit Gewürzmischungen, Pizzas, Mit Quiches, Waren aus Bienenprodukten, Mit Reisgerichten, Mit Reisplätzchen und Chips aus Getreide; Einzelhandels- und Großhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Tee, Mit Teeextrakten, Von Kaffee, Getränke (auf Kakao basierend), Ernährungsergänzungen, Stiele, Mit Energie- und Proteinriegeln, Süßwaren, Zuckerwaren, Konfekt, Schokoladewaren, Bonbons, Butterkekse, Zwieback, Oblaten, Bonbons, Biskuits, Mit süßem und pikantem Gebäck, Mit Aromawürzstoffen zur Verwendung bei der Zubereitung von Getränken und Präparate für die Zubereitung von Getränken, Torten, Patisserie, Mit Waren aus Schokolade, Brotauftstriche, Eisdesserts, Waffeltüten für Eiscreme, Mit gefrorenem Jogurt und Sorbets, Honig, Melassesirup, Zuckerwaren, Mit Kühleis, Brot und Feine Back-; Einzel- und Großhandelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf Backwaren, Mit Gewürzmischungen, Pizzas, Mit Quiches, Waren aus Bienenprodukten, Mit Reisgerichten, Mit Reisplätzchen und Chips aus Getreide; Export- und Importdienste in Bezug auf Tee, Mit Teeextrakten, Von Kaffee, Getränke (auf Kakao basierend), Ernährungsergänzungen, Stiele, Mit Energie- und Proteinriegeln, Süßwaren, Zuckerwaren, Konfekt, Schokoladewaren, Bonbons, Butterkekse, Zwieback, Oblaten, Bonbons, Biskuits, Mit süßem und pikantem Gebäck, Mit Aromawürzstoffen zur Verwendung bei der Zubereitung von Getränken und Präparate für die Zubereitung von Getränken, Torten, Patisserie, Mit Waren aus Schokolade, Brotauftstriche, Eisdesserts, Waffeltüten für Eiscreme, Mit gefrorenem Jogurt und Sorbets, Honig, Melassesirup, Zuckerwaren, Mit Kühleis, Brot, Gebäck und Backwaren; Export- und Importdienste in Bezug auf Gewürzmischungen, Pizzas, Mit Quiches, Waren aus Bienenprodukten, Mit Reisgerichten, Mit Reisplätzchen und Chips aus Getreide; Internethandel (E-Shop) in Bezug auf Tee, Mit Teeextrakten, Von Kaffee, Getränke (auf Kakao basierend), Ernährungsergänzungen, Stiele, Mit Energie- und Proteinriegeln, Süßwaren, Zuckerwaren, Konfekt, Schokoladewaren, Bonbons, Butterkekse, Zwieback, Oblaten, Bonbons, Biskuits, Mit süßem und pikantem Gebäck, Mit Aromawürzstoffen zur Verwendung bei der Zubereitung von Getränken und Präparate für die Zubereitung von Getränken, Torten, Patisserie, Mit Waren aus Schokolade, Brotauftstriche, Eisdesserts, Waffeltüten für Eiscreme, Mit gefrorenem Jogurt und Sorbets, Honig, Melassesirup, Zuckerwaren, Mit Kühleis, Brot, Feine Back-; Internethandel (E-Shop) in Bezug auf Backwaren, Mit Gewürzmischungen, Pizzas, Mit Quiches, Waren aus Bienenprodukten, Mit Reisgerichten, Mit Reisplätzchen und Chips aus Getreide; Telemarketing (Telefonverkauf) in Bezug auf Tee, Mit Teeextrakten, Von Kaffee, Getränke (auf Kakao basierend), Ernährungsergänzungen, Stiele, Mit Energie- und Proteinriegeln, Süßwaren, Zuckerwaren, Konfekt, Schokoladewaren, Bonbons, Butterkekse, Zwieback, Oblaten, Bonbons, Biskuits, Mit süßem und pikantem Gebäck, Mit Aromawürzstoffen zur Verwendung bei der Zubereitung von Getränken und Präparate für die Zubereitung von Getränken, Torten, Patisserie, Mit Waren aus Schokolade, Brotauftstriche, Eisdesserts, Waffeltüten für Eiscreme, Mit gefrorenem Jogurt und Sorbets, Honig, Melassesirup, Zuckerwaren, Mit Kühleis, Brot und Feine Back-; Telemarketing (Telefonverkauf) in Bezug auf Backwaren, Mit Gewürzmischungen, Pizzas, Mit Quiches, Waren aus Bienenprodukten, Mit Reisgerichten, Mit Reisplätzchen und Chips aus Getreide; Verkauf von Waren für Dritte in Bezug auf Tee, Mit Teeextrakten, Von Kaffee, Getränke (auf Kakao basierend), Ernährungsergänzungen, Stiele, Mit Energie- und Proteinriegeln, Süßwaren, Zuckerwaren, Konfekt, Schokoladewaren, Bonbons, Butterkekse, Zwieback, Oblaten, Bonbons, Biskuits, Mit süßem und pikantem Gebäck, Mit Aromawürzstoffen zur Verwendung bei der Zubereitung von Getränken und Präparate für die Zubereitung von Getränken, Torten, Patisserie, Mit Waren aus Schokolade, Brotauftstriche, Eisdesserts, Waffeltüten für Eiscreme, Mit gefrorenem Jogurt und Sorbets, Honig, Melassesirup, Zuckerwaren, Mit Kühleis, Brot und Feine Back-; Verkauf von Waren für Dritte in Bezug auf Backwaren, Mit Gewürzmischungen, Pizzas, Mit Quiches, Waren aus Bienenprodukten, Mit Reisgerichten, Mit Reisplätzchen und Chips aus Getreide; Marketing; Verteilung (Verbreitung) von Warenproben zu Werbezwecken; Vorführung von Waren für Werbezwecke; Rabattaktionen; Werbung; Verkaufsförderung und Verbreitung von Werbeanzeigen mittels aller Medienarten; Marktforschung und -anaiyse; Beratungsdienste; Anwendung eines Systems zur Unterstützung von Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen auf der Grundlage von Vergünstigungen für Stammkunden; Handelsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf ein mehrstufiges Kundentreueprogramm; Verwaltung von Handelsbetrieben; Unternehmensverwaltung; Geschäftsführung und -verwaltung; Online-Werbung; Dienstleistungen im Rahmen der Öffentlichkeitsarbeit; Werbung für Unternehmen; Layoutgestaltung für Werbezwecke; Verkaufsfördernde Marketingdienstleistungen unter Einsatz audiovisueller Medien; Marketing über das Internet; Verbreitung von Werbeanzeigen über das Internet; Internetwerbung; Vermietung von Internetwerbeflächen; Werbung im Internet für Dritte; Verbreitung von Werbung für Dritte über das Internet; Werbepräsentation von Waren und Dienstleistungen anderer im Internet; Verbreitung von Werbung; Online-Verteilung von Werbeanzeigen; Online-Werbung und -Marketingdienstleistungen; Werbung, einschließlich Online-Werbung über ein Computernetz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες προώθησης και εμπορευματοποίηση· Υπηρεσίες αγγελιών και προώθησης σε σχέση με το εμπόριο, παρεχόμενες επί γραμμής από το Διαδίκτυο· Προβολή εμπορευμάτων μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Δραστηριότητες διαμεσολάβησης στον τομέα του εμπορίου τσαγιού, Εκχυλίσματα τσαγιού, Ροφήματα με βάση τον καφέ, Ροφήματα (με βάση το κακάο), Συμπληρώματα διατροφής, Ράβδοι, Εργογόνα και πρωτεϊνούχα μικρογεύματα σε μορφή ράβδου, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, ζαχαρώδη, ζαχαρωτά, Είδη σοκολατοποιίας, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Φρυγανιές, Γκοφρέτες, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Γλυκά και αλμυρά είδη αρτοποιίας, Αρώματα για ποτοποιία και Παρασκευάσματα για ποτοποιία, Τάρτες, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, Προϊόντα σοκολάτας, Παρασκευάσματα σε μορφή κρέμας, επιδόρπια παγωτού, Χωνάκια παγωτού, Κατεψυγμένα γιαούρτια και σορμπέ, Μέλι, σιρόπι μελάσας, Ζαχαρωτά, Πάγος και cρτος· Δραστηριότητα διαμεσολάβησης στον τομέα εμπορίου σε σχέση με αρτοσκευάσματα, Προϊόντα αρτοποιίας, Πρόσθετα που προσδίδουν γεύση, Πίτσα, Κις, Είδη από μελισσοκομικά προϊόντα, Τρόφιμα με ρύζι, Γκοφρέτες ρυζιού και νιφάδες δημητριακών· Λιανικό και χονδρικό εμπόριο σε σχέση με τσάι, Εκχυλίσματα τσαγιού, Ροφήματα με βάση τον καφέ, Ροφήματα (με βάση το κακάο), Συμπληρώματα διατροφής, Ράβδοι, Εργογόνα και πρωτεϊνούχα μικρογεύματα σε μορφή ράβδου, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, ζαχαρώδη, ζαχαρωτά, Είδη σοκολατοποιίας, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Φρυγανιές, Γκοφρέτες, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Γλυκά και αλμυρά είδη αρτοποιίας, Αρώματα για ποτοποιία και Παρασκευάσματα για ποτοποιία, Τάρτες, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, Προϊόντα σοκολάτας, Παρασκευάσματα σε μορφή κρέμας, επιδόρπια παγωτού, Χωνάκια παγωτού, Κατεψυγμένα γιαούρτια και σορμπέ, Μέλι, σιρόπι μελάσας, Ζαχαρωτά, Πάγος, cρτος και Γλυκά· Λιανικό-χονδρικό εμπόριο σε σχέση με προϊόντα αρτοποιίας, Πρόσθετα που προσδίδουν γεύση, Πίτσα, Κις, Είδη από μελισσοκομικά προϊόντα, Τρόφιμα με ρύζι, Γκοφρέτες ρυζιού και νιφάδες δημητριακών· Εισαγωγές-εξαγωγές σε σχέση με τσάι, Εκχυλίσματα τσαγιού, Ροφήματα με βάση τον καφέ, Ροφήματα (με βάση το κακάο), Συμπληρώματα διατροφής, Ράβδοι, Εργογόνα και πρωτεϊνούχα μικρογεύματα σε μορφή ράβδου, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, ζαχαρώδη, ζαχαρωτά, Είδη σοκολατοποιίας, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Φρυγανιές, Γκοφρέτες, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Γλυκά και αλμυρά είδη αρτοποιίας, Αρώματα για ποτοποιία και Παρασκευάσματα για ποτοποιία, Τάρτες, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, Προϊόντα σοκολάτας, Παρασκευάσματα σε μορφή κρέμας, επιδόρπια παγωτού, Χωνάκια παγωτού, Κατεψυγμένα γιαούρτια και σορμπέ, Μέλι, σιρόπι μελάσας, Ζαχαρωτά, Πάγος, cρτος, Αρτοσκευάσματα και προϊόντα αρτοποιίας· Εισαγωγές-εξαγωγές σε σχέση με πρόσθετα που προσδίδουν γεύση, Πίτσα, Κις, Είδη από μελισσοκομικά προϊόντα, Τρόφιμα με ρύζι, Γκοφρέτες ρυζιού και νιφάδες δημητριακών· Διαδικτυακό εμπόριο (ηλεκτρονικό κατάστημα) σε σχέση με τσάι, Εκχυλίσματα τσαγιού, Ροφήματα με βάση τον καφέ, Ροφήματα (με βάση το κακάο), Συμπληρώματα διατροφής, Ράβδοι, Εργογόνα και πρωτεϊνούχα μικρογεύματα σε μορφή ράβδου, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, ζαχαρώδη, ζαχαρωτά, Είδη σοκολατοποιίας, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Φρυγανιές, Γκοφρέτες, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Γλυκά και αλμυρά είδη αρτοποιίας, Αρώματα για ποτοποιία και Παρασκευάσματα για ποτοποιία, Τάρτες, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, Προϊόντα σοκολάτας, Παρασκευάσματα σε μορφή κρέμας, επιδόρπια παγωτού, Χωνάκια παγωτού, Κατεψυγμένα γιαούρτια και σορμπέ, Μέλι, σιρόπι μελάσας, Ζαχαρωτά, Πάγος, cρτος, Γλυκά· Διαδικτυακό εμπόριο (ηλεκτρονικό κατάστημα) σε σχέση με προϊόντα αρτοποιίας, Πρόσθετα που προσδίδουν γεύση, Πίτσα, Κις, Είδη από μελισσοκομικά προϊόντα, Τρόφιμα με ρύζι, Γκοφρέτες ρυζιού και νιφάδες δημητριακών· Τηλεπωλήσεις (πωλήσεις μέσω τηλεφώνου) σε σχέση με τσάι, Εκχυλίσματα τσαγιού, Ροφήματα με βάση τον καφέ, Ροφήματα (με βάση το κακάο), Συμπληρώματα διατροφής, Ράβδοι, Εργογόνα και πρωτεϊνούχα μικρογεύματα σε μορφή ράβδου, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, ζαχαρώδη, ζαχαρωτά, Είδη σοκολατοποιίας, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Φρυγανιές, Γκοφρέτες, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Γλυκά και αλμυρά είδη αρτοποιίας, Αρώματα για ποτοποιία και Παρασκευάσματα για ποτοποιία, Τάρτες, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, Προϊόντα σοκολάτας, Παρασκευάσματα σε μορφή κρέμας, επιδόρπια παγωτού, Χωνάκια παγωτού, Κατεψυγμένα γιαούρτια και σορμπέ, Μέλι, σιρόπι μελάσας, Ζαχαρωτά, Πάγος, cρτος και Γλυκά· Τηλεπωλήσεις (πωλήσεις μέσω τηλεφώνου) σε σχέση με προϊόντα αρτοποιίας, Πρόσθετα που προσδίδουν γεύση, Πίτσα, Κις, Είδη από μελισσοκομικά προϊόντα, Τρόφιμα με ρύζι, Γκοφρέτες ρυζιού και νιφάδες δημητριακών· Πώληση εμπορευμάτων για λογαριασμό τρίτων σε σχέση με το τσάι, Εκχυλίσματα τσαγιού, Ροφήματα με βάση τον καφέ, Ροφήματα (με βάση το κακάο), Συμπληρώματα διατροφής, Ράβδοι, Εργογόνα και πρωτεϊνούχα μικρογεύματα σε μορφή ράβδου, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, ζαχαρώδη, ζαχαρωτά, Είδη σοκολατοποιίας, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Φρυγανιές, Γκοφρέτες, Καραμέλες, Μπισκότα, Γλυκά και αλμυρά είδη αρτοποιίας, Αρώματα για ποτοποιία και Παρασκευάσματα για ποτοποιία, Τάρτες, Είδη ζαχαροπλαστικής, Προϊόντα σοκολάτας, Παρασκευάσματα σε μορφή κρέμας, επιδόρπια παγωτού, Χωνάκια παγωτού, Κατεψυγμένα γιαούρτια και σορμπέ, Μέλι, σιρόπι μελάσας, Ζαχαρωτά, Πάγος, cρτος και Γλυκά· Πώληση εμπορευμάτων για λογαριασμό τρίτων σε σχέση με προϊόντα αρτοποιίας, Πρόσθετα που προσδίδουν γεύση, Πίτσα, Κις, Είδη από μελισσοκομικά προϊόντα, Τρόφιμα με ρύζι, Γκοφρέτες ρυζιού και νιφάδες δημητριακών· Υπηρεσίες μάρκετινγκ· Διαβίβαση (διανομή) διαφημιστικών δειγμάτων· Επίδειξη προϊόντων· Εκπτώσεις· Διαφήμιση· Προώθηση και υπηρεσίες αγγελιών μέσω κάθε είδους μέσου· Έρευνα και ανάλυση αγοράς· Δραστηριότητα παροχής συμβουλών· Χρήση συστήματος για υποστήριξη λιανικών πωλήσεων, το οποίο βασίζεται σε προνομιακή μεταχείριση πιστών πελατών· Εμπορικές υπηρεσίες προγράμματος πιστών πελατών· Εμπορική διαχείριση· Διαχείριση επιχειρήσεων· Διοίκηση και διαχείριση επιχειρήσεων· Επιγραμμική διαφήμιση· Υπηρεσίες δημοσιότητας· Υπηρεσίες προώθησης επιχειρήσεων· Υπηρεσίες διάταξης για διαφημιστικούς σκοπούς· Υπηρεσίες προωθητικού μάρκετινγκ με χρήση οπτικοακουστικών μέσων· Πωλήσεις μέσω διαδικτύου· Διάδοση διαφημίσεων μέσω του διαδικτύου· Υπηρεσίες διαφήμισης παρεχόμενες μέσω του Διαδικτύου (ΙΝΤΕΡΝΕΤ)· Εκμίσθωση διαφημιστικού χώρου στο Διαδίκτυο (Internet)· Διαφήμιση για λογαριασμό τρίτων στο Διαδίκτυο (INTERNET)· Διανομή διαφημιστικού υλικού για λογαριασμό τρίτων μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Προώθηση των αγαθών και υπηρεσιών άλλων μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Διάδοση διαφημιστικών μηνυμάτων· Διάδοση διαφημιστικού υλικού μέσω διαδικτύου· Υπηρεσίες επί γραμμής διαφήμισης και εμπορίας (μάρκετινγκ)· Διαφήμιση, όπου περιλαμβάνεται επί γραμμής (on-line) διαφήμιση μέσω δικτύου πληροφορικής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Promotional services and merchandising; Advertising and promotion relating to commerce provided online via the internet; Online demonstration of goods; Brokerage in the field of the tea trade, Tea extracts, Coffee, Beverages (cocoa-based), Supplements for food, sticks, Energy and protein bars, Confectionery, Chocolate goods, candies, Biscuits, Biscotti, Wafers, candies, Biscuits, Sweet and salty baked goods, Flavourings for beverages and Preparations for making beverages, Tarts, Patisserie, Chocolate products, spreads, Ice desserts, ice cream cones, Frozen yoghurts and sorbets, Honey, treacle, Bonbons, Ice and bread; Brokerage in the sale of pastries, Bakery products, Condiments, Pizzas, Quiches, Goods made from bee products, Rice meals, Rice biscuits and cereal flakes; Retailing and wholesaling of tea, Tea extracts, Coffee, Beverages (cocoa-based), Supplements for food, sticks, Energy and protein bars, Confectionery, Chocolate goods, candies, Biscuits, Biscotti, Wafers, candies, Biscuits, Sweet and salty baked goods, Flavourings for beverages and Preparations for making beverages, Tarts, Patisserie, Chocolate products, spreads, Ice desserts, ice cream cones, Frozen yoghurts and sorbets, Honey, treacle, Bonbons, Ice, bread and Pastries; Retailing and wholesaling of bakery goods, Condiments, Pizzas, Quiches, Goods made from bee products, Rice meals, Rice biscuits and cereal flakes; Export and import of tea, Tea extracts, Coffee, Beverages (cocoa-based), Supplements for food, sticks, Energy and protein bars, Confectionery, Chocolate goods, candies, Biscuits, Biscotti, Wafers, candies, Biscuits, Sweet and salty baked goods, Flavourings for beverages and Preparations for making beverages, Tarts, Patisserie, Chocolate products, spreads, Ice desserts, ice cream cones, Frozen yoghurts and sorbets, Honey, treacle, Bonbons, Ice, bread, Pastries and bakery goods; Export and import of condiments, Pizzas, Quiches, Goods made from bee products, Rice meals, Rice biscuits and cereal flakes; Tea online shop services, Tea extracts, Coffee, Beverages (cocoa-based), Supplements for food, sticks, Energy and protein bars, Confectionery, Chocolate goods, candies, Biscuits, Biscotti, Wafers, candies, Biscuits, Sweet and salty baked goods, Flavourings for beverages and Preparations for making beverages, Tarts, Patisserie, Chocolate products, spreads, Ice desserts, ice cream cones, Frozen yoghurts and sorbets, Honey, treacle, Bonbons, Ice, bread, Pastries; Online sale of bakery goods, Condiments, Pizzas, Quiches, Goods made from bee products, Rice meals, Rice biscuits and cereal flakes; Telemarketing (telesales services) relating to tea, Tea extracts, Coffee, Beverages (cocoa-based), Supplements for food, sticks, Energy and protein bars, Confectionery, Chocolate goods, candies, Biscuits, Biscotti, Wafers, candies, Biscuits, Sweet and salty baked goods, Flavourings for beverages and Preparations for making beverages, Tarts, Patisserie, Chocolate products, spreads, Ice desserts, ice cream cones, Frozen yoghurts and sorbets, Honey, treacle, Bonbons, Ice, bread and Pastries; Telemarketing of bakery goods, Condiments, Pizzas, Quiches, Goods made from bee products, Rice meals, Rice biscuits and cereal flakes; Sale of goods relating to tea for others, Tea extracts, Coffee, Beverages (cocoa-based), Supplements for food, sticks, Energy and protein bars, Confectionery, Chocolate goods, candies, Biscuits, Biscotti, Wafers, candies, Biscuits, Sweet and salty baked goods, Flavourings for beverages and Preparations for making beverages, Tarts, Patisserie, Chocolate products, spreads, Ice desserts, ice cream cones, Frozen yoghurts and sorbets, Honey, treacle, Bonbons, Ice, bread and Pastries; Sale, for others, of bakery goods, Condiments, Pizzas, Quiches, Goods made from bee products, Rice meals, Rice biscuits and cereal flakes; Marketing services; Distribution of advertising samples; Demonstration of goods; Price reduction events; Advertising; Advertising via media of all kinds; Market research and analysis; Consultancy; Application of a system for promoting retailing based on preferential treatment of regular customers; Commercial services relating to an extension customer loyalty scheme; Commercial management; Business administration; Business administration and management; Online advertising; Publicity services; Business promotion; Layout services for advertising purposes; Promotional marketing services using audiovisual media; Internet marketing; Dissemination of advertisements via the Internet; Advertising services provided via the internet; Rental of advertising space on the internet; Advertisement for others on the Internet; Dissemination of advertising for others via the Internet; Promoting the goods and services of others over the Internet; Dissemination of advertisements; Dissemination of advertising matter online; Online advertising and marketing; Advertising, including on-line advertising on a computer network.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Promoción y comercialización; Servicios de publicidad y propaganda relacionados con el comercio en línea desde Internet; Demostración de productos, entre otros en internet; Servicios de mediación en el ámbito del comercio del té, Extractos de té, de café, Bebidas (con base de cacao), Suplementos alimenticios, Palos, Barritas energéticas y proteicas, Productos de confitería, productos de azúcar, confites, Productos de chocolate, Golosinas, Galletas, Biscotes, Obleas, Golosinas, Pastas (galletas), Bollería dulce y salada, Sabores para la elaboración de bebidas y Preparados para la elaboración de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelería, Productos de chocolate, Pastas para untar, Postres de helado, Cucuruchos de helado, Yogures helados y sorbetes, Miel, jarabe de melaza (siropes), Confituras, Hielo y Pan; Servicios de mediación en el ámbito del comercio de bollería, Productos de la industria panadera, Condimentos, Pizzas, Quiche, Artícultos que contienen productos de abejas, Platos de arroz, Galletas de arroz y copos de cereales; Venta al detalle y al por mayor de tés, Extractos de té, de café, Bebidas (con base de cacao), Suplementos alimenticios, Palos, Barritas energéticas y proteicas, Productos de confitería, productos de azúcar, confites, Productos de chocolate, Golosinas, Galletas, Biscotes, Obleas, Golosinas, Pastas (galletas), Bollería dulce y salada, Sabores para la elaboración de bebidas y Preparados para la elaboración de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelería, Productos de chocolate, Pastas para untar, Postres de helado, Cucuruchos de helado, Yogures helados y sorbetes, Miel, jarabe de melaza (siropes), Confituras, Hielo, Pan y Artículos de repostería; Comercio al por menor y al por mayor de productos de la industria panadera, Condimentos, Pizzas, Quiche, Artícultos que contienen productos de abejas, Platos de arroz, Galletas de arroz y copos de cereales; Exportación e importación de tés, Extractos de té, de café, Bebidas (con base de cacao), Suplementos alimenticios, Palos, Barritas energéticas y proteicas, Productos de confitería, productos de azúcar, confites, Productos de chocolate, Golosinas, Galletas, Biscotes, Obleas, Golosinas, Pastas (galletas), Bollería dulce y salada, Sabores para la elaboración de bebidas y Preparados para la elaboración de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelería, Productos de chocolate, Pastas para untar, Postres de helado, Cucuruchos de helado, Yogures helados y sorbetes, Miel, jarabe de melaza (siropes), Confituras, Hielo, Pan, Bollería y productos de la industria panadera; Exportación e importación de condimentos, Pizzas, Quiche, Artícultos que contienen productos de abejas, Platos de arroz, Galletas de arroz y copos de cereales; Tienda de tés en Internet (e-shop), Extractos de té, de café, Bebidas (con base de cacao), Suplementos alimenticios, Palos, Barritas energéticas y proteicas, Productos de confitería, productos de azúcar, confites, Productos de chocolate, Golosinas, Galletas, Biscotes, Obleas, Golosinas, Pastas (galletas), Bollería dulce y salada, Sabores para la elaboración de bebidas y Preparados para la elaboración de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelería, Productos de chocolate, Pastas para untar, Postres de helado, Cucuruchos de helado, Yogures helados y sorbetes, Miel, jarabe de melaza (siropes), Confituras, Hielo, Pan, Artículos de repostería; Tienda por internet (e-shop) de artículos de panadería, Condimentos, Pizzas, Quiche, Artícultos que contienen productos de abejas, Platos de arroz, Galletas de arroz y copos de cereales; Telemarketing (servicios de venta por teléfono) de tés, Extractos de té, de café, Bebidas (con base de cacao), Suplementos alimenticios, Palos, Barritas energéticas y proteicas, Productos de confitería, productos de azúcar, confites, Productos de chocolate, Golosinas, Galletas, Biscotes, Obleas, Golosinas, Pastas (galletas), Bollería dulce y salada, Sabores para la elaboración de bebidas y Preparados para la elaboración de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelería, Productos de chocolate, Pastas para untar, Postres de helado, Cucuruchos de helado, Yogures helados y sorbetes, Miel, jarabe de melaza (siropes), Confituras, Hielo, Pan y Artículos de repostería; Telemarketing (servicios de venta por teléfono) de artículos de panadería, Condimentos, Pizzas, Quiche, Artícultos que contienen productos de abejas, Platos de arroz, Galletas de arroz y copos de cereales; Venta de productos de té para terceros, Extractos de té, de café, Bebidas (con base de cacao), Suplementos alimenticios, Palos, Barritas energéticas y proteicas, Productos de confitería, productos de azúcar, confites, Productos de chocolate, Golosinas, Galletas, Biscotes, Obleas, Golosinas, Pastas (galletas), Bollería dulce y salada, Sabores para la elaboración de bebidas y Preparados para la elaboración de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelería, Productos de chocolate, Pastas para untar, Postres de helado, Cucuruchos de helado, Yogures helados y sorbetes, Miel, jarabe de melaza (siropes), Confituras, Hielo, Pan y Artículos de repostería; Venta de productos de panadería para terceros, Condimentos, Pizzas, Quiche, Artícultos que contienen productos de abejas, Platos de arroz, Galletas de arroz y copos de cereales; Servicios de marketing; Difusión (distribución) de muestras publicitarias; Demostración de productos; Eventos de rebajas; Publicidad; Publicidad y promoción en todo tipo de medios de comunicación; Estudio y análisis de mercados; Actividad de consultoría; Aplicación del sistema de apoyo de la venta al detalle basada en ventajas para la clientela fija; Servicios comerciales del programa de fidelización empresarial; Gestión comercial; Administración comercial; Gestión y administración de empresas; Publicidad en línea; Servicios publicitarios; Promoción de negocios comerciales; Servicios de composición de páginas con fines publicitarios; Servicios de promoción de marketing que utilizan medios audiovisuales; Mercadotecnia a través de Internet; Difusión de anuncios a través de Internet; Servicios de publicidad prestados a través de Internet; Alquiler de espacio publicitario en Internet; Publicidad en Internet para terceros; Divulgación de publicidad para terceros a través de Internet; Promoción de productos y servicios de terceros por Internet; Difusión de anuncios; Divulgación de material publicitario en línea; Servicios de publicidad y marketing en línea; Publicidad, incluida la publicidad en línea (online) en redes informáticas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Müügiedendus ja kauplemine; Sidusalt internetist pakutavad kuulutus- ja müügiedendusteenused kaubanduse valdkonnas; kaupade demonstreermine internetis; Teekaubanduse vahendamine, Tee-ekstraktid, Kohvi-, Joogid (kakaopõhised), Dieetlisandid, Kepid, Energia- ja proteiinibatoonid, Kondiitritooted, Šokolaadid, Kompvekid, Küpsised, Kuivikud, Vahvlid, Karamellkompvekid, Biskviidid, Magusad ja soolased küpsetised, Maitselisandid jookide valmistamiseks ja Joogivalmistuspreparaadid, Tordid, Kondiitrikoogid, Šokolaaditooted, Määrded, Jäädesserdid, Jäätisetorbikud, Külmutatud jogurtid ja sorbetid, Mesi, melass (siirupid), Maiustused, Jää ja Leib; Vahendustegevus kondiitritööstuses, Pagaritooted, Maitselisandid, Pitsad, Quiche'id, Mesindussaadused, Riisitoidud, Riisivahvlid ja teraviljahelbed; Tee jae- ja hulgimüük, Tee-ekstraktid, Kohvi-, Joogid (kakaopõhised), Dieetlisandid, Kepid, Energia- ja proteiinibatoonid, Kondiitritooted, Šokolaadid, Kompvekid, Küpsised, Kuivikud, Vahvlid, Karamellkompvekid, Biskviidid, Magusad ja soolased küpsetised, Maitselisandid jookide valmistamiseks ja Joogivalmistuspreparaadid, Tordid, Kondiitrikoogid, Šokolaaditooted, Määrded, Jäädesserdid, Jäätisetorbikud, Külmutatud jogurtid ja sorbetid, Mesi, melass (siirupid), Maiustused, Jää, Leib ja Saiakesed ja pirukad; Pagaritoodete jae- ja hulgimüük, Maitselisandid, Pitsad, Quiche'id, Mesindussaadused, Riisitoidud, Riisivahvlid ja teraviljahelbed; Tee eksport ja import, Tee-ekstraktid, Kohvi-, Joogid (kakaopõhised), Dieetlisandid, Kepid, Energia- ja proteiinibatoonid, Kondiitritooted, Šokolaadid, Kompvekid, Küpsised, Kuivikud, Vahvlid, Karamellkompvekid, Biskviidid, Magusad ja soolased küpsetised, Maitselisandid jookide valmistamiseks ja Joogivalmistuspreparaadid, Tordid, Kondiitrikoogid, Šokolaaditooted, Määrded, Jäädesserdid, Jäätisetorbikud, Külmutatud jogurtid ja sorbetid, Mesi, melass (siirupid), Maiustused, Jää, Leib, Kondiitri- ja pagaritooted; Maitseainete jae- ja hulgimüük, Pitsad, Quiche'id, Mesindussaadused, Riisitoidud, Riisivahvlid ja teraviljahelbed; Tee internetimüük (e-poed), Tee-ekstraktid, Kohvi-, Joogid (kakaopõhised), Dieetlisandid, Kepid, Energia- ja proteiinibatoonid, Kondiitritooted, Šokolaadid, Kompvekid, Küpsised, Kuivikud, Vahvlid, Karamellkompvekid, Biskviidid, Magusad ja soolased küpsetised, Maitselisandid jookide valmistamiseks ja Joogivalmistuspreparaadid, Tordid, Kondiitrikoogid, Šokolaaditooted, Määrded, Jäädesserdid, Jäätisetorbikud, Külmutatud jogurtid ja sorbetid, Mesi, melass (siirupid), Maiustused, Jää, Leib, Saiakesed ja pirukad; Pagaritoodete internetipood, Maitselisandid, Pitsad, Quiche'id, Mesindussaadused, Riisitoidud, Riisivahvlid ja teraviljahelbed; Tee kaugmüük (müük telefoni teel), Tee-ekstraktid, Kohvi-, Joogid (kakaopõhised), Dieetlisandid, Kepid, Energia- ja proteiinibatoonid, Kondiitritooted, Šokolaadid, Kompvekid, Küpsised, Kuivikud, Vahvlid, Karamellkompvekid, Biskviidid, Magusad ja soolased küpsetised, Maitselisandid jookide valmistamiseks ja Joogivalmistuspreparaadid, Tordid, Kondiitrikoogid, Šokolaaditooted, Määrded, Jäädesserdid, Jäätisetorbikud, Külmutatud jogurtid ja sorbetid, Mesi, melass (siirupid), Maiustused, Jää, Leib ja Saiakesed ja pirukad; Pagaritoodete telemarketingiteenused, Maitselisandid, Pitsad, Quiche'id, Mesindussaadused, Riisitoidud, Riisivahvlid ja teraviljahelbed; Järgmiste kaupade müük kolmandatele isikutele: tee, Tee-ekstraktid, Kohvi-, Joogid (kakaopõhised), Dieetlisandid, Kepid, Energia- ja proteiinibatoonid, Kondiitritooted, Šokolaadid, Kompvekid, Küpsised, Kuivikud, Vahvlid, Karamellkompvekid, Biskviidid, Magusad ja soolased küpsetised, Maitselisandid jookide valmistamiseks ja Joogivalmistuspreparaadid, Tordid, Kondiitrikoogid, Šokolaaditooted, Määrded, Jäädesserdid, Jäätisetorbikud, Külmutatud jogurtid ja sorbetid, Mesi, melass (siirupid), Maiustused, Jää, Leib ja Saiakesed ja pirukad; Pagaritoodetega seotud kaupade müük kolmandatele isikutele, Maitselisandid, Pitsad, Quiche'id, Mesindussaadused, Riisitoidud, Riisivahvlid ja teraviljahelbed; Turundus; Reklaamialaste näidiste (proovide) levitamine (kättetoimetamine); Kaupade demonstreerimine; Allahindluskampaaniad; Reklaam; Müügiedendus ja kuulutused kõigis meediakanalites; Turu-uuringud ja -analüüsid; Konsultatsioonitegevus; Püsiklientide eeliskohtlemisest lähtuva jaemüügi edendamise süsteemi rakendamine; Täiendavate püsikliendiprogrammidega seotud äriteenused; Kaubandusalane juhtimine; Ärikorraldus; Ärijuhtimine ja -haldus; Sidusreklaam; Reklaamiteenused; Ettevõtte reklaam; Reklaamide küljendamine teenusena; Müügiedenduslikud turundusteenused audiovisuaalmeedia abil; Internetiturundus; Reklaami levitamine Interneti kaudu; Interneti kaudu pakutavad reklaamiteenused; Reklaamipinna rentimine internetis; Reklaam internetis teenusena; Reklaami levitamise teenus interneti teel; Kolmandate isikute kaupade ja teenuste müügiedendus Interneti kaudu; Reklaammaterjalide levitamine; Reklaammaterjalide levitamine veebis; Sidusad reklaami- ja turundusteenused; Reklaam, sh veebireklaam.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Myynninedistämispalvelut ja myynti; Online-periaatteella Internetistä tarjottavat myynninedistämis- ja ilmoituspalveluihin kaupankäynnin alalla; Tuote-esittelyt Internetissä; Välitystoiminta seuraavien tuotteiden kaupan alalla: tee, Teeuutteet, Kahvijuomat, Juomat (kaakaopohjaiset), Ravintolisäaineet, Puikot, Energia- ja proteiinipatukat, Makeiset, sokerituotteet, konvehdit, Suklaatuotteet, Karamellit, Pikkuleivät, Korput, Vohvelit, Karamellit, Keksit, Makeat ja suolaiset leivonnaiset, Juomien makuaineet ja Juomien valmistusaineet, Tortut, Leivonnaiset, Suklaatuotteet, Levitteet, Jäätelöjälkiruoat, Jäätelötuutit, Jäädytetyt jogurtit ja sorbetit, Hunaja, siirappi, Makeiset, Jää ja Leipä; Välitystoiminta seuraavien tuotteiden kaupan alalla: leivonnaiset, Leipomotuotteet, Mausteet, Pitsat, Piirakat, Mehiläistuotteista tehdyt valmisteet, Riisiruoat, Riisikeksit ja viljahiutaleet; Vähittäis- ja tukkukauppapalvelut seuraavien tuotteiden alalla: tee, Teeuutteet, Kahvijuomat, Juomat (kaakaopohjaiset), Ravintolisäaineet, Puikot, Energia- ja proteiinipatukat, Makeiset, sokerituotteet, konvehdit, Suklaatuotteet, Karamellit, Pikkuleivät, Korput, Vohvelit, Karamellit, Keksit, Makeat ja suolaiset leivonnaiset, Juomien makuaineet ja Juomien valmistusaineet, Tortut, Leivonnaiset, Suklaatuotteet, Levitteet, Jäätelöjälkiruoat, Jäätelötuutit, Jäädytetyt jogurtit ja sorbetit, Hunaja, siirappi, Makeiset, Jää, Leipä ja Leivonnaiset; Seuraavien tuotteiden vähittäiskauppa ja tukkukauppa: leipomotuotteet, Mausteet, Pitsat, Piirakat, Mehiläistuotteista tehdyt valmisteet, Riisiruoat, Riisikeksit ja viljahiutaleet; Vienti ja tuonti seuraavien tuotteiden alalla: tee, Teeuutteet, Kahvijuomat, Juomat (kaakaopohjaiset), Ravintolisäaineet, Puikot, Energia- ja proteiinipatukat, Makeiset, sokerituotteet, konvehdit, Suklaatuotteet, Karamellit, Pikkuleivät, Korput, Vohvelit, Karamellit, Keksit, Makeat ja suolaiset leivonnaiset, Juomien makuaineet ja Juomien valmistusaineet, Tortut, Leivonnaiset, Suklaatuotteet, Levitteet, Jäätelöjälkiruoat, Jäätelötuutit, Jäädytetyt jogurtit ja sorbetit, Hunaja, siirappi, Makeiset, Jää, Leipä, Leivonnaiset ja leipomotuotteet; Seuraavien tuotteiden vienti ja myynti: makuaineet, Pitsat, Piirakat, Mehiläistuotteista tehdyt valmisteet, Riisiruoat, Riisikeksit ja viljahiutaleet; Internet-myynti seuraavien tuotteiden alalla: tee, Teeuutteet, Kahvijuomat, Juomat (kaakaopohjaiset), Ravintolisäaineet, Puikot, Energia- ja proteiinipatukat, Makeiset, sokerituotteet, konvehdit, Suklaatuotteet, Karamellit, Pikkuleivät, Korput, Vohvelit, Karamellit, Keksit, Makeat ja suolaiset leivonnaiset, Juomien makuaineet ja Juomien valmistusaineet, Tortut, Leivonnaiset, Suklaatuotteet, Levitteet, Jäätelöjälkiruoat, Jäätelötuutit, Jäädytetyt jogurtit ja sorbetit, Hunaja, siirappi, Makeiset, Jää, Leipä, Leivonnaiset; Internetmyynti seuraavien tuotteiden alalla: leipomotuotteet, Mausteet, Pitsat, Piirakat, Mehiläistuotteista tehdyt valmisteet, Riisiruoat, Riisikeksit ja viljahiutaleet; Puhelinmarkkinointi (telemyyntipalvelut) seuraavien tuotteiden alalla: tee, Teeuutteet, Kahvijuomat, Juomat (kaakaopohjaiset), Ravintolisäaineet, Puikot, Energia- ja proteiinipatukat, Makeiset, sokerituotteet, konvehdit, Suklaatuotteet, Karamellit, Pikkuleivät, Korput, Vohvelit, Karamellit, Keksit, Makeat ja suolaiset leivonnaiset, Juomien makuaineet ja Juomien valmistusaineet, Tortut, Leivonnaiset, Suklaatuotteet, Levitteet, Jäätelöjälkiruoat, Jäätelötuutit, Jäädytetyt jogurtit ja sorbetit, Hunaja, siirappi, Makeiset, Jää, Leipä ja Leivonnaiset; Puhelinmarkkinointi (telemyyntipalvelut) seuraavien tuotteiden alalla: leipomotuotteet, Mausteet, Pitsat, Piirakat, Mehiläistuotteista tehdyt valmisteet, Riisiruoat, Riisikeksit ja viljahiutaleet; Tavaroiden myynti muiden lukuun seuraavien tuotteiden alalla: tee, Teeuutteet, Kahvijuomat, Juomat (kaakaopohjaiset), Ravintolisäaineet, Puikot, Energia- ja proteiinipatukat, Makeiset, sokerituotteet, konvehdit, Suklaatuotteet, Karamellit, Pikkuleivät, Korput, Vohvelit, Karamellit, Keksit, Makeat ja suolaiset leivonnaiset, Juomien makuaineet ja Juomien valmistusaineet, Tortut, Leivonnaiset, Suklaatuotteet, Levitteet, Jäätelöjälkiruoat, Jäätelötuutit, Jäädytetyt jogurtit ja sorbetit, Hunaja, siirappi, Makeiset, Jää, Leipä ja Leivonnaiset; Tavaroiden myynti muiden lukuun seuraavien tuotteiden alalla: leipomotuotteet, Mausteet, Pitsat, Piirakat, Mehiläistuotteista tehdyt valmisteet, Riisiruoat, Riisikeksit ja viljahiutaleet; Markkinointipalvelut; Mainosnäytteiden levitys (jakelu); Tavaroiden esittely; Tarjouskampanjat; Mainonta; Myynninedistäminen ja ilmoitustoiminta kaikenlaisten tiedotusvälineiden välityksellä; Markkinatutkimus ja -analyysi; Konsultointitoiminta; Kanta-asiakasetujen tarjoamiseen perustuvan vähittäismyynnin tukijärjestelmän soveltaminen; Erityiskanta-asiakasohjelmaan liittyvät myyntipalvelut; Kaupallinen johtaminen; Yrityshallinto; Liikkeenjohto ja hallinto; Verkkomainonta; Mainospalvelut; Liiketoiminnan edistämispalvelut; Tekstin sommittelu mainostarkoituksiin; Myyntiä edistävät markkinointipalvelut audiovisuaalisten välineiden välityksellä; Markkinointi Internetin välityksellä; Mainosten levittäminen Internetin välityksellä; Internetin kautta tarjottavat mainontapalvelut; Mainostilan vuokraus Internetissä; Mainonta kolmansille osapuolille Internetissä; Mainosten jakelu muiden puolesta Internetin kautta; Muiden tarjoamien tavaroiden ja palveluiden myynninedistäminen Internetissä; Mainosten jakelu; Mainosmateriaalin jakaminen verkossa; Online-muotoiset mainonta- ja markkinointipalvelut; Mainonta, mukaan lukien online-mainonta tietoverkossa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Promotion et marchandisage; Services de petites annonces et de promotion proposés en ligne sur l'internet et concernant le commerce; Démonstration de produits sur internet; Services d'intermédiaire dans le domaine du commerce du thé, D'extraits de thés, De café, Boissons (à base de cacao), compléments alimentaires, Bâtons, De barres énergétiques et protéinées, Confiseries, sucreries, Chocolats, Bonbons, Biscuits, Biscottes, Gaufres, Bonbons, De biscuits, De gâteaux sucrés ou salés, D'arômes pour la préparation de boissons et Préparations pour faire des boissons, Tartes, Pâtisseries, De produits de chocolaterie, Pâtes à tartiner, Desserts à base de glace, Cornets à glace, De yaourts glacés et de sorbets, Miel, sirop de mélasse, Sucreries, De glace et Pain; Activité d'intermédiaire dans le domaine du commerce en produits de pâtisserie, De produits de boulangerie, De condiments, Pizzas, De quiches, Produits fabriqués à partir des substances produites par les abeilles, De plats à base de riz, De biscuits de riz et de flocons de céréales; Commerce de détail et commerce de gros de thés, D'extraits de thés, De café, Boissons (à base de cacao), compléments alimentaires, Bâtons, De barres énergétiques et protéinées, Confiseries, sucreries, Chocolats, Bonbons, Biscuits, Biscottes, Gaufres, Bonbons, De biscuits, De gâteaux sucrés ou salés, D'arômes pour la préparation de boissons et Préparations pour faire des boissons, Tartes, Pâtisseries, De produits de chocolaterie, Pâtes à tartiner, Desserts à base de glace, Cornets à glace, De yaourts glacés et de sorbets, Miel, sirop de mélasse, Sucreries, De glace, Pain et Pâtisseries; Commerce de détail et commerce de gros de produits de boulangerie-pâtisserie, De condiments, Pizzas, De quiches, Produits fabriqués à partir des substances produites par les abeilles, De plats à base de riz, De biscuits de riz et de flocons de céréales; Exportation et importation de thés, D'extraits de thés, De café, Boissons (à base de cacao), compléments alimentaires, Bâtons, De barres énergétiques et protéinées, Confiseries, sucreries, Chocolats, Bonbons, Biscuits, Biscottes, Gaufres, Bonbons, De biscuits, De gâteaux sucrés ou salés, D'arômes pour la préparation de boissons et Préparations pour faire des boissons, Tartes, Pâtisseries, De produits de chocolaterie, Pâtes à tartiner, Desserts à base de glace, Cornets à glace, De yaourts glacés et de sorbets, Miel, sirop de mélasse, Sucreries, De glace, Pain, De pâtisseries et de produits de boulangerie-pâtisserie; Exportation et importation de condiments, Pizzas, De quiches, Produits fabriqués à partir des substances produites par les abeilles, De plats à base de riz, De biscuits de riz et de flocons de céréales; Vente sur l'internet (boutique en ligne) de thés, D'extraits de thés, De café, Boissons (à base de cacao), compléments alimentaires, Bâtons, De barres énergétiques et protéinées, Confiseries, sucreries, Chocolats, Bonbons, Biscuits, Biscottes, Gaufres, Bonbons, De biscuits, De gâteaux sucrés ou salés, D'arômes pour la préparation de boissons et Préparations pour faire des boissons, Tartes, Pâtisseries, De produits de chocolaterie, Pâtes à tartiner, Desserts à base de glace, Cornets à glace, De yaourts glacés et de sorbets, Miel, sirop de mélasse, Sucreries, De glace, Pain, Pâtisseries; Vente sur l'internet (boutique en ligne) de produits de boulangerie-pâtisserie, De condiments, Pizzas, De quiches, Produits fabriqués à partir des substances produites par les abeilles, De plats à base de riz, De biscuits de riz et de flocons de céréales; Télémarketing (vente par téléphone) de thés, D'extraits de thés, De café, Boissons (à base de cacao), compléments alimentaires, Bâtons, De barres énergétiques et protéinées, Confiseries, sucreries, Chocolats, Bonbons, Biscuits, Biscottes, Gaufres, Bonbons, De biscuits, De gâteaux sucrés ou salés, D'arômes pour la préparation de boissons et Préparations pour faire des boissons, Tartes, Pâtisseries, De produits de chocolaterie, Pâtes à tartiner, Desserts à base de glace, Cornets à glace, De yaourts glacés et de sorbets, Miel, sirop de mélasse, Sucreries, De glace, Pain et Pâtisseries; Services de télémarketing (vente par téléphone) concernant des produits de boulangerie-pâtisserie, De condiments, Pizzas, De quiches, Produits fabriqués à partir des substances produites par les abeilles, De plats à base de riz, De biscuits de riz et de flocons de céréales; Vente de thés pour le compte de tiers, D'extraits de thés, De café, Boissons (à base de cacao), compléments alimentaires, Bâtons, De barres énergétiques et protéinées, Confiseries, sucreries, Chocolats, Bonbons, Biscuits, Biscottes, Gaufres, Bonbons, De biscuits, De gâteaux sucrés ou salés, D'arômes pour la préparation de boissons et Préparations pour faire des boissons, Tartes, Pâtisseries, De produits de chocolaterie, Pâtes à tartiner, Desserts à base de glace, Cornets à glace, De yaourts glacés et de sorbets, Miel, sirop de mélasse, Sucreries, De glace, Pain et Pâtisseries; Vente de produits de boulangerie-pâtisserie pour le compte de tiers, De condiments, Pizzas, De quiches, Produits fabriqués à partir des substances produites par les abeilles, De plats à base de riz, De biscuits de riz et de flocons de céréales; Services de marketing; Diffusion (distribution) d'échantillons publicitaires; Démonstration de produits; Actions de promotion ou soldes; Publicité; Promotion et insertion d'annonces par l'intermédiaires de médias en tous genres; Études et analyses de marchés; Activité de consultation; Application d'un système de promotion de ventes au détail reposant sur les privilèges accordés aux clients fidèles; Services commerciaux relatifs à des programmes complémentaires de fidélisation de la clientèle; Gestion commerciale; Administration commerciale; Administration et gestion d'entreprises; Publicités en ligne; Services publicitaires; Services de promotion commerciale; Mise en pages à buts publicitaires; Services de marketing promotionnel utilisant des supports audiovisuels; Marketing sur internet; Diffusion de publicités sur Internet; Services publicitaires fournis via Internet; Location d'espaces publicitaires sur Internet; Publicité sur Internet pour le compte de tiers; Diffusion de publicités pour le compte de tiers via Internet; Services de promotion des produits et services de tiers par Internet; Diffusion d'annonces; Diffusion d'annonces publicitaires en ligne; Services de publicité et marketing en ligne; Publicité, y compris publicité en ligne sur un réseau informatique.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge promidžbe i komercijalizacije; Reklamne i promotivne usluge u vezi s trgovinom pružene mrežno putem interneta; Predstavljanje robe posredstvom interneta; Djelatnost posredovanja u području trgovine čajevima, Ekstrakti čaja, Kave, Napitci (na bazi kakaa), Dodaci prehrani, Štapovi, Energetske i proteinske pločice, Slastice, Pripravci na bazi čokolade, Slatkiši, Suhi kolačići, Dvopek [prepečenac], Vafli, Karamele, Kremasta juha, Slatka i slana peciva, Arome za izradu pića i Pripravci za pripremu pića, Torte, Paste za spravljanje juhe, Proizvodi od čokolade, Namazi, Deserti od leda, Korneti za sladoled, Zamrznuti jogurti i šerbeti, Med, šećerni sirup, Proizvodi od šećera, Led i Kruh; Djelatnost posredovanja u području prodaje peciva, Pekarski proizvodi, Arome, Pizza, Slane pite, Proizvodi od pčelinjih proizvoda, Jela od riže, Rižini kolačići i čips od žitarica; Maloprodaja i veleprodaja čajeva, Ekstrakti čaja, Kave, Napitci (na bazi kakaa), Dodaci prehrani, Štapovi, Energetske i proteinske pločice, Slastice, Pripravci na bazi čokolade, Slatkiši, Suhi kolačići, Dvopek [prepečenac], Vafli, Karamele, Kremasta juha, Slatka i slana peciva, Arome za izradu pića i Pripravci za pripremu pića, Torte, Paste za spravljanje juhe, Proizvodi od čokolade, Namazi, Deserti od leda, Korneti za sladoled, Zamrznuti jogurti i šerbeti, Med, šećerni sirup, Proizvodi od šećera, Led, Kruh i Fina peciva; Maloprodaja i veleprodaja pekarskih proizvoda, Arome, Pizza, Slane pite, Proizvodi od pčelinjih proizvoda, Jela od riže, Rižini kolačići i čips od žitarica; Izvoz i uvoz čajeva, Ekstrakti čaja, Kave, Napitci (na bazi kakaa), Dodaci prehrani, Štapovi, Energetske i proteinske pločice, Slastice, Pripravci na bazi čokolade, Slatkiši, Suhi kolačići, Dvopek [prepečenac], Vafli, Karamele, Kremasta juha, Slatka i slana peciva, Arome za izradu pića i Pripravci za pripremu pića, Torte, Paste za spravljanje juhe, Proizvodi od čokolade, Namazi, Deserti od leda, Korneti za sladoled, Zamrznuti jogurti i šerbeti, Med, šećerni sirup, Proizvodi od šećera, Led, Kruh, Peciva i pekarski proizvodi; Izvoz i uvoz dodataka za arome, Pizza, Slane pite, Proizvodi od pčelinjih proizvoda, Jela od riže, Rižini kolačići i čips od žitarica; Internetska trgovina (e-trgovina) čajevima, Ekstrakti čaja, Kave, Napitci (na bazi kakaa), Dodaci prehrani, Štapovi, Energetske i proteinske pločice, Slastice, Pripravci na bazi čokolade, Slatkiši, Suhi kolačići, Dvopek [prepečenac], Vafli, Karamele, Kremasta juha, Slatka i slana peciva, Arome za izradu pića i Pripravci za pripremu pića, Torte, Paste za spravljanje juhe, Proizvodi od čokolade, Namazi, Deserti od leda, Korneti za sladoled, Zamrznuti jogurti i šerbeti, Med, šećerni sirup, Proizvodi od šećera, Led, Kruh, Fina peciva; Internetska prodaja (e-trgovina) pekarskih proizvoda, Arome, Pizza, Slane pite, Proizvodi od pčelinjih proizvoda, Jela od riže, Rižini kolačići i čips od žitarica; Telemarketing (prodaja putem telefona) čajeva, Ekstrakti čaja, Kave, Napitci (na bazi kakaa), Dodaci prehrani, Štapovi, Energetske i proteinske pločice, Slastice, Pripravci na bazi čokolade, Slatkiši, Suhi kolačići, Dvopek [prepečenac], Vafli, Karamele, Kremasta juha, Slatka i slana peciva, Arome za izradu pića i Pripravci za pripremu pića, Torte, Paste za spravljanje juhe, Proizvodi od čokolade, Namazi, Deserti od leda, Korneti za sladoled, Zamrznuti jogurti i šerbeti, Med, šećerni sirup, Proizvodi od šećera, Led, Kruh i Fina peciva; Telemarketing (prodaja putem telefona) pekarskih proizvoda, Arome, Pizza, Slane pite, Proizvodi od pčelinjih proizvoda, Jela od riže, Rižini kolačići i čips od žitarica; Prodaja proizvoda za druge s čajevima, Ekstrakti čaja, Kave, Napitci (na bazi kakaa), Dodaci prehrani, Štapovi, Energetske i proteinske pločice, Slastice, Pripravci na bazi čokolade, Slatkiši, Suhi kolačići, Dvopek [prepečenac], Vafli, Karamele, Kremasta juha, Slatka i slana peciva, Arome za izradu pića i Pripravci za pripremu pića, Torte, Paste za spravljanje juhe, Proizvodi od čokolade, Namazi, Deserti od leda, Korneti za sladoled, Zamrznuti jogurti i šerbeti, Med, šećerni sirup, Proizvodi od šećera, Led, Kruh i Fina peciva; Prodaja za druge pekarskih proizvoda, Arome, Pizza, Slane pite, Proizvodi od pčelinjih proizvoda, Jela od riže, Rižini kolačići i čips od žitarica; Marketing; Distribucija oglasnih uzoraka; Demonstracija proizvoda; Akcije popusta; Oglašavanje; Promidžba i oglašavanje putem svih vrsta medija; Tržišne studije i analize; Konzultantska djelatnost; Primjena sustava za promicanje maloprodaje na temelju prednosti stalnih kupaca; Poslovne usluge programa vjernosti korisnika; Komercijalno upravljanje; Komercijalna administracija; Poslovno upravljanje i administracija; Reklamiranje putem interneta; Reklamne usluge; Promocija poslovnih djelatnosti; Usluge prijeloma u reklamne svrhe; Promidžbene marketinške usluge uz upotrebu audio-vizualnih medija; Internetski marketing; Širenje oglasa internetom; Usluge oglašavanja pružene putem Interneta; Iznajmljivanje oglasnog prostora na Internetu; Oglašavanje za treće osobe na Internetu; Širenje reklamnih materijala za druge, putem Interneta; Promocija robe i usluga drugih putem Interneta; Distribucija reklamnih oglasa; Širenje oglasnog materijala na internetu; Usluge online reklame i marketinga; Oglašavanje, uključujući online oglašavanje na računalnoj mreži.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Promóció és termékfejlesztés; Hirdetési és promóciós szolgáltatások online, az interneten keresztül biztosított szolgáltatásokkal kapcsolatban; Árubemutatás interneten; Közvetítői tevékenység tea kereskedelme terén, Teakivonatok, Kávé, Kakaó alapú italok, Étrend kiegészítő termékek, Pálcikák, Energia- és proteinszeletek, Cukrászsütemények, Csokoládék, Bonbonok (cukorkák), Kekszek, Piskóták, Ostyák, Cukorkák, Kekszek, Édes és savanyú süteménytészták, Ízesítések italok készítéshez és Italok készítéséhez való készítmények, Lepények (gyümölcsös), Cukrászsütemény, Csokoládétermékek, Kenhetők, Jégdesszertek, Jégkrémtölcsérek, Fagyasztott joghurtok és szorbetek, Méz, szirupok, Édességek, Jég és Kenyér; Közvetítő tevékenység tésztakereskedelem területén, Péktermékek, Ételízesítők, Pizzák, Quiche, Méhészeti termékekből készült áruk, Rizses ételek, Rizses sütemények és gabona chipsek; Tea kis-és nagykereskedelme, Teakivonatok, Kávé, Kakaó alapú italok, Étrend kiegészítő termékek, Pálcikák, Energia- és proteinszeletek, Cukrászsütemények, Csokoládék, Bonbonok (cukorkák), Kekszek, Piskóták, Ostyák, Cukorkák, Kekszek, Édes és savanyú süteménytészták, Ízesítések italok készítéshez és Italok készítéséhez való készítmények, Lepények (gyümölcsös), Cukrászsütemény, Csokoládétermékek, Kenhetők, Jégdesszertek, Jégkrémtölcsérek, Fagyasztott joghurtok és szorbetek, Méz, szirupok, Édességek, Jég, Kenyér és Finom pékáru; Sütőipari termékek kis- és nagykereskedelme, Ételízesítők, Pizzák, Quiche, Méhészeti termékekből készült áruk, Rizses ételek, Rizses sütemények és gabona chipsek; Tea exportja és importja, Teakivonatok, Kávé, Kakaó alapú italok, Étrend kiegészítő termékek, Pálcikák, Energia- és proteinszeletek, Cukrászsütemények, Csokoládék, Bonbonok (cukorkák), Kekszek, Piskóták, Ostyák, Cukorkák, Kekszek, Édes és savanyú süteménytészták, Ízesítések italok készítéshez és Italok készítéséhez való készítmények, Lepények (gyümölcsös), Cukrászsütemény, Csokoládétermékek, Kenhetők, Jégdesszertek, Jégkrémtölcsérek, Fagyasztott joghurtok és szorbetek, Méz, szirupok, Édességek, Jég, Kenyér, Sütemények és pékáruk; Aromaanyagok exportja és importja, Pizzák, Quiche, Méhészeti termékekből készült áruk, Rizses ételek, Rizses sütemények és gabona chipsek; Tea internetes értékesítése (e-boltokon keresztül), Teakivonatok, Kávé, Kakaó alapú italok, Étrend kiegészítő termékek, Pálcikák, Energia- és proteinszeletek, Cukrászsütemények, Csokoládék, Bonbonok (cukorkák), Kekszek, Piskóták, Ostyák, Cukorkák, Kekszek, Édes és savanyú süteménytészták, Ízesítések italok készítéshez és Italok készítéséhez való készítmények, Lepények (gyümölcsös), Cukrászsütemény, Csokoládétermékek, Kenhetők, Jégdesszertek, Jégkrémtölcsérek, Fagyasztott joghurtok és szorbetek, Méz, szirupok, Édességek, Jég, Kenyér, Finom pékáru; Internetes üzlet (e-shop) sütőipari termékekkel kapcsolatban, Ételízesítők, Pizzák, Quiche, Méhészeti termékekből készült áruk, Rizses ételek, Rizses sütemények és gabona chipsek; Teával kapcsolatos telemarketing (telefonos értékesítés), Teakivonatok, Kávé, Kakaó alapú italok, Étrend kiegészítő termékek, Pálcikák, Energia- és proteinszeletek, Cukrászsütemények, Csokoládék, Bonbonok (cukorkák), Kekszek, Piskóták, Ostyák, Cukorkák, Kekszek, Édes és savanyú süteménytészták, Ízesítések italok készítéshez és Italok készítéséhez való készítmények, Lepények (gyümölcsös), Cukrászsütemény, Csokoládétermékek, Kenhetők, Jégdesszertek, Jégkrémtölcsérek, Fagyasztott joghurtok és szorbetek, Méz, szirupok, Édességek, Jég, Kenyér és Finom pékáru; Sütőipari termékek telemarketingje (telefonos értékesítés), Ételízesítők, Pizzák, Quiche, Méhészeti termékekből készült áruk, Rizses ételek, Rizses sütemények és gabona chipsek; Teával kapcsolatos árukereskedelem mások számára, Teakivonatok, Kávé, Kakaó alapú italok, Étrend kiegészítő termékek, Pálcikák, Energia- és proteinszeletek, Cukrászsütemények, Csokoládék, Bonbonok (cukorkák), Kekszek, Piskóták, Ostyák, Cukorkák, Kekszek, Édes és savanyú süteménytészták, Ízesítések italok készítéshez és Italok készítéséhez való készítmények, Lepények (gyümölcsös), Cukrászsütemény, Csokoládétermékek, Kenhetők, Jégdesszertek, Jégkrémtölcsérek, Fagyasztott joghurtok és szorbetek, Méz, szirupok, Édességek, Jég, Kenyér és Finom pékáru; Áruk eladása mások számára sütőipari termékek vonatkozásában, Ételízesítők, Pizzák, Quiche, Méhészeti termékekből készült áruk, Rizses ételek, Rizses sütemények és gabona chipsek; Marketing szolgáltatások; Reklámozási áruminták terjesztése (szétosztása); Árubemutatás; Árengedmények; Reklámozás; Promóció és hirdetések minden típusú média közvetítésével; Piackutatás és elemzés; Tanácsadó tevékenység; Rendszerek alkalmazása állandó vásárlók preferenciáin alapuló kiskereskedelmi értékesítés promótálása céljából; Üzleti hűségprogramok ügyfélszolgálata; Kereskedelmi menedzsment; Kereskedelmi adminisztráció; Üzleti adminisztráció és menedzsment; Online hirdetési szolgáltatások; Reklámozási szolgáltatások; Üzleti promóció; Tördelési szolgáltatások hirdetési célokból; Promóciós marketing-szolgáltatások audiovizuális média felhasználásával; Internetes marketing; Reklámok terjesztése interneten keresztül; Interneten keresztül biztosított hirdetési szolgáltatások; Internetes hirdetési felület bérbeadása; Internetes reklámozási szolgáltatások; Reklámterjesztési szolgáltatások az interneten keresztül; Harmadik személyek termékeinek és szolgáltatásainak Interneten való reklámozása; Reklámterjesztés; Reklámanyagok online terjesztése; Online reklámozási és marketing szolgáltatások; Reklámozás, hirdetés, beleértve a számítógépes hálózatokon történő online reklámozást.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Promozione e merchandising; Servizi promozionali e pubblicitari relativi al commercio online su internet; Dimostrazione pratica di prodotti tramite Internet; Attività di mediazione nel settore del commercio del tè, Estratti di tè, Di caffè, Bevande (a base di cacao), Integratori alimentari, Bastoni, Barrette proteiche ed energetiche, Dolciumi, confetteria, cioccolatini, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Caramelle, Biscotti, Pane biscottato, Cialde, Caramelle, Biscotti, Prodotti da forno dolci e salati, Aromi per la produzione di bevande e Preparati per l'elaborazione di bevande, Torte, Pasticceria, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Creme da spalmare, Dessert al gelato, Coni per gelati, Sorbetti e ghiaccioli allo yogurt, Miele, sciroppo di melassa, Confetteria, Ghiaccio e Pane; Attività di intermediazione nel settore della pasticceria, Prodotti da forno, Condimenti, Pizze, Quiche, Miele, Pasti a base di riso, Biscotti di riso e fiocchi di cereali; Vendita all'ingrosso - al dettaglio di tè, Estratti di tè, Di caffè, Bevande (a base di cacao), Integratori alimentari, Bastoni, Barrette proteiche ed energetiche, Dolciumi, confetteria, cioccolatini, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Caramelle, Biscotti, Pane biscottato, Cialde, Caramelle, Biscotti, Prodotti da forno dolci e salati, Aromi per la produzione di bevande e Preparati per l'elaborazione di bevande, Torte, Pasticceria, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Creme da spalmare, Dessert al gelato, Coni per gelati, Sorbetti e ghiaccioli allo yogurt, Miele, sciroppo di melassa, Confetteria, Ghiaccio, Pane e Pasticceria; Vendita al dettaglio di prodotti da forno, Condimenti, Pizze, Quiche, Miele, Pasti a base di riso, Biscotti di riso e fiocchi di cereali; Export - import di tè, Estratti di tè, Di caffè, Bevande (a base di cacao), Integratori alimentari, Bastoni, Barrette proteiche ed energetiche, Dolciumi, confetteria, cioccolatini, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Caramelle, Biscotti, Pane biscottato, Cialde, Caramelle, Biscotti, Prodotti da forno dolci e salati, Aromi per la produzione di bevande e Preparati per l'elaborazione di bevande, Torte, Pasticceria, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Creme da spalmare, Dessert al gelato, Coni per gelati, Sorbetti e ghiaccioli allo yogurt, Miele, sciroppo di melassa, Confetteria, Ghiaccio, Pane, Pasticceria e prodotti da forno; Vendita al dettaglio di condimenti, Pizze, Quiche, Miele, Pasti a base di riso, Biscotti di riso e fiocchi di cereali; Negozio online di tè, Estratti di tè, Di caffè, Bevande (a base di cacao), Integratori alimentari, Bastoni, Barrette proteiche ed energetiche, Dolciumi, confetteria, cioccolatini, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Caramelle, Biscotti, Pane biscottato, Cialde, Caramelle, Biscotti, Prodotti da forno dolci e salati, Aromi per la produzione di bevande e Preparati per l'elaborazione di bevande, Torte, Pasticceria, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Creme da spalmare, Dessert al gelato, Coni per gelati, Sorbetti e ghiaccioli allo yogurt, Miele, sciroppo di melassa, Confetteria, Ghiaccio, Pane, Pasticceria; Negozio online di prodotti da forno, Condimenti, Pizze, Quiche, Miele, Pasti a base di riso, Biscotti di riso e fiocchi di cereali; Telemarketing (servizi di televendite) di tè, Estratti di tè, Di caffè, Bevande (a base di cacao), Integratori alimentari, Bastoni, Barrette proteiche ed energetiche, Dolciumi, confetteria, cioccolatini, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Caramelle, Biscotti, Pane biscottato, Cialde, Caramelle, Biscotti, Prodotti da forno dolci e salati, Aromi per la produzione di bevande e Preparati per l'elaborazione di bevande, Torte, Pasticceria, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Creme da spalmare, Dessert al gelato, Coni per gelati, Sorbetti e ghiaccioli allo yogurt, Miele, sciroppo di melassa, Confetteria, Ghiaccio, Pane e Pasticceria; Telemarketing (servizi di televendita) di prodotti da forno, Condimenti, Pizze, Quiche, Miele, Pasti a base di riso, Biscotti di riso e fiocchi di cereali; Classificazione e distribuzione di beni per terze persone, Estratti di tè, Di caffè, Bevande (a base di cacao), Integratori alimentari, Bastoni, Barrette proteiche ed energetiche, Dolciumi, confetteria, cioccolatini, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Caramelle, Biscotti, Pane biscottato, Cialde, Caramelle, Biscotti, Prodotti da forno dolci e salati, Aromi per la produzione di bevande e Preparati per l'elaborazione di bevande, Torte, Pasticceria, Prodotti a base di cioccolato, Creme da spalmare, Dessert al gelato, Coni per gelati, Sorbetti e ghiaccioli allo yogurt, Miele, sciroppo di melassa, Confetteria, Ghiaccio, Pane e Pasticceria; Vendita di prodotti da forno per conto terzi, Condimenti, Pizze, Quiche, Miele, Pasti a base di riso, Biscotti di riso e fiocchi di cereali; Marketing; Distribuzione di campioni pubblicitari; Dimostrazione pratica di prodotti per scopi pubblicitari; Offerte di sconti; Pubblicità; Pubblicità e inserzione tramite ogni tipo di mezzo di comunicazione; Studi e analisi di mercato; UN'ATTIVITÀ DI CONSULENZA; Applicazione di un sistema per la promozione di vendita al dettaglio basato sul trattamento preferenziale dei clienti regolari; Servizi commerciali di un programma di fedeltà clienti esteso; Gestione commerciale; Amministrazione commerciale; Gestione e amministrazione aziendale; Pubblicità online; Servizi pubblicitari; Promozione aziendale; Layout per scopi pubblicitari; Servizi di marketing promozionale utilizzando mezzi audiovisivi; Web marketing; Diffusione di pubblicità via Internet; Servizi di pubblicità forniti via Internet; Noleggio di spazi pubblicitari su Internet; Pubblicità su Internet per conto terzi; Diffusione d'annunci pubblicitari per terzi via Internet; Promozione di prodotti e servizi per conto terzi tramite internet; Diffusione di annunci pubblicitari; Diffusione di materiale pubblicitario online; Pubblicità e marketing on-line; Pubblicità, compresa pubblicità on-line su una rete informatica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Pardavimų skatinimas ir prekyba; Internetu teikiamos skelbimų ir reklamos paslaugos, susijusios su komercija; Prekių demonstravimas internete; Tarpininkavimo veikla prekybos arbata srityje, Arbatos ekstraktai, Kavos gėrimai, Gėrimai (kakavos pagrindu), Maisto papildai, Lazdelės, Energetiniai ir baltyminiai batonėliai, Saldumynai, konditerijos gaminiai, šokoladiniai saldainiai, Šokoladiniai saldainiai, Saldainiai (ledinukai), Tešlainiai, Džiūvėsiai, Vafliai, Karamelės [saldainiai], Sausainiai, Saldūs ir sūrūs pyragai, Gėrimų gaminimo aromatai ir Gėrimų ruošimo preparatai, Tortai, Sausainėliai, Šokolado produktai, Užtepai, Ledų desertai, Kūginiai ledai, Šaldyti jogurtai ir šerbetai, Medus, melasa (sirupai), Saldumynai, Ledai ir Duona; Tarpininkavimo veikla prekybos konditerijos gaminiais srityje, Kepiniai, Prieskoniai, Picos, Kiaušinių plakinio pyragai su įdarais, Bičių produktų gaminiai, Patiekalai iš ryžių, Ryžių ir dribsnių sausainiai; Mažmeninė ir didmeninė prekyba arbata, Arbatos ekstraktai, Kavos gėrimai, Gėrimai (kakavos pagrindu), Maisto papildai, Lazdelės, Energetiniai ir baltyminiai batonėliai, Saldumynai, konditerijos gaminiai, šokoladiniai saldainiai, Šokoladiniai saldainiai, Saldainiai (ledinukai), Tešlainiai, Džiūvėsiai, Vafliai, Karamelės [saldainiai], Sausainiai, Saldūs ir sūrūs pyragai, Gėrimų gaminimo aromatai ir Gėrimų ruošimo preparatai, Tortai, Sausainėliai, Šokolado produktai, Užtepai, Ledų desertai, Kūginiai ledai, Šaldyti jogurtai ir šerbetai, Medus, melasa (sirupai), Saldumynai, Ledai, Duona ir Pyragas; Mažmeninė ir didmeninė prekyba konditerijos gaminiais ir duona, Prieskoniai, Picos, Kiaušinių plakinio pyragai su įdarais, Bičių produktų gaminiai, Patiekalai iš ryžių, Ryžių ir dribsnių sausainiai; Arbatos eksportas ir importas, Arbatos ekstraktai, Kavos gėrimai, Gėrimai (kakavos pagrindu), Maisto papildai, Lazdelės, Energetiniai ir baltyminiai batonėliai, Saldumynai, konditerijos gaminiai, šokoladiniai saldainiai, Šokoladiniai saldainiai, Saldainiai (ledinukai), Tešlainiai, Džiūvėsiai, Vafliai, Karamelės [saldainiai], Sausainiai, Saldūs ir sūrūs pyragai, Gėrimų gaminimo aromatai ir Gėrimų ruošimo preparatai, Tortai, Sausainėliai, Šokolado produktai, Užtepai, Ledų desertai, Kūginiai ledai, Šaldyti jogurtai ir šerbetai, Medus, melasa (sirupai), Saldumynai, Ledai, Duona, Pyragais ir kepiniais; Prieskonių importas ir eksportas, Picos, Kiaušinių plakinio pyragai su įdarais, Bičių produktų gaminiai, Patiekalai iš ryžių, Ryžių ir dribsnių sausainiai; Arbatos prekyba internetu (elektroninėje parduotuvėje), Arbatos ekstraktai, Kavos gėrimai, Gėrimai (kakavos pagrindu), Maisto papildai, Lazdelės, Energetiniai ir baltyminiai batonėliai, Saldumynai, konditerijos gaminiai, šokoladiniai saldainiai, Šokoladiniai saldainiai, Saldainiai (ledinukai), Tešlainiai, Džiūvėsiai, Vafliai, Karamelės [saldainiai], Sausainiai, Saldūs ir sūrūs pyragai, Gėrimų gaminimo aromatai ir Gėrimų ruošimo preparatai, Tortai, Sausainėliai, Šokolado produktai, Užtepai, Ledų desertai, Kūginiai ledai, Šaldyti jogurtai ir šerbetai, Medus, melasa (sirupai), Saldumynai, Ledai, Duona, Pyragas; Internetinė prekyba (elektroninė parduotuvė) konditerijos gaminiais ir duona, Prieskoniai, Picos, Kiaušinių plakinio pyragai su įdarais, Bičių produktų gaminiai, Patiekalai iš ryžių, Ryžių ir dribsnių sausainiai; Arbatos telerinkodara (pardavimai telefonu), Arbatos ekstraktai, Kavos gėrimai, Gėrimai (kakavos pagrindu), Maisto papildai, Lazdelės, Energetiniai ir baltyminiai batonėliai, Saldumynai, konditerijos gaminiai, šokoladiniai saldainiai, Šokoladiniai saldainiai, Saldainiai (ledinukai), Tešlainiai, Džiūvėsiai, Vafliai, Karamelės [saldainiai], Sausainiai, Saldūs ir sūrūs pyragai, Gėrimų gaminimo aromatai ir Gėrimų ruošimo preparatai, Tortai, Sausainėliai, Šokolado produktai, Užtepai, Ledų desertai, Kūginiai ledai, Šaldyti jogurtai ir šerbetai, Medus, melasa (sirupai), Saldumynai, Ledai, Duona ir Pyragas; Telerinkodaros (prekybos telefonu) konditerijos gaminių ir duonos srityje paslaugos, Prieskoniai, Picos, Kiaušinių plakinio pyragai su įdarais, Bičių produktų gaminiai, Patiekalai iš ryžių, Ryžių ir dribsnių sausainiai; Prekių su arbata pardavimas tretiesiems asmenims, Arbatos ekstraktai, Kavos gėrimai, Gėrimai (kakavos pagrindu), Maisto papildai, Lazdelės, Energetiniai ir baltyminiai batonėliai, Saldumynai, konditerijos gaminiai, šokoladiniai saldainiai, Šokoladiniai saldainiai, Saldainiai (ledinukai), Tešlainiai, Džiūvėsiai, Vafliai, Karamelės [saldainiai], Sausainiai, Saldūs ir sūrūs pyragai, Gėrimų gaminimo aromatai ir Gėrimų ruošimo preparatai, Tortai, Sausainėliai, Šokolado produktai, Užtepai, Ledų desertai, Kūginiai ledai, Šaldyti jogurtai ir šerbetai, Medus, melasa (sirupai), Saldumynai, Ledai, Duona ir Pyragas; Konditerijos gaminių ir duonos pardavimas tretiesiems asmenims, Prieskoniai, Picos, Kiaušinių plakinio pyragai su įdarais, Bičių produktų gaminiai, Patiekalai iš ryžių, Ryžių ir dribsnių sausainiai; Rinkodara; Reklaminių pavyzdžių paskirstymas (platinimas); Prekių rodymas; Nuolaidų pasiūlymai; Reklama; Reklama ir skelbimai, platinami visomis komunikacijos priemonėmis; Rinkos tyrimai ir analizė; Konsultavimo paslaugos; Mažmeninės prekybos reklamos sistema, taikoma kaip privilegijos lojaliems klientams; Komercinės paslaugos, susijusios su papildomomis klientų lojalumo skatinimo programomis; Komercinė vadyba; Verslo tvarkyba; Verslo vadyba ir administravimas; Internetinė reklama; Reklamos paslaugos; Verslo skatinimas; Maketavimo paslaugos reklamos tikslams; Skatinamoji rinkodara audiovizualinėje žiniasklaidoje; Internetinė rinkodara; Reklamos platinimas internetu; Reklamos paslaugos, teikiamos per internetą; Reklamos erdvės nuoma internete; Reklamavimas kitiems internete; Reklamos platinimas internetu (kitiems); Kitų tiekėjų prekių ir paslaugų reklamavimas internete; Reklamų skleidimas; Reklaminių skelbimų platinimas internetu; Internetinės reklamos ir rinkodaros paslaugos; Reklama, įskaitant tiesioginę reklamą kompiuterių tinkle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Noieta sekmēšana un preču mārketinga plānošana; Reklāmas un veicināšanas pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar tiešsaistes tirdzniecību internetā; Preču demonstrēšana internetā; Starpniecība tējas tirdzniecības jomā, Tējas ekstrakti, Kafija, Kakao dzērieni, Diētiskās piedevas, Nūjas, Enerģijas un proteīnu batoniņi, Konditorejas izstrādājumi, Šokolādes, Saldumu konditoreja, Cepumi, Sausiņi, Vafeles, Karameles, Biskvīti, Saldie un sāļie cepumi, Dzērienu pagatavošanai paredzētas garšvielas un Preparāti dzērienu pagatavošanai, Tortes, Saldumu konditoreja, Šokolādes produkti, Pastas, Saldējuma deserti, Saldējuma konusi, Saldēti jogurti un sorbeti, Medus, sīrups (sīrupi), Saldumi, Ledus un Maize; Starpniecība konditorejas izstrādājumu tirdzniecības jomā, Maizes produkti, Garšvielas, Picas, Pīrāgi, Biškopības produkti, Rīsu ēdieni, Rīsu sausiņi un graudaugu čipši; Tējas mazumtirdzniecība un vairumtirdzniecība, Tējas ekstrakti, Kafija, Kakao dzērieni, Diētiskās piedevas, Nūjas, Enerģijas un proteīnu batoniņi, Konditorejas izstrādājumi, Šokolādes, Saldumu konditoreja, Cepumi, Sausiņi, Vafeles, Karameles, Biskvīti, Saldie un sāļie cepumi, Dzērienu pagatavošanai paredzētas garšvielas un Preparāti dzērienu pagatavošanai, Tortes, Saldumu konditoreja, Šokolādes produkti, Pastas, Saldējuma deserti, Saldējuma konusi, Saldēti jogurti un sorbeti, Medus, sīrups (sīrupi), Saldumi, Ledus, Maize un Sviesta mīkla; Maizes produktu mazumtirdzniecība un vairumtirdzniecība, Garšvielas, Picas, Pīrāgi, Biškopības produkti, Rīsu ēdieni, Rīsu sausiņi un graudaugu čipši; Tējas eksports un imports, Tējas ekstrakti, Kafija, Kakao dzērieni, Diētiskās piedevas, Nūjas, Enerģijas un proteīnu batoniņi, Konditorejas izstrādājumi, Šokolādes, Saldumu konditoreja, Cepumi, Sausiņi, Vafeles, Karameles, Biskvīti, Saldie un sāļie cepumi, Dzērienu pagatavošanai paredzētas garšvielas un Preparāti dzērienu pagatavošanai, Tortes, Saldumu konditoreja, Šokolādes produkti, Pastas, Saldējuma deserti, Saldējuma konusi, Saldēti jogurti un sorbeti, Medus, sīrups (sīrupi), Saldumi, Ledus, Maize, Konditorejas izstrādājumi un maizes produkti; Garšvielu eksports un imports, Picas, Pīrāgi, Biškopības produkti, Rīsu ēdieni, Rīsu sausiņi un graudaugu čipši; Tējas tirdzniecība internetā (e-veikals), Tējas ekstrakti, Kafija, Kakao dzērieni, Diētiskās piedevas, Nūjas, Enerģijas un proteīnu batoniņi, Konditorejas izstrādājumi, Šokolādes, Saldumu konditoreja, Cepumi, Sausiņi, Vafeles, Karameles, Biskvīti, Saldie un sāļie cepumi, Dzērienu pagatavošanai paredzētas garšvielas un Preparāti dzērienu pagatavošanai, Tortes, Saldumu konditoreja, Šokolādes produkti, Pastas, Saldējuma deserti, Saldējuma konusi, Saldēti jogurti un sorbeti, Medus, sīrups (sīrupi), Saldumi, Ledus, Maize, Sviesta mīkla; Maizes produktu tirdzniecība internetā (e-veikals), Garšvielas, Picas, Pīrāgi, Biškopības produkti, Rīsu ēdieni, Rīsu sausiņi un graudaugu čipši; Tējas teletirgvedība (pārdošana pa telefonu), Tējas ekstrakti, Kafija, Kakao dzērieni, Diētiskās piedevas, Nūjas, Enerģijas un proteīnu batoniņi, Konditorejas izstrādājumi, Šokolādes, Saldumu konditoreja, Cepumi, Sausiņi, Vafeles, Karameles, Biskvīti, Saldie un sāļie cepumi, Dzērienu pagatavošanai paredzētas garšvielas un Preparāti dzērienu pagatavošanai, Tortes, Saldumu konditoreja, Šokolādes produkti, Pastas, Saldējuma deserti, Saldējuma konusi, Saldēti jogurti un sorbeti, Medus, sīrups (sīrupi), Saldumi, Ledus, Maize un Sviesta mīkla; Maizes produktu teletirgvedība (pārdošana pa telefonu), Garšvielas, Picas, Pīrāgi, Biškopības produkti, Rīsu ēdieni, Rīsu sausiņi un graudaugu čipši; Tējas pārdošana trešām personām, Tējas ekstrakti, Kafija, Kakao dzērieni, Diētiskās piedevas, Nūjas, Enerģijas un proteīnu batoniņi, Konditorejas izstrādājumi, Šokolādes, Saldumu konditoreja, Cepumi, Sausiņi, Vafeles, Karameles, Biskvīti, Saldie un sāļie cepumi, Dzērienu pagatavošanai paredzētas garšvielas un Preparāti dzērienu pagatavošanai, Tortes, Saldumu konditoreja, Šokolādes produkti, Pastas, Saldējuma deserti, Saldējuma konusi, Saldēti jogurti un sorbeti, Medus, sīrups (sīrupi), Saldumi, Ledus, Maize un Sviesta mīkla; Maizes produktu pārdošana trešām personām, Garšvielas, Picas, Pīrāgi, Biškopības produkti, Rīsu ēdieni, Rīsu sausiņi un graudaugu čipši; Tirgvedības pakalpojumi; Paraugu izplatīšana reklāmas nolūkos (izdalīšana); Preču demonstrēšanas pakalpojumi; Atlaižu akcijas; Reklāma; Reklāma un sludinājumi dažādos plašsaziņas līdzekļos; Tirgus izpēte un analīze; Konsultāciju sniegšana; Tādu sistēmu piemērošana, kas paredzētas mazumtirdzniecībai, kuras pamatā ir priekšrocību nodrošināšana pastāvīgajiem klientiem; Komercpakalpojumi saistībā ar klientu lojalitātes programmām; Komerciālā vadība; Uzņēmumu pārvaldīšana; Uzņēmējdarbības vadība, uzņēmējdarbības administrēšana; reklāma tiešsaistes režīmā; Publicitātes pakalpojumi; Uzņēmējdarbības veicināšana; Reklāmas materiālu maketēšana; Veicināšanas tirgvedības pakalpojumi ar audiovizuālo līdzekļu palīdzību; Interneta tirgvedība; Reklāmas izplatīšana ar interneta starpniecību; Reklāmas pakalpojumi, kas nodrošināti ar interneta starpniecību; Reklāmas platību noma internetā; Trešo personu reklamēšana internetā; Trešo personu reklāmas izplatīšana, izmantojot internetu; Preču un pakalpojumu veicināšana internetā citiem; Reklāmas izplatīšana; Reklāmas materiālu izplatīšana tiešsaistē; Reklāmas un tirgvedības pakalpojumi tiešsaistē; Reklāma, ieskaitot reklāmu tiešsaistē datoru tīklā.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' promozzjoni u l-bejgħ ta' merkanzija promozzjonali; Servizzi ta' reklamar u pubbliċitarji marbuta man-negozju pprovdut online fuq l-Internet; Preżentazzjoni ta' oġġetti anki fuq l-internet; Aġenzija kummerċjali fil-qasam tat-te, Estratti tat-te, Kafé, Xorb (fuq bażi ta' kawkaw), Supplimenti tad-dieta, Stikek, Bars li jagħtu l-enerġija u tal-proteini, Ħelu, prodotti tad-dolċier, Ċikkulata, Ħelu, Gallettini, Prodotti li jqarmċu, Waffles, Ħelu, Gallettini, Ħobż ħelu u bil-melħ, Essenzi għall-preparazzjoni ta' xarbiet u Preparazzjonijiet għat-tħejjija ta' xorb, Torti baxxi bi mili tal-frott, Patisserie, Prodotti taċ-ċikkulata, Ikel għat-tidlik, Deżerti iffriżati, Koni tal-ġelat, Jogurt iffriżat u sorbetti, Għasel, għasel iswed (ġulepp), Ħelu, Silġ u Ħobż; Senserija kummerċjali fil-qasam ta' prodotti tal-forn, Prodotti tal-ħami, Ħwawar, Pizez, Quiche, Prodotti magħmula minn prodotti tan-naħal, Dixxijiet tar-ross, Gallettini tar-ross u ċereali; Bejgħ bl-imnut/bl-ingrossa ta' te, Estratti tat-te, Kafé, Xorb (fuq bażi ta' kawkaw), Supplimenti tad-dieta, Stikek, Bars li jagħtu l-enerġija u tal-proteini, Ħelu, prodotti tad-dolċier, Ċikkulata, Ħelu, Gallettini, Prodotti li jqarmċu, Waffles, Ħelu, Gallettini, Ħobż ħelu u bil-melħ, Essenzi għall-preparazzjoni ta' xarbiet u Preparazzjonijiet għat-tħejjija ta' xorb, Torti baxxi bi mili tal-frott, Patisserie, Prodotti taċ-ċikkulata, Ikel għat-tidlik, Deżerti iffriżati, Koni tal-ġelat, Jogurt iffriżat u sorbetti, Għasel, għasel iswed (ġulepp), Ħelu, Silġ, Ħobż u Ikel bl-għaġina; Bejgħ bl-imnut u bl-ingrossa ta' prodotti tal-forn, Ħwawar, Pizez, Quiche, Prodotti magħmula minn prodotti tan-naħal, Dixxijiet tar-ross, Gallettini tar-ross u ċereali; Esportazzjoni/importazzjoni ta' te, Estratti tat-te, Kafé, Xorb (fuq bażi ta' kawkaw), Supplimenti tad-dieta, Stikek, Bars li jagħtu l-enerġija u tal-proteini, Ħelu, prodotti tad-dolċier, Ċikkulata, Ħelu, Gallettini, Prodotti li jqarmċu, Waffles, Ħelu, Gallettini, Ħobż ħelu u bil-melħ, Essenzi għall-preparazzjoni ta' xarbiet u Preparazzjonijiet għat-tħejjija ta' xorb, Torti baxxi bi mili tal-frott, Patisserie, Prodotti taċ-ċikkulata, Ikel għat-tidlik, Deżerti iffriżati, Koni tal-ġelat, Jogurt iffriżat u sorbetti, Għasel, għasel iswed (ġulepp), Ħelu, Silġ, Ħobż, Ħobż u ħelu; Esportazzjoni u importazzjoni ta' prodotti tat-togħma, Pizez, Quiche, Prodotti magħmula minn prodotti tan-naħal, Dixxijiet tar-ross, Gallettini tar-ross u ċereali; Bejgħ online (e-shop) b'rabta mat-te, Estratti tat-te, Kafé, Xorb (fuq bażi ta' kawkaw), Supplimenti tad-dieta, Stikek, Bars li jagħtu l-enerġija u tal-proteini, Ħelu, prodotti tad-dolċier, Ċikkulata, Ħelu, Gallettini, Prodotti li jqarmċu, Waffles, Ħelu, Gallettini, Ħobż ħelu u bil-melħ, Essenzi għall-preparazzjoni ta' xarbiet u Preparazzjonijiet għat-tħejjija ta' xorb, Torti baxxi bi mili tal-frott, Patisserie, Prodotti taċ-ċikkulata, Ikel għat-tidlik, Deżerti iffriżati, Koni tal-ġelat, Jogurt iffriżat u sorbetti, Għasel, għasel iswed (ġulepp), Ħelu, Silġ, Ħobż, Ikel bl-għaġina; Kummerċ onlajn (e-shop) ta' prodotti tal-forn, Ħwawar, Pizez, Quiche, Prodotti magħmula minn prodotti tan-naħal, Dixxijiet tar-ross, Gallettini tar-ross u ċereali; Telepromozzjoni (servizzi ta' telebejgħ) marbuta mat-te, Estratti tat-te, Kafé, Xorb (fuq bażi ta' kawkaw), Supplimenti tad-dieta, Stikek, Bars li jagħtu l-enerġija u tal-proteini, Ħelu, prodotti tad-dolċier, Ċikkulata, Ħelu, Gallettini, Prodotti li jqarmċu, Waffles, Ħelu, Gallettini, Ħobż ħelu u bil-melħ, Essenzi għall-preparazzjoni ta' xarbiet u Preparazzjonijiet għat-tħejjija ta' xorb, Torti baxxi bi mili tal-frott, Patisserie, Prodotti taċ-ċikkulata, Ikel għat-tidlik, Deżerti iffriżati, Koni tal-ġelat, Jogurt iffriżat u sorbetti, Għasel, għasel iswed (ġulepp), Ħelu, Silġ, Ħobż u Ikel bl-għaġina; Telekummerċjalizzazzjoni (telebejgħ) ta' prodotti tal-forn, Ħwawar, Pizez, Quiche, Prodotti magħmula minn prodotti tan-naħal, Dixxijiet tar-ross, Gallettini tar-ross u ċereali; Bejgħ ta' oġġetti għal oħrajn fil-qasam tat-te, Estratti tat-te, Kafé, Xorb (fuq bażi ta' kawkaw), Supplimenti tad-dieta, Stikek, Bars li jagħtu l-enerġija u tal-proteini, Ħelu, prodotti tad-dolċier, Ċikkulata, Ħelu, Gallettini, Prodotti li jqarmċu, Waffles, Ħelu, Gallettini, Ħobż ħelu u bil-melħ, Essenzi għall-preparazzjoni ta' xarbiet u Preparazzjonijiet għat-tħejjija ta' xorb, Torti baxxi bi mili tal-frott, Patisserie, Prodotti taċ-ċikkulata, Ikel għat-tidlik, Deżerti iffriżati, Koni tal-ġelat, Jogurt iffriżat u sorbetti, Għasel, għasel iswed (ġulepp), Ħelu, Silġ, Ħobż u Ikel bl-għaġina; Bejgħ ta' prodotti għal oħrajn b'rabta ma' prodotti tal-forn, Ħwawar, Pizez, Quiche, Prodotti magħmula minn prodotti tan-naħal, Dixxijiet tar-ross, Gallettini tar-ross u ċereali; Servizzi ta' kummerċjalizzazzjoni; It-tixrid (distribuzzjoni) ta' kampjuni bħala reklami; Dimostrazzjoni ta' prodotti; Kampanji promozzjonali; Reklamar; Promozzjoni u reklamar permezz tat-tipi kollha ta' midja; Riċerka u analiżi tas-suq; Attività ta' konsulenza; Użu ta' sistema għall-promozzjoni tal-bejgħ bl-imnut abbażi tal-preferenzi tal-klijenti regolari; Servizzi kummerċjali marbuta ma' programm għall-bini tal-lealtà tal-klijenti; Ġestjoni kummerċjali; L-amministrazzjoni ta' negozju; Ġestjoni u amministrazzjoni ta' negozju; Reklamar online; Servizzi ta' pubbliċità; Il-promozzjoni tan-negozju; Servizzi ta' taqsim/arranġament skond pjan għal skopijiet ta' reklamar; Servizzi ta' marketing promozzjonali bl-użu ta' mezzi awdjoviżivi; Marketing permezz ta' l-Internet; Tixrid ta' reklami permezz tal-Internet; Servizzi ta' reklamar ipprovduti permezz tal-Internet; Il-kiri ta' spazju għar-reklamar fuq l-Internet; Reklamar għal terzi persuni permezz tal-Internet; It-tixrid ta' reklamar għal oħrajn permezz tal-Internet; Il-promozzjoni ta' oġġetti u servizzi ta' oħrajn fuq l-Internet; It-tixrid ta' materjal ta' reklamar; Tixrid ta' materjal ta' reklamar online; Servizzi ta' reklamar u kummerċjalizzazzjoni onlajn; Reklamar, inklużi reklamar online fuq netwerk tal-kompjuters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Promotie en merchandising; Advertentie- en promotiediensten met betrekking tot onlinehandel via internet; Demonstratie van goederen, o.a. via internet; Bemiddeling op het gebied van de handel in thee, Thee-extracten, Koffie, Dranken (op basis van cacao), Voedingssupplementen, Sticks, Energie- en proteïnerepen, Suikerbakkerswaren, Producten van chocolade, Snoepgoed, Koekjes, Beschuiten, Wafels, Snoepgoed, Biscuits, Zoet en zout gebak, Smaakstoffen voor de bereiding van dranken en Preparaten voor de bereiding van dranken, Vlaaien, Banketbakkerswaren, Chocoladewaren, Smeersels, Ijsdesserten, Ijshoorntjes, Bevroren yoghurts en sorbets, Honing, melassestroop (siropen), Suikerbakkerswaren, Ijs en Brood; Bemiddeling bij de handel in gebak, Bakkerijproducten, Smaakstoffen, Pizza, Quiche, Imkerijproducten, Rijstgerechten, Rijstkoekjes en granenchips; Detailhandel-groothandel in theesoorten, Thee-extracten, Koffie, Dranken (op basis van cacao), Voedingssupplementen, Sticks, Energie- en proteïnerepen, Suikerbakkerswaren, Producten van chocolade, Snoepgoed, Koekjes, Beschuiten, Wafels, Snoepgoed, Biscuits, Zoet en zout gebak, Smaakstoffen voor de bereiding van dranken en Preparaten voor de bereiding van dranken, Vlaaien, Banketbakkerswaren, Chocoladewaren, Smeersels, Ijsdesserten, Ijshoorntjes, Bevroren yoghurts en sorbets, Honing, melassestroop (siropen), Suikerbakkerswaren, Ijs, Brood en banketbakkers-; Detailhandel-groothandel in bakkerijproducten, Smaakstoffen, Pizza, Quiche, Imkerijproducten, Rijstgerechten, Rijstkoekjes en granenchips; Import en export van thee, Thee-extracten, Koffie, Dranken (op basis van cacao), Voedingssupplementen, Sticks, Energie- en proteïnerepen, Suikerbakkerswaren, Producten van chocolade, Snoepgoed, Koekjes, Beschuiten, Wafels, Snoepgoed, Biscuits, Zoet en zout gebak, Smaakstoffen voor de bereiding van dranken en Preparaten voor de bereiding van dranken, Vlaaien, Banketbakkerswaren, Chocoladewaren, Smeersels, Ijsdesserten, Ijshoorntjes, Bevroren yoghurts en sorbets, Honing, melassestroop (siropen), Suikerbakkerswaren, Ijs, Brood, Gebak en bakkerijproducten; Export-import van smaakstoffen, Pizza, Quiche, Imkerijproducten, Rijstgerechten, Rijstkoekjes en granenchips; Internetwinkel (e-shop) met theesoorten, Thee-extracten, Koffie, Dranken (op basis van cacao), Voedingssupplementen, Sticks, Energie- en proteïnerepen, Suikerbakkerswaren, Producten van chocolade, Snoepgoed, Koekjes, Beschuiten, Wafels, Snoepgoed, Biscuits, Zoet en zout gebak, Smaakstoffen voor de bereiding van dranken en Preparaten voor de bereiding van dranken, Vlaaien, Banketbakkerswaren, Chocoladewaren, Smeersels, Ijsdesserten, Ijshoorntjes, Bevroren yoghurts en sorbets, Honing, melassestroop (siropen), Suikerbakkerswaren, Ijs, Brood, banketbakkers-; Internetwinkel (e-shop) met bakkerijproducten, Smaakstoffen, Pizza, Quiche, Imkerijproducten, Rijstgerechten, Rijstkoekjes en granenchips; Telemarketing (telefonische verkoop) met betrekking tot theesoorten, Thee-extracten, Koffie, Dranken (op basis van cacao), Voedingssupplementen, Sticks, Energie- en proteïnerepen, Suikerbakkerswaren, Producten van chocolade, Snoepgoed, Koekjes, Beschuiten, Wafels, Snoepgoed, Biscuits, Zoet en zout gebak, Smaakstoffen voor de bereiding van dranken en Preparaten voor de bereiding van dranken, Vlaaien, Banketbakkerswaren, Chocoladewaren, Smeersels, Ijsdesserten, Ijshoorntjes, Bevroren yoghurts en sorbets, Honing, melassestroop (siropen), Suikerbakkerswaren, Ijs, Brood en banketbakkers-; Telemarketing (telefonische verkoop) met betrekking tot bakkerijproducten, Smaakstoffen, Pizza, Quiche, Imkerijproducten, Rijstgerechten, Rijstkoekjes en granenchips; Verkoop van waren voor derden in de vorm van thee, Thee-extracten, Koffie, Dranken (op basis van cacao), Voedingssupplementen, Sticks, Energie- en proteïnerepen, Suikerbakkerswaren, Producten van chocolade, Snoepgoed, Koekjes, Beschuiten, Wafels, Snoepgoed, Biscuits, Zoet en zout gebak, Smaakstoffen voor de bereiding van dranken en Preparaten voor de bereiding van dranken, Vlaaien, Banketbakkerswaren, Chocoladewaren, Smeersels, Ijsdesserten, Ijshoorntjes, Bevroren yoghurts en sorbets, Honing, melassestroop (siropen), Suikerbakkerswaren, Ijs, Brood en banketbakkers-; Verkoop van artikelen voor derden in de vorm van bakkerijproducten, Smaakstoffen, Pizza, Quiche, Imkerijproducten, Rijstgerechten, Rijstkoekjes en granenchips; Marketing; Verspreiding (levering) van reclamemonsters; Demonstratie van producten; Kortingsacties; Reclame; Reclame en publiciteit via allerlei soorten media; Marktonderzoek en -analyse; Advisering; Het toepassen van een systeem voor de stimulering van de detailhandel, gebaseerd op de bevoordeling van vaste klanten; Zakelijke diensten in het kader van een loyaliteitsprogramma voor klanten; Commercieel management; Zakelijke administratie; Commercieel-zakelijk beheer en commercieel-zakelijke administratie; Reclame [on-line]; Diensten op het gebied van reclamemaken; Promotie (Zakelijke -); Lay-out verzorging voor publicitaire doeleinden; Promotionele marketing met behulp van audiovisuele media; Internetmarketing; Verspreiding van reclame via het internet; Reclame via het Internet; Verhuur van advertentieruimte op het Internet; Reclame voor anderen op het internet; Verspreiding van reclame voor derden via internet; Promoten van goederen en diensten van anderen op het internet; Verspreiding van reclame; Onlineverspreiding van reclamemateriaal; on-line reclame en marketing diensten; Reclame, waaronder onlinereclame op een computernetwerk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi promocyjne i promowanie towarów; Usługi ogłoszeniowe i reklamowe dotyczące handlu udzielane online przez internet; Pokazy towarów w internecie; Pośrednictwo w dziedzinie handlu herbatą, Ekstrakty herbaciane, Kawowe, Napoje (na bazie kakao), Suplementy diety, Przetyczki, Energetycznymi i proteinowymi batonami, Słodycze, wyroby cukiernicze, wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladki, Słodycze [cukierki], Herbatnikami, Suchary, Waflami, Cukierków, Biszkopty, Słodkim i słonym pieczywem, Aromatami do produkcji napojów i Preparatów do sporządzania napojów, Tarty (z owocami), Wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladowymi wyrobami, Pasty [do smarowania pieczywa], Desery lodowe, Rożki do lodów, Mrożonymi jogurtami i sorbetami, Miód, melasa (syropy), Słodycze, Lodem i Chleb; Pośrednictwo w dziedzinie handlu pieczywem, Wyrobami piekarskimi, Dodatkami smakowymi, Pizze, Quichem, Produkty pszczele, Potrawami ryżowymi, Ryżowymi ciastkami i płatkami zbożowymi; Handel detaliczny i hurtowy herbatą, Ekstrakty herbaciane, Kawowe, Napoje (na bazie kakao), Suplementy diety, Przetyczki, Energetycznymi i proteinowymi batonami, Słodycze, wyroby cukiernicze, wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladki, Słodycze [cukierki], Herbatnikami, Suchary, Waflami, Cukierków, Biszkopty, Słodkim i słonym pieczywem, Aromatami do produkcji napojów i Preparatów do sporządzania napojów, Tarty (z owocami), Wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladowymi wyrobami, Pasty [do smarowania pieczywa], Desery lodowe, Rożki do lodów, Mrożonymi jogurtami i sorbetami, Miód, melasa (syropy), Słodycze, Lodem, Chleb i Ciasta; Sprzedaż detaliczna i hurtowa wyrobów piekarniczych, Dodatkami smakowymi, Pizze, Quichem, Produkty pszczele, Potrawami ryżowymi, Ryżowymi ciastkami i płatkami zbożowymi; Eksport i import herbaty, Ekstrakty herbaciane, Kawowe, Napoje (na bazie kakao), Suplementy diety, Przetyczki, Energetycznymi i proteinowymi batonami, Słodycze, wyroby cukiernicze, wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladki, Słodycze [cukierki], Herbatnikami, Suchary, Waflami, Cukierków, Biszkopty, Słodkim i słonym pieczywem, Aromatami do produkcji napojów i Preparatów do sporządzania napojów, Tarty (z owocami), Wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladowymi wyrobami, Pasty [do smarowania pieczywa], Desery lodowe, Rożki do lodów, Mrożonymi jogurtami i sorbetami, Miód, melasa (syropy), Słodycze, Lodem, Chleb, Pieczywa i wyrobów piekarniczych; Eksport i import dodatkami smakowymi, Pizze, Quichem, Produkty pszczele, Potrawami ryżowymi, Ryżowymi ciastkami i płatkami zbożowymi; Handel internetowy (e-shop) herbatą, Ekstrakty herbaciane, Kawowe, Napoje (na bazie kakao), Suplementy diety, Przetyczki, Energetycznymi i proteinowymi batonami, Słodycze, wyroby cukiernicze, wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladki, Słodycze [cukierki], Herbatnikami, Suchary, Waflami, Cukierków, Biszkopty, Słodkim i słonym pieczywem, Aromatami do produkcji napojów i Preparatów do sporządzania napojów, Tarty (z owocami), Wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladowymi wyrobami, Pasty [do smarowania pieczywa], Desery lodowe, Rożki do lodów, Mrożonymi jogurtami i sorbetami, Miód, melasa (syropy), Słodycze, Lodem, Chleb, Ciasta; Handel internetowy (e-shop) wyrobami piekarniczymi, Dodatkami smakowymi, Pizze, Quichem, Produkty pszczele, Potrawami ryżowymi, Ryżowymi ciastkami i płatkami zbożowymi; Telemarketing (usługi telesprzedaży) związany z herbatą, Ekstrakty herbaciane, Kawowe, Napoje (na bazie kakao), Suplementy diety, Przetyczki, Energetycznymi i proteinowymi batonami, Słodycze, wyroby cukiernicze, wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladki, Słodycze [cukierki], Herbatnikami, Suchary, Waflami, Cukierków, Biszkopty, Słodkim i słonym pieczywem, Aromatami do produkcji napojów i Preparatów do sporządzania napojów, Tarty (z owocami), Wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladowymi wyrobami, Pasty [do smarowania pieczywa], Desery lodowe, Rożki do lodów, Mrożonymi jogurtami i sorbetami, Miód, melasa (syropy), Słodycze, Lodem, Chleb i Ciasta; Telemarketing (sprzedaż telefoniczna) wyrobów piekarniczych, Dodatkami smakowymi, Pizze, Quichem, Produkty pszczele, Potrawami ryżowymi, Ryżowymi ciastkami i płatkami zbożowymi; Sprzedaż towarów na rzecz innych osób w związku z herbatą, Ekstrakty herbaciane, Kawowe, Napoje (na bazie kakao), Suplementy diety, Przetyczki, Energetycznymi i proteinowymi batonami, Słodycze, wyroby cukiernicze, wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladki, Słodycze [cukierki], Herbatnikami, Suchary, Waflami, Cukierków, Biszkopty, Słodkim i słonym pieczywem, Aromatami do produkcji napojów i Preparatów do sporządzania napojów, Tarty (z owocami), Wyroby cukiernicze, Czekoladowymi wyrobami, Pasty [do smarowania pieczywa], Desery lodowe, Rożki do lodów, Mrożonymi jogurtami i sorbetami, Miód, melasa (syropy), Słodycze, Lodem, Chleb i Ciasta; Sprzedaż towarów na rzecz innych osób w związku z wyrobami piekarniczymi, Dodatkami smakowymi, Pizze, Quichem, Produkty pszczele, Potrawami ryżowymi, Ryżowymi ciastkami i płatkami zbożowymi; Usługi marketingowe; Rozpowszechnianie (dystrybucja) próbek reklamowych; Pokazy towarów; Akcje promocyjne; Reklama; Promowanie i ogłoszenia za pośrednictwem wszystkich rodzajów mediów; Badania i analizy rynkowe; DZIAŁALNOŚĆ DORADCZA; Zastosowanie systemu wspierającego handel detaliczny opierającego się na promowaniu stałych klientów; Usługi handlowe uzupełniającego lojalnościowego programu dla klientów; Zarządzanie działalnością handlową; Administrowanie działalności gospodarczej; Administrowanie i zarządzanie działalnością gospodarczą; Reklama w internecie; Usługi w zakresie reklamy; Promowanie działalności gospodarczej; Usługi w zakresie opracowania graficznego do celów reklamowych; Usługi promocyjno-marketingowe przy użyciu mediów audiowizualnych; Marketing internetowy; Rozpowszechnianie reklam poprzez Internet; Usługi reklamowe za pośrednictwem Internetu; Wynajem przestrzeni reklamowej w Internecie; Reklama w Internecie dla osób trzecich; Rozpowszechnianie reklam na rzecz osób trzecich przez Internet; Promowanie towarów i usług osób trzecich w Internecie; Rozpowszechnianie reklam; Rozpowszechnianie materiałów reklamowych w internecie; Reklama online i usługi marketingowe; Usługi reklamowe, w tym reklama on-line w sieci komputerowej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Promoções e merchandising; Serviços de anúncios classificados e de promoção no domínio do comércio, prestados em linha via Internet; Demonstração de produtos na Internet; Serviços de mediação no domínio do comércio de chá, Extratos de chá, De café, Bebidas (à base de cacau), Complementos alimentares, Varetas, Barras energéticas e proteicas, Guloseimas, doçarias, confeitaria, Produtos em chocolate, Guloseimas, Bolachas, Biscoitarias, Waffles, Guloseimas, Biscoitos, Produtos de padaria doces e salgados, Aromas para o fabrico de bebidas e Preparações para a elaboração de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelaria, Produtos de chocolate, Pastas para barrar, Sobremesas geladas, Cones para gelados, Iogurtes gelados e sorvetes, Mel, xarope de melaço, Doçarias, Gelo e Pão; Serviços de mediação no domínio do comércio de produtos de padaria, Produtos de panificação, Condimentos, Pizzas, Quiches, Produtos à base de produtos apícolas, Refeições à base de arroz, Bolachas de arroz e flocos de cereais; Venda a retalho e por grosso de chás, Extratos de chá, De café, Bebidas (à base de cacau), Complementos alimentares, Varetas, Barras energéticas e proteicas, Guloseimas, doçarias, confeitaria, Produtos em chocolate, Guloseimas, Bolachas, Biscoitarias, Waffles, Guloseimas, Biscoitos, Produtos de padaria doces e salgados, Aromas para o fabrico de bebidas e Preparações para a elaboração de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelaria, Produtos de chocolate, Pastas para barrar, Sobremesas geladas, Cones para gelados, Iogurtes gelados e sorvetes, Mel, xarope de melaço, Doçarias, Gelo, Pão e Pastelaria; Comércio a retalho/por grosso de produtos de panificação, Condimentos, Pizzas, Quiches, Produtos à base de produtos apícolas, Refeições à base de arroz, Bolachas de arroz e flocos de cereais; Exportação/importação de chás, Extratos de chá, De café, Bebidas (à base de cacau), Complementos alimentares, Varetas, Barras energéticas e proteicas, Guloseimas, doçarias, confeitaria, Produtos em chocolate, Guloseimas, Bolachas, Biscoitarias, Waffles, Guloseimas, Biscoitos, Produtos de padaria doces e salgados, Aromas para o fabrico de bebidas e Preparações para a elaboração de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelaria, Produtos de chocolate, Pastas para barrar, Sobremesas geladas, Cones para gelados, Iogurtes gelados e sorvetes, Mel, xarope de melaço, Doçarias, Gelo, Pão, Produtos de padaria e de panificação; Exportação/importação de condimentos, Pizzas, Quiches, Produtos à base de produtos apícolas, Refeições à base de arroz, Bolachas de arroz e flocos de cereais; Comércio eletrónico (loja na Internet) de chás, Extratos de chá, De café, Bebidas (à base de cacau), Complementos alimentares, Varetas, Barras energéticas e proteicas, Guloseimas, doçarias, confeitaria, Produtos em chocolate, Guloseimas, Bolachas, Biscoitarias, Waffles, Guloseimas, Biscoitos, Produtos de padaria doces e salgados, Aromas para o fabrico de bebidas e Preparações para a elaboração de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelaria, Produtos de chocolate, Pastas para barrar, Sobremesas geladas, Cones para gelados, Iogurtes gelados e sorvetes, Mel, xarope de melaço, Doçarias, Gelo, Pão, Pastelaria; Comércio eletrónico (loja na Internet) de produtos de panificação, Condimentos, Pizzas, Quiches, Produtos à base de produtos apícolas, Refeições à base de arroz, Bolachas de arroz e flocos de cereais; Telemarketing (televendas) de chás, Extratos de chá, De café, Bebidas (à base de cacau), Complementos alimentares, Varetas, Barras energéticas e proteicas, Guloseimas, doçarias, confeitaria, Produtos em chocolate, Guloseimas, Bolachas, Biscoitarias, Waffles, Guloseimas, Biscoitos, Produtos de padaria doces e salgados, Aromas para o fabrico de bebidas e Preparações para a elaboração de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelaria, Produtos de chocolate, Pastas para barrar, Sobremesas geladas, Cones para gelados, Iogurtes gelados e sorvetes, Mel, xarope de melaço, Doçarias, Gelo, Pão e Pastelaria; Telemarketing (vendas por telefone) de produtos de panificação, Condimentos, Pizzas, Quiches, Produtos à base de produtos apícolas, Refeições à base de arroz, Bolachas de arroz e flocos de cereais; Venda de chá para terceiros, Extratos de chá, De café, Bebidas (à base de cacau), Complementos alimentares, Varetas, Barras energéticas e proteicas, Guloseimas, doçarias, confeitaria, Produtos em chocolate, Guloseimas, Bolachas, Biscoitarias, Waffles, Guloseimas, Biscoitos, Produtos de padaria doces e salgados, Aromas para o fabrico de bebidas e Preparações para a elaboração de bebidas, Tortas, Pastelaria, Produtos de chocolate, Pastas para barrar, Sobremesas geladas, Cones para gelados, Iogurtes gelados e sorvetes, Mel, xarope de melaço, Doçarias, Gelo, Pão e Pastelaria; Venda de mercadoria para terceiros, especificamente de produtos de panificação, Condimentos, Pizzas, Quiches, Produtos à base de produtos apícolas, Refeições à base de arroz, Bolachas de arroz e flocos de cereais; Serviços de marketing; Difusão (distribuição) de amostras publicitárias; Demonstração de produtos; Promoções; Publicidade; Promoção e anúncios através de todo o tipo de meios de comunicação social; Estudos e análises de mercados; Atividade de consultoria; Operação de sistemas de promoção de vendas a retalho, baseados em benefícios para clientes habituais; Serviços comerciais relacionados com programas complementares de fidelização de clientes; Gestão comercial; Administração comercial; Administração e gestão empresarial; Publicidade on-line; Serviços de publicidade; Promoção de negócios comerciais; Serviços de paginação [layout] para fins publicitários; Serviços de marketing promocional, através de meios audiovisuais; Marketing de Internet; Divulgação de anúncios através da Internet; Serviços de publicidade prestados através da Internet; Aluguer de espaços publicitários na Internet; Publicidade para terceiros na Internet; Difusão de publicidade para terceiros através da internet; Promoção de produtos e serviços de terceiros através da Internet; Difusão de publicidade; Difusão de material publicitário on-line; Serviços de publicidade e marketing em linha; Publicidade, incluindo publicidade online em redes informáticas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Promovare şi comercializare; Servicii de mică publicitate și de promovare legate de comerț oferite online pe internet; Prezentare de marfă prin intermediul internetului; Activitate de intermediere în domeniul comerțului cu ceai, Extracte de ceai, Băuturi pe bază de cafea, Băuturi (pe bază de cacao), Suplimente nutritive, Batoane, Batoane energetice și proteice, Produse de cofetărie, Produse de ciocolată, Dulciuri (bomboane), Napolitane, Crutoane, Vafe, Caramele, Biscuiți, Produse de patiserie dulci și sărate, Arome pentru fabricarea de băuturi şi Produse pentru prepararea de băuturi, Tarte, Produse de patiserie, Produse cu ciocolată, Paste tartinabile, Deserturi din îngheţată, Îngheţată la cornet, Iaurturi congelate și sorbeturi, Miere, melasă, Produse de cofetărie, Gheață şi Pâine; Activitate de intermediere în domeniul comerțului cu produse de panificație, Produse de brutărie, Condimente, Pizza, Tarte, Preparate din produse apicole, Mâncăruri cu orez, Biscuiți din orez și fulgi de cereale; Vânzare cu amănuntul și cu ridicata de ceai, Extracte de ceai, Băuturi pe bază de cafea, Băuturi (pe bază de cacao), Suplimente nutritive, Batoane, Batoane energetice și proteice, Produse de cofetărie, Produse de ciocolată, Dulciuri (bomboane), Napolitane, Crutoane, Vafe, Caramele, Biscuiți, Produse de patiserie dulci și sărate, Arome pentru fabricarea de băuturi şi Produse pentru prepararea de băuturi, Tarte, Produse de patiserie, Produse cu ciocolată, Paste tartinabile, Deserturi din îngheţată, Îngheţată la cornet, Iaurturi congelate și sorbeturi, Miere, melasă, Produse de cofetărie, Gheață, Pâine şi Patiserie; Vânzare cu amănuntul și cu ridicata de produse de brutărie, Condimente, Pizza, Tarte, Preparate din produse apicole, Mâncăruri cu orez, Biscuiți din orez și fulgi de cereale; Export și import de ceai, Extracte de ceai, Băuturi pe bază de cafea, Băuturi (pe bază de cacao), Suplimente nutritive, Batoane, Batoane energetice și proteice, Produse de cofetărie, Produse de ciocolată, Dulciuri (bomboane), Napolitane, Crutoane, Vafe, Caramele, Biscuiți, Produse de patiserie dulci și sărate, Arome pentru fabricarea de băuturi şi Produse pentru prepararea de băuturi, Tarte, Produse de patiserie, Produse cu ciocolată, Paste tartinabile, Deserturi din îngheţată, Îngheţată la cornet, Iaurturi congelate și sorbeturi, Miere, melasă, Produse de cofetărie, Gheață, Pâine, Produse de panificație și de brutărie; Export și import de condimente, Pizza, Tarte, Preparate din produse apicole, Mâncăruri cu orez, Biscuiți din orez și fulgi de cereale; Vânzare pe internet (e-shop) de ceai, Extracte de ceai, Băuturi pe bază de cafea, Băuturi (pe bază de cacao), Suplimente nutritive, Batoane, Batoane energetice și proteice, Produse de cofetărie, Produse de ciocolată, Dulciuri (bomboane), Napolitane, Crutoane, Vafe, Caramele, Biscuiți, Produse de patiserie dulci și sărate, Arome pentru fabricarea de băuturi şi Produse pentru prepararea de băuturi, Tarte, Produse de patiserie, Produse cu ciocolată, Paste tartinabile, Deserturi din îngheţată, Îngheţată la cornet, Iaurturi congelate și sorbeturi, Miere, melasă, Produse de cofetărie, Gheață, Pâine, Patiserie; Vânzare pe internet (e-shop) de produse de panificație, Condimente, Pizza, Tarte, Preparate din produse apicole, Mâncăruri cu orez, Biscuiți din orez și fulgi de cereale; Telemarketing (vânzare prin telefon) de ceai, Extracte de ceai, Băuturi pe bază de cafea, Băuturi (pe bază de cacao), Suplimente nutritive, Batoane, Batoane energetice și proteice, Produse de cofetărie, Produse de ciocolată, Dulciuri (bomboane), Napolitane, Crutoane, Vafe, Caramele, Biscuiți, Produse de patiserie dulci și sărate, Arome pentru fabricarea de băuturi şi Produse pentru prepararea de băuturi, Tarte, Produse de patiserie, Produse cu ciocolată, Paste tartinabile, Deserturi din îngheţată, Îngheţată la cornet, Iaurturi congelate și sorbeturi, Miere, melasă, Produse de cofetărie, Gheață, Pâine şi Patiserie; Telemarketing (servicii de vânzare prin telefon) de produse de brutărie, Condimente, Pizza, Tarte, Preparate din produse apicole, Mâncăruri cu orez, Biscuiți din orez și fulgi de cereale; Vânzare de ceai către terți, Extracte de ceai, Băuturi pe bază de cafea, Băuturi (pe bază de cacao), Suplimente nutritive, Batoane, Batoane energetice și proteice, Produse de cofetărie, Produse de ciocolată, Dulciuri (bomboane), Napolitane, Crutoane, Vafe, Caramele, Biscuiți, Produse de patiserie dulci și sărate, Arome pentru fabricarea de băuturi şi Produse pentru prepararea de băuturi, Tarte, Produse de patiserie, Produse cu ciocolată, Paste tartinabile, Deserturi din îngheţată, Îngheţată la cornet, Iaurturi congelate și sorbeturi, Miere, melasă, Produse de cofetărie, Gheață, Pâine şi Patiserie; Vânzare pentru terți de produse de brutărie, Condimente, Pizza, Tarte, Preparate din produse apicole, Mâncăruri cu orez, Biscuiți din orez și fulgi de cereale; Servicii de marketing; Difuzare (distribuire) de esantioane publicitare; Prezentare de produse; Campanii de reducere de prețuri; Publicitate; Promovare şi mica publicitate prin intermediul tuturor tipurilor de media; Cercetare şi analiză de piaţă; Activitate de consultanță; Aplicarea unui sistem de promovare de vânzări cu amănuntul bazate pe privilegii acordate clienților fideli; Servicii comerciale referitoare la programe complementare de fidelizare a clienților; Managementul activităţilor comerciale; Administraţie comercială; Managementul şi administrarea afacerilor; Publicitate on-line; Servicii de reclamă şi publicitate; Promovarea comercială; Servicii de layout în scopuri publicitare; Servicii de marketing promoţional folosind mijloace audiovizuale; Marketing pe Internet; Difuzare de anunţuri publicitare prin Internet; Servicii de publicitate furnizate pe Internet; Închiriere de spaţiu publicitar pe Internet; Publicitate pentru terţi pe internet; Difuzarea publicităţii pe Internet pentru terţi; Promovarea produselor şi serviciilor altor persoane prin internet; Difuzare de anunţuri; Difuzare de materiale publicitare online; Servicii de publicitate online şi marketing; Publicitate, inclusiv publicitatea online în reţele informatice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Propagácia a marketing; Inzertné a propagačné služby týkajúce sa obchodu, poskytované online prostredníctvom internetu; Predvádzanie tovaru prostredníctvom internetu; Sprostredkovateľská činnosť v oblasti obchodu s čajmi, Čajovými výťažkami, Kávové, Nápoje na báze kakaa, Potravinové doplnky, Palice, Energetickými a proteínovými tyčinkami, Cukrovinky, sladkosti, cukríky, Čokolády, Pralinky, sušienkami, Sucháre, oblátkami, Karamelky (cukríky), Biskvity, Sladkým a slaným pečivom, Príchuťami na výrobu nápojov a Prípravky na výrobu nápojov, Torty, Patiséria, Čokoládovými výrobkami, Nátierky, Mrazené zákusky, Zmrzlinnové kornútky, Mrazenými jogurtami a šerbetmi, Med, melasa (sirupy), Cukroviniek, Ľadom a Chlieb; Sprostredkovateľská činnosť v oblasti obchodu s pečivom, Pekárskymi výrobkami, Chuťovými prísadami, Pizze, Kišom, Výrobky z včelích produktov, Ryžovými pokrmami, Ryžovými sušienkami a cereálnymi lupienkami; Maloobchod a veľkoobchod s čajmi, Čajovými výťažkami, Kávové, Nápoje na báze kakaa, Potravinové doplnky, Palice, Energetickými a proteínovými tyčinkami, Cukrovinky, sladkosti, cukríky, Čokolády, Pralinky, sušienkami, Sucháre, oblátkami, Karamelky (cukríky), Biskvity, Sladkým a slaným pečivom, Príchuťami na výrobu nápojov a Prípravky na výrobu nápojov, Torty, Patiséria, Čokoládovými výrobkami, Nátierky, Mrazené zákusky, Zmrzlinnové kornútky, Mrazenými jogurtami a šerbetmi, Med, melasa (sirupy), Cukroviniek, Ľadom, Chlieb a Sladké pečivo; Maloobchod a veľkoobchod so zameraním na pekárske výrobky, Chuťovými prísadami, Pizze, Kišom, Výrobky z včelích produktov, Ryžovými pokrmami, Ryžovými sušienkami a cereálnymi lupienkami; Dovoz a vývoz čajov, Čajovými výťažkami, Kávové, Nápoje na báze kakaa, Potravinové doplnky, Palice, Energetickými a proteínovými tyčinkami, Cukrovinky, sladkosti, cukríky, Čokolády, Pralinky, sušienkami, Sucháre, oblátkami, Karamelky (cukríky), Biskvity, Sladkým a slaným pečivom, Príchuťami na výrobu nápojov a Prípravky na výrobu nápojov, Torty, Patiséria, Čokoládovými výrobkami, Nátierky, Mrazené zákusky, Zmrzlinnové kornútky, Mrazenými jogurtami a šerbetmi, Med, melasa (sirupy), Cukroviniek, Ľadom, Chlieb, Pečivo a pekárske výrobky; Dovoz a vývoz so zameraním na chuťové prísady, Pizze, Kišom, Výrobky z včelích produktov, Ryžovými pokrmami, Ryžovými sušienkami a cereálnymi lupienkami; Internetový obchod (e-shop) s čajmi, Čajovými výťažkami, Kávové, Nápoje na báze kakaa, Potravinové doplnky, Palice, Energetickými a proteínovými tyčinkami, Cukrovinky, sladkosti, cukríky, Čokolády, Pralinky, sušienkami, Sucháre, oblátkami, Karamelky (cukríky), Biskvity, Sladkým a slaným pečivom, Príchuťami na výrobu nápojov a Prípravky na výrobu nápojov, Torty, Patiséria, Čokoládovými výrobkami, Nátierky, Mrazené zákusky, Zmrzlinnové kornútky, Mrazenými jogurtami a šerbetmi, Med, melasa (sirupy), Cukroviniek, Ľadom, Chlieb, Sladké pečivo; Internetový obchod (e-shop) so zameraním na pekárske výrobky, Chuťovými prísadami, Pizze, Kišom, Výrobky z včelích produktov, Ryžovými pokrmami, Ryžovými sušienkami a cereálnymi lupienkami; Telemarketing (predaj prostredníctvom telefónu) so zameraním na čaje, Čajovými výťažkami, Kávové, Nápoje na báze kakaa, Potravinové doplnky, Palice, Energetickými a proteínovými tyčinkami, Cukrovinky, sladkosti, cukríky, Čokolády, Pralinky, sušienkami, Sucháre, oblátkami, Karamelky (cukríky), Biskvity, Sladkým a slaným pečivom, Príchuťami na výrobu nápojov a Prípravky na výrobu nápojov, Torty, Patiséria, Čokoládovými výrobkami, Nátierky, Mrazené zákusky, Zmrzlinnové kornútky, Mrazenými jogurtami a šerbetmi, Med, melasa (sirupy), Cukroviniek, Ľadom, Chlieb a Sladké pečivo; Telemarketing (predaj prostredníctvom telefónu) so zameraním na pekárske výrobky, Chuťovými prísadami, Pizze, Kišom, Výrobky z včelích produktov, Ryžovými pokrmami, Ryžovými sušienkami a cereálnymi lupienkami; Predaj tovaru s čajmi pre tretie osoby, Čajovými výťažkami, Kávové, Nápoje na báze kakaa, Potravinové doplnky, Palice, Energetickými a proteínovými tyčinkami, Cukrovinky, sladkosti, cukríky, Čokolády, Pralinky, sušienkami, Sucháre, oblátkami, Karamelky (cukríky), Biskvity, Sladkým a slaným pečivom, Príchuťami na výrobu nápojov a Prípravky na výrobu nápojov, Torty, Patiséria, Čokoládovými výrobkami, Nátierky, Mrazené zákusky, Zmrzlinnové kornútky, Mrazenými jogurtami a šerbetmi, Med, melasa (sirupy), Cukroviniek, Ľadom, Chlieb a Sladké pečivo; Predaj tovaru pre tretie osoby so zameraním na pekárske výrobky, Chuťovými prísadami, Pizze, Kišom, Výrobky z včelích produktov, Ryžovými pokrmami, Ryžovými sušienkami a cereálnymi lupienkami; Marketing; Rozširovanie (distribúcia) reklamných vzoriek; Predvádzanie tovaru; Zľavové akcie; Reklamné služby; Propagácia a inzercia prostredníctvom všetkých druhov médií; Prieskum a analýza trhu; Konzultačná činnosť; Uplatňovanie systému na podporu maloobchodného predaja založeného na zvýhodnení stálych zákazníkov; Obchodné služby nadstavbového vernostného zákazníckeho programu; Komerčný manažment; Obchodná administratíva; Obchodná administratíva a manažment; Reklama on-line; Propagačné a reklamné služby; Obchodná reklama; Grafická úprava tlačovín na reklamné účely; Propagačné marketingové služby využívajúce audiovizuálne médiá; Internetový marketing; Šírenie reklám prostredníctvom internetu; Reklamné služby poskytované prostredníctvom internetu; Prenájom reklamného priestoru na internete; Reklama na internete pre tretie osoby; Šírenie reklamy pre tretie osoby prostredníctvom internetu; Propagovanie tovaru a služieb klientov prostredníctvom internetu; Rozširovanie reklamných oznamov; Šírenie reklamných materiálov online; On-line reklama a marketingové služby; Reklama vrátane on-line reklamy na počítačovej sieti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Promocijske storitve in trgovanje; Oglaševalske in promocijske storitve v zvezi s trgovino, nudene preko spleta na internetu; Predstavitve blaga preko interneta; Posredniška dejavnost na področju trgovine s čaji, Čajni ekstrakti, Kavne, Pijače (na osnovi kakava), Dodatki k prehrani, Paličice, Energijske in beljakovinske tablice, Slaščice, Čokoladni proizvodi, Bonboni, Polnjeni piškoti, Prepečenec, Oblati, Bomboni, Piškoti, Sladko in slano pecivo, Arome za izdelavo pijač in Pripravki za proizvodnjo pijač, Kolač z nadevom (običajno sadnim), Drobno pecivo, Čokoladni izdelki, Namazi, Ledeni deserti, Korneti za sladoled, Zmrznjeni jogurti in sorbeti, Med, melasni sirup, Sladkarije, Led in Kruh; Posredniška dejavnost na področju trgovine s pecivom, Pekovski izdelki, Začimbni dodatki jedem, Pizze, Quichem, Izdelki iz čebeljih proizvodov, Riževe jedi, Riževi piškoti in žitni otrobi; Maloprodaja in veleprodaja čajev, Čajni ekstrakti, Kavne, Pijače (na osnovi kakava), Dodatki k prehrani, Paličice, Energijske in beljakovinske tablice, Slaščice, Čokoladni proizvodi, Bonboni, Polnjeni piškoti, Prepečenec, Oblati, Bomboni, Piškoti, Sladko in slano pecivo, Arome za izdelavo pijač in Pripravki za proizvodnjo pijač, Kolač z nadevom (običajno sadnim), Drobno pecivo, Čokoladni izdelki, Namazi, Ledeni deserti, Korneti za sladoled, Zmrznjeni jogurti in sorbeti, Med, melasni sirup, Sladkarije, Led, Kruh in Tortno pecivo; Maloprodaja-veleprodaja pekovskih izdelkov, Začimbni dodatki jedem, Pizze, Quichem, Izdelki iz čebeljih proizvodov, Riževe jedi, Riževi piškoti in žitni otrobi; Izvoz in uvoz čajev, Čajni ekstrakti, Kavne, Pijače (na osnovi kakava), Dodatki k prehrani, Paličice, Energijske in beljakovinske tablice, Slaščice, Čokoladni proizvodi, Bonboni, Polnjeni piškoti, Prepečenec, Oblati, Bomboni, Piškoti, Sladko in slano pecivo, Arome za izdelavo pijač in Pripravki za proizvodnjo pijač, Kolač z nadevom (običajno sadnim), Drobno pecivo, Čokoladni izdelki, Namazi, Ledeni deserti, Korneti za sladoled, Zmrznjeni jogurti in sorbeti, Med, melasni sirup, Sladkarije, Led, Kruh, Pecivo in pekovski izdelki; Izvoz-uvoz začimbnih dodatkov jedem, Pizze, Quichem, Izdelki iz čebeljih proizvodov, Riževe jedi, Riževi piškoti in žitni otrobi; Internetna trgovina (e-trgovina) s čaji, Čajni ekstrakti, Kavne, Pijače (na osnovi kakava), Dodatki k prehrani, Paličice, Energijske in beljakovinske tablice, Slaščice, Čokoladni proizvodi, Bonboni, Polnjeni piškoti, Prepečenec, Oblati, Bomboni, Piškoti, Sladko in slano pecivo, Arome za izdelavo pijač in Pripravki za proizvodnjo pijač, Kolač z nadevom (običajno sadnim), Drobno pecivo, Čokoladni izdelki, Namazi, Ledeni deserti, Korneti za sladoled, Zmrznjeni jogurti in sorbeti, Med, melasni sirup, Sladkarije, Led, Kruh, Tortno pecivo; Internetna trgovina (e-trgovina) pekovskih izdelkov, Začimbni dodatki jedem, Pizze, Quichem, Izdelki iz čebeljih proizvodov, Riževe jedi, Riževi piškoti in žitni otrobi; Trženje čajev po telefonu (prodaja po telefonu), Čajni ekstrakti, Kavne, Pijače (na osnovi kakava), Dodatki k prehrani, Paličice, Energijske in beljakovinske tablice, Slaščice, Čokoladni proizvodi, Bonboni, Polnjeni piškoti, Prepečenec, Oblati, Bomboni, Piškoti, Sladko in slano pecivo, Arome za izdelavo pijač in Pripravki za proizvodnjo pijač, Kolač z nadevom (običajno sadnim), Drobno pecivo, Čokoladni izdelki, Namazi, Ledeni deserti, Korneti za sladoled, Zmrznjeni jogurti in sorbeti, Med, melasni sirup, Sladkarije, Led, Kruh in Tortno pecivo; Prodaja po televiziji (prodaja po telefonu) pekovskih izdelkov, Začimbni dodatki jedem, Pizze, Quichem, Izdelki iz čebeljih proizvodov, Riževe jedi, Riževi piškoti in žitni otrobi; Prodaja čajnih izdelkov za druge, Čajni ekstrakti, Kavne, Pijače (na osnovi kakava), Dodatki k prehrani, Paličice, Energijske in beljakovinske tablice, Slaščice, Čokoladni proizvodi, Bonboni, Polnjeni piškoti, Prepečenec, Oblati, Bomboni, Piškoti, Sladko in slano pecivo, Arome za izdelavo pijač in Pripravki za proizvodnjo pijač, Kolač z nadevom (običajno sadnim), Drobno pecivo, Čokoladni izdelki, Namazi, Ledeni deserti, Korneti za sladoled, Zmrznjeni jogurti in sorbeti, Med, melasni sirup, Sladkarije, Led, Kruh in Tortno pecivo; Prodaja pekovskih izdelkov za druge, Začimbni dodatki jedem, Pizze, Quichem, Izdelki iz čebeljih proizvodov, Riževe jedi, Riževi piškoti in žitni otrobi; Storitve trženja; Širjenje (razdeljevanje) reklamnih vzorcev blaga; Predstavitev izdelkov; Razprodaje; Oglasna dejavnost; Promocija in oglaševanje preko vseh vrst medijev; Raziskava in analiza tržišča; SVETOVALNA DEJAVNOST; Uporaba sistema za promocijo maloprodaje na osnovi preferenc rednih kupcev; Storitve programa poslovne zvestobe za stranke; Komercialno upravljanje; Poslovna administracija; Poslovno upravljanje in administracija; Reklamno spletno oglaševanje; Propagandne storitve; Poslovna promocija; Storitve urejanja v oglaševalske namene; Storitve promocijskega trženja z uporabo avdiovizualnih medijev; Trženje preko interneta; Širjenje oglasov preko interneta; Oglaševalske storitve preko interneta; Najem oglaševalskega prostora na internetu; Internetno oglaševanje za tretje osebe; Razširjanje reklamnih sporočil za tretje preko interneta; Promocija blaga in storitev drugih na internetu; Širjenje oglasov; Širjenje oglaševalskega materiala preko spleta; Spletno oglaševanje in trženjske storitve; Oglaševanje, vključno s spletnim oglaševanjem prek računalniškega omrežja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Marknadsföring och försäljning; Reklam- och pr-tjänster relaterade till handel online via internet; Demonstration av varor, bl.a. på Internet; Förmedlingsverksamhet avseende handel med te, Teextrakt, Kaffe-, Drycker (kakaobaserade), Tillsatser för livsmedel, Pinnar, Energi- och proteinstänger, Godsaker, sötsaker, konfekt, Chokladvaror, Godis, Småkakor, Skorpor, Med våfflor, Godis, Biskvier, Söta och salta bakverk, Smaker för framställning av drycker och Preparat för framställning av drycker, Mördegstårtor, Konditori, Chokladprodukter, Bredbara pålägg, Glassefterrätter, Glasstrutar, Yoghurtglass och sorbet, Honung, sirap, Sötsaker, Is och Bröd; Förmedlingsverksamhet avseende handel med bakverk, Bageriprodukter, Smaktillsatser, Pizzor, Quicher, Varor av biprodukter, Risrätter, Riskex och spannmålschips; Detalj- och grosshandel med te, Teextrakt, Kaffe-, Drycker (kakaobaserade), Tillsatser för livsmedel, Pinnar, Energi- och proteinstänger, Godsaker, sötsaker, konfekt, Chokladvaror, Godis, Småkakor, Skorpor, Med våfflor, Godis, Biskvier, Söta och salta bakverk, Smaker för framställning av drycker och Preparat för framställning av drycker, Mördegstårtor, Konditori, Chokladprodukter, Bredbara pålägg, Glassefterrätter, Glasstrutar, Yoghurtglass och sorbet, Honung, sirap, Sötsaker, Is, Bröd och Konditori-; Detaljhandel och partihandel med bageriprodukter, Smaktillsatser, Pizzor, Quicher, Varor av biprodukter, Risrätter, Riskex och spannmålschips; Export-import av te, Teextrakt, Kaffe-, Drycker (kakaobaserade), Tillsatser för livsmedel, Pinnar, Energi- och proteinstänger, Godsaker, sötsaker, konfekt, Chokladvaror, Godis, Småkakor, Skorpor, Med våfflor, Godis, Biskvier, Söta och salta bakverk, Smaker för framställning av drycker och Preparat för framställning av drycker, Mördegstårtor, Konditori, Chokladprodukter, Bredbara pålägg, Glassefterrätter, Glasstrutar, Yoghurtglass och sorbet, Honung, sirap, Sötsaker, Is, Bröd, Med bakverk och bageriprodukter; Export-import av smaktillsatser, Pizzor, Quicher, Varor av biprodukter, Risrätter, Riskex och spannmålschips; Internethandel (e-handel) med te, Teextrakt, Kaffe-, Drycker (kakaobaserade), Tillsatser för livsmedel, Pinnar, Energi- och proteinstänger, Godsaker, sötsaker, konfekt, Chokladvaror, Godis, Småkakor, Skorpor, Med våfflor, Godis, Biskvier, Söta och salta bakverk, Smaker för framställning av drycker och Preparat för framställning av drycker, Mördegstårtor, Konditori, Chokladprodukter, Bredbara pålägg, Glassefterrätter, Glasstrutar, Yoghurtglass och sorbet, Honung, sirap, Sötsaker, Is, Bröd, Konditori-; Internethandel (e-handel) med bageriprodukter, Smaktillsatser, Pizzor, Quicher, Varor av biprodukter, Risrätter, Riskex och spannmålschips; Telemarknadsföring (telefonförsäljning) av te, Teextrakt, Kaffe-, Drycker (kakaobaserade), Tillsatser för livsmedel, Pinnar, Energi- och proteinstänger, Godsaker, sötsaker, konfekt, Chokladvaror, Godis, Småkakor, Skorpor, Med våfflor, Godis, Biskvier, Söta och salta bakverk, Smaker för framställning av drycker och Preparat för framställning av drycker, Mördegstårtor, Konditori, Chokladprodukter, Bredbara pålägg, Glassefterrätter, Glasstrutar, Yoghurtglass och sorbet, Honung, sirap, Sötsaker, Is, Bröd och Konditori-; Telemarknadsföring (telefonförsäljning) med bageriprodukter, Smaktillsatser, Pizzor, Quicher, Varor av biprodukter, Risrätter, Riskex och spannmålschips; Försäljning av varor för tredje part med te, Teextrakt, Kaffe-, Drycker (kakaobaserade), Tillsatser för livsmedel, Pinnar, Energi- och proteinstänger, Godsaker, sötsaker, konfekt, Chokladvaror, Godis, Småkakor, Skorpor, Med våfflor, Godis, Biskvier, Söta och salta bakverk, Smaker för framställning av drycker och Preparat för framställning av drycker, Mördegstårtor, Konditori, Chokladprodukter, Bredbara pålägg, Glassefterrätter, Glasstrutar, Yoghurtglass och sorbet, Honung, sirap, Sötsaker, Is, Bröd och Konditori-; Försäljning av varor för tredje part avseende bageriprodukter, Smaktillsatser, Pizzor, Quicher, Varor av biprodukter, Risrätter, Riskex och spannmålschips; Marknadsföringstjänster; Distribution av reklamvaruprover; Varudemonstrationer; Prissänkningsaktiviteter; Annons- och reklamverksamhet; Reklam och annonsering medelst alla slags media; Marknadsstudier och -analyser; Konsultverksamhet; Tillämpning av ett system för stöd till detaljhandelsförsäljning baserad på stamkunders förmåner; Affärstjänster avseende utvidgning av kundtrohetsprogrammet; Kommersiell företagsledning; Företagsadministration; Företagsledning och företagsadministration; Online annonsering; Reklamtjänster; Främjande av företag; Layout-tjänster för reklamändamål; Säljfrämjande marknadsföringstjänster med användning av audiovisuella medier; Internetmarknadsföring; Distribution av reklam via internet; Annons- och reklamtjänster via internet; Uthyrning av reklamutrymme på Internet; Reklam för andra på internet; Spridning av reklam för andras räkning via Internet; Reklam för varor och tjänster via internet åt andra; Spridning av reklamannonser; Spridning av reklammaterial online; Annons- och reklamverksamhet och marknadsföring online; Reklam, inklusive reklam online via datornätverk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>38</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Комуникационни услуги през компютърни мрежи; Предоставяне на данни, информация или изображения и пренос на новини и информация с изображения с помощта на интернет; Телекомуникационни услуги; Видео стрийминг; Предоставяне на телекомуникационен достъп до видео и аудио съдържание чрез онлайн услуга за видео по заявка; Предоставяне на телекомуникационен достъп до видео съдържание чрез интернет; Предоставяне на телекомуникационен достъп до телевизионни програми, осигурявани чрез услуги за достъп при поискване; Предоставяне на телекомуникационен достъп до филми и телевизионни програми, осигурени чрез услуги за видео по заявка; Излъчване по кабелна телевизия; Излъчване на аудиовизуално и мултимедийно съдържание чрез интернет; Излъчване на програми през интернет; Излъчване на видеозаписи по поръчка; Предаване на мултимедийно съдържание чрез интернет; Стрийминг на аудиовизуален материал по интернет; Излъчване на видео и аудио програми чрез интернет; Стрийминг на аудио и видео материали по интернет; Услуги за видео-, аудио- и телевизионен стрийминг; Стрийминг на аудио, видео и аудио-визуални материали чрез глобална компютърна мрежа.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Počítačová síťová komunikace; poskytování dat, informací nebo obrázků a přenos zpráv a obrazových informací pomocí Internetu; telekomunikační služby; videovysílaní; poskytování telekomunikačního přístupu k video a audio obsahu poskytovanému prostřednictvím on-line služby video na objednávku; poskytování telekomunikačního přístupu k videoobsahu poskytované prostřednictvím internetu; poskytování telekomunikačního přístupu k televizním pořadům prostřednictvím služby video na objednávku; poskytování telekomunikačního přístupu k filmům a televizním pořadům prostřednictvím služby video na objednávku; vysílání kabelové televize; vysílání audiovizuálního a multimediálního obsahu prostřednictvím internetu; vysílání programů přes internet; přenos videa na vyžádání; přenos multimediálního obsahu prostřednictvím internetu; streaming videomateriálu na internetu; vysílání video a audio programů prostřednictvím internetu; streaming audio a video materiálů na internetu; video, audio a televizní streaming; streaming zvukového, vizuálního a audiovizuálního materiálu prostřednictvím globální počítačové sítě.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kommunikationsvirksomhed via computernetværk; Udbydelse af data, information eller billeder og transmission af meddelelser og billedinformation via internettet; Telekommunikation; Video-streaming; Tilvejebringelse af telekommunikationsadgang til video- og lydindhold udbudt via video on demand; Tilvejebringelse af telekommunikationsadgang til videoindhold udbudt via internettet; Tilvejebringelse af telekommunikationsadgang til tv-programmer via video-on-demand; Tilvejebringelse af telekommunikationsadgang til film og tv-programmer udbudt via video on demand; Kabel-TV- transmission; Udsendelse af audiovisuelt indhold og multimedieindhold via internettet; Udsendelse af programmer via internettet; Transmission af videoer mod betaling [video-on-demand]; Transmission af multimedieindhold via internettet; Streaming af visuelt materiale på internettet; Transmission af video- og lydprogrammer via internettet; Streaming af lyd- og videomateriale på internettet; Tjenester vedrørende video-, lyd- og tv-streaming; Streaming af lyd- og billedmateriale samt af audiovisuelt materiale via et globalt computernetværk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kommunikationsdienste über Computernetzwerke; Bereitstellung von Daten, Informationen oder Bildern und Nachrichten- und Bildübermittlung über das Internet; Telekommunikationsdienste; Video-Streaming; Bereitstellung eines Telekommunikationszugangs zu On-Demand-Video- und Audioinhalten; Bereitstellung eines Telekommunikationszugangs zu Videos im Internet; Bereitstellung eines Telekommunikationszugangs zu On-Demand-Fernsehsendungen; Bereitstellung des Telekommunikationszugangs zu Filmen und Fernsehprogrammen über einen Video-on-Demand-Dienst; Ausstrahlung von Kabelfernsehsendungen; Ausstrahlung von audiovisuellen und multimedialen Inhalten über das Internet; Ausstrahlung von Programmen über das Internet; Videoübertragungen auf Anfrage; Übertragung von Multimediainhalten über das Internet; Streaming von Bildmaterial im Internet; Übertragung von Video- und Audioprogrammen über das Internet; Streaming von Ton- und Bildmaterial im Internet; Streaming von Video, Audio und Fernsehen; Streaming von Ton-, Bild- und audiovisuellem Material über ein weltweites Computernetz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες επικοινωνιών μέσω ηλεκτρονικών δικτύων· Παροχή δεδομένων, πληροφοριών ή εικόνων και μετάδοση ειδήσεων και πληροφοριών εικόνας με τη βοήθεια του Διαδικτύου· Υπηρεσίες τηλεπικοινωνίας· Δυναμικό βίντεο· Παροχή τηλεπικοινωνιακής πρόσβασης σε περιεχόμενο βίντεο και ήχου που διατίθεται μέσω διαδικτυακής υπηρεσίας βίντεο κατά παραγγελία· Παροχή τηλεπικοινωνιακής πρόσβασης σε περιεχόμενο βίντεο που διατίθεται μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Παροχή τηλεπικοινωνιακής πρόσβασης σε τηλεοπτικά προγράμματα που διατίθενται μέσω υπηρεσίας βίντεο κατά παραγγελία· Παροχή τηλεπικοινωνιακής πρόσβασης σε κινηματογραφικές ταινίες και τηλεοπτικά προγράμματα που διατίθενται μέσω υπηρεσίας βίντεο κατά παραγγελία· Εκπομπή καλωδιακής τηλεόρασης· Εκπομπή οπτικοακουστικού και πολυμεσικού περιεχομένου μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Εκπομπή προγραμμάτων μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Μεταδόσεις βίντεο κατά παραγγελία· Μετάδοση περιεχομένου πολυμέσων μέσω Διαδικτύου· Συνεχής ροή οπτικού υλικού στο Διαδίκτυο· Εκπομπή προγραμμάτων βίντεο και ήχου μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Συνεχής ροή ήχου και βίντεο στο Διαδίκτυο· Υπηρεσίες συνεχούς ροής βίντεο, ήχου και τηλεόρασης· Συνεχής ροή ακουστικού, οπτικού και οπτικοακουστικού υλικού μέσω παγκόσμιου ηλεκτρονικού δικτύου.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Communication services over computer networks; Providing data, information or images and transmission of messages and images via the internet; Telecommunication services; Video streaming; Provision of telecommunication access to video and audio content provided via an online video-on-demand service; Provision of telecommunication access to video content provided via the Internet; Provision of telecommunication access to television programs provided via an on-demand service; Provision of telecommunication access to films and television programs provided via a video-on-demand service; Cable television broadcasting; Broadcasting of audiovisual and multimedia content via the Internet; Broadcasting of programmes via the internet; Video-on-demand transmission services; Transmission of multimedia content via the Internet; streaming of visual material on the internet; Broadcasting of video and audio programming over the Internet; Streaming audio and video material on the Internet; Video, audio and television streaming services; Streaming of audio, visual and audiovisual material via a global computer network.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de comunicaciones a través de redes de ordenadores; Suministro de datos, información o imágenes y transmisión de mensajes e información visual a través de Internet; Servicios de telecomunicaciones; Flujo de vídeo; Servicios de acceso por medios de telecomunicación a contenidos de vídeo y de audio disponibles mediante un servicio en línea de vídeo a la carta; Servicios de acceso por medios de telecomunicación a contenidos de vídeo disponibles en Internet; Servicios de acceso por medios de telecomunicación a programas de televisión disponibles mediante un servicio a la carta; Servicios de acceso por medios de telecomunicación a películas y programas de televisión disponibles mediante un servicio de vídeo a la carta; Servicios de televisión por cable; Difusión de contenidos audiovisuales y multimedia por Internet; Emisión de programas a través de Internet; Transmisiones de video a demanda; Transmisión de contenidos multimedia por Internet; Emisión continua de materiales visuales a través de Internet; Difusión de programación de vídeo y audio a través de Internet; Difusión continua de contenidos de audio y de vídeo por Internet; Servicios de difusión continua de contenidos de vídeo y de audio; Emisión en continuo de contenidos de audio, visuales y audiovisuales a través de redes informáticas mundiales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Sideteenused arvutivõrgu kaudu; Andmete, teabe või kujutiste pakkumine ning teadete ja kujutisteabe edastamine interneti teel; Sideteenused; Video voogedastus; Videolaenutuse teel pakutavale video- ja audiosisule juurdepääsu pakkumine; Interneti vahendusel pakutavale videosisule juurdepääsu pakkumine; Videolaenutuse teel pakutavatele telesaadetele juurdepääsu pakkumine; Videolaenutuse teel pakutavatele filmidele ja telesaadetele juurdepääsu pakkumine; Kaabeltelevisioonisaadete edastamine, kaabellevi; Audiovisuaal- ja multimeediasisu levitamine Interneti kaudu; Saadete edastamine interneti vahendusel; Videoülekanded nõudmisel; Multimeediasisu edastamine Interneti kaudu; Videomaterjali voogedastus Internetis; Heli- ja videosaadete ülekandmine internetis; Audio- ja videomaterjali voogedastus Internetis; Video, audio ja televisiooni voogedastamise teenused; Audio-, visuaal- ja audiovisuaalmaterjali voogedastus ülemaailmse arvutivõrgu kaudu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Viestintäpalvelut tietokoneverkkojen välityksellä; Datan, tietojen tai kuvien tarjoaminen ja sanomien ja kuvatietojen siirto Internetin välityksellä; Kaukoviestintä; Videon suoratoisto; Tietoliikenneyhteyden tarjoaminen online-tilausvideopalvelun kautta tarjottavaan kuva- ja äänisisältöön; Tietoliikenneyhteyden tarjoaminen Internetin välityksellä tarjottavaan kuvasisältöön; Tietoliikenneyhteyden tarjoaminen tilausvideopalvelun kautta tarjottaviin televisio-ohjelmiin; Tietoliikenneyhteyden tarjoaminen tilausvideopalvelun kautta tarjottaviin elokuviin ja televisio-ohjelmiin; Kaapelitelevisiolähetys; Audiovisuaalisen sisällön ja multimediasisällön lähetys Internetin välityksellä; Ohjelmien lähetys Internetin välityksellä; Tilauksesta tapahtuvat videonsiirtopalvelut; Multimediasisällön siirto Internetin kautta; Kuvamateriaalin suoratoisto Internetissä; Ääni- ja videolähetyspalvelut Internetin kautta; Ääni- ja kuvamateriaalin suoratoisto Internetissä; Videon, äänen ja television suoratoistopalvelut; Ääni-, kuva- ja audiovisuaalisen materiaalin suoratoisto maailmanlaajuisen tietokoneverkon kautta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de communications par réseaux informatiques; Mise à disposition de données, d'informations ou d'images et transmission de messages et d'informations visuelles par le biais de l'internet; Services de télécommunications; Lecture vidéo en transit; Fourniture d'accès de télécommunication à des contenus vidéo et audio fournis par un service en ligne de vidéo à la demande; Fourniture d'accès de télécommunication à des contenus vidéo fournis par Internet; Fourniture d'accès de télécommunication à des émissions télévisées fournies par un service à la demande; Fourniture d'accès de télécommunication à des films et des émissions télévisées fournis par un service de vidéo à la demande; Télévision par câble; Diffusion de contenus audiovisuels et multimédias par Internet; Diffusion de programmes via Internet; Services de transmission de vidéos à la demande; Transmission de contenus multimédias par Internet; Lecture en transit de contenu visuel sur l'internet; Diffusion de programmes vidéo et audio sur Internet; Diffusion en flux de contenus audio et vidéo sur Internet; Services de transmission en flux de vidéo et d'audio; Diffusion en continu de contenus audio, visuels et audiovisuels par le biais d'un réseau informatique mondial.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Komunikacijske usluge putem računalnih mreža; Pružanje podataka, informacija ili slika i prijenos poruka i slikovnih informacija putem interneta; Telekomunikacijske usluge; Video streaming; Davanje telekomunikacijskog pristupa video i audio sadržaju koji se pruža putem online usluge videa na zahtjev; Davanje telekomunikacijskog pristupa video sadržaju koji se pruža putem Interneta; Davanje telekomunikacijskog pristupa televizijskim programima koji se pružaju putem usluge na zahtjev; Davanje telekomunikacijskog pristupa filmskim i televizijskim programima koji se pružaju putem usluge videa na zahtjev; Emitiranje kabelske televizije; Emitiranje audiovizualnog i multimedijskog sadržaja putem Interneta; Emitiranje programa putem Interneta; Prijenosi video sadržaja na zahtjev; Prijenos multimedijskog sadržaja putem Interneta; Prijenos uživo vizualnog materijala na internetu; Emitiranje video i audio programa putem Interneta; Prijenos audio i video materijala na Internetu; Usluge streaminga videa, zvuka i televizije; Strujanje audiomaterijala, vizualnih materijala i audiovizualnih materijala putem globalne računalne mreže.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kommunikációs szolgáltatások számítógépes hálózatokon keresztül; Adatok, információk vagy képek biztosítása, üzenetek és képinformációk átvitele az interneten keresztül; Távközlési szolgáltatások; Video-streaming szolgáltatás; Online video-on-demand szolgáltatáson keresztül biztosított video- és audiotartalmakhoz való hozzáférés rendelkezésre bocsátása; Az internet segítségével biztosított videotartalmakhoz való telekommunikációs hozzáférés; Igény szerinti szolgáltatás keretében rendelkezésre bocsátott televízió-műsorokhoz való telekommunikációs hozzáférés biztosítása; Online video-on-demand szolgáltatáson keresztül biztosított filmekhez és televízió-műsorokhoz való hozzáférés rendelkezésre bocsátása; Kábeltelevíziós műsorszórás; Audiovizuális és multimédiás tartalom közvetítése az interneten keresztül; Műsorközvetítés interneten keresztül; Video-on-demand szolgáltatások; Multimédiás tartalmak interneten keresztül történő továbbítása; Vizuális anyagok folyamatos sugárzása az interneten; Video- és audioműsorok közvetítése az interneten keresztül; Internetes audio- és video streaming [egyidejű vagy azonnali adatfolyam]; Adatfolyamos (streaming) video-, audio- és televíziós szolgáltatások; Audio-, vizuális és audiovizuális anyagok adatfolyamos sugárzása globális számítógépes hálózaton keresztül.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di comunicazione su reti informatiche; Fornitura di dati, informazioni o immagini e trasmissioni di messaggi e informazioni visive via internet; Servizi di telecomunicazione; Videostreaming; Fornitura di servizi d'accesso tramite telecomunicazione a contenuti audio e video disponibili per mezzo di servizi video online on-demand; Fornitura di servizi d'accesso tramite telecomunicazione a contenuti video disponibili su internet; Fornitura di servizi d'accesso tramite telecomunicazione a programmi televisivi disponibili per mezzo di servizi on-demand; Fornitura di servizi d'accesso tramite telecomunicazione a film e programmi televisivi disponibili per mezzo di servizi video on-demand; Telediffusione via cavo; Trasmissione di contenuti audiovisivi e multimediali tramite internet; Trasmissione di programmi su Internet; Trasmissioni di video su richiesta; Trasmissione di contenuti multimediali tramite internet; Streaming di materiale video su Internet; Trasmissione di programmi video e audio su Internet; Trasmissione in continuo di materiali audio e video su internet; Servizi audio, video e televisivi in streaming; Diffusione continua di materiale sonoro, visivo e audiovisivo attraverso una rete informatica mondiale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Ryšių paslaugos kompiuterių tinklais; Duomenų, informacijos arba vaizdų viešinimas, naujienų ir vaizdo informacijos perdavimas internetu; Telekomunikacijų paslaugos; Vaizdo perdavimas internetu; Vaizdo ir garso turinio telekomunikacinės prieigos teikimas, naudojantis vaizdo pagal pareikalavimą paslauga internetu; Telekomunikacijų prieigos prie vaizdo turinio, teikiamo internetu, teikimas; Televizijos programų, teikiamų naudojantis vaizdo pagal pareikalavimą paslauga, telekomunikacinės prieigos teikimas; Naudojantis vaizdo pagal pareikalavimą paslauga teikiamų filmų ir televizijos programų telekomunikacinės prieigos teikimas; Kabelinės televizijos transliavimas; Audiovizualinio ir multimedijos turinio transliacijos internetu; Programų transliavimas per internetą; Vaizdo transliacija pagal pareikalavimą; Multimedijos turinio perdavimas internetu; Vaizdinės medžiagos srautinis siuntimas internete; Vaizdo ir garso programų transliavimas internetu; Garso ir vaizdo medžiagos srautinė transliacija internete; Vaizdo, garso ir televizijos srautinio siuntimo paslaugos; Srautinis garso, vaizdo ir audiovizualinės medžiagos perdavimas visuotiniu kompiuterių tinklu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Datortīklu sakaru pakalpojumi; Datu, informācijas vai attēlu publicēšana un ziņu un attēlu informācijas pārsūtīšana ar interneta starpniecību; Telesakaru pakalpojumi; Video straumēšana; Telekomunikācijas piekļuves nodrošināšana video un audio saturam, kas nodrošināts ar pieprasījumvideo pakalpojumu starpniecību tiešsaistē; Telekomunikāciju piekļuves nodrošināšana video saturam, kas tiek nodrošināts internetā; Telekomunikāciju piekļuves nodrošināšana televīzijas raidījumiem, kas nodrošināti pēc pieprasījuma; Telekomunikāciju piekļuves nodrošināšana filmām un televīzijas raidījumiem, kas nodrošināti ar pieprasījumvideo pakalpojumu starpniecību; Kabeļtelevīzijas apraide; Audiovizuāla un multivides satura apraide, izmantojot internetu; Programmu apraide ar interneta starpniecību; Videopārraides pēc pieprasījuma; Multivides satura pārraide internetā; Vizuālā materiāla straumēšana internetā; Video un audio programmu apraide ar interneta starpniecību; Audio un video materiāla straumēšana internetā; Video, audio un televīzijas straumēšanas pakalpojumi; Audio, vizuālo un audiovizuālo materiālu straumēšana, izmantojot globālo datortīklu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' komunikazzjoni permezz ta' network tal-kompjuter; Provvista ta' data, informazzjoni jew immaġni u trażmissjoni ta' aħbarijiet u informazzjoni b'immaġni fuq l-Internet; Servizzi tat-telekommunikazzjoni; Video-Streaming; Provvista ta' aċċess bit-telekomunikazzjoni għal kontenut tal-vidjow u tal-awdjo pprovdut permezz ta' servizz onlajn ta' vidjow skont it-talba; Il-provvista ta' aċċess għat-telekomunikazzjoni għal kontenut tal-vidjow ipprovdut permezz tal-internet; Provvista ta' aċċess bit-telekomunikazzjoni għal programmi televiżivi pprovduti permezz ta' servizz skont it-talba; Provvista ta' aċċess bit-telekomunikazzjoni għal films u programmi televiżivi pprovdut permezz ta' servizz ta' vidjow skont it-talba; Xandir fuq televiżjoni tal-kejbil; Xandir ta' kontenut awdjoviżiv u multimedjali permezz tal-Internet; Xandir ta' programmi permezz tal-internet; Servizzi ta' trasmissjoni tal-vidjo skond id-domanda; Trasmissjoni ta' kontenut multimedjali bl-Internet; Streaming ta' materjal viżwali fuq l-Internet; Xandir ta' programmazzjoni ta' vidjo u awdjo fuq l-Internet; Strimjar ta' materjal awdjo u vidjow fuq l-Internet; Servizzi ta' xandir ta' vidjow, awdjo u televiżjoni; Xandir ta' awdjo, viżwal u materjal awdjoviżiv permezz ta' netwerk informatiku globali.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Communicatie via computernetwerken; Het verlenen van data, informatie of afbeeldingen en de overdracht van berichten en beeldinformatie met behulp van het internet; Telecommunicatiediensten; Video-streaming; Verschaffen van telecommunicatietoegang tot video- en audio-inhoud beschikbaar via een online video-on-demand dienst; Verschaffen van telecommunicatietoegang tot video-inhoud beschikbaar via het internet; Verschaffen van telecommunicatietoegang tot televisieprogramma's beschikbaar via een on-demand dienst; Verschaffen van telecommunicatietoegang tot films en televisieprogramma's beschikbaar via een video-on-demand dienst; Televisie-uitzending via de kabel; Uitzending van audiovisuele en multimedia-inhoud via het internet; Uitzending van programma's via het Internet; Verzending op verzoek van videobeelden; Transmissie van multimedia-inhoud via internet; Streaming van visueel materiaal op internet; Uitzending van beeld- en geluidsprogramma's via het internet; Streamen van audio- en videomateriaal op het internet; Video, audio en televisie streamingdiensten; Streaming van audio, visueel materiaal en audiovisueel materiaal via een wereldwijd computernetwerk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi komunikacyjne za pośrednictwem sieci komputerowych; Udostępnianie danych, informacji lub obrazów oraz transmisja wiadomości i informacji obrazowych przy pomocy internetu; Usługi telekomunikacyjne; Video-Streaming; Zapewnianie dostępu telekomunikacyjnego do treści wideo i audio udostępnianych za pośrednictwem usługi wideo na życzenie online; Zapewnianie dostępu telekomunikacyjnego do treści wideo za pośrednictwem Internetu; Zapewnianie dostępu telekomunikacyjnego do programów telewizyjnych dostarczanych za pośrednictwem usługi na życzenie; Zapewnianie dostępu telekomunikacyjnego do filmów i programów telewizyjnych udostępnianych za pośrednictwem usługi wideo na życzenie; Nadawanie telewizji kablowej; Nadawanie treści audiowizualnych i multimedialnych za pośrednictwem Internetu; Nadawanie programów za pośrednictwem Internetu; Usługi transmisji wideo na żądanie; Transmisja treści multimedialnych przez Internet; Transmisja strumieniowa materiałów wizualnych w internecie; Nadawanie programów wizualnych i dźwiękowych za pośrednictwem Internetu; Transmisja strumieniowa materiałów audio i wideo w Internecie; Usługi transmisji strumieniowej w zakresie treści wideo, audio i telewizji; Transmisja strumieniowa materiałów audio, wizualnych i audiowizualnych za pośrednictwem światowej sieci komputerowej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de comunicação através de redes informáticas; Disponibilização de dados, informações ou imagens, e transmissão de mensagens e de informações de imagem via Internet; Serviços de telecomunicações; "video-streaming"; Disponibilização de acesso, por meio de telecomunicações, a conteúdos de vídeo e áudio disponibilizados por serviços de vídeo a pedido online; Disponibilização de acesso, por meio de telecomunicações, a conteúdos de vídeo disponíveis na Internet; Disponibilização de acesso, por meio de telecomunicações, a programas televisivos a pedido; Disponibilização de acesso, por meio de telecomunicações, a filmes cinematográficos e programas televisivos disponibilizados por serviços de vídeo a pedido; Transmissão televisiva por cabo; Difusão de conteúdos audiovisuais e de multimédia através da Internet; Emissão de programas através da internet; Serviços de transmissão de vídeo a pedido; Transmissão de conteúdos multimédia através da Internet; Transmissão contínua de materiais de vídeo na Internet; Emissão de programação de vídeo e áudio através da Internet; Transmissão contínua de material de áudio e vídeo na Internet; Serviços de transmissão contínua de vídeo, áudio e televisão; Streaming de material áudio, visual e audiovisual através de uma rede mundial de computadores.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de comunicaţii prin reţele de calculatoare; Furnizare de date, informații sau imagini și transmisie de știri și informații video prin internet; Servicii de telecomunicaţii; Transmisie video continua; Furnizarea accesului de telecomunicaţii la conţinut video şi audio furnizat printr-un serviciu online de video la cerere; Furnizarea accesului de telecomunicaţii la conţinut video furnizat pe internet; Furnizarea accesului de telecomunicaţii la programe de televiziune furnizate printr-un serviciu la cerere; Furnizarea accesului de telecomunicaţii la filme şi programe de televiziune, furnizat printr-un serviciu video la cerere; Televiziune prin cablu; Radiodifuziune de conţinut audiovizual şi multimedia pe internet; Difuzare de programe prin Internet; Servicii de transmisie video la cerere; Transmitere de conţinuturi multimedia pe internet; Transmisia materialelor vizuale pe Internet; Difuzare de programe video şi audio prin internet; Difuzare de material audio şi video pe internet; Servicii de difuzare video, audio şi TV; Transmisie continuă [streaming] de material audio, video şi audiovizual printr-o reţea globală de calculatoare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Komunikačné služby prostredníctvom počítačových sietí; Poskytovanie údajov, informácií alebo obrázkov a prenos správ a obrazových informácií pomocou internetu; Telekomunikačné služby; Video-streaming; Poskytovanie telekomunikačného prístupu k videu a zvukovému obsahu prostredníctvom on-line služieb videa na požiadanie; Poskytovanie telekomunikačného prístupu k video obsahu prostredníctvom internetu; Poskytovanie telekomunikačného prístupu k televíznym programom poskytovaným prostredníctvom služieb videa na požiadanie; Poskytovanie telekomunikačného prístupu k filmom a televíznym programom prostredníctvom služieb videa na požiadanie; Vysielanie káblovej televízie; Vysielanie audiovizuálneho a multimediálneho obsahu prostredníctvom internetu; Vysielanie programov cez internet; Služby v oblasti prenosu video na požiadanie; Prenos multimediálneho obsahu prostredníctvom internetu; Prenos obrazových materiálov na internete v reálnom čase; Vysielanie video a audio programov prostredníctvom internetu; Prenos audio a video materiálov na internete; Služby v oblasti prenosu videa, zvuku a televízie prostredníctvom internetu v reálnom čase; Prenos zvukového, vizuálneho a audiovizuálneho materiálu prostredníctvom globálnej počítačovej siete.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Komunikacijske storitve preko računalniških omrežij; Nudenje podatkov, informacij ali slik ter prenos sporočil in slikovnih informacij s pomočjo interneta; Telekomunikacijske storitve; Video pretok; Nudenje telekomunikacijskega dostopa do video in avdio vsebin, nudenih preko spletne storitve videa na zahtevo; Nudenje telekomunikacijskega dostopa do video vsebin, nudenih preko interneta; Nudenje telekomunikacijskega dostopa do televizijskih programov, nudenih preko storitve na zahtevo; Nudenje telekomunikacijskega dostopa do filmov in televizijskih programov, nudenih preko storitve videa na zahtevo; Oddajanje kabelske televizije; Oddajanje avdiovizualne in multimedijske vsebine preko interneta; Oddajanje programov preko interneta; Predvajanje videa na zahtevo; Prenos multimedijskih vsebin preko interneta; Pretočno predvajanje vizualnega gradiva v internetu; Oddajanje video in avdio programja preko interneta; Pretočni prenos avdio in video materiala na internetu; Storitve pretočnega prenosa videa, avdioposnetkov in televizije; Pretočno predvajanje avdio, vizualnega in avdiovizualnega materiala prek globalnega računalniškega omrežja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kommunikationstjänster via datornät; Upplåtande av data, information eller bilder och överföring av meddelanden och bilder med hjälp av internet; Telekommunikationstjänster; Direktuppspelad video; Tillhandahållande av telekommunikationsåtkomst till direktanslutna tjänster för video- och ljudinnehåll på begäran; Tillhandahållande av telekommunikationsåtkomst till videoinnehåll via internet; Tillhandahållande av telekommunikationsåtkomst till tjänster för tv-program på begäran; Tillhandahållande av telekommunikationsåtkomst till tjänster för film och tv-program på begäran; Kabeltelevisionssändning; Sändning av audiovisuellt- och multimediainnehåll via internet; Utsändning av program via Internet; Sändningstjänster avseende video-on-demand; Överföring av multimedieinnehåll via internet; Streaming av visuellt material på Internet; Utsändning av video- och ljudprogram via internet; Strömning av ljud- och videomaterial på internet; Tjänster avseende video-, audio- och tv-strömning; Strömning av ljudmaterial, visuellt och audiovisuellt material via ett globalt datornät.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Образование; Обучение; Развлечение, спортни и атлетически мероприятия; Услуги за образование, развлечение и спорт; Продуциране на видеозаписи върху ленти; Производство на радио- и телевизионни програми; Организиране на конкурси [образование или развлечения]; Телевизионни развлечения; Осигуряване на радио и телевизионни развлекателни услуги; Развлечение чрез безжични телевизионни предавания; Развлечения от типа на телевизионни новинарски програми; Развлечение от рода на текущи телевизионни програми в областта на вариете; Продуциране на аудиовизуални презентации; Изготвяне на развлекателни програми за излъчване; Развлекателни услуги, предоставяни чрез онлайн потоци; Осигуряване на онлайн развлечение; Предоставяне на видео онлайн, без възможност за сваляне; Онлайн интерактивно развлечение; Предоставяне на онлайн информация във връзка с аудио и визуални медии; Развлечение; Развлечения предоставени чрез интернет; Услуги в областта на видео развлечението; Предоставяне на мулти-медийни развлечения чрез уебсайт; Предоставяне на аудио и визуални медии чрез комуникационни мрежи; Производство на аудиовизуални записи.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Výchova; vzdělávání; zábava a sportovní činnost; služby v oblasti vzdělávání, zábavy a sportu; videoprodukce; televizní programy (produkce rozhlasových a televizních programů); soutěže (organizování vzdělávacích a zábavných -); televizní zábava; televizní a rozhlasová zábava; zábava prostřednictvím bezdrátového televizního vysílání; zábava ve formě televizních zpravodajských show; zábava ve formě varietních televizních programů na pokračování; produkce audiovizuálních představení; příprava zábavních programů k vysílání; zábavní služby poskytované pomocí on-line streamů; poskytování on-line zábavy; poskytování videí on-line bez možnosti stažení; on-line interaktivní zábava; poskytování on-line informací o audio a vizuálních médiích; zábava; zábava poskytovaná prostřednictvím internetu; služby v oblasti videozábavy; poskytování multimediální zábavy prostřednictvím webových stránek; poskytování audio a vizuálních médií prostřednictvím komunikačních sítí; výroba audiovizuálních nahrávek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Uddannelsesvirksomhed; Undervisningsvirksomhed; Underholdningsvirksomhed og sportsarrangementer; Uddannelsesvirksomhed, underholdningsvirksomhed og sportsydelser; Produktion af videobånd; Produktion af radio- og fjernsynsprogrammer; Organisering af konkurrencer [uddannelse eller underholdning]; Fjernsynsunderholdning; Radio- og tv-underholdningsvirksomhed; Underholdning udbudt ved hjælp af trådløs tv-udsendelse; Underholdning i form af tv-nyhedsshows; Underholdningsvirksomhed i form af fortløbende tv-programmer inden for varieté; Produktion af audiovisuelle præsentationer; Udarbejdelse af underholdningsprogrammer til transmission; Underholdningsvirksomhed leveret via streaming; Udbydelse af onlineunderholdning; Stillen online videoer til rådighed, ikke-downloadable; Interaktiv onlineunderholdning; Formidling af onlineinformation vedrørende lyd- og visuelle medier; Underholdningsvirksomhed; Underholdning udbudt via internettet; Videounderholdning; Udbydelse af multimedieunderholdning via et websted; Stille af lyd- og visuelle medier til rådighed via kommunikationsnetværk; Produktion af audiovisuelle optagelser.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Erziehung; Ausbildung; Aktivitäten in den Bereichen Unterhaltung und Sport; Bildung, Erziehung, Unterhaltung und Sport; Videoaufnahme; Zusammenstellung von Rundfunk- und Fernsehprogrammen; Veranstaltung von Wettbewerben [Erziehung und Unterhaltung]; Fernsehunterhaltung; Radio- und TV-Unterhaltung; Unterhaltung mittels drahtlose Fernsehsendungen; Unterhaltung in Form von Fernsehnachrichtensendungen; Unterhaltung in Form von fortlaufenden Fernsehsendungen aus verschiedenen Themenbereichen; Produktion von Ton- und Bildpräsentationen; Zusammenstellung von Fernseh- und Rundfunkunterhaltungssendungen; Mittels Online-Streams bereitgestellte Unterhaltungsdienstleistungen; Bereitstellung von Online-Unterhaltung; Bereitstellung von Online-Videos, nicht herunterladbar; Interaktive Online-Unterhaltung; Bereitstellung von Online-Informationen in Bezug auf Audio- und visuelle Medien; Unterhaltung; Über das Internet bereitgestellte Unterhaltung; Dienstleistungen auf dem Gebiet der Videounterhaltung; Bereitstellen von Multimedia-Unterhaltungsdienstleistungen über eine Website; Bereitstellung von Audio- und visuellen Medien über Kommunikationsnetze [nicht herunterladbar]; Bild- und Tonaufzeichnungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εκπαίδευση· Επιμόρφωση (επαγγελματική κατάρτιση)· Ψυχαγωγία και αθλητικές δραστηριότητες, ειδικότερα δραστηριότητες γκολφ· Υπηρεσίες εκπαίδευσης, ψυχαγωγίας και αθλητισμού· Παραγωγή βιντεοταινιών· Παραγωγή ραδιοφωνικών και τηλεοπτικών προγραμμάτων· Οργάνωση διαγωνισμών ή αγώνων [εκπαίδευση και ψυχαγωγία]· Ψυχαγωγία τηλεοπτική· Ραδιοφωνικές και τηλεοπτικές ψυχαγωγικές υπηρεσίες· Ψυχαγωγία μέσω ασύρματης τηλεοπτικής αναμετάδοσης· Ψυχαγωγία υπό μορφή τηλεοπτικών εκπομπών ενημέρωσης· Ψυχαγωγία με τη μορφή τηλεοπτικών προγραμμάτων ποικίλης ύλης σε συνέχειες· Παραγωγή οπτικοακουστικών παρουσιάσεων· Προετοιμασία προγραμμάτων ψυχαγωγίας προς μετάδοση· Υπηρεσίες ψυχαγωγίας παρεχόμενες διαδικτυακά σε πραγματικό χρόνο· Παροχή επιγραμμικής ψυχαγωγίας· Παροχή διαδικτυακών βίντεο, μη μεταφορτώσιμων· Αλληλεπιδραστική ψυχαγωγία επί γραμμής· Παροχή επιγραμμικών πληροφοριών σε σχέση με ηχητικά και οπτικά μέσα· Ψυχαγωγία· Ψυχαγωγία παρεχόμενη μέσω του Διαδικτύου· Υπηρεσίες στον τομέα της ψυχαγωγίας μέσω βίντεο· Πολυμεσική ψυχαγωγία μέσω δικτυακού τόπου· Παροχή ηχητικών και οπτικών μέσων μέσω δικτύων επικοινωνίας· Υπηρεσίες παραγωγής οπτικοακουστικών εγγραφών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Education; Providing of training; Entertainment and sporting activities; Education, entertainment and sport services; Videotape production; Production of television and radio programs; Organisation of competitions [education or entertainment]; Television entertainment; Provision of radio and television entertainment services; Entertainment by means of wireless television broadcasts; Entertainment in the nature of television news shows; Entertainment in the nature of on-going television programs in the field of variety; Production of audio/visual presentations; Preparation of entertainment programmes for broadcasting; Entertainment services provided by on-line streams; providing online entertainment; Providing on-line videos, not downloadable; Online interactive entertainment; Provision of online information relating to audio and visual media; Entertainment; Entertainment provided via the internet; Services in the field of video entertainment; Providing multi-media entertainment via a website; Provision of audio and visual media via communications networks; Production of audio-visual recordings.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Educación; Formación; Actividades de esparcimiento y deportivas; Servicios de educación, entretenimiento y de actividades deportivas; Producción de videocintas; Montaje de programas de radio y televisión; Organización de concursos [actividades educativas o recreativas]; Entretenimiento televisivo; Servicios de entretenimiento televisivo y radiofónico; Servicios de entretenimiento prestados mediante teledifusión inalámbrica; Servicios de entretenimiento en forma de programas informativos de televisión; Entretenimiento del tipo de series de programas de televisión en el ámbito de las variedades; Producción de presentaciones audiovisuales; Preparación de programas de entretenimiento para su difusión; Servicios de esparcimiento, facilitados a través de emisiones en directo en línea; Suministro de entretenimiento en línea; Provisión de vídeos en línea no descargables; Esparcimiento interactivo en línea; Suministro de información en línea relacionada con medios audiovisuales; Servicios de entretenimiento; Esparcimiento facilitado a través de Internet; Servicios de esparcimiento con vídeo; Suministro de entretenimiento multimedia a través de una página web; Provisión de medios audiovisuales por medio de redes de telecomunicaciones; Producción de grabaciones audiovisuales.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Haridus; Väljaõpe; Meelelahutus- ja sporditegevus; Haridus-, meelelahutus- ja sporditeenused; Videote tootmine; Raadio- ja teleprogrammide lavastamine, produtseerimine; Hariduslike või meelelahutuslike võistluste organiseerimine; Televisioonimeelelahutussaated, telemeelelahutus; Televisiooni- ja raadiomeelelahutus; Meelelahutus juhtmevaba teleülekande abil; Meelelahutus televisiooni uudistesaadetena; Meelelahutus telesarjadena varietee valdkonnas; Audiovisuaalsete esitluste tootmine; Meelelahutuslike saadete ringhäälinguks ettevalmistamine; Sidusvoogedastuse kaudu pakutavad meelelahutusteenused; Sidusa meelelahutuse pakkumine; On-line-videote (v.a allalaaditavate) pakkumine; Interaktiivne on-line-meelelahutus; Audio- ja visuaalmeediaga seotud veebiteabe pakkumine; Meelelahutus; Interneti kaudu pakutav meelelahutus; Videomeelelahutusega seotud teenused; Multimeedium-meelelahutus veebisaidi kaudu; Audio- ja visuaalmeedia pakkumine sidevõrkude kaudu; Audiovisuaalsete salvestiste tootmine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Koulutus; Koulutuksen järjestäminen; Ajanviete ja urheilutoiminta; Koulutus-, ajanviete- ja urheilupalvelut; Videonauhatuotanto; Radio- ja televisio-ohjelmien tuotanto; Kilpailujen organisointi [koulutus- tai ajanvietepalveluina]; Televisioviihde; Radio- ja televisioviihdepalvelujen tarjoaminen; Ajanviete langattomien televisiolähetysten muodossa; Ajanviete television uutisesitysten muodossa; Ajanviete eri aiheita käsittelevien jatkuvien televisio-ohjelmien muodossa; Audiovisuaalisten esitysten tuotanto; Ajanvieteohjelmien valmistelu lähetyksiä varten; Online-suoratoistona tarjottavat ajanvietepalvelut; Online-ajanvietteen tarjoaminen; Muiden kuin ladattavien online-videoiden tarjoaminen; Vuorovaikutteinen online-ajanviete; Ääni- ja kuvavälineisiin liittyvien online-tietojen tarjoaminen; Ajanviete; Ajanviete Internetin välityksellä tarjottuna; Videoviihteeseen liittyvät palvelut; Multimediaviihteen tarjoaminen verkkosivuston kautta; Ääni- ja kuvavälineiden tarjoaminen viestintäverkkojen kautta; Audiovisuaalisten tallenteiden tuotanto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Éducation; Formation; Activités récréatives et sportives; Services d'éducation, de divertissement et de sport; Production de vidéos; Montage de programmes radiophoniques et de télévision; Organisation de concours [éducation ou divertissement]; Divertissement télévisé; Services de divertissement télévisé et radiophonique; Divertissement par le biais d'émissions de télédiffusion sans fil; Divertissement sous forme de spectacles d'actualités télévisées; Divertissement sous forme de programmes télévisés en plusieurs parties dans le domaine de la variété; Production de présentations audiovisuelles; Préparation de programmes de divertissement pour leur diffusion; Services de divertissement fournis en ligne; Fourniture de divertissement en ligne; Mise à disposition en ligne de vidéos non téléchargeables; Services de divertissement interactif en ligne; Fourniture d'informations en ligne relatives aux supports audio et visuels; Divertissement; Divertissement fourni via Internet; Services dans le domaine du divertissement vidéo; Fourniture de divertissement multimédia par l'intermédiaire d'un site web; Fourniture de supports audio et visuels par le biais de réseaux de communication; Production d'enregistrements audiovisuels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Obrazovanje; Stručno osposobljavanje; Slobodno vrijeme (usluge za ispunjavanje slobodnog vremena)i sportske aktivnosti; Obrazovne, zabavne i sportske usluge; Produkcija video filmova; Montaža radijskih i televizijskih programa; Organiziranje natjecanja [obrazovanje ili zabava]; Razonoda posredstvom televizije; Pružanje radijskih i televizijskih zabavnih sadržaja; Zabava pomoću bežične radiodifuzije televizijskih kanala; Zabava u obliku televizijskih dnevnika; Zabava u obliku televizijskih programa uživo iz raznih područja; Produkcija audio / vizualnih prezentacija; Pripremanje zabavnih programa za emitiranje; Zabavne usluge pružene internetskim prijenosom; Pružanje mrežne zabave; Pružanje on-line video snimaka, koji nisu za preuzimanje; Online interaktivna zabava; Pružanje online informacija u vezi s audio i vizualnim medijima; Razonoda; Zabava putem Interneta; Usluge na području video zabave; Usluge pružanja multimedijske zabave putem internetske stranice; Pružanje audio i vizualnih medija putem komunikacijskih mreža; Produkcija audiovizualnih snimaka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nevelés; Szakmai képzés; Szórakoztatás és sporttevékenységek; Oktatási, szórakoztatási és sportszolgáltatások; Videoszalagok gyártása; Rádió- és televízióműsorok készítése; Versenyek szervezése [oktatás vagy szórakoztatás]; Televíziós szórakoztatás; Rádiós és televíziós szórakoztató szolgáltatások; Vezeték nélküli televíziós közvetítésen keresztüli szórakoztatás; Szórakoztatás televíziós hírműsorok formájában; Szórakoztatás állandó televízióműsorok formájában a varieté területén; Audio/vizuális bemutatók készítése; Szórakoztató műsorok készítése közvetítés céljából; Online egyidejű adatfolyammal nyújtott szórakoztató szolgáltatások; Online szórakoztatás biztosítása; Online, nem letölthető videók biztosítása; Online interaktív szórakoztatás; Online információk szolgáltatása audio- és vizuális médiával kapcsolatban; Szórakoztatás; Interneten keresztül nyújtott szórakoztatási szolgáltatások; Szolgáltatások a videos szórakoztatás területén; Multimédiás szórakoztatás biztosítása weboldalon keresztül; Audio- és vizuális média biztosítása kommunikációs hálózatokon keresztül; Audiovizuális felvételek készítése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Educazione; Formazione; Attività di divertimento e attività sportive; Servizi relativi a educazione, divertimento e sport; Produzione di pellicole video; Montaggio di programmi radiofonici e televisivi; Organizzazione di concorsi [istruzione o intrattenimento]; Divertimento televisivo; Servizi nell' ambito dell'intrattenimento radiofonico e televisivo; Servizi d'intrattenimento per mezzo di trasmissioni televisive wireless; Divertimento sotto forma di notiziari televisivi; Intrattenimento sotto forma di serie di programmi televisivi di varietà; Produzione di presentazioni audiovisive; Preparazione di programmi di divertimento per la trasmissione; Servizi di intrattenimento disponibili online in streaming; Fornitura di intrattenimento on-line; Fornitura di video on-line, non scaricabili; Intrattenimento interattivo on-line; Fornitura di informazioni online in materia di supporti audio e video; Divertimento; Intrattenimento fornito via Internet; Servizi nel settore dell'intrattenimento con video; Fornitura di servizi di intrattenimento multimediali tramite un sito web; Fornitura di supporti audio e video attraverso reti di comunicazione; Produzione di registrazioni audiovisive.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Švietimas; Mokymas; Pramogos ir sportinė veikla; Švietimo, pramogų ir sporto paslaugos; Vaizdo įrašų gamyba; Radijo ir televizijos programų rengimas; Pramoginių ar mokomųjų konkursų rengimas; Televizijos pramoginės laidos; Televizijos ir radijo pramogų paslaugos; Pramogų per belaidę televiziją transliacija; Pramogos, būtent televizijos naujienų laidos; Pramogos, būtent tęstinės televizijos laidos varjetė srityje; Garso/vaizdo pristatymų kūrimas; Pramoginių laidų rengimas transliavimui; Pramoginės prijungtinio srautinio siuntimo paslaugos; Internetinių pramogų teikimas; Tiesioginis vaizdo įrašų pateikimas per kompiuterių tinklą (ne parsisiunčiamųjų); Interaktyviosios tiesioginio ryšio pramogos; Internetinės informacijos, susijusios su garso ir vaizdo žiniasklaida, teikimas; Pramogos; Pramogos internetu; Paslaugos vaizdo pramogų srityje; Įvairialypės terpės pramogų paslaugų teikimas internetu; Garso ir vaizdo priemonių teikimas komunikaciniais tinklais; Audiovizualinių įrašų gaminimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Audzināšana; Apmācība; Sarīkojumi un sporta pasākumi; Izglītības, izklaides un sporta pakalpojumi; Videofilmu ražošana; Radio un televīzijas programmu veidošana; Izglītības vai izklaides konkursu organizēšana; Televīzijas izklaides raidījumu veidošana; Radio un televīzijas izklaides pakalpojumu nodrošināšana; Izklaide, izmantojot bezvadu televīzijas apraides; Televīzijas ziņas (izklaide); Izklaide, proti, dažādas tematikas televīzijas raidījumi; Audio/vizuālo prezentāciju veidošana; Izklaides raidījumu sagatavošana televīzijai un radio; Izklaides pakalpojumi, ko nodrošina ar tiešsaistes straumēšanu; Izklaides nodrošināšana tiešsaistē; Nelejupielādējamu videoierakstu nodrošināšana tiešsaistē; Interaktīva izklaide tiešsaistē; Tiešsaistes informācijas nodrošināšana saistībā ar audio un vizuāliem līdzekļiem; Izpriecas; Izklaide, kas nodrošināta internetā; Pakalpojumi video izklaides jomā; Multivides izklaides nodrošināšana ar tīmekļa vietnes starpniecību; Audio un vizuālo līdzekļu nodrošināšana, izmantojot komunikāciju tīklus; Audiovizuālo ierakstu sagatavošana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Edukazzjoni; Provvediment ta' taħriġ; Attivitajiet ta' divertiment u sportivi; Servizzi ta' edukazzjoni, ta' divertiment u ta' sports; Produzzjoni ta' tejps tal-vidjo; Il-produzzjoni ta' programmi għar-radju u t-televiżjoni; Kompetizzjonijiet (Organizzazzjoni ta' -) [edukazzjoni jew divertiment]; Divertiment fuq it-televiżjoni; Provvista ta' servizzi ta' divertiment għar-radju u għat-televiżjoni; Divertiment permezz ta' xandiriet tat-televiżjoni mingħajr fili; Divertiment fil-forma ta' programmi televiżivi ta' aħbarijiet; Divertiment f'għamla ta' programmi kontinwi tat-televiżjoni fil-qasam tal-varjetà; Produzzjoni ta' preżentazzjonijiet awdjo/viżivi; It-tħejjija ta' programmi tad-divertiment għax-xandir; Servizzi ta' divertiment ipprovduti permezz ta' xandir online; Provvista ta' divertiment onlajn; Forniment ta' vidjows online, li ma jitniżżlux; Divertiment interattiv onlajn; Provvediment ta' informazzjoni online relatata mal-midja tal-awdjo u viżiva; Divertiment; Servizzi ta' divertiment provduti permezz tal-Internet; Servizzi fil-qasam ta' video chats; Il-provvediment ta' divertiment multimedja permezz ta' sit web; Provvediment ta' midja tal-awdjo u viżiva permezz ta' netwerks ta' komunikazzjoni; Il-produzzjoni ta' reġistrazzjonijiet awdjoviżivi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Opvoeding; Opleiding; Activiteiten op het gebied van ontspanning en sportactiviteiten; Diensten op het gebied van opvoeding, ontspanning en sport; Productie van videobanden; Samenstelling van radio- en televisieprogramma's; Organisatie van wedstrijden [opvoeding of ontspanning]; Ontspanning via de televisie; Diensten op het gebied van radio- en televisieamusement; Entertainment door middel van draadloze televisie-uitzendingen; Ontspanning in de vorm van televisienieuwsshows; Ontspanning in de vorm van een reeks televisieprogramma's op het gebied van variété; Productie van audiovisuele presentaties; Voorbereiding van amusementsprogramma's voor uitzending; Amusement geleverd via online-streaming; Het aanbieden van onlineontspanning; Ter beschikking stellen van online niet-downloadbare video's; Online interactief entertainment; Verstrekking van online-informatie met betrekking tot geluids- en beeldmedia; Ontspanning; Ontspanning via internet; Dienstverlening op het gebied van videoamusement; Verschaffing van multimedia-amusement via een website; Verstrekken van geluids- en beeldmedia via communicatienetwerken; Productie van audiovisuele opnamen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Nauczanie; Kształcenie; Rozrywka i dzialalność sportowa; Usługi edukacyjne, rozrywkowe i sportowe; Produkcja filmów wideo; Produkcja programów radiowych i telewizyjnych; Organizowanie konkursów [edukacja lub rozrywka]; Telewizyjne usługi rozrywkowe; Świadczenie usług w zakresie rozrywki radiowej i telewizyjnej; Rozrywka za pomocą bezprzewodowej emisji telewizyjnej; Rozrywka w formie telewizyjnych programów informacyjnych; Rozrywka w postaci toczących się programów telewizyjnych z różnorodnych dziedzin; Produkcja prezentacji audiowizualnych; Przygotowywanie programów rozrywkowych do emisji; Usługi rozrywkowe udostępniane dzięki strumieniom online; Udostępnianie rozrywki online; Udostępnianie filmów online nie do pobrania; Rozrywka interaktywna online; Udostępnianie informacji online związanych z mediami audiowizualnymi; Rozrywka; Usługi rozrywkowe dostarczane przez Internet; Usługi z zakresu rozrywki wideo; Udostępnianie rozrywki multimedialnej za pomocą strony internetowej; Udostępnianie mediów audiowizualnych za pośrednictwem sieci łączności; Produkcja nagrań audiowizualnych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Educação; Formação; Actividades de divertimento e desportivas; Serviços de educação, entretenimento e desporto; Produção de cassetes de vídeo; Produção de programas de rádio e de televisão; Organização de competições [educação ou divertimento]; Divertimento televisivo; Prestação de serviços de entretenimento de rádio e de televisão; Entretenimento prestado mediante transmissões por televisão por fio; Entretenimento sob a forma de programas noticiosos de televisão; Entretenimento sob a forma de programas de televisão em série no domínio das variedades; Produção de apresentações audiovisuais; Preparação de programas de divertimento para transmissão; Serviços de entretenimento fornecidos por transmissões contínuas em linha; Fornecimento de entretenimento em linha; Disponibilização de vídeos on-line, não para download; Entretenimento interativo em linha; Fornecimento de informações em linha relacionadas com meios audiovisuais; Divertimento; Fornecimento de entretenimento através da Internet; Serviços no domínio do entretimento de vídeo; Fornecimento de entretenimento multimédia através de um website; Fornecimento de meios de áudio e/ou visuais através de redes de comunicação; Produção de gravações audiovisuais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Educaţie; Instruire; Divertisment, activităţi sportive şi educaţie fizică; Servicii educative, de divertisment şi sportive; Producţie de benzi video; Producţie de programe radiofonice şi de televiziune; Organizarea de concursuri [educaţie sau divertisment]; Divertisment televizat; Divertisment de radio şi televiziune; Divertisment difuzat prin TV fără fir; Divertisment de natura emisiunilor de ştiri televizate; Divertisment de tipul programelor de televiziune continue în domeniul varietăţilor; Producţie de prezentări audiovizuale; Pregătire de programe de divertisment pentru difuzare; Servicii de divertisment furnizate prin transmisii continue online; Furnizarea de divertisment online; Furnizare de materiale video on-line, nedescărcabile; Divertisment interactiv on-line; Furnizare de informaţii online referitoare la mijloace media audio şi vizuale; Divertisment; Furnizarea de divertisment prin intermediul internetului; Servicii în domeniul divertismentului video; Furnizare de divertisment multimedia printr-un site internet; Furnizare de mijloace media audio şi vizuale prin reţele de comunicaţii; Producţie de înregistrări audiovizuale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vzdelávanie; Zabezpečovanie výcvikov, kurzov a školení; Zábavné a športové aktivity; Služby v oblasti vzdelávania, zábavy a športu; Produkcia videofilmov; Tvorba rozhlasových a televíznych programov; Organizovanie vedomostných alebo zábavných súťaží; Televízna zábava; Služby v oblasti rozhlasovej a televíznej zábavy; Zábava prostredníctvom bezdrôtového televízneho vysielania; Zábava vo forme televíznych spravodajských šou; Zábava v podobe nonstop televíznych programov v oblasti varieté; Výroba audio/vizuálnych prezentácií; Príprava zábavných programov pre vysielanie; Služby v oblasti zábavy poskytované prostredníctvom on-line vysielania; Poskytovanie on-line zábavy; Online poskytovanie videozáznamov (bez možnosti kopírovania); On-line interaktívna zábava; Poskytovanie online informácií o audio a vizuálnych médiách; Zábava; Zábava poskytovaná prostredníctvom internetu; Služby v oblasti video zábavy; Multimediálna zábava poskytovaná prostredníctvom webových stránok; Poskytovanie audio a vizuálnych médií prostredníctvom komunikačných sietí; Produkcia audiovizuálnych nahrávok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Izobraževanje; Pouk; Zabavne in športne dejavnosti; Izobraževalne, razvedrilne in športne storitve; Produkcija video kaset; Produkcija televizijskih in radijskih programov; Organizacija tekmovanj [zabavnih in izobraževalnih]; Televizijski zabavni program; Nudenje storitev radijskega in televizijskega razvedrila; Razvedrilo s sredstvi brezžičnega televizijskega oddajanja; Zabava v obliki televizijskih informativnih oddaj; Razvedrilo v obliki stalnih televizijskih oddaj z raznovrstnimi nastopi; Produkcija avdiovizualnih predstavitev; Priprava razvedrilnih programov za oddajanje; Razvedrilne storitve, nudene s spletnim pretočnim predvajanjem; Nudenje spletnega razvedrila; Nudenje spletnih videoposnetkov, ki se jih ne da naložiti preko računalniške mreže; Spletno interaktivno razvedrilo; Nudenje spletnih informacij v zvezi z avdio in vizualnimi mediji; Razvedrilo; Razvedrilne storitve preko interneta; Storitve na področju video razvedrila; Nudenje večpredstavnostnega razvedrila prek spletnega mesta; Nudenje avdio in vizualnih medijev prek komunikacijskih omrežij; Produkcija avdiovizualnih posnetkov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Undervisning/utbildning; Anordnande av handledning/instruktion; Underhållning, sport- och idrottaktiviteter; Tjänster avseende utbildning, underhållning och sport; Videofilmproduktion; Produktion av radio- och televisionsprogram; Anordnande av tävlingar [utbildning eller underhållning]; Televisionsunderhållning; Tillhandhållande av radio- och tv-underhållning; Underhållning medelst trådlösa tv-sändningar; Underhållningstjänster i form av tv-nyhetsshower; Underhållning i form av återkommande tv-program inom varietéområdet; Produktion av audio/visuella presentationer; Utarbetande av underhållningsprogram för sändning; Underhållningstjänster tillhandahållna via direktansluten strömning; Tillhandahållande av direktansluten underhållning; Upplåtande av filmer on-line, inte nedladdningsbara; Interaktiv online underhållning; Tillhandahållande av information om ljudmedier och visuella medier online; Underhållning; Upplåtande av underhållning via internet; Tjänster inom området för videounderhållning; Tillhandahållande av multimedieunderhållning via en webbplats; Tillhandahållande av ljudmedier och visuella medier via kommunikationsnät; Produktion av audiovisuella inspelningar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>43</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ресторантьорство.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby zajišťující stravování a nápoje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tilvejebringelse af mad og drikke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Dienstleistungen zur Verpflegung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες παροχής διατροφής και ποτών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Services for providing food and drink.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de restauración (alimentación).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Toitlustusteenused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ravitseminen ja juomien anniskelu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de restauration (alimentation).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge pružanja hrane i pića [okrepa].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vendéglátás (élelmezés).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di ristorazione (alimentazione).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Maisto ir gėrimų parūpinimo paslaugos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apgāde ar uzturu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi għall-provvista ta' ikel u xorb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Restauratie (het verstrekken van voedsel en dranken).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi zaopatrzenia w żywność i napoje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de restauração (alimentação).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de alimentaţie publică.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Reštauračné služby (strava).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Nudenje hrane in pijače.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Utskänkning av mat och dryck.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/099</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-27</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/169</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>471311</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>79595</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
