<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:45</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224930</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224930</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>HOTERB</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Периферни устройства, пригодени за използване с компютри; Везни; Окуляри; Физични апарати и уреди; Батерии за осветление; Измерватели; Радио; Апарати за анализ на хранителни продукти; Уреди за отчитане; Облекла за защита от злополуки, радиация и огън; Предупредителни устройства против кражби; Измервателни устройства, електрически; Щепсели, фасунги и други контакти [електрически връзки]; Компютърни кабели; Слушалки; Електрически ключове за осветление; Уреди и апарати за научни изследвания и лаборатории, уреди, апарати и симулатори за обучение; Магнити; Поставки, пригодени за мобилни телефони; Предупредителни устройства против кражби.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Periferní zařízení počítačů; Váhy; Okuláry; Fyzikální přístroje a nástroje; Baterie na zapalování; Měřidla; Rádia; Zařízení pro analýzu potravin; Přístroje a prostředky pro měření; Ochranné obleky k ochraně před úrazem, radiací a ohněm; Výstražná zařízení proti krádeží; Elektrické měřicí přístroje; Zásuvky, zástrčky a jiné elektrické kontakty (elektrické spojky); Počítačové kabely; Sluchátka; Spínače elektrického osvětlení; Vědecké výzkumné a laboratorní přístroje, přístroje pro vyučování a simulátory; Magnety; Stojany přizpůsobené pro mobilní telefony; Výstražná zařízení proti krádeži.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Perifere enheder til computere; Vægte; Okularer; Apparater og instrumenter til fysik; Batterier til belysning; Måleredskaber; Radioapparater; Apparater til næringsmiddelanalyse; Måleinstrumenter; Tøj til beskyttelse mod ulykker, bestråling og ild; Tyverialarmindretninger; Måleapparater, elektriske; Elektriske stik; Computerkabler; Hovedtelefoner; Elektriske lyskontakter; Videnskabelige forsknings og laboratorie apparater, undervisningsapparater og simulatorer; Magneter; Holdere til mobiltelefoner; Tyverialarmer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">An Computer angepasste Peripheriegeräte; Waagen; Okulare; Physikalische Apparate und Instrumente; Zündbatterien; Maße; Radios; Nahrungsmittelanalysegeräte; Messinstrumente; Unfall-, Strahlen- und Feuerschutzbekleidungsstücke; Diebstahlalarmgeräte; Elektrische Messgeräte; Elektrische Stecker; Computerkabel; Kopfhörer; Elektrische Lichtschalter; Apparate für wissenschaftliche Forschung und Labor, Unterrichtsapparate und Simulatoren; Magnete; Angepasste Halter für Mobiltelefone; Diebstahlalarmgeräte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Περιφερειακός εξοπλισμός προσαρμοσμένος για χρήση σε ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Ζυγαριές· Φακοί προσοφθάλμιοι· Φυσικής (Συσκευές και όργανα -)· Μπαταρίες φωτισμού· Μέτρα προληπτικά· Συσκευές ραδιοφωνικές· Τροφίμων (Συσκευές για την ανάλυση -)· Μέτρηση (όργανα -ης)· Ενδύματα για προστασία από ατυχήματα, ακτινοβολία και πυρκαγιά· Συναγερμοί αντικλεπτικοί· Μέτρηση (ηλεκτρικές συσκευές -ης)· Ρευματοδότες,ρευματολήπτες και άλλες επαφές [ηλεκτρικές συνδέσεις]· Καλώδια ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Ακουστικά κεφαλής με μικρόφωνο· Ηλεκτρικοί διακόπτες φωτισμού· Συσκευές επιστημονικής έρευνας και εργαστηρίων, συσκευές εκπαίδευσης και εξομοιωτές· Ηλεκτρομαγνητικά πηνία· Βάσεις για κινητά τηλέφωνα· Συναγερμοί αντικλεπτικοί.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Computer peripheral devices; scales; eyepieces; apparatus and instruments for physics; batteries for lighting; measures; radios; food analysis apparatus; measuring instruments; clothing for protection against accidents, irradiation and fire; anti-theft warning apparatus; Measuring devices, electric; Plugs, sockets and other contacts [electric connections]; computer cables; headsets; electric light switches; Scientific research and laboratory apparatus, educational apparatus and simulators; Magnets; Stands adapted for mobile phones; Burglar alarms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Dispositivos periféricos utilizados con ordenadores; Balanzas; Oculares; Aparatos e instrumentos de física; Baterías de arranque; Medidores; Aparatos de radio; Aparatos para analizar alimentos; Instrumentos de medición; Trajes de protección contra los accidentes, las radiaciones y el fuego; Alarmas antirrobo; Aparatos eléctricos de medición; Enchufes macho; Cables para ordenadores; Cascos con micrófono; Interruptores eléctricos para el alumbrado; Aparatos para la investigación científica y de laboratorio, aparatos educativos y simuladores; Imanes; Soportes adaptados para teléfonos móviles; Alarmas antirrobo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arvutite välisseadmed; Kaalud; Okulaarid; Füüsikaaparaadid ja -seadmed; Valgustusakud, valgustuspatareid; Mõõtevahendid; Raadiod; Toiduanalüsaatorid; Mõõteriistad, mõõdikud; Kaitserõivad, sh kiirgus- ja tulekindlad; Vargavastased seadmed; Elektrilised mõõteseadmed; Pistikud, pistikupesad jm ühendused [elektrilised ühendused]; Arvutijuhtmed; Mikrofoniga kõrvaklapid; Elektrivalguslülitid; Teaduslikud uuringu- ja laboriseadmed, õppeseadmed ning -simulaatorid; Magnetid; Mobiiltelefonide kohandatud alused; Vargusvastane signalisatsioon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tietokoneiden oheislaitteet; Vaa’at; Okulaarit; Fysiikan laitteet ja kojeet; Paristot lamppuihin; Mitat; Radiot; Elintarvikkeiden analyysilaitteet; Mittalaitteet; Vaatteet suojaksi tapaturmilta, säteilyltä ja tulelta; Varkaudenestovaroittimet; Mittalaitteet, sähkötoimiset; Pistokkeet, pistorasiat ja muut sähköliittimet; Tietokonekaapeloinnit; Kuulokkeet; Valokatkaisijat (sähkö); Tieteelliset tutkimus- ja laboratoriolaitteet, opetuslaitteet ja simulaattorit; Käämit, sähkömagneettiset; Matkapuhelimille tarkoitetut telineet; Varkaudenestovaroittimet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Périphériques adaptés pour utilisation avec des ordinateurs; Balances; Oculaires; Appareils et instruments de physique; Batteries d'allumage; Mesures; Appareils de radio; Appareils pour l'analyse des aliments; Instruments de mesure; Vêtements de protection contre les accidents, les radiations et le feu; Avertisseurs contre le vol; Appareils électriques de mesure; Prises électriques mâles; Câbles pour ordinateurs; Casques d'écoute; Interrupteurs d'éclairage électrique; Appareils de recherche scientifique et de laboratoire, appareils et simulateurs didactiques; Aimants; Supports adaptés pour téléphones portables; Avertisseurs contre le vol.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Periferni uređaji prilagođeni za uporabu s računalima; Vage; Okulari; Fizika (uređaji i instrumenti za-); Baterije za osvjetljenje; Mjerila; Radioaparati; Uređaji za analizu prehrambenih namirnica; Mjerni instrumenti; Odjeća za zaštitu od nesreća, zračenja i vatre; Signalni uredjaji protiv krađe; Električne naprave za mjerenje; Utičnice, utikači i ostali kontakti [električni kontakti]; Računalni kablovi; Slušalice; Električni prekidači za svjetla; Uređaji za znanstveno istraživanje i laboratorije, obrazovni uređaji i simulatori; Elektromagnetni svici; Stalak za mobilne telefone; Signalni uredjaji protiv krađe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Számítógéphez kialakított perifériák; Kiegyensúlyozó készülékek, mérlegek; Szemlencsék, okulárok; Fizikai kísérletekhez való készülékek és eszközök; Elemek, telepek világításhoz; Mérőeszközök, mértékek; Rádiókészülékek; Ételelemző készülékek; Mérőműszerek; Védőruhák balesetek, sugárzás és tűz ellen; Betörésgátló riasztókészülékek; Mérőkészülékek, elektromos; Dugók, csatlakozó aljzatok és más kapcsolások [elektromos csatlakozások]; Számítógép kábelek; Fejhallgatók; Elektromos villanykapcsolók; Berendezések tudományos kutatáshoz és laboratóriumi használatra, oktatási berendezések és szimulátorok; Elektromágneses tekercsek; Mobiltelefonokhoz kialakított állványok; Betörésgátló riasztókészülékek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Periferiche concepite per essere utilizzate con i computer; Bilance; Oculari; Apparecchi e strumenti di fisica; Batterie d'accensione; Misure; Apparecchi radio; Apparecchi per l'analisi degli alimenti; Strumenti di misura; Indumenti di protezione contro gli infortuni, le irradiazioni e il fuoco; Avvisatori antifurto; Apparecchi elettrici di misura; Prese elettriche maschili; Cavi per elaboratori elettronici; Cuffie per la musica; Interruttori elettrici della luce; Strumenti, indicatori e regolatori per misurare, rilevare e monitorare; Magneti; Supporti per telefoni cellulari; Avvisatori antifurto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kompiuterių išoriniai įrenginiai; Svarstyklės; Okuliarai; Fizikos aparatai ir prietaisai; Apšvietimo baterijos; Matai; Radijo aparatai; Pašarų analizės aparatai; Matavimo prietaisai; Apsauginiai drabužiai nuo nelaimingų atsitikimų, jonizuojančios spinduliuotės ir ugnies; Signalizacijos įrenginiai nuo vagysčių; Elektriniai matavimo prietaisai; Lizdai, kištukai ir kitokie kontaktai [elektros jungtys]; Kompiuterių kabeliai; Ausinės; Elektros šviesos jungikliai; Mokslinių tyrimų ir laboratoriniai aparatai, mokymo prietaisai ir imituokliai; Magnetai; Mobiliųjų telefonų laikikliai; Apsaugos nuo vagysčių signalizacijos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Datoru perifērijas ierīces; Balansēšanas ierīces; Okulāri; Fizikālie aparāti un instrumenti; Akumulatori apgaismes ierīcēm; Mēri; Radioaparāti; Aparāti pārtikas produktu analīzei; Mēraparatūra; Apģērbi aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem, starojumu un uguni; Pretielaušanās brīdinājuma sistēmas; Elektriskie mēraparāti; Elektriskās kontaktdakšas; Datoru kabeļi; Radioaustiņas; Elektriskie gaismas slēdži; Zinātniskās pētniecības un laboratoriju aparāti, mācību aparāti un simulatori; Magnēti; Mobilajiem tālruņiem pielāgoti statīvi; Pretzagļu signalizācijas ierīces.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Periferali addattati għall-użu mal-kompjuters; Apparat għall-użin; Lenti ta' tromba, ta' teleskopju jew ta' mikroskopju; Fiżika (Tagħmir u strumenti tal- -); Batteriji għad-dawl; Kejl; Radjijiet; Tagħmir għall-analiżi tal-ikel; Strumenti tal-kejl; Ilbies għall-protezzjoni kontra l-inċidenti, irradjazzjoni u n-nar; Apparat ta' twissija ta' serq; Strumenti tal-kejl elettriċi; Sòkits, plaggs u kuntatti oħrajn [konnessjonijiet elettriċi]; Kejbils tal-kompjuter; Kuffji; Swiċċijiet għad-dawl elettriku; Apparat għar-riċerka xjentifika u fil-laboratorju, apparat edukattiv u simulaturi; Kolji elettromanjetiċi; Stends adattati għal telefons ċellulari; Apparat ta' twissija ta' serq.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Computerrandapparatuur; Weegschalen; Oculairs; Natuurkundige apparaten en instrumenten; Ontstekingsbatterijen; Maten; Radio's; Apparaten voor het analyseren van voedingsmiddelen; Meetinstrumenten; Beschermende kleding tegen ongevallen, straling en vuur; Alarmtoestellen tegen diefstal; Elektrische meetapparaten; Elektrische stekkers; Computerkabels; Hoofdtelefoons; Lichtschakelaars (Elektrische -); Apparaten voor wetenschappelijk onderzoek en laboratoria, onderwijsapparaten en simulatoren; Elektromagnetische spoelen; Standaards aangepast voor mobiele telefoons; Alarmtoestellen tegen diefstal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Sprzęt peryferyjny do komputerów; Urządzenia do wyważania; Zestawy soczewek [wzierniki, okulary]; Urządzenia i przyrządy do fizyki; Baterie do oświetlania; Miary; Radia [odbiorniki radiowe]; Urządzenia do analizy żywności; Przyrządy pomiarowe; Odzież chroniąca przed wypadkami, napromieniowaniem i ogniem; Alarmy antywłamaniowe; Elektryczne urządzenia pomiarowe; Gniazdka, wtyczki i inne kontakty [złącza elektryczne]; Okablowanie do komputerów; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Elektryczne wyłączniki oświetleniowe; Urządzenia do badań naukowych i laboratoryjne, urządzenia dydaktyczne i symulatory; Cewki elektromagnetyczne; Stojaki dostosowane do telefonów komórkowych; Alarmy antywłamaniowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Periféricos adaptados para uso com computadores; Balanças; Oculares; Aparelhos e instrumentos de física; Baterias de ignição; Medidores; Aparelhos de rádio; Aparelhos para a análise de alimentos; Instrumentos de medida; Vestuário de proteção contra acidentes, radiações e fogo; Aparelhos de alerta antirroubo; Aparelhos elétricos de medida; Fichas elétricas; Cabos de computador; Auriculares; Interruptores elétricos de luz; Aparelhos de pesquisa científica e de laboratório, aparelhos educacionais e simuladores; Ímanes; Suportes adaptados a telemóveis; Aparelhos de alerta anti-roubo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Periferice adaptate pentru a fi folosite la calculatoare; Balanțe; Oculare; Aparate și instrumente de fizică; Iluminat (Baterii pentru -); Măsuri; Radiouri; Aparate pentru analiza alimentelor; Instrumente de măsurare; Îmbrăcăminte de protecție contra accidentelor, iradierii și incendiilor; Sisteme de alarmă antiefracție; Aparate electrice de măsurare; Prize, fișe și alte dispozitive de cuplare [conexiuni electrice]; Cabluri pentru calculatoare; Căști; Întrerupătoare electrice de lumină; Aparate pentru cercetare științifică și de laborator, aparate și simulatoare educaționale; Magneți; Suporturi adaptate pentru telefoane mobile; Sisteme de alarmă antiefracție.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Periférne zariadenia počítačov; Váhy; Okuláre; Fyzikálne prístroje a nástroje; Batérie do svietidiel; Mierky; Rádiá; Prístroje na rozbor potravín; Nástroje na meranie; Ochranné odevy proti úrazom, proti rádioaktívnej kontaminácii a protipožiarne ochranné odevy; Zabezpečovacie zariadenia proti odcudzeniu; Elektrické meracie zariadenia; Elektrické zásuvky; Počítačové káble; Slúchadlá s mikrofónom; Spínače elektrického osvetlenia; Vedeckovýskumné a laboratórne prístroje, vzdelávacie prístroje a simulátory; Magnety; Stojany na mobilné telefóny; Alarmy proti vlámaniu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zunanje enote, prilagojene za uporabo z računalniki; Tehtnice; Okularji; Fizikalni aparati in instrumenti; Baterije za razsvetljavo; Mere; Radii; Aparati za analizo hrane; Merilni instrumenti; Zaščitna oblačila proti nesrečam, sevanju in ognju; Protivlomni opozorilni aparati; Električne merilne naprave; Vtikači, vtičnice in ostali kontakti [električni konektorji]; Računalniški kabli; Slušalke; Električna stikala za razsvetljavo; Znanstveno-raziskovalni in laboratorijski aparati, učni aparati in simulatorji; Elektromagnetne tuljave; Stojala, prirejena za prenosne telefone; Protivlomni opozorilni aparati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kringutrustning anpassade för användning med datorer; Vågar; Okularlinser; Fysikaliska apparater och instrument; Batterier för tändning; Mått; Radioapparater; Apparater för livsmedelsanalys; Mätinstrument; Skyddskläder mot skador, strålning och eld; Stöldvarnare; Elektriska mätredskap; Elektriska kontakter; Kablar till datorer; Headsets; Strömbrytare för belysning; Utrustning för vetenskaplig forskning och laboratorier, undervisningsapparater och simulatorer; Magneter; Ställ för mobiltelefoner; Inbrottsalarm.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Вълнени отпадъци за чистене; Гъбички за чистене; Саксии; Съдове за разтопяване на туткал; Купички за плодове; Кухненски мелници, неелектрически; Плетени кошчета; Рендета за кухненска употреба; Капаци за съдове; Килимочистачки; Гребени; Тоалетни етажерки; Ръкавици за домакински цели; Съдове за домакински или кухненски цели [с изключение на такива от благороден метал]; Готварски форми; Цедки за домакински цели; Сервизи за хранене; Сервизи за чай, не от благороден метал; Кухненски принадлежности, не от благороден метал.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vlněný odpad na čištění; Drátěnky; Květináče; Nádobky na lepidlo; Misky na ovoce; Kuchyňské mlýnky, ne elektrické; Kbelíky z tkaniny; Kuchyňská struhadla; Poklopy na nádobí; Zametače na koberce; Hřebeny; Toaletní houby; Rukavice pro použití v domácnosti; Dózy, boxy a nádoby pro použití v domácnosti a kuchyni; Formy na pečení, vaření; Cedníky pro použití v domácnosti; Jídelní soupravy [nádobí]; Čajové servisy [stolní nádobí]; Kuchyňské potřeby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Uldaffald til rengøring; Svampe til rengøring; Urtepotter; Limpotter; Frugtbowle; Køkkenkværne, ikke-elektriske; Spande af vævede stoffer; Rivejern til køkkenbrug; Låg til fade; Tæppefejeredskaber; Kamme; Svampe til toiletbrug; Handsker til husholdningsbrug; Beholdere til husholdnings- eller køkkenbrug; Forme til madlavning; Sier til husholdningsbrug; Service [spisestel]; Teservicer [bordservice]; Køkkenredskaber.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wollabfälle für Reinigungszwecke; Putzkissen; Blumentöpfe; Leimtöpfe; Obstschüsseln; Nicht elektrische Mühlen für die Küche; Stoffeimer; Reiben für die Küche; Schüsseldeckel; Teppichkehrer; Kämme; Toilettenschwämme; Haushaltshandschuhe; Gefäße für Haushalt oder Küche; Kochformen [Küchenartikel]; Löchersiebe für den Haushalt; Tafelservice [Geschirr]; Teeservice [Tafelgeschirr]; Küchengeräte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπολείμματα μαλλιού για καθαρισμό· Σφουγγαράκια καθαρισμού· Γλάστρες· Κόλλας (Δοχεία -)· Φρουτιέρες· Μύλοι κουζίνας, μη ηλεκτρικοί· Ύφασμα (Κάδοι από -)· Τρίφτες [οικιακά σκεύη]· Καλύμματα πιάτων· Σκούπες μηχανικές· Χτένες· Σπόγγοι τουαλέτας· Γάντια οικιακής χρήσης· Δοχεία οικιακά ή μαγειρικά· Μαγειρικής φόρμες· Φίλτρα οικιακής χρήσης· Υπηρεσίες [πιάτα]· Σερβίτσια τσαγιού [επιτραπέζια σκεύη]· Σκεύη μαγειρικής χρήσης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Wool waste for cleaning; Cleaning pads; Flower pots; glue-pots; fruit bowls; kitchen grinders, non-electric; buckets made of woven fabrics; graters for kitchen use; dish covers; carpet sweepers; combs; toilet sponges; gloves for household purposes; containers for household or kitchen use; cookery moulds; Strainers for household use; Dishware; tea services [tableware]; kitchen utensils.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Desechos de lana para limpiar; Estropajos metálicos para limpiar; Macetas [tiestos]; Botes para pegamento; Cuencos para frutas; Trituradoras no eléctricas para uso culinario; Cubos de tela; Ralladores para uso culinario; Tapas para platos y fuentes; Escobas mecánicas; Peines; Esponjas de aseo personal; Guantes para uso doméstico; Recipientes para uso doméstico o culinario; Moldes de cocina; Filtros para uso doméstico; Servicios de mesa [vajilla]; Servicios de té; Utensilios de cocina.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Villajäätmed puhastamiseks; Puhastuspadjakesed; Lillepotid; Liimipotid; Puuviljakausid; Köögis kasutatavad jahvatid, v.a elektrilised; Tekstiilämbrid; Köögiriivid; Lauanõude kaaned; Mehaanilised vaibaharjad; Kammid; Tualettkäsnad; Majapidamiskindad; Köögi- või majapidamismahutid; Toiduvormid; Majapidamiskurnad; Serviisid [lauanõud]; Teeserviisid [lauanõud]; Köögitarbed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Villatrasseli puhdistukseen; Puhdistustyynyt; Kukkaruukut; Liimapurkit; Hedelmäkulhot; Keittiömyllyt, ei sähkökäyttöiset; Sangot kudotusta kankaasta; Raastimet keittiökäyttöön; Kannet astioille; Mattomikot; Kammat; Toalettisienet; Käsineet kotitalouskäyttöön; Säiliöt koti- tai keittiökäyttöön; Keittiövuoat; Läviköt keittiövälineinä; Astiastot; Teeserviisit [astiastot]; Keittokattilasarjat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Déchets de laine pour le nettoyage; Tampons à nettoyer; Pots à fleurs; Pots à colle; Coupelles à fruits; Moulins de cuisine non électriques; Seaux en étoffe; Râpes de cuisine; Couvercles de plats; Balais mécaniques; Peignes; Éponges de toilette; Gants de ménage; Récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine; Moules de cuisine; Passoires à usage domestique; Services [vaisselle]; Services à thé; Ustensiles de cuisine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Vuneni otpaci za čišćenje; Tamponi za čišćenje; Lončanice za cvijeće; Posude za ljepilo; Zdjele za voće; Kuhinjski mlinci [neelektrični]; Vedra od tkanih materijala; Ribeži za kuhinjsku uporabu; Poklopci za plitke posude; Mehaničke metle; Češljevi; Toaletne spužve; Rukavice za kućanstvo; Posude za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju; Kalupi za kuhinjske potrebe; Filtri za kućanstvo; Servisi za jelo; Čaj [servisi za čaj]; Posuđe (kuhinjsko metalno posuđe).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Gyapjúhulladék tisztításhoz; Tisztítópárnák, súrolószivacsok; Virágcserepek; Enyvesfazekak; Kompótos tálka; Konyhai darálók, nem elektromos; Textilből készült vödrök; Reszelők konyhai használatra; Ételburák; Szőnyegseprők; Fésűk; Mosdószivacsok, szivacsok mosakodáshoz; Kesztyűk háztartási használatra; Tárolók, tároló edények háztartási vagy konyhai célokra; Sütőformák, süteményszaggatók; Háztartási szűrők; Étkészletek; Teáskészletek [terítékek]; Konyhai eszközök, kis méretű.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cascami di lana per pulire; Tamponi per pulire; Vasi da fiori; Vasi per la colla; Fruttiere; Tritatori per la casa non elettrici; Canestro in stoffa; Grattugie [utensili per la casa]; Coperchi per piatti; Scope meccaniche; Pettini; Spugne per toilette; Guanti per uso domestico; Recipienti per la casa o per la cucina; Stampi per la cucina; Filtri per uso domestico; Servizi [vasellame]; Servizi da tè; Utensili da cucina.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vilnų atliekos (valymui); Šveistukai; Vazonai; Klijų virimo katilai; Vaisių dubenys; Ne elektriniai virtuviniai malimo prietaisai; Kibirai iš audinių; Virtuvinės trintuvės; Indų dangčiai; Kilimų valymo įtaisai; Šukos; Prausiamosios plaušinės; Buitinės pirštinės; Buitinės ar virtuvinės talpyklos; Kulinarinės formos; Buitiniai sieteliai; Servizai [valgomieji indai]; Arbatos servizai [valgomieji reikmenys]; Virtuviniai indai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tīrīšanai paredzēti vilnas atgriezumi; Tīrīšanas spilventiņi; Puķu podi; Līmes katli; Bļodas augļiem; Neelektriski virtuves rīki smalcināšanai; Spaiņi no auduma; Virtuves rīves; Galda trauku vāki; Birstes tepiķu tīrīšanai; Ķemmes; Tualetes sūkļi; Cimdi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Tilpnes mājturības vai virtuves nolūkiem; Veidnes (virtuves piederumi); Caurduri mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Servīzes (trauki); Tējas servīzes (galda piederumi); Ēdienu gatavošanas trauku komplekti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Suf superfluwu u mhux maħdum għat-tindif; Kuxxinetti għat-tindif; Qsari; Kontenituri tal-kolla; Bwieqi tal-frott; Apparat tal-kċina għat-tħin, mhux tal-elettriku; Tessuti Minsuġa (Bramel magħmula minn -); Mħakek għall-użu fil-kċina; Għotjien għal dixxijiet; Oġġetti li jikinsu t-twapet; Pettnejiet; Sponoż tat-tojlits; Ingwanti għal skopijiet domestiċi; Kontenituri għal użu domestiku jew għal użu fil-kċina; Forom tat-tisjir; Passaturi għal użu domestiku; Settijiet [dixxijiet]; Servizzi tat-tè [oġġetti tal-mejda]; Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Wolafval voor reinigingsdoeleinden; Sponzen voor reinigingsdoeleinden; Bloempotten; Lijmpotten; Fruitschalen; Maalapparaten voor de keuken, niet elektrisch; Emmers van weefsel; Raspen voor gebruik in de keuken; Schoteldeksels; Rolbezems; Kammen; Toiletsponzen; Handschoenen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Houders voor de huishouding of de keuken; Bakvormen; Filters [zeven] voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Tafelserviezen; Theeserviezen; Keukengerei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Wełniane odpady do czyszczenia; Gąbki czyszczące; Doniczki na kwiaty; Pojemniki na kleje; Miski na owoce; Nieelektryczne młynki kuchenne; Wiadra płócienne; Tarki do celów kuchennych; Przykrywki do dań; Szczotki do dywanów; Grzebienie; Gąbki toaletowe; Rękawice do użytku domowego; Pojemniki do użytku domowego lub kuchennego; Formy i foremki [przybory kuchenne]; Cedzaki do użytku domowego; Serwisy [zastawy stołowe]; Serwisy do herbaty; Przybory kuchenne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Desperdícios de lã, para limpeza; Esfregões; Vasos para flores; Frascos para cola; Fruteiras; Trituradores [moinhos] de cozinha, não elétricos; Baldes em tecido; Raladores, para cozinha; Tampas para pratos; Espanadores para carpetes; Pentes; Esponjas para casa de banho; Luvas para uso doméstico; Recipientes para uso doméstico ou para cozinha; Formas para culinária; Filtros para uso doméstico; Serviços de loiça; Serviços de chá [louça de mesa]; Utensílios para cozinha.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Deșeuri de lână pentru curățat; Tampoane pentru curățare; Ghivece de flori; Clei (Oale pentru -); Fructiere; Dispozitive de măcinat de bucătărie, neelectrice; Materiale țesute (Recipiente din -); Răzătoare pentru utilizare în bucătărie; Capace pentru farfurii; Mături mecanice; Piepteni; Bureți de toaletă; Mănuși de menaj; Recipiente pentru menaj sau bucătărie; Forme pentru bucătărie; Filtre pentru menaj; Servicii [veselă]; Servicii de ceai [veselă]; Ustensile de bucătărie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vlnený odpad na čistenie; Drôtenky na čistenie; Kvetináče; Kotlíky na ohrievanie lepidla, gleja; Misy na ovocie; Kuchynské mlynčeky, nie elektrické; Textilné vedrá; Strúhadlá pre domácnosť; Príklopy na jedlo; Mechanické metly; Hrebene; Špongie na umývanie; Rukavice pre domácnosť; Nádoby na použitie v domácnosti alebo v kuchyni; Formy na prípravu jedál; Cedidlá pre domácnosť; Jedálenské súpravy (riad); Čajové súpravy (stolový riad); Kuchynský riad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Volneni odpadki za čiščenje; Čistilne krpice; Lončki za rože; Posode za lepilo; Sklede za sadje; Gospodinjski mlinčki, neelektrični; Vedra iz tkanih materialov; Kuhinjski strgalniki; Pokrovke za sklede; Pometači za preproge; Glavniki; Toaletne gobice; Rokavice za gospodinjske namene; Posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo; Modeli za kuho; Cedila za gospodinjstva; Servisi [namizni pribor]; Čajni servisi; Kuharski pripomočki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Ylleavfall för rengöring; Kuddar för rengöring; Blomkrukor; Limpannor; Fruktskålar; Kökskvarnar, inte elektriska; Ämbar av väv; Rivjärn för köksändamål; Lock för karotter; Mattsopare; Kammar; Tvättsvampar; Handskar för hushållsändamål; Behållare för hushålls- eller köksändamål; Formar för matlagning; Silar för hushållsändamål; Serviser [bordsserviser]; Teserviser [bordsserviser]; Köksgeråd.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Уреди за трениране на тялото; Дартс [хвърляне на стрелички]; Строителни игри; Играчки за бебета; Карти за игра; Чашки за зарове; Топки за игра; Ръкавици за игри; Обръчи за игри; Строителни кубчета [играчки]; Електронни механизирани играчки; Играчки за домашни любимци; Гимнастически уреди; Уреди за фитнес упражнения; Гимнастически и спортни артикули; Предпазители за тялото за спортни цели; Спортна оборудване.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Posilovací stroje; Šipky [hra]; Stavebnice [hračky]; Dětské hračky; Hrací karty; Pohárky na hry s kostkami; Míče na hraní; Rukavice na hry; Kroužky (hra, při které se kroužky házejí na kolíky); Stavebnicové kostky [hračky]; Elektronické aktivní hračky; Hračky pro domácí zvířata; Posilovače prsních svalů (expandéry); Přístroje na tělesná cvičení; Gymnastické a sportovní zboží; Chrániče těla pro sportovní účely; Sportovní vybavení.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Apparater til bodybuilding; Kastepile [dart]; Byggelegetøj; Legetøj til børn; Spillekort; Raflebægre; Bolde [legetøj]; Handsker til sport [sportsudstyr]; Ringspil; Byggeklodser [legetøj]; Elektronisk aktivitetslegetøj; Legetøj til kæledyr; Ekspandere [muskelstrækkere]; Maskiner til legemsøvelser; Gymnastik- og sportsartikler; Kropsbeskyttere til sportsbrug; Sportsudstyr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bodybuilding-Geräte; Wurfpfeile; Baukästen [Spielwaren]; Kinderspielzeug; Kartenspiele; Würfelbecher; Spielkugeln; Handschuhe [Zubehör für Spiele]; Ringspiele; Bauklötze [Spielwaren]; Elektronisches Bewegungsspielzeug; Spielzeug für Haustiere; Expander; Geräte für Körperübungen; Turn- und Sportartikel; Körperschutzausstattung für Sportler; Sportgeräte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αποκατάστασης σώματος συσκευές· Βέλη· Κατασκευών (Παιχνίδια -)· Παιδικά αθύρματα· Μάρκες για παιχνίδια· Κύπελλα για ζάρια· Μπάλες παιχνιδιού· Γάντια [εξαρτήματα παιχνιδιού]· Δακτυλίων (Παιχνίδια -)· Κύβοι κατασκευών [παιχνίδια]· Ηλεκτρονικά παιχνίδια δράσης· Παιχνίδια για κατοικίδια ζώα· Ανάπτυξης-όργανα· Συσκευές άσκησης και γυμναστικής· Είδη γυμναστικής και αθλητισμού· Προστατευτικά σώματος για αθλητική χρήση· Αθλητικός εξοπλισμός.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Body-building apparatus; darts; building games; infant toys; playing cards; cups for dice; playing balls; gloves for games; ring games; toy construction blocks; electronic action toys; toys for domestic pets; chest expanders; Machines for physical exercises; gymnastic and sporting articles; body protectors for sports use; sports equipment.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de culturismo; Dardos; Juegos de construcción; Juguetes para niños; Naipes; Cubiletes para dados; Bolas de juego; Guantes [accesorios para juegos]; Juegos de anillas; Bloques de construcción [juguetes]; Juguetes electrónicos de actividades; Juguetes para animales de compañía; Extensores para pectorales; Aparatos para ejercicios físicos; Artículos de deporte y gimnasia; Equipos de protección corporal para deportes; Equipamientos deportivos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Füüsilise vormi parandamise/taastamise seadmed; Viskenooled, noolemängud; Ehituskonstruktorid [mängud]; Väikelaste mänguasjad; Mängukaardid; Täringutopsid; Mängukuulid; Sportmängukindad; Rõngamängud; Ehitusklotsid [mänguasjad]; Elektroonilised tegevusmänguasjad; Lemmikloomade mänguasjad; Ekspandrid, tõmmitsad; Jõuharjutuste seadmed; Võimlemis- ja sportimistarbed; Kehakaitsmed spordis kasutamiseks; Spordiriistad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kehonrakennusvälineet; Tikat; Rakennuspelit; Vauvojen lelut; Pelikortit; Noppapikarit; Leikkipallot; Käsineet (Peli -); Rengaspelit; Rakennuspalikat [leluina]; Elektroniset toimintalelut; Lelut lemmikkieläimille; Voimaharjoitusvälineet [venytyslaitteet]; Kuntosalilaitteet; Voimistelu- ja urheiluvälineet; Vartalosuojukset urheilukäyttöön; Urheiluvarusteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils pour le culturisme; Fléchettes; Jeux de construction; Jouets pour enfants; Cartes à jouer; Gobelets pour jeux; Boules de jeu; Gants [accessoires de jeux]; Jeux d'anneaux; Blocs de construction [jouets]; Jouets d'éveil électroniques; Jouets pour animaux de compagnie; Exerciseurs [extenseurs]; Engins pour exercices corporels; Articles de gymnastique et de sport; Équipements de protection corporelle pour le sport; Équipements de sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sprave za body building; Strelice; Graditeljske igre; Dječje igračke; Igraće karte; Posude za bacanje kocki; Lopte za igru; Rukavice [oprema za igru]; Kolutovi za igru; Kocke za slaganje [igračke]; Elektroničke igračke za razne aktivnosti; Igračke za ljubimce; Ekspanderi za prsa; Aparati za tjelovježbu; Gimnastička i sportska oprema; Sportski štitnici za tijelo; Sportska oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Testedző berendezések; Darts; Építőjátékok; Játékszerek gyermekeknek; Játékkártyák; Poharak kockajátékhoz; Játéklabdák, játszólabdák; Kesztyűk [játékok tartozékai]; Karikajátékok; Építőkockák [játékok]; Elektronikus foglalkoztató játékok; Játékok kisállatoknak; Mellkas expanderek [edzőeszközök]; Fitnesz gépek; Torna- és sporttermékek; Testvédők sportoláshoz; Sportfelszerelés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi per il culturismo; Freccette; Giochi di costruzione; Giocattoli per bambini; Carte da gioco; Bussolotti per giochi; Bocce da gioco; Guanti [accessori per giochi]; Giochi di anelli; Blocchi per costruzioni [giocattoli]; Giocattoli d'azione elettronici; Giocattoli per animali da compagnia; Estensori [attrezzi ginnici]; Attrezzi per esercizi fisici; Articoli per la ginnastica e lo sport; Protezioni corporali per lo sport; Attrezzature sportive.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Fizinių pratimų prietaisai [kūnui treniruoti]; Strėlės; Konstrukciniai žaidimai; Vaikų žaislai; Lošiamosios kortos; Žaidimo kauliukų dėžutės; Žaidimo sviediniai; Žaidimų pirštinės; Žaidimai su žiedais; Konstrukciniai kubeliai [žaislai]; Elektroniniai veiksmo žaislai; Kambarinių gyvūnėlių žaislai; Krūtinės treniravimo espanderiai; Fizinių pratimų prietaisai; Gimnastikos ir sporto reikmenys; Kūno apsaugos sporto reikmėms; Sportinė įranga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Atlētiskās vingrošanas ierīces; Šautriņas; Spēļu konstruktori; Bērnu rotaļlietas; Spēļu kārtis; Spēļu kauliņu kausi; Spēļu bumbas; Cimdi spēlēm; Riņķu spēles; Rotaļu klucīši [konstruktori]; Elektroniskas aktivitāšu rotaļlietas; Mājas (istabas) dzīvnieku rotaļlietas; Espanderi; Trenažieri; Vingrošanas un sporta preces; Ķermeņa aizsargi izmantošanai sportā; Sporta piederumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat għat-taħriġ tal-muskoli; Darts; Logħob fejn tibni; Oġġetti tal-logħob tat-tfal; Karti tal-logħob; Tazzi għad-dadi; Blalen tal-logħob; Ingwanti għall-użu fil-logħob; Logħob biċ-ċrieki; Blokki għal bini ta' kostruzzjonijiet [ġugarelli]; Ġugarelli attivi elettroniċi; Ġugarelli għal annimali domestiċi; Wessiegħa tas-sider [apparat għall-eżerċizzji fiżiċi]; Eżerċizzju fiżiku (Magni għall- -); Artikli tal-ġinnastika u ta' l-isports; Protetturi tal-ġisem għall-użu sportiv; Tagħmir tal-isports.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Fitnesstoestellen; Darts; Constructiespellen; Kinderspeelgoederen; Speelkaarten; Bekers voor dobbelstenen; Speelballen; Handschoenen [speeltoebehoren]; Ringspellen; Bouwblokken [speelgoed]; Elektronisch activiteitenspeelgoed; Speelgoed voor huisdieren; Trekveren voor spieroefeningen; Toestellen voor lichaamsoefeningen; Gymnastiek- en sportartikelen; Lichaamsbeschermers voor sportgebruik; Sportuitrusting.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przyrządy stosowane do ćwiczeń fizycznych; Rzutki, strzałki [gra]; Gry polegające na budowaniu; Artykuły do zabawy dla dzieci; Karty do gry; Kubki na kości do gry; Piłki do gier i zabaw; Rękawice do gier; Gry z obręczami; Klocki do zabawy [konstrukcyjne]; Elektroniczne zabawki wielofunkcyjne; Zabawki dla zwierząt domowych; Ekspandery [ćwiczenia]; Maszyny do ćwiczeń sprawnościowych; Artykuły gimnastyczne i sportowe; Ochraniacze ciała do użytku sportowego; Sprzęt sportowy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos para o culturismo; Dardos; Jogos de construção; Brinquedos para crianças; Cartas de jogar; Copos para dados [jogos]; Bolas de jogo; Luvas [acessórios de jogos]; Jogos de argolas; Blocos de construção [brinquedos]; Brinquedos de atividades eletrónicos; Brinquedos para animais de estimação; Exercitadores [extensores]; Máquinas para exercício físico; Artigos de ginástica e desporto; Protetores corporais para uso desportivo; Aparelhos de desporto.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate pentru culturism; Săgeți pentru jocul de Darts; Jocuri de construcție; Jucării pentru copii; Cărți de joc; Cupe pentru amestecat zaruri; Mingi de joc; Mănuși [accesorii de joc]; Jocuri cu inele; Blocuri de construcție [jucării]; Jucării de acțiune electronice; Jucării pentru animale de companie; Extensoare; Aparate pentru exerciții fizice; Articole de gimnastică și de sport; Protecții de corp pentru sport; Echipamente pentru sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Posilňovacie stroje; Šípky (hra); Stavebnice; Detské hračky; Hracie karty; Poháre na kocky (na hru); Hracie lopty; Hracie rukavice; Krúžky (hádzanie obručí); Stavebnicové kocky (hračky); Elektronické hračky na rozvoj aktivity; Hračky pre zvieratá chované v domácnosti; Cvičebné náradie na posilňovanie hrudníka; Stroje na telesné cvičenia; Gymnastické a športové predmety; Chrániče tela používané pri športe; Športové vybavenie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Naprave za telovadbo; Pikado; Igre za gradnjo; Otroške igrače; Igralne karte; Posodice za kocke (za kockanje); Igralne žoge; Rokavice za igre; Igre z obroči; Kocke [igrače]; Elektronske akcijske igrače; Igrače za hišne ljubljence; Ekspanderji [za raztegovanje prsnih mišic]; Naprave za telesno vadbo; Gimnastične in športne potrebščine; Ščitniki za telo za uporabo pri športu; Športna oprema.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Träningsapparater; Pilar; Byggsatser; Leksaker avsedda för barn; Spelkort; Bägare för tärningar; Bollar för lek; Handskar för spel; Spel med ringar; Byggklossar [leksaker]; Elektroniska aktivitetsleksaker; Leksaker för husdjur; Muskelstärkare; Maskiner för fysisk träning; Gymnastik- och sportartiklar; Kroppsskydd för sportbruk; Sportutrustning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079094</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>85806</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
