<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:43</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224427</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224427</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>GOVNDVN</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Видеомонитори; USB памет; Слушалки; Преобразуватели за електрически щепсели; Адаптори за енергия; Портативни устройства за измерване на спортна активност; Зареждащи устройства за батерии за употребата с телефони; Зарядни устройства за електронни цигари; Бебефони; Инсталации, предпазващи от кражба, електрически; Етикети за радиочестотни идентификатори [RFID]; Видеокамери, приспособени за наблюдаване; Калъфи за смартфони; Мрежови зарядни устройства; Устройства за четене на карти; Четящи устройства за карти памет; Презареждащи се батерии; Кабелни конектори; Електрически конектори; Защитни тънкослойни покрития, пригодени за смартфони; Слушалки за слагане в уши.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Video monitory; USB flash disky; Sluchátka; Měniče pro elektrické zástrčky; Adaptéry elektrického proudu; Monitorovací zařízení nošená na těle; Nabíječky baterií používané s telefony; Nabíječky elektronických cigaret; Chůvičky; Elektrická zabezpečovací zařízení proti krádeži; Štítky pro radiofrekvenční identifikaci (RFID); Videokamery přizpůsobené pro účely monitorování; Pouzdra na chytré telefony (smartphony); Nabíječky; Čtečky karet; Čtečky paměťových karet; Dobíjecí baterie; Kabelové konektory; Elektrické konektory; Ochranné fólie na chytré telefony; Pecky do uší.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Videoskærme; USB flash drivere; Høretelefoner; Konvertere til elektriske stik; Elektrisk strømadaptere; Wearable aktivitetstrackere; Batteriopladere til brug med telefoner; Opladere til elektroniske cigaretter; Babyalarmer; Tyverihindrende installationer, elektriske; Mærker til radiofrekvensidentifikation [RFID]; Videokameraer til overvågningsformål; Etuier til smartphones; Opladere til stikkontakt; Kortlæserudstyr; Kortlæsere med hukommelse; Genopladelige batterier; Konnektorer til kabler; Elektriske stikforbindelser; Beskyttelsesfilm tilpasset til smartphones; Øresnegle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Videomonitore; USB-Sticks; Kopfhörer; Adapter für elektrische Stecker; Stromadapter; Tragbare Activity Tracker; Batterieladegeräte zur Verwendung mit Telefonen; Ladegeräte für elektronische Zigaretten; Babyüberwachungsgeräte; Elektrische Diebstahlalarmanlagen; Funkfrequenzidentifikations-Tags [RFID-Tags]; Videokameras für Überwachungszwecke; Schalen für Smartphones; Netzladegeräte; Kartenlesegeräte; Speicherkartenleser; Wiederaufladbare Batterien; Kabelstecker; Stromverbindungselemente; Angepasste Schutzfolien für Smartphones; Ohrhörer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Οθόνες βίντεο· Οδηγοί USB (καθολικού σειριακού αγωγού)· Ακουστικά· Μετατροπείς για ρευματολήπτες [φις]· Μετασχηματιστές ηλεκτρικής ισχύος· Φορετοί ανιχνευτές δραστηριότητας· Φορτιστές μπαταρίας χρησιμοποιούμενοι με τηλέφωνα· Φορτιστές για ηλεκτρονικά τσιγάρα· Μέσα παρακολούθησης βρεφών· Αντικλεπτικές εγκαταστάσεις ηλεκτρικές· Ετικέτες ραδιοσυχνικής αναγνώρισης [RFID]· Βιντεοκάμερες προσαρμοσμένες για χρήσεις παρακολούθησης· Θήκες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Φορτιστές τροφοδοτούμενοι με ρεύμα· Εξοπλισμός ανάγνωσης καρτών· Αναγνώστες καρτών μνήμης· Επαναφορτιζόμενες μπαταρίες· Σύνδεσμοι καλωδίων· Ηλεκτρικοί σύνδεσμοι· Προστατευτικές μεμβράνες προσαρμοσμένες για έξυπνα τηλέφωνα· Ακουστικά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Video monitors; Blank USB flash drives; Earphones; Converters for electric plugs; Power adapters; Wearable activity trackers; Battery chargers for use with telephones; Chargers for electronic cigarettes; baby monitors; theft prevention installations, electric; radio-frequency identification [RFID] tags; video surveillance cameras; cases for smartphones; mains chargers; card readers; memory card readers; rechargeable batteries; Cable connectors; power connectors; protective films adapted for smartphones; Earbuds.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Monitores de vídeo; Memorias USB; Auriculares intraurales; Convertidores de enchufe; Adaptadores de corriente; Monitores de actividad física ponibles; Cargadores de baterías para su uso con teléfonos; Cargadores para cigarrillos electrónicos; Dispositivos de audio y vídeo para la vigilancia de bebés; Instalaciones eléctricas antirrobo; Etiquetas de identificación por radiofrecuencias; Videocámaras adaptadas para la monitorización; Estuches para teléfonos inteligentes; Cargadores de red; Equipos lectores de tarjetas; Lectores de tarjeta de memoria; Baterías recargables; Conectores de cables; Conectores de alimentación [eléctricos]; Películas de protección para teléfonos inteligentes [smartphones]; Auriculares de botón.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Videomonitorid; USB-mälupulgad; Kõrvaklapid; Elektripistikute konverterid; Elektritoiteadapterid; Kantavad aktiivsusmonitorid; Telefonide akulaadijad; E-sigarettide laadurid; Beebimonitorid; Elektrilised vargust ennetavad seadmed; Raadiosagedustuvastuse [RFID] märgised; Videokaamerad jälgimise otstarbel; Nutitelefonide ümbrised; Toitevõrku ühendatavad laadijad; Kaardilugejad; Mälukaardilugejad; Akupatareid; Kaabliklemmid; Elektripistikud, pistikuühendused; Nutitelefonide kaitsekiled; Kõrvatropid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Videomonitorit; USB-muistit; Kuulokkeet; Muuntimet sähköpistokkeita varten; Verkkomuuntajat; Puettavat aktiivisuusmittarit; Puhelinten kanssa käytettävät akkulaturit; Elektronisten savukkeiden laturit; Vauvamonitorit; Varkaudenestolaitteet, sähkökäyttöiset; Radiotaajuustunnistuksella (RFID) toimivat tunnistusmerkit; Videovalvontakamerat; Älypuhelinten kuoret; Verkkojohdot; Kortinlukijat; Muistikorttien lukijat; Ladattavat akut; Kaapeliliittimet; Teholiittimet; Älypuhelimille tarkoitetut suojakalvot; Korvanappikuulokkeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Moniteurs vidéo; Clés USB; Casques d'écoute; Convertisseurs pour fiches électriques; Adaptateurs de courant; Capteurs d'activité à porter sur soi; Chargeurs de batteries pour téléphones; Chargeurs pour cigarettes électroniques; Dispositifs audio et vidéo pour la surveillance de bébés; Installations électriques pour préserver du vol; Étiquettes d'identification par radiofréquence [étiquettes IRF]; Caméras de surveillance; Étuis pour smartphones; Chargeurs secteur; Lecteurs de cartes; Lecteurs de cartes mémoire; Batteries rechargeables; Connecteurs de câbles; Connecteurs d'alimentation; Films de protection conçus pour ordiphones [smartphones]; Écouteurs-boutons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Video monitori; USB uređaji [USB stickovi]; Slušalice; Pretvarači za električne utikače; Strujni adapteri; Uređaji za praćenje aktivnosti koji se nose; Punjači za telefonske baterije; Punjači za elektroničke cigarete; Monitori za bebe; Električne instalacije protiv krađe; Oznake za prepoznavanje radijskih frekvencija [RFID]; Kamere za video nadzor; Etuiji za pametne telefone; Mrežni punjači; Oprema za čitanje kartica; Čitači memorijskih kartica; Punjive baterije; Konektori za kablove; Konektori za struju; Zaštitne folije prilagođene za pametne telefone; Slušalice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Videomonitorok; USB pendrive-ok; Fejhallgatók; Átalakítók elektromos csatlakozókhoz; Elektromos hálózati adapterek; Viselhető aktivitásészlelők; Akkumulátortöltők telefonokhoz; Töltők elektromos cigarettákhoz; Bébiőrök; Lopásgátló berendezések, elektromos; Rádiófrekvenciás azonosító [RFID] címkék; Monitorozási, megfigyelési célokra kialakított videokamerák; Tokok okostelefonhoz; Hálózati töltők; Kártyaolvasó készülékek, berendezések; Memóriakártya olvasók; Újratölthető elemek; Kábelcsatlakozók, kábelösszekötők; Elektromos csatlakozók [konnektorok]; Védőfóliák okostelefonokhoz; Fülhallgatók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Monitor video; Chiavi USB; Auricolari; Convertitori per prese elettriche; Adattatori per alimentazioni elettriche; Tracciatori di attività fisica indossabili; Caricabatteria per telefoni; Ricariche per sigarette elettroniche; Dispositivi audio e video per la sorveglianza dei neonati; Impianti di allarme antifurto elettrici; Cartellini d'identificazione a radiofrequenza [RFID]; Telecamere di sorveglianza; Custodie per smartphones; Caricatori di rete; Apparecchiature per la lettura di schede; Lettori di schede di memoria; Batterie ricaricabili; Connettori per cavi; Connettori di alimentazione; Pellicola protettiva adattata per smartphone; Auricolari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vaizdo monitoriai; Atmintukai [USB]; Ausinės; Elektros kištukų keitikliai; Elektros galios adapteriai; Dėvimieji fizinio aktyvumo įrašymo įrenginiai; Telefonų baterijų įkrovikliai; Elektroninių cigarečių įkrovimo įtaisai; Prietaisai kūdikiams stebėti; Elektriniai įrenginiai nuo vagystės; Radijo dažnių atpažinties (RFID) žymenos; Vaizdo kameros stebėjimo reikmėms; Išmaniųjų telefonų dėklai; Maitinimo tinklo įkrovikliai; Kortelių skaitymo įranga; Atminties kortelių nuskaitymo prietaisai; Įkraunamos baterijos; Kabelių jungtys; Elektros jungtukai; Išmaniųjų telefonų ekranų apsauginės plėvelės; Ausinės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Video novērošanas ekrāni; USB zibatmiņas; Ieaušu austiņas; Pārveidotāji elektriskajiem slēdžiem; Strāvas adapteri; Valkājamas ierīces fiziskās aktivitātes izsekošanai; Akumulatoru uzlādes ierīces telefoniem; Elektronisko cigarešu lādētāji; Elektroniskas ierīces zīdaiņu uzraudzībai; Elektriskās iekārtas zādzību novēršanai; Radiofrekvences identifikācijas [RFID] tagi; Videokameras pielāgotas novērošanas nolūkiem; Viedtālruņu maciņi; Tīklu uzlādes ierīces; Karšu lasīšanas aprīkojums; Atmiņu karšu lasītāji; Uzlādējamas baterijas; Kabeļu savienotājelementi; Elektriski savienotājelementi; Aizsargplēves, kas īpaši paredzētas viedtālruņiem; Ieauši (austiņas).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Moniters tal-vidjo; Flash drives tal-USB; Kuffji; Konvertituri għall-plakek tal-elettriku; Adapters tal-enerġija; Apparat li jirreġistra l-attività li jista' jinġarr; Ċarġers tal-batteriji għall-użu mat-telefons; Ċarġers għal sigaretti elettroniċi; Moniters tat-trabi; Installazzjonijiet li jipprevjenu s-serq, tal-elettriku; Tikketti għall-identifikazzjoni tal-frekwenza tar-radju (RFID); Vidjowkameras għas-sorveljanza; Kaxxi għall-ismartphones; Apparat li jtella' n-net; Apparat għall-qari ta' kards; Apparat li jaqra l-iskedi tal-memorja; Batteriji li jistgħu jerġgħu jiġu ċċarġjati; Konnetturi għall-kejbils; Konnetturi tal-elettriku; Films protettivi adattati għal smartfowns; Earbuds.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Videomonitors; USB-sticks; Oortelefoons; Omzetters voor elektrische stekkers; Stroom adapters; Draagbare activiteitsmeters; Batterijopladers voor telefoons; Opladers voor elektronische sigaretten; Babyfoons; Elektrische installaties voor diefstalpreventie; Radiofrequentie-identificatielabels [rfid]; Videocamera' s voor bewakingsdoeleinden; Etuis voor smartphones; Laders voor in het stopcontact; Kaartlezers; Geheugenkaartlezers; Oplaadbare batterijen; Kabelconnectors; Stroomconnectoren; Beschermende folie aangepast aan smartphones; Oortjes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Monitory wideo; Pamięci zewnętrzne USB; Słuchawki [douszne]; Przejściówki do wtyczek elektrycznych; Zasilacze sieciowe; Przyrządy do śledzenia aktywności do noszenia na sobie; Ładowarki baterii do użytku z telefonami; Ładowarki do papierosów elektronicznych; Urządzenia do monitorowania niemowląt; Elektryczne instalacje przeciwwłamaniowe; Znaczniki RFID [wykorzystujące technologię identyfikacji radiowej]; Kamery wideo przystosowane do celów monitoringowych; Etui na smartfony; Ładowarki sieciowe; Sprzęt do odczytywania kart; Czytniki kart pamięci; Baterie do ponownego ładowania; Złącza do kabli; Wtyki przewodów zasilających; Folie ochronne dostosowane do smartfonów; Słuchawki douszne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Monitores de vídeo; Unidades de disco amovível [USB flash drives]; Auriculares; Conversores para fichas elétricas; Adaptadores de corrente; Dispositivos de uso corporal para registo de atividade física; Carregadores de baterias para usar em telefones; Carregadores de cigarros eletrónicos; Dispositivos para vigilância de bebés; Instalações elétricas antirroubo; Etiquetas de identificação por radiofrequência [RFID]; Câmaras de vídeo para fins de monitorização; Capas para smartphones; Carregadores de rede; Equipamento para leitura de cartões; Leitores de cartões de memória; Baterias recarregáveis; Conetores de cabos; Conectores elétricos; Películas protetoras adaptadas para smartphones; Auriculares.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Monitoare video; Memorii USB; Căști auriculare; Convertoare pentru fișe electrice; Adaptoare de curent; Dispozitive portabile de urmărire a activității; Încărcătoare de baterii pentru telefoane; Încărcătoare pentru țigarete electronice; Dispozitive de monitorizare a bebelușilor; Instalații electrice antifurt; Marcaje pentru identificarea frecvenței radio [RFID]; Camere video de supraveghere; Carcase pentru telefoane inteligente; Încărcătoare de rețele de alimentare; Dispozitive pentru citirea cardurilor; Cititoare pentru cardurile de memorie; Baterii reîncărcabile; Conectori de cabluri; Conectoare de alimentare; Folii de protecție adaptate pentru telefoane inteligente; Minicăști de urechi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Video monitory; USB kľúče; Slúchadlá; Meniče pre elektrické zásuvky; Elektrické adaptéry; Zariadenia na sledovanie fyzickej aktivity nosené na tele; Nabíjačky na batérie pre použitie s telefónmi; Nabíjačky na elektronické cigarety; Audiovizuálne prístroje na monitorovanie bábätiek; Elektrické zariadenia proti krádežiam; Rádiofrekvenčné identifikačné štítky [RFID]; Videokamery na prispôsobené na monitorovacie účely; Puzdrá na smartfóny; Sieťová nabíjačka; Zariadenia na čítanie kariet; Čítačky pamäťových kariet; Dobíjateľné batérie; Káblové konektory; Sieťové konektory; Ochranné fólie na smartfóny; Slúchadlá do uší.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Video monitorji; USB ključki; Slušalke; Pretvorniki za električne vtiče; Adapterji za električno omrežje; Nosljive naprave za spremljanje aktivnosti; Polnilci baterij za telefone; Polnilci za elektronske cigarete; Otroške varuške; Protivlomne napeljave, električne; Radiofrekvenčne identifikacijske [RFID] oznake; Video kamere, prilagojene za spremljanje; Etuiji za pametne telefone; Omrežni polnilci; Oprema za branje kartic; Čitalniki pomnilniških kartic; Baterije za ponovno polnjenje; Kabelski konektorji; Električni konektorji; Zaščitne folije, prilagojene za pametne telefone; Slušalke za v uho.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Videomonitorer; USB-minnen; Hörlurar; Adaptrar till elkontakter; Nätadaptrar; Bärbara aktivitetsband; Batteriladdare för användning med telefoner; Laddare för elektroniska cigaretter; Övervakningsapparater för spädbarn; Elektriska stöldförhindrande installationer; Taggar för radiofrekvensidentifiering [RFID-taggar]; Videokameror anpassade för övervakningsändamål; Skal för smartphones; Nätladdare; Kortläsningsutrustning; Läsare för minneskort; Återuppladdningsbara batterier; Kabelanslutningar; Strömkontakter; Skyddsfilm för smartphones; Öronsnäckor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079095</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>85806</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
