<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:43</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224162</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224162</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>VARACL</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162199996</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/224/018224162/000162199996.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.01</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Лепила за цели от типа „направи си сам"; Пергаментова хартия; Ваденки; Стативи за художници; Торбички за подаръци; Лепила за канцеларски цели и домашна употреба; Картички за различни празници; Хартия за етикети; Шаблони за нокти; Четки за рисуване; Хартиени декорации; Етикети от хартия; Временни татуировки; Восък за печати; Чертожни кабърчета; Хартиени чантички за опаковане на подаръци; Хартиени декорации за поставяне върху торти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Lepidla pro kutily; Pergamenový papír; Obtisky; Malířské stojany; Dárkové tašky; Lepicí pasty pro kancelářské potřeby nebo pro domácnost; Blahopřání, která se posílají na svátky; Papír na etikety; Šablony na nehty; Malířské štětce (výtvarné potřeby); Papírové ozdoby na dorty; Papírové etikety; Dočasná tetování; Pečetní vosk; Připínáčky; Papírové dárkové tašky; Papírové ozdoby na dorty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Lim til gør det selv-formål; Pergamentpapir; Overføringsbilleder; Staffelier til malere; Gaveposer; Klister til husholdningsbrug og som papirhandlervarer; Lykønskningskort; Etiketpapir; Negleskabeloner; Malerpensler; Papirdekorationer til kager; Etiketter af papir; Midlertidige tatoveringer; Segllak; Tegnestifter; Gaveposer af papir; Papirpynt til kager.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Do-it-yourself-Klebstoffe [Bastelbedarf]; Pergamentpapier; Abziehbilder; Malstaffeleien; Geschenktüten; Klebstoffe für Papier- und Schreibwaren oder für Haushaltszwecke; Grußkarten; Etikettenpapier; Schablonen für Fingernägel; Malpinsel; Kuchendekorationen aus Papier; Papieraufkleber; Entfernbare Tattoos [Klebebilder]; Siegellack; Reißnägel [Heftzwecken]; Geschenkbeutel aus Papier; Tortenaufsätze aus Papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κόλλες για ιδιοκατασκευές· Χαρτί περγαμηνής· Χαλκομανίες που εμφανίζονται με τριβή· Ζωγραφικής καβαλέτα· Τσάντες για δώρα· Κολλητικές ύλες για γραφική ύλη ή για οικιακούς σκοπούς· Εορταστικές κάρτες· Χαρτί για ετικέτες· Διάτρητα (στένσιλ) για νύχια· Πινέλα ζωγραφικής· Χάρτινα διακοσμητικά για τούρτες· Χάρτινες ετικέτες· Προσωρινά τατουάζ· Βουλοκέρι· Πινέζες[αιχμές]· Χάρτινες τσάντες δώρων· Χάρτινες διακοσμητικές φιγούρες για τούρτες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Adhesives for do-it-yourself purposes; Baking paper; Decals; Easels; Gift bags; Glue for stationery or household use; Holiday cards; Label paper; Nail stencils; Paint brushes; Paper cake decorations; Paper tags; Temporary tattoos; Wax (Sealing -); Push pins; Paper gift bags; Paper cake toppers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pegamentos para bricolaje; Papel pergamino; Calcomanías; Caballetes de pintura; Bolsas de regalo; Colas de papelería o para uso doméstico; Tarjetas de felicitación de festividades; Papel para etiquetas; Plantillas para las uñas; Pinceles; Decoraciones de papel para pasteles; Etiquetas de papel; Tatuajes temporales; Lacre; Chinchetas; Bolsas de papel para regalos; Decoraciones de papel para tartas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meisterdamisliimid; Pärgamentpaber; Dekalkomaantrükised, siirdepildid, ülekantavad pildid; Molbertid; Kinkekotid; Kantselei- või majapidamisliim; Piltpostkaardid; Etiketipaber; Küünešabloonid; Värvipintslid; Paberist tordikaunistused; Paberetiketid; Ajutised tätoveeringud; Kirjalakk, pitsativaha; Knopkad; Paberist kingikotid; Paberist tordikaunistused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Liimat askartelukäyttöön; Pergamenttipaperi; Hangattavat siirtokuvat; Taiteilijoiden maalaustelineet; Lahjakassit; Liimat toimisto- ja kotitalouskäyttöön; Lomakortit; Etikettipaperi; Kynsimallineet; Siveltimet; Paperiset kakunkoristeet; Paperiset etiketit; Väliaikaiset tatuoinnit; Sinettivaha; Piirustusnastat; Paperiset lahjakassit; Paperiset kakun päällyskoristeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Adhésifs pour le bricolage; Papier-parchemin; Décalcomanies; Chevalets pour la peinture; Sacs-cadeaux en papier; Colles pour la papeterie ou le ménage; Cartes de vœux; Papier pour étiquettes; Pochoirs pour les ongles; Pinceaux; Décorations en papier pour gâteaux; Étiquettes en papier; Tatouages temporaires (autocollants); Cire à cacheter; Punaises [pointes]; Sacs-cadeaux en papier; Décorations en papier pour gâteaux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Ljepila za uradi sam aktivnosti; Pergament; Preslikači; Slikarski stalci; Poklon vrećice; Ljepila za papirnate proizvode ili kućanske potrebe; Čestitke za praznike; Papir za etikete; Šablone za nokte; Kistovi; Papirnati ukrasi za kolače; Papirnate etikete; Privremene tetovaže; Vosak, pečatni; Pribadače; Papirnate poklon vrećice; Papirnati ukrasi za tortu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ragasztók barkácsoláshoz; Pergamenpapír; Kaparós matricák; Festőállványok; Ajándékzacskók; Ragasztók irodai és otthoni célokra; Képeslapok; Címkepapír; Körömsablonok; Ecsetek; Papírdíszek süteményekhez, tortákhoz; Papírcímkék; Ideiglenes tetoválások; Pecsétviasz; Rajzszegek; Ajándék táskák, szatyrok papírból; Papír tortadíszek/süteménydíszek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Adesivi per il bricolage; Carta pergamena; Decalcomanie; Cavalletti da pittore; Sacchetti da regalo; Adesivi per la cartoleria o per uso domestico; Biglietti d'auguri per le festività; Carta per etichette; Stencil per unghie; Pennelli; Decorazioni di carta per dolci; Etichette di carta; Tatuaggi temporanei; Cera per sigillare [ceralacca]; Puntine da disegno; Sacchetti di carta per regali; Decorazioni di carta per torte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Lipniosios medžiagos mėgėjiško meistravimo reikmėms; Pergamentinis popierius; Dekalkomanijos; Molbertai; Dovanų maišeliai; Klijai (raštinės ar buities reikmėms); Šventiniai atvirukai; Etikečių popierius; Nagų šablonai; Dažų teptukai; Popieriniai tortų papuošimai; Popierinės etiketės; Laikinosios tatuiruotės; Kietasis antspaudų lakas; Braižybiniai smeigtukai; Popieriniai dovanų maišeliai; Popierinės tortų puošmenos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Līmvielas rokdarbiem; Pergamenta papīrs; Novelkamās bildītes (dekalkomānija); Molberti; Dāvanu maisiņi; Līme kancelejas un mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Ziemassvētku kartiņas; Uzlīmju papīrs; Nagu šabloni; Otas; Papīra dekorācijas kūkām; Etiķetes no papīra; Tetovējumu uzlīmes; Zīmoglaka; Spraudītes; Papīra dāvanu maisiņi; Kūku dekorācijas no papīra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Sustanzi li jwaħħlu għal skopijiet do-it-yourself; Parċmina; Karti għar-riproduzzjoni litografika; Kavalletti tal-pitturi; Basktijiet għar-rigali; Adeżivi għal skopijiet ta' kartolerija jew domestiku; Kartolini tal-vaganzi; Karti bħala tikketti; Stensils għad-dwiefer; Pniezel taż-żebgħa; Dekorazzjonijiet tal-karti għall-kejkijiet; Tikketti tal-karti; Tatwaġġi temporanji; Xemgħa li tissiġilla; Labar għat-twaħħil tal-karti tad-disinn mat-tavlozza; Boroż tal-karti għar-rigali; Dekorazzjonijiet tal-karti għall-kejkijiet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kleefstoffen voor doe-het-zelfgebruik; Perkamentpapier; Overdrukplaatjes; Schildersezels; Geschenktasjes; Kleefstoffen voor kantoor- en huishoudelijk gebruik; Kaarten voor de feestdagen; Etikettenpapier; Nagelsjablonen; Penselen; Papieren taartversieringen; Papieren etiketten; Tijdelijke tatoeëringen; Zegellak; Punaises; Tassen van papier voor geschenken; Taartversieringen van papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kleje do celów majsterkowania; Papier pergaminowy; Suche kalkomanie; Sztalugi malarskie; Torby na prezenty; Kleje do materiałów papierniczych lub do użytku domowego; Kartki świąteczne; Papier do etykietowania; Szablony do paznokci; Pędzle; Papierowe ozdoby do ciast; Etykiety z papieru; Tatuaże zmywalne; Lak do pieczętowania; Pinezki; Papierowe torby na prezenty; Papierowe ozdoby do ciast.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Adesivos para bricolage; Papel de pergaminho; Decalques [decalcomanias]; Cavaletes para a pintura; Sacos para presentes; Adesivos para papelaria ou uso doméstico; Cartões festivos; Papel para etiquetas; Stencils para as unhas; Pincéis; Decorações em papel para bolos; Etiquetas em papel; Tatuagens temporárias; Lacre; Tachas [pioneses]; Sacos de papel para presentes; Decorações em papel para bolos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Adezivi pentru bricolaj; Hârtie pergament; Decalcomanii; Șevalete pentru pictură; Pungi pentru cadouri; Adezivi; Cărți poștale ilustrate; Hârtie pentru etichete; Șabloane pentru unghii; Pensule; Decorațiuni din hârtie pentru prăjituri; Etichete din hârtie; Tatuaje temporare; Ceară pentru sigilii; Pioneze (metalice) pentru panouri și table școlare; Pungi de hârtie pentru cadouri; Ornamente de hârtie pentru torturi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Lepidlá na použitie pri domácom majstrovaní; Pergamenový papier; Obtlačky; Maliarske stojany; Darčekové tašky; Lepidlá na kancelárske použitie alebo pre domácnosť; Prázdninové pohľadnice; Papier na štítky; Šablóny na nechty; Štetce; Papierové ozdoby na koláč; Papierové etikety; Dočasné tetovačky; Pečatné vosky; Pripináčiky; Papierové darčekové tašky; Papierové ozdoby na torty.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Lepila za amaterska hišna dela; Pergamentni papir; Odtisi za otiranje; Slikarska stojala; Darilne vrečke; Lepila za pisarniške in gospodinjske namene; Razglednice; Papir za etikete; Šablone za nohte; Čopiči; Papirnate dekoracije za torte; Etikete iz papirja; Začasne tetovaže; Pečatni vosek; Risalni žebljički; Papirnate darilne vrečke; Papirnati okraski za torte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Lim för hobbybruk; Pergamentpapper; Gnuggbilder; Målarstafflier; Presentpåsar; Klister för kontors- eller hushållsändamål; Kort för olika högtider; Etikettpapper; Nagelschabloner; Målarpenslar; Tårtdekorationer av papper; Pappersetiketter; Borttagbara tatueringar; Sigillvax; Häftstift; Presentpåsar i papper; Papperspynt för tårtor av papper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>71845</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
