<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-28T12:49:20</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224914</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224914</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-08</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-25</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-08</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-28</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>EYSO Home</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>6</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Куки от метал за окачалки за дрехи; Шкафове от метал; Куки от метал за окачалки за дрехи; Кошници от метал; Куки от метал за огнища; Пощенски кутии от метал; Кутии от неблагородни метали.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kovové háčky pro řadové věšáky na šaty; Bedny (kovové); Kovové háčky na věšení oděvů; Kovové koše; Háčky [železářské zboží]; Kovové poštovní schránky; Krabice z běžných kovů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Metalkroge til tøjstativer; Metalbokse; Tøjkroge af metal; Kurve af metal; Kroge af metal; Brevkasser af metal; Kasser af uædle metaller.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Garderobenhaken aus Metall; Kästen, Kisten aus Metall; Kleiderhaken aus Metall [Einrichtungsartikel]; Körbe aus Metall; Haken [Kleineisenwaren]; Briefkästen aus Metall; Kästen aus unedlen Metallen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Άγκιστρα μεταλλικά για ενδύματα· Μεταλλικά δοχεία· Άγκιστρα μεταλλικά για ενδύματα· Κάνιστρα μεταλλικά· Άγκιστρα μεταλλικά· Γραμματοκιβώτια [μεταλλικά]· Κουτιά από κοινά μέταλλα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hooks of metal for clothes rails; Chests of metal; Metal clothes hooks; Baskets of metal; Metal hooks; Letter boxes of metal; Boxes of common metal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Ganchos metálicos para percheros; Cajas de metal; Ganchos metálicos para prendas de vestir; Cestos metálicos; Ganchos metálicos; Buzones de correo metálicos; Cajas de metales comunes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Riidepuude metallist konksud; Kirstud (metallist); Riidepuude metallist konksud; Metallist korvid; Konksud, haagid [rauakaubad]; Metallist postkastid; Lihtmetallist kastid, karbid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vaatekoukut, metalliset; Metallikorit; Metalliset vaatekoukut; Korit (Metalli -); Patakoukut, metalliset; Metalliset postilaatikot; Rasiat, epäjaloa metallia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Crochets de portemanteaux métalliques; Huches métalliques; Patères métalliques pour vêtements; Corbeilles métalliques; Crochets métalliques; Boîtes aux lettres métalliques; Boîtes en métaux communs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Metalne kuke za stalke za odjeću; Kutije, sanduci od metala; Metalne kuke za stalke za odjeću; Metalne košarice; Metalne kuke; Pisma (metalni sandučići za pisma); Kutije od neplemenitih metala.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Fémakasztók ruhafogasokhoz; Fémdobozok; Fémakasztók ruhafogasokhoz; Fémkosarak; Edényakasztók fémből; Levélszekrények fémből; Dobozok fémből.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Ganci per attaccapanni in metallo; Casse di metallo; Patere [ganci] per abbigliamento [in metallo]; Panieri in metallo; Uncini [chincaglieria in metallo]; Cassette per lettere in metallo; Scatole in metalli comuni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Metaliniai drabužių pakabų kabliai; Bunkeriai (metaliniai --- ); Metaliniai drabužių kabliukai; Metaliniai krepšiai; Kabliai (Metaliniai puodų -); Dėžutės (Metalinės laiškų -); Paprastųjų metalų dėžutės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Drēbju pakaramie no metāla; Metāla konteineri; Metāla āķi apģērbu pakāršanai; Metāla grozi; Āķi [metāla izstrādājumi]; Metāla pasta kastītes; Kastes no parastajiem metāliem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ganċijiet tal-metall għal gwardarobbi; Kontenituri għaż-żibel tal-metall; Ganċijiet tal-metall għal gwardarobbi; Basktijiet tal-metall; Ganċijiet tal-metall li magħhom tiddendel borma; Kaxxi tal-ittri tal-metall; Kaxxi tal-metall komuni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kapstokhaken van metaal; Kisten van metaal; Kleerhaken van metaal; Manden van metaal; Haken van metaal; Brievenbussen van metaal; Dozen van onedele metalen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Haki do wieszania ubrań, metalowe; Skrzynie metalowe; Haki do wieszania ubrań, metalowe; Kosze metalowe; Haki metalowe; Skrzynki na listy metalowe; Pudełka z metali nieszlachetnych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Ganchos de cabides metálicos; Uchas metálicas; Cabides metálicos para vestuário; Cestos metálicos; Ganchos [ferragens metálicas]; Caixas de correio metálicas; Caixas em metais comuns.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cârlige metalice pentru portmantouri; Casete metalice; Cârlige metalice pentru portmantouri; Coşuri metalice; Cârlige metalice de uz menajer; Cutii metalice pentru scrisori; Cutii din metale obişnuite.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kovové vešiakové háčiky; Kontajnery (kovové -); Kovové háčiky vešiakov na odevy; Kovové koše; Háčiky (železiarsky tovar); Poštové schránky (Kovové -); Kovové skrinky, krabice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kovinski kavlji za garderobna stojala; Zaboji kovinski; Kljuke za obleke iz kovine; Košare iz kovine; Kovinski kavlji za obešanje posode; Poštni nabiralniki iz kovine; Zaboji iz nežlahtne kovine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Klädkrokar av metall; Kistor av metall; Klädkrokar av metall; Korgar av metall; Metallkrokar; Brevlådor av metall; Askar av oädel metall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Стоки от хартия; Торби за отпадъци [от хартия или от полиетилен]; Папки за книжа; Папки [за офиси]; Подноси за писма; Контейнери за съхранение, изработени от хартия; Контейнери за съхранение, изработени от картон; Дръжки за моливи; Преспапиета; Офисни принадлежности; Поставки за писалки и моливи; Подложки за документи с щипка; Картини, фотографии; Бележници [канцеларски принадлежности]; Книжки; Кламери; Щипки за държачи за баджове за имена [офисни принадлежности]; Канцеларски принадлежности за съхраняване на документи; Държачи за баджове за имена [офисни принадлежности]; Пликове [канцеларски принадлежности]; Календари; Лента за отбелязване на страници в книга; Офисни перфоратори; Писалки за маркиране; Значки с имена [oфис консумативи]; Тетрадки; Кламери; Гуми за триене; Пособия за писане; Несесери за принадлежности за писане [канцеларски]; Подложка за ръка; Настолни шкафове за канцеларски материали [офисни принадлежности].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Papírové zboží; Pytle na odpad z papíru nebo plastických hmot; Desky na dokumenty; Desky na dokumenty [kancelářské potřeby]; Kancelářské odkladače; Ukládací, skladovací krabice z papíru; Ukládací nádoby z lepenkového kartonu; Stojánky na tužky; Těžítka; Kancelářské potřeby, s výjimkou nábytku; Stojany na pera a tužky; Psací podložky s klipem; Obrazy; Bloky [kancelářské potřeby]; Brožuřky; Sponky na papír; Klipy pro držáky na jmenovky [kancelářské potřeby]; Stojánky na dokumenty [kancelářské potřeby]; Držáky na jmenovky [kancelářské potřeby]; Obálky [papírnické zboží]; Kalendáře; Záložky do knih; Kancelářské děrovačky; Značkovače [kancelářské potřeby]; Jmenovky [kancelářské potřeby]; Zápisníky (notesy); Sponky na papír; Gumy na mazání; Psací potřeby; Pouzdra na psací potřeby [papírnické zboží]; Podložky na stůl; Stolní skříňky na psací potřeby [kancelářské potřeby].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Papirvarer; Affaldsposer af papir eller plastic; Charteques [dokumentomslag]; Samlemapper [kontorrekvisitter]; Brevbakker; Opbevaringsbeholdere af papir; Opbevaringsbeholdere af papkarton; Blyantsholdere; Brevpressere; Kontorrekvisitter, ikke møbler; Holdere til blyanter og penne; Skriveplader med papirklemme; Billeder; Blokke [papirvarer]; Brochurer; Papirclips; Klemmer til navneskilteholdere [kontorartikler]; Dokumentholdere [kontorartikler]; Navneskilteholdere [kontorartikler]; Kuverter; Kalendere; Bogmærker; Hulleapparater til kontorbrug; Markeringspenne [kontorartikler]; Navneskilte [kontorartikler]; Notesbøger; Papirclips; Viskelæder; Skriveredskaber; Skrivemapper [kontorartikler]; Skriveunderlag; Skrivebordskabinetter til kontorartikler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Papierwaren; Abfallsäcke aus Papier oder Kunststoff; Aktenhüllen; Aktenordner; Briefkörbe; Aufbewahrungsbehälter aus Papier; Aufbewahrungsbehälter aus Pappkarton; Bleistifthalter; Briefbeschwerer; Büroartikel [ausgenommen Möbel]; Halter für Schreibfedern und Bleistifte; Klemmtafeln [Büroartikel]; Bilder; Blöcke [Papier- und Schreibwaren]; Booklets; Büroklammern; Clips für Halter von Namensschildern [Büroartikel]; Dokumentenhüllen; Halter für Namensschilder [Büroartikel]; Hüllen [Papier- und Schreibwaren]; Kalender; Lesezeichen; Locher [Büroartikel]; Markierstifte; Namensschilder [Büroartikel]; Notizbücher; Notizklemmen [Papeteriewaren]; Radiergummis; Schreibgeräte; Schreibmappen [Papeteriewaren]; Schreibtischunterlagen; Tischbehälter und -kästen für Papier- und Schreibwaren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Είδη από χαρτί· Σακκούλες σκουπιδιών [από χαρτί ή πλαστικό]· Καλύμματα εγγράφων· Ντοσιέ εγγράφων γραφείου· Ραφάκια οργάνωσης γραφείου· Χάρτινα δοχεία αποθήκευσης· Χάρτινοι περιέκτες αποθήκευσης· Μολύβια μηχανικά· Βάρη για χαρτιά (πρες-παπιέ)· Είδη γραφείου· Θήκες για πένες και μολύβια· Πινάκια (είδη γραφείου)· Εικόνες· Σημειωματάρια [μπλοκ] είδη χαρτοπωλείου· Φυλλάδια· Συνδετήρες εγγράφων· Κλιπ για υποδοχές κάρτας ονόματος [είδη γραφείου]· Θήκες εγγράφων [είδη γραφείου]· Υποδοχές κάρτας ονόματος [είδη γραφείου]· Φάκελοι [είδη χαρτοπωλείου]· Ημεροδείκτες· Βιβλία (σελιδοδείκτες -ων)· Διατρητικά γραφείου· Μαρκαδόροι υπογράμμισης· Ταμπελίτσες ονόματος [είδη γραφείου]· Σημειωματάρια· Συνδετήρες εγγράφων· Γομολάστιχες· Γραφή (όργανα -ής)· Θήκες γραφής [χαρτικά]· Επιτραπέζια σημειωματάρια· Επιτραπέζια ερμάρια για χαρτικά [είδη γραφείου].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Paper goods; Garbage bags of paper or of plastics; Folders for papers; Document files [stationery]; Desk trays; Storage containers made of paper; Storage containers made of cardboard; Pencil holders; Paperweights; Office requisites; Stands for pens and pencils; Clipboards; Pictures; Pads [stationery]; Booklets; Paper-clips; Clips for name badge holders [office requisites]; Document holders [stationery]; Name badge holders [office requisites]; Envelopes [stationery]; Calendars; Bookmarkers; Office perforators; Marker pens; Name badges [office requisites]; Notebooks; Paper-clips; Rubber erasers; Writing instruments; Writing cases [stationery]; Desk pads; Desktop cabinets for stationery [office requisites].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Productos de papel; Bolsas de basura de papel o materias plásticas; Fundas para documentos; Carpetas para documentos; Bandejas de escritorio; Recipientes para almacenamiento hechos de papel; Contenedores de almacenamiento de cartón; Portalápices; Pisapapeles; Artículos de oficina, excepto muebles; Soportes para plumas, bolígrafos y lápices; Portapapeles de clip [artículos de oficina]; Ilustraciones; Blocs [artículos de papelería]; Cartillas [cuadernillos]; Clips para sujetar papeles; Pinzas de sujeción para soportes de tarjetas de identificación [artículos de oficina]; Fundas portadocumentos [artículos de papelería]; Soportes de tarjetas de identificación [artículos de oficina]; Sobres [artículos de papelería]; Calendarios; Marcapáginas; Máquinas perforadoras para la oficina; Marcadores [artículos de papelería]; Tarjetas de identificación [artículos de oficina]; Libretas; Clips para sujetar papeles; Gomas de borrar; Instrumentos de escritura; Estuches de escritura [artículos de papelería]; Tapetes de escritorio; Archivadores [armarios] de escritorio para artículos de papelería [artículos de oficina].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Paberikaubad; Paberist või plastist prügikotid; Paberitaskud; Dokumendimapid, aktimapid [kantseleitarbed]; Dokumendisahtlid; Paberist hoiumahutid; Kartongist hoiumahutid; Pliiatsihoidlid; Paberipressid; Kantseleitarbed, v.a mööbel; Sulepea- ja pliiatsihoidlid; Kirjutusalused; Pildid; Plokid [kirjatarbed]; Brošüürid; Kirjaklambrid; Nimekaardihoidikute klambrid [kontoritarbed]; Dokumendimapid [kantseleitarbed]; Nimekaardihoidikud [kontoritarbed]; Ümbrikud [kirjatarbed]; Kalendrid; Järjehoidjad; Augurauad, mulgustid, perforaatorid [kantseleitarbed]; Markerid [kantseleitarbed]; Nimesildid [kontoritarbed]; Märkmikud; Kirjaklambrid; Kustutuskummid; Kirjutusvahendid; Kirjatarvete karbid; Kirjutuslauamatid; Kirjatarvete sahtliboksid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Paperitavarat; Roskapussit [paperia tai muovia]; Asiakirjakuoret; Mapit; Pöytätelineet; Paperiset säilytysastiat; Pahviset säilytysastiat; Lyijykynän pitimet; Paperipainot; Toimistotarvikkeet; Mustekynien ja lyijykynien telineet; Kirjoituslevyt paperinpidikkeellä; Kuvat; Lehtiöt; Kirjaset; Paperiklemmarit; Nipistimet nimikylttien pidikkeisiin [toimistotarvikkeet]; Asiakirjatelineet [toimistotarvike]; Nimikylttien pidikkeet [toimistotarvikkeet]; Kirjekuoret (paperikauppatavarat); Kalenterit; Kirjanmerkit; Toimistorei'ittimet; Korostuskynät; Nimitunnukset [toimistotarvikkeet]; Muistikirjat; Paperiklemmarit; Pyyhekumit; Kirjoitusvälineet; Kirjoitusvälinekotelot; Kirjoitusalustat; Pöydälle asetettavat kaapit paperikauppatavaroille [toimistotarvikkeet].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Articles en papier; Sacs à ordures en papier ou en matières plastiques; Chemises pour documents; Dossiers [papeterie]; Bacs à courrier; Boîtes de rangement en papier; Récipients de rangement en carton; Porte-crayons; Presse-papiers; Articles de bureau à l'exception des meubles; Supports pour plumes et crayons; Planchettes à pince [articles de bureau]; Images; Blocs [papeterie]; Livrets; Trombones à papier; Pinces pour porte-badges d'identification [articles de bureau]; Pochettes pour documents; Porte-badges d'identification [articles de bureau]; Enveloppes [papeterie]; Calendriers; Marque-pages; Perforeuses de bureau; Stylos marqueurs; Badges d'identification [articles de bureau]; Carnets; Trombones à papier; Gommes à effacer; Instruments d'écriture; Nécessaires pour écrire [papeterie]; Sous-main; Armoires de rangement de bureau pour la papeterie [articles de bureau].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Papirnati proizvodi; Vreće za smeće, papirnate ili plastične; Košuljice za spise; Fascikli; Košare za pisma; Spremnici za čuvanje od papira; Spremnici za pohranu od kartona; Držači za olovke; Utezi za papir; Uredski pribor; Stalci za olovke i kemijske olovke; Ploče s kopčom za papire; Slike; Blokovi [papirnati proizvodi]; Brošure; Spajalice za papir; Kopče za navlake za kartice s imenom [uredski pribor]; Stalci za držanje papira [uredski pribor]; Navlake za kartice s imenom [uredski pribor]; Omotnice [papirnati proizvodi]; Kalendari; Označivači stranica u knjizi; Uredske bušilice; Markeri; Bedževi s imenom [uredski pribor]; Bilježnice; Spajalice za papir; Gumice za brisanje; Oprema za pisanje; Poslovne mape [uredski materijal]; Podloge za stol; Ormarići za uredski pribor [uredske potrepštine].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Papíráru; Szemeteszsákok papírból vagy műanyagból; Iratgyűjtők, dossziék; Dossziék [papíráruk]; Asztali iratrendező tálcák; Papírdobozok tárolásra; Kartondobozos tárolódobozok; Ceruzatartók; Papírnehezékek; Irodai kellékek; Toll- és ceruzatartók; Csipeszes felírótáblák; Képek; Blokkok [papíráruk]; Könyvecskék, brosúrák; Gémkapocs; Csatok névjegykártya-tartókhoz [irodai felszerelések]; Irattartók [papíráru]; Névtábla-tartók [irodai felszerelések]; Borítékok [papíráruk]; Naptárak; Könyvjelzők; Irodai lyukasztógépek; Szövegkiemelő tollak; Névbadgek [hivatali kellékek]; Noteszok; Gémkapocs; Radírgumik; Íróeszközök; Írókészletek [papíráruk]; Asztali könyöklők; Irodaszer szekrények [irodai berendezések].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Articoli in carta; Sacchi per la spazzatura di carta o di materie plastiche; Cartelle per documenti; Raccoglitori [cartoleria]; Cestini per la corrispondenza; Contenitori per deposito in carta; Contenitori da deposito di cartone; Porta-matite; Fermacarte; Articoli per ufficio; Sostegni per penne e matite; Tavolette a pinza [articoli per l'ufficio]; Immagini; Blocchi [cartoleria]; Libretti; Graffette da ufficio; Clips per porta badge [articoli per ufficio]; Portadocumenti [cartoleria]; Porta badge [articoli per ufficio]; Buste [cartoleria]; Calendari; Segnalibri; Perforatori da ufficio; Evidenziatori [cartoleria]; Badge nominativi [articoli per ufficio]; Taccuini; Graffette da ufficio; Gomme per cancellare; Strumenti per scrivere; Astucci portapenne [cartoleria]; Cartelle da scrivania; Armadietti da scrivania per articoli di cartoleria [articoli per ufficio].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Popieriaus prekės; Plastikiniai ar popieriniai šiukšlių maišai; Popieriaus segtuvai; Dokumentų segtuvai [raštinės reikmenys]; Laiškų padėklai; Popierinės talpyklos; Kartoninė tara; Pieštukų koteliai; Prespapjė; Raštinės reikmenys (išskyrus baldus); Plunksnakočių ir pieštukų stoveliai; Rašomosios lentelės su spaustuku; Paveikslai; Bloknotai [raštinės reikmenys]; Bukletai; Popieriaus sąvaržėlės; Vardinių kortelių laikiklių segtukai [raštinės reikmenys]; Dokumentų laikikliai [raštinės reikmenys]; Vardinių kortelių laikikliai [raštinės reikmenys]; Vokai [raštinės reikmenys]; Kalendoriai; Knygų juostelės; Raštinės skylmušos [perforatoriai]; Teksto žymekliai; Vardinės kortelės [raštinės reikmenys]; Užrašų knygutės; Popieriaus sąvaržėlės; Guminiai trintukai; Rašikliai; Rašymo reikmeninės [raštinės reikmenys]; Rašomųjų stalų patiesalai; Raštinės darbo stalų spintelės [biuro reikmenys].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Papīra izstrādājumi; Atkritumu maisi no papīra un sintētiskiem materiāliem; Apvāki papīram; Dokumentu mapes [biroja piederumi]; Galda plaukti dokumentu kārtošanai; Papīra kārbas priekšmetu glabāšanai; Uzglabāšanas tilpnes no kartona kārbām; Zīmuļu turētāji; Preses (rakstāmgalda piederumi); Biroja piederumi (izņemot mēbeles); Statīvi pildspalvām un zīmuļiem; Planšetes; Attēli; Bloknoti [kancelejas preces]; Bukleti; Papīra saspraudes; Klipši vārdu kartīšu turētājiem (biroja rekvizīti); Dokumentu turētāji [kancelejas preces]; Vārdu kartīšu turētāji (biroja piederumi); Aploksnes [rakstāmpiederumi]; Kalendāri; Grāmatzīmes; Caurumotāji biroja vajadzībām; Marķieri; Žetoni ar vārdu (biroja piederumi); Piezīmju grāmatiņas; Papīra saspraudes; Dzēšamgumijas; Rakstāmpiederumi; Rakstāmlietu komplekti [kancelejas piederumi]; Galda paliktņi; Uz darbvirsmas novietojamas kancelejas piederumu kastītes (biroja piederumi).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Oġġetti tal-karti; Boroż taż-żibel (tal-karta jew tal-plastik); Tagħmir għat-tiwi tal-karti; Fajls [kartolerija]; Trejs tal-iskrivanija; Kontenituri tal-karti għall-ħażna; Kaxxi tal-ħżin tal-kartun; Kontenituri għall-lapsijiet; Pożakarti; Oġġetti neċessarji għall-uffiċju (apparti l-għamara); Sostenn għal pinen u għal lapsijiet; Klippbord; Stampi; Folji tal-karti mehmużin flimkien [kartolerija]; Kotba żgħar; Klipps tal-karti; Klipep għall-ħowlders tal-ismijiet [rekwiżiti tal-uffiċċju]; Kontenituri għad-dokumenti [kartolerija]; Ħowlders għall-beġġijiet tal-isem [rekwiżiti tal-uffiċċju]; Envelops [kartoleriji]; Kalendarji; Markaturi għall-kotba li juruk fejn trid tkompli taqra; Għodda għat-titqib tal-karti, għal użu fl-uffiċċju; Highlighters (pinen b'lewn jgħajjat); Beġis tal-ismijiet [rekwiżiti tal-uffiċċju]; Takkwini; Klipps tal-karti; Gomom għat-tħassir; Strumenti għall-kitba; Kaxxetti għal strumenti tal-kitba [kartolerija]; Karti għal fuq l-iskrivanija; Kabinetti ta' fuq l-iskrivanija għall-kartolerija [oġġetti neċessarji għall-uffiċċji].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Papieren goederen; Vuilniszakken van papier of plastic; Documentenmappen; Dossiers [kantoorbehoeften]; Postbakjes; Opslaghouders van papier; Opslagdozen van karton; Potloodhouders; Presse-papiers; Kantoorartikelen, uitgezonderd meubelen; Houders voor pennen en potloden; Klemborden [kantoorartikelen]; Afbeeldingen; Blocnotes; Boekjes; Paperclips; Clips voor houders voor naamkaartjes (kantoorbenodigdheden); Hoesjes voor documenten; Ouders voor naamkaartjes [kantoorbenodigdheden]; Enveloppen; Kalenders; Boekenleggers; Perforators voor kantoorgebruik; Markeerpennen [kantoorbehoeften]; Naambadges [kantoorartikelen]; Notitieboekjes; Paperclips; Vlakgom; Schrijfinstrumenten; Schrijfbehoeften; Sousmains; Kastjes voor papierwaren [kantoorartikelen].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Artykuły papierowe; Worki na śmieci wykonane z papieru lub z tworzyw sztucznych; Skoroszyty na dokumenty; Teczki na dokumenty [artykuły biurowe]; Tacki biurkowe; Papierowe pojemniki do przechowywania; Pojemniki do przechowywania wykonane z kartonu; Pojemniki na ołówki; Przyciski do papieru; Artykuły biurowe [z wyjątkiem mebli]; Podstawki do długopisów i ołówków; Podkładki do pisania z klipsem; Obrazy i zdjęcia; Bloki [artykuły papiernicze]; Broszury; Spinacze do papieru; Klipsy do etui na identyfikatory [artykuły biurowe]; Aktówki [artykuły biurowe]; Etui na identyfikatory [artykuły biurowe]; Koperty [artykuły piśmienne]; Kalendarze; Zakładki do książek; Perforatory biurowe; Zakreślacze; Identyfikatory [artykuły biurowe]; Notatniki [notesy]; Spinacze do papieru; Gumki do ścierania; Przyrządy do pisania; Teczki z notatnikiem i przyborami do pisania [artykuły papiernicze]; Podkładki na biurko; Kasetki na biurko na materiały biurowe [artykuły biurowe].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Produtos de papel; Sacos de lixo em papel ou em matérias plásticas; Capas para papéis; Dossiers [papelaria]; Tabuleiros de secretária; Recipientes de armazenamento feitos de papel; Recipientes de armazenamento em cartão; Porta-lápis [lapiseiras]; Pisa-papéis; Artigos de escritório; Suportes para canetas e lápis; Pranchetas de pinça [artigos de escritório]; Imagens; Blocos [papelaria]; Brochuras; Clipes para papéis; Grampos para crachás [artigos de escritório]; Porta documentos [artigos de papelaria]; Suportes para crachás [artigos de escritório]; Envelopes [papelaria]; Calendários; Marcadores de páginas; Perfuradores de escritório; Marcadores [artigos de papelaria]; Etiquetas de identificação [artigos de escritório]; Blocos de notas; Clipes para papéis; Borrachas para apagar; Instrumentos de escrita; Estojos para escrita [papelaria]; Bases para secretárias; Caixas de arrumação de secretária para papelaria [artigos de escritório].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Produse din hârtie; Saci de gunoi din hârtie sau din material plastic; Mape pentru documente; Dosare [papetărie]; Tăviţe pentru corespondenţă; Recipiente de depozitare fabricate din hârtie; Recipiente de depozitare din carton; Suporturi pentru creioane; Prespapieruri; Birou (articole de -) [cu excepţia mobilelor]; Suporturi pentru stilouri şi creioane; Planşete cu clamă pentru hârtii; Imagini; Blocuri [papetărie]; Broşuri; Agrafe de birou pentru hârtie; Clipsuri pentru suporturi pentru ecusoane cu nume [articole de birou; Dosare pentru documente [papetărie]; Suporturi pentru ecusoane cu nume [articole de birou]; Plicuri [papetărie]; Calendare; Semne de carte; Perforatoare de birou; Markere fluorescente; Ecusoane cu nume [articole de birou]; Carnete de notiţe; Agrafe de birou pentru hârtie; Gume de şters; Instrumente de scris; Mape pentru scris [papetărie]; Blocnotes de birou; Suporturi cu sertare pentru articole de papetărie [birotică].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Papierové tovary; Papierové alebo plastové vrecká na odpadky; Obaly na doklady; Spisové obaly (papiernický tovar); Zásuvky na spisy; Papierové škatule na skladovanie; Nádoby na skladovanie z lepenky; Násady na ceruzky; Ťažidlo na papiere; Kancelárske potreby okrem nábytku; Stojany na perá a ceruzky; Tabule na zapichovanie oznamov; Obrazy; Útržkové bloky; Brožované knihy; Kancelárske sponky; Spony pre držiaky na menovky [kancelárske potreby]; Obálky na dokumenty (papiernický tovar); Držiaky na menovky [kancelárske potreby]; Obálky (papiernický tovar); Kalendáre; Záložky do kníh; Kancelárske dierkovače; Značkovacie perá (papiernický tovar); Menovky [kancelárske potreby]; Poznámkové zošity; Kancelárske sponky; Gumy na gumovanie; Písacie nástroje; Písacie súpravy (papiernický tovar); Podložky na písanie; Stolové skrinky na písacie potreby [kancelárske potreby].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Papirnati izdelki; Vreče za odpadke iz papirja ali plastike; Mape za papirje; Mape za dokumente (pisarniške potrebščine); Namizni pladnji; Posode za shranjevanje iz papirja; Vsebniki za shranjevanje iz kartona; Držala za svinčnike; Pisemski obtežilniki; Pisarniški pripomočki; Stojala za peresa in svinčnike; Podloge s sponkami; Slike; Bloki [pisarniški material]; Knjižice; Papirne sponke; Sponke za držala za imenske priponke [pisarniški pripomočki]; Stojala za dokumente [pisarniški material]; Držala za imenske priponke [pisarniški pripomočki]; Ovoji [pisalne potrebščine]; Koledarji; Označevalci za knjige; Pisarniški luknjači; Marker; Priponke z imeni [pisarniški pripomočki]; Zvezki; Papirne sponke; Radirke; Pisalni pripomočki; Peresnice za pisala [pisalne potrebščine]; Namizne podloge; Namizne omarice za pisarniške potrebščine [pisarniški pripomočki].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Pappersvaror; Soppåsar av papper eller av plast; Aktomslag; Dossierer; Brevkorgar; Förvaringsbehållare av papper; Förvaringsbehållare av pappkartong; Blyertspennhållare; Brevpressar; Kontorsförnödenheter; Ställ för bläckpennor och blyertspennor; Skrivskivor; Tavlor; Block [pappersvaror]; Häften; Pappersgem; Klämmor till namnbrickehållare [kontorsförnödenheter]; Dokumenthållare [kontorsartiklar]; Namnbrickehållare [kontorsförnödenheter]; Kuvert; Kalendrar; Bokmärken; Hålslag för kontor; Markeringspennor; Namnskyltar [kontorsartiklar]; Memo-böcker; Pappersgem; Radergummin; Skrivredskap; Skrivportföljer [kontorsmaterial]; Skrivbordsunderlägg; Förvaringslådor för kontorsartiklar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>20</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Кутии от дърво или пластмаса; Кукички, неметални, за стенни закачалки; Закачалки за дрехи с куки, неметални; Кошове, неметални; Сандъци за играчки; Разделители за чекмеджета; Рафтове за съхранение, направени от пластмаса; Кутии за съхранение от текстили; Куки от метал за окачалки за дрехи, за закрепване на врати; Шкафчета с ключ; Плъзгачи за чекмеджета [железария за мебели]; Багажни клетки за транспортни средства [Мебели]; Контейнери, неметални, за съхранение; Кукички за дрехи; Закачалки за дрехи, стойки за дрехи [мебели] и закачалки за дрехи с куки; Шкаф с плъзгащи чекмеджета; Сгъваеми кутии, неметални; Класьори от пластмаса; Табели от дърво или пластмаса; Табла за окачване на ключове; Масички на колела за сервиране [мебели]; Подложки, сменяеми, за мивки; Рафтове за списания; Поставки за вестници; Шкафове; Чинове; Сандъци, неметални.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Krabice ze dřeva nebo plastu; Háčky na věšení oděvů, ne kovové; Háčky na oděvy, ne kovové; Košíky, ne kovové; Bedny na hračky; Rozdělovače do zásuvek; Skladovací bedny z plastu; Ukládací boxy z textilu; Háčky na šaty z kovu pro umístění na dveře; Uzamykatelné skříňky; Posuvné kolejnice na zásuvky (železářství); Skladovací zásuvky (nábytek); Nekovové nádoby na skladování; Háčky na věšení oděvů; Věšáky na oděvy, stojany na oděvy [nábytek] a ramínka na oděvy; Skříně se zásuvkami; Skládací boxy, nekovové; Stohovatelné tácy z plastu; Vývěsní štíty ze dřeva nebo plastu; Věšáky na klíče (desky); Servírovací stolky na kolečkách [nábytek]; Vyjímatelné podložky do dřezů; Stojany na časopisy; Stojany na noviny; Skříně (kuchyňské); Psací stoly; Bedny, ne kovové.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Æsker af træ eller plastic; Knager, ikke af metal, til knagerækker; Knager, ikke af metal, til beklædningsgenstande; Kurve, ikke af metal; Kister til legetøj; Ruminddelere til skuffer; Opbevaringskister af plastic; Opbevaringsbokse af tekstilstoffer; Garderobeknager af metal til anbringelse på døre; Skuffer; Glideskinner til skuffer [møbelbeslag]; Opbevaringsskuffer [møbler]; Beholdere til opbevaring, ikke af metal; Frakkekroge; Tøjbøjler, tøjstativer [møbler] og tøjknager; Skab med skuffer; Sammenklappelige bokse, ikke af metal; Stabelbakker af plastic; Skilte af træ eller plastic; Nøglebrætter; Rulleborde [møbler]; Løse måtter til køkkenvaske; Tidsskrifthylder; Udstillingsstativer til aviser; Skabe; Skriveborde; Kasser, ikke af metal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Boxen aus Holz oder Kunststoff; Garderobenhaken, nicht aus Metall; Kleiderhaken [Einrichtungsartikel], nicht aus Metall; Körbe, nicht aus Metall; Spielzeugkisten; Trenneinlagen für Schubladen; Aufbewahrungskisten aus Kunststoff; Boxen aus Stoff; Garderobenhaken aus Metall zur Anbringung an Türen; Schubladen; Schubladenführungen; Aufbewahrungskisten [Möbel]; Behälter, nicht aus Metall, zu Aufbewahrungszwecken; Haken für Kleiderstangen; Kleiderbügel, Kleiderständer [Möbel] und Kleiderhaken; Schubladenschrank; faltbare Boxen, nicht aus Metall; Stapelbare Ablagekästen aus Kunststoff; Schilder aus Holz oder Kunststoff; Schlüsselbretter; Servierwagen [Möbel]; Spülsteinmatten; Zeitungshalter; Zeitungsständer; Schränke; Schreibtische; Kästen, Kisten, nicht aus Metall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Κουτιά από ξύλο ή πλαστικό· Άγκιστρα κρεμαστρών [μη μεταλλικά]· Άγκιστρα μη μεταλλικά για ενδύματα· Καλάθια, μη μεταλλικά· Κιβώτια παιχνιδιών· Διαχωριστικά συρταριών· Συρταριέρες αποθήκευσης από πλαστικό· Υφασμάτινα κουτιά φύλαξης· Άγκιστρα ανάρτησης ενδυμάτων από μέταλλο για τοποθέτηση σε θύρες· Φοριαμοί· Ολισθητήρες συρταριών [είδη σιδηροπωλείου για έπιπλα]· Έπιπλα φύλαξης με συρτάρια· Μη μεταλλικά δοχεία για αποθήκευση· Γάντζοι για κρεμάστρες· Κρεμάστρες ενδυμάτων, καλόγεροι (έπιπλα) και άγκιστρα για ενδύματα· Ντουλάπα με συρτάρια· Πτυσσόμενα κουτιά, όχι από μέταλλο· Δίσκοι στοίβαξης από πλαστικό· Πινακίδες από ξύλο ή από πλαστικό· Κλειδιών (Πίνακες ανάρτησης -)· Τροχήλατο τραπεζάκι σερβιρίσματος [έπιπλα]· Επενδύσεις αποσπώμενες για νεροχύτες· Θήκες για περιοδικά· Εφημερίδες (προθήκες -ων)· Ντουλάπια· Γραφεία· Σεντούκια μη μεταλλικά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Boxes of wood or plastic; Hooks, not of metal, for clothes rails; Clothes hooks, not of metal; Baskets, non-metallic; Chests for toys; Dividers for drawers; Storage chests made of plastic; Storage boxes of textile; Hooks of metal for clothes rails for attaching to doors; Lockers; Drawer slides [furniture hardware]; Storage drawers [furniture]; Containers, not of metal, for storage; Coathooks; Clothes hangers, clothes stands [furniture] and clothes hooks; Chest of drawers; Collapsible boxes, not of metal; Stacking trays of plastic; Signboards of wood or plastics; Keyboards for hanging keys; Trolleys [furniture]; Mats, removable, for sinks; Magazine racks; Newspaper display stands; Cupboards; Desks; Chests, not of metal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cajas de madera o de materias plásticas; Ganchos no metálicos para percheros; Prendas de vestir (ganchos [garfios] no metálicos para -); Cestos no metálicos; Baúles para juguetes; Divisores para cajones; Arcones de almacenamiento de plástico; Cajas de almacenamiento de materias textiles; Ganchos metálicos para prendas de vestir para su aplicación en puertas; Cajones; Guías de deslizamiento para cajones [herrajes de muebles]; Cajones de almacenamiento [mobiliario (piezas de -)]; Contenedores que no sean de metal para almacenar; Ganchos de percheros; Perchas para ropa, colgadores de ropa [muebles] y ganchos de ropa; Armario de cajones; Cajas plegables, no de metal; Bandejas apilables de plástico; Letreros de madera o materias plásticas; Tableros para colgar llaves; Carritos [mobiliario]; Esterillas removibles para fregaderos; Revisteros; Expositores para periódicos; Armarios empotrados; Escritorios [muebles]; Cofres no metálicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Puit- või plastkastid; Riidenagid, v.a metallist; Rõivasiinide konksud, riidenagid, v.a metallist; Korvid, v.a metallist; Kastid mänguasjadele, mänguasjakastid; Sahtlite vahejaotused; Plastist säilituskirstud; Riidest säilituskastid; Ustele paigaldatavad metallist riidenagid; Lukustatavad hoiukapid; Sahtliliugurid [rauast mööblimanused]; Ladustuskarbid, -kastid [mööbel]; Hoiumahutid, v.a metallist; Riidevarnad, -nagid; Riidepuud, riidevarnad [mööbel] ja riidenagid; Sahtlitega kapid; Kokkupandavad kastid, v.a metallist; Üksteise otsa virnastatavad plastsahtlid; Puidust või plastist sildid; Alused võtmete riputamiseks; Serveerlauad [mööbel]; Eemaldatavad valamumatid või -katted; Ajakirjaalused, ajakirjahoidlid; Ajalehehoidlid, ajalehealused; Seinakapid; Kirjutuslauad, koolipingid; Kirstud, kastid, v.a metallist.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Laatikot, puuta tai muovia; Koukut vaatetankoja varten, ei-metalliset; Vaatekoukut, ei-metalliset; Korit, ei-metalliset; Kirstut (Lelu -); Vetolaatikoiden välilevyt; Muovista tehdyt säilytysarkut; Kankaiset säilytyslaatikot; Metalliset naulakkokoukut oviin kiinnitettäviksi; Lukittavat kaapit; Vetolaatikkojen liukukiskot [huonekalujen tarvikkeet]; Säilytyslaatikot [huonekalut]; Muut kuin metalliset varastosäiliöt; Vaatekoukut; Vaateripustimet, vaatenaulakot [huonekalut] ja vaatekoukut; Laatikostokaappi; Taitettavat laatikot, ei metallista; Muoviset pinoamiskaukalot; Kyltit, puuta tai muovia; Avaintaulut; Tarjoiluvaunut [kalusteina]; Matot pesualtaisiin, irrotettavat; Lehtitelineet; Sanomalehtitelineet; Kaapit; Pulpetit; Säilytyslaatikot, ei-metalliset.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Caisses en bois ou en matières plastiques; Crochets de portemanteaux non métalliques; Patères [crochets] non métalliques pour vêtements; Paniers non métalliques; Coffres à jouets; Séparateurs pour tiroirs; Coffres de rangement en matières plastiques; Boîtes de rangement textiles; Crochets à vêtements métalliques à poser sur des portes; Tiroirs; Glissières de tiroirs [quincaillerie pour meubles]; Tiroirs de rangement [meubles]; Conteneurs non métalliques de stockage; Patères [portemanteaux]; Cintres pour vêtements, valets [meubles] et patères pour vêtements; Armoires à tiroirs; Caisses pliables non métalliques; Plateaux empilables en matières plastiques; Enseignes en bois ou en matières plastiques; Tableaux accroche-clés; Chariots [mobilier]; Tapis d'évier amovibles; Porte-revues; Présentoirs pour journaux; Placards; Bureaux [meubles]; Coffres non métalliques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kutije, drvene ili plastične; Kuke vješalica za odijela, nemetalne; Vješalice za kapute, nemetalne; Košare, nemetalne; Sanduci za igračke; Pregrade za ladice; Škrinje za skladištenje od plastike; Tekstilne kutije za skladištenje; Metalne kuke za odjeću za postavljanje na vrata; Ormari s bravama; Vodilice ladice [oprema za namještaj]; Kutije za odlaganje [namještaj]; Nemetalni spremnici za pohranjivanje; Kuke za vješanje odjeće; Vješalice, stalci [namještaj] i kuke za odjeću; Ormar s ladicama; Sklopive kutije, nemetalne; Plastične kašete; Natpisi firmi od drva ili plastike; Ploče za vješanje ključeva; Kolica za posluživanje [namještaj]; Sudoperi (prostirači za sudopere); Stalci za časopise; Stalci za izlaganje novina; Ormari; Pisaći stolovi; Škrinje, nemetalne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Dobozok fából vagy műanyagból; Kampók, fogasok ruhaakasztó rúdhoz, nem fémből; Ruhafogasok, nem fémből; Nem fém kosarak; Dobozok játékokhoz; Fiókosztók; Tároló ládák műanyagból; Tárolódobozok textilből; Fém fogaskampók ajtókhoz; Fiókok; Vezetősínek fiókokhoz [bútorok szerelvényei]; Fiókos tárolók [bútorok]; Tartályok, nem fémből, tárolási célokra; Kabátakasztók, fogasok; Vállfák, ruhaállványok [bútorzat] és ruhaakasztók; Fiókos szekrények; Nem fém összehajtható dobozok; Egymásra rakható műanyag tálcák; Cégtáblák, cégérek fából vagy műanyagból; Kulcstartó táblák; Zsúrkocsik [bútorok]; Csúszásgátlók mosogatóba; Folyóirattartók, folyóirattartó állványok; Újságtartó állványok; Gardróbszekrények; Álló asztalok; Ládák, dobozok, nem fémből.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cassette in legno o plastica; Ganci di attaccapanni non metallici; Ganci per abiti [non metallici]; Cesti, non in metallo; Casse per giocattoli; Divisori per cassetti; Casse per archiviazione in plastica; Scatole di conservazione in materie tessili; Ganci per attaccapanni in metallo per l'applicazione a porte; Armadietti con serratura; Guide di scorrimento per cassetti [ferramenta per mobili]; Scatole portaoggetti [articoli di arredamento]; Contenitori, non in metallo, per immagazzinamento; Ganci per attaccapanni; Appendiabiti, attaccapanni a stelo [mobili] e grucce per indumenti; Cassettiera; Scatole pieghevoli, non in metallo; Vaschette impilabili in plastica; Insegne in legno o in materie plastiche; Pannelli appendi-chiavi; Carrelli [mobili]; Rivestimenti amovibili per acquai; Porta-riviste; Espositori per giornali; Stipi; Scrivanie; Casse non metalliche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Medinės ar plastikinės dėžės; Ne metaliniai apsiaustų kabliai; Ne metaliniai drabužių kabliai; Ne metaliniai krepšiai; Žaislų dėžės; Stalčių skirtukai; Plastikinės sandėliavimo skrynios; Tekstilinės daiktų laikymo dėžės; Metaliniai drabužinių kabliukai, tvirtinami prie durų; Rakinamosios spintelės, dėžės, stalčiai; Stalčių bėgeliai [baldų furnitūra]; Sandėliavimo stalčiai [baldai]; Ne metaliniai sandėliavimo konteineriai; Drabužių kabliai; Drabužių kabyklos, drabužių stovai [baldai] ir drabužių kabliukai; Komodos; Sulankstomos nemetalinės dėžės; Plastikiniai padėklai [dedami vienas ant kito]; Medinės ar plastikinės iškabos; Raktų [kabinimo] lentos; Vežimėliai [baldai]; Išimamieji plautuvių įdėklai; Žurnalų padėklai; Laikraščių stendai; Spintos; Stovimieji stalai; Ne metalinės dėžės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Koka vai plastmasas kastes; Nemetāliski drēbju pakaramo āķi; Nemetāliski āķi drēbju pakaramajiem; Nemetāliski grozi; Rotaļlietu kastes; Atvilktņu sadalītāji; Uzglabāšanas kastes no plastmasas; Uzglabāšanas kastes no auduma; Drēbju pakaramo āķi no metāla piestiprināšanai pie durvīm; Aizslēdzami skapīši; Atvilktņu vadotnes [mēbeļu piederumi]; Uzglabāšanas atvilktnes [mēbeles]; Nemetāliski konteineri glabāšanai; Drēbju pakaramo āķi; Apģērbu pakaramie, statīvi (mēbeles) un āķi apģērbiem; Atvilktņu skapis; Salokāmas kastes, nav no metāla; Vertikāli kraujami paliktņi no plastmasas; Koka vai plastmasas izkārtnes; Paneļi atslēgu karināšanai; Ēdienu ratiņi [mēbeles]; Izņemami izlietņu paklājiņi; Žurnālu turētāji; Laikrakstu stendi; Skapji; Rakstāmgaldi; Nemetāliskas lādes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kaxxi tal-injam jew tal-plastik; Ganċijiet għall-ħbula tal-inxir tal-ħwejjeġ, mhux tal-metall; Ganċijiet għall-ħwejjeġ, mhux tal-metall; Basktijiet, mhux tal-metall; Gradenzi għall-ġugarelli; Diviżorji għall-kxaxen; Sniedaq tal-ħażna, magħmula mill-plastik; Kaxxi tal-ħżin magħmula mit-tessut; Ganċijiet għall-kowtijiet magħmula mill-metall għall-iffissar mal-bibien; Kaxxarizzi; Tagħmir biex jiżżerżqu l-kxaxen fuqhom [tagħmir għall-għamara]; Kxaxen għall-ħażna [għamara]; Kontenituri mhux tal-metall għall-ħażna; Ganċijiet għall-kowtijiet; Spallieri tal-ħwejjeġ, stends tal-ħwejjeġ [għamara] u ganċijiet tal-ħwejjeġ; Armarji bil-kxaxen; Kaxxi jintwew, mhux tal-metall; Gabarrejiet tal-plastik, għall-istivar; Tabelli tal-injam jew tal-plastik; Plakek ta' mal-ħajt li fuqhom jiddendlu ċ-ċwievet; Tròlis [għamara]; Metts, li jitneħħew, għas-sinkijiet; Xtilliera għar-rivisti; Stends għall-wiri tal-gazzetti; Armarji; Skrivaniji; Kaxxi, armarji mhux tal-metall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Dozen van hout of plastic; Kapstokhaken, niet van metaal; Kleerhaken, niet van metaal; Manden, niet van metaal; Speelgoedkisten; Indelers voor laden; Opbergkisten van plastic; Opbergboxen van textiel; Kapstokhaken van metaal voor bevestiging aan deuren; Schuifladen; Glij-inrichtingen voor laden [beslag voor meubelen]; Opbergladekasten [meubelen]; Opslagcontainers, niet van metaal; Kapstokhaken; Klerenhangers, kledingrekken [meubilair] en kledinghaken; Ladenkast; Vouwbare boxen, niet van metaal; Stapelbakken van plastic; Uithangborden van hout of plastic; Sleutelborden; Wagentjes [meubilair]; Gootsteenmatjes; Tijdschriftenstandaards; Krantenstandaards; Kasten; Bureaus [meubelen]; Kisten, niet van metaal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pudełka drewniane lub z tworzyw sztucznych; Haczyki, niemetalowe, do wieszaków stojących na ubrania; Haczyki na ubrania, niemetalowe; Kosze niemetalowe; Skrzynki na zabawki; Rozdzielacze do szuflad; Skrzynie wykonane z tworzyw sztucznych do przechowywania; Tekstylne pudełka do przechowywania przedmiotów; Haki do wieszania ubrań z metalu do mocowania na drzwiach; Szafki zamykane; Prowadnice do szuflad [okucia meblowe]; Szuflady do przechowywania [meble]; Niemetalowe pojemniki do przechowywania; Haki do wieszania płaszczy; Wieszaki na ubrania, wieszaki stojące do ubrań [meble] i haczyki na ubrania; Szafki z szufladami; Składane pudła, nie z metalu; Tace z tworzyw sztucznych przystosowane do układania w stosy; Szyldy z drewna lub tworzyw sztucznych; Tablice do zawieszania kluczy; Wózki [meble]; Maty wyjmowane do zlewów; Stojaki na czasopisma; Stojaki do wystawiania gazet; Szafy wnękowe; Biurka; Skrzynie [paki] niemetalowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Caixas em madeira ou em plástico; Ganchos, não metálicos, para cabides de rodas; Ganchos, não metálicos, para vestuário; Cestos, não metálicos; Arcas ou baús para brinquedos; Separadores para gavetas; Arcas de armazenamento em matérias plásticas; Caixas de guardar objetos em matérias têxteis; Ganchos de bengaleiros em metal para aplicar em portas; Cacifos; Corrediças de gavetas [material de mobiliário]; Gavetas para arrumação [mobiliário]; Contentores não metálicos para armazenamento; Cabides de parede; Bengaleiros e cabides para roupa [móveis] e ganchos para a roupa; Armário com gavetas; Caixas dobráveis, não metálicas; Tabuleiros empilháveis em matérias plásticas; Letreiros em madeira ou em matérias plásticas; Quadros para pendurar chaves; Carrinhos [mobiliário]; Revestimentos amovíveis para lavatórios; Porta-revistas; Expositores de jornais; Closets; Secretárias [mobiliário]; Arcas, não metálicas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cutii din lemn sau din materiale plastice; Cârlige nemetalice pentru bare de haine; Îmbrăcăminte (cuiere nemetalice pentru -)[cârlige]; Coşuri, nemetalice; Jucării (Cutii pentru -); Separatoare pentru sertare; Lăzi de stocare confecţionate din plastic; Cutii de depozitare din materiale textile; Cuiere metalice pentru montare pe uși; Dulăpioare; Ghidaje (dispozitive de culisare) pentru sertare [articole metalice pentru mobilier]; Corpuri cu sertare pentru depozitare [mobilier]; Recipiente, nu din metal, pentru depozitare; Agăţători pentru haine; Umeraşe şi cuiere pentru haine, suporturi pentru haine [mobilier] şi cârlige pentru îmbrăcăminte; Dulapuri cu sertare; Cutii pliabile nemetalice; Tăvi de stivuire din plastic; Indicatoare din lemn sau plastic; Tablouri de agăţat chei; Cărucioare [mobilier]; Covoraşe de protecţie, detaşabile, pentru chiuvete; Suporturi pentru reviste; Suporturi pentru ziare; Dulapuri pentru haine; Birouri; Coveţi nemetalice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Drevené alebo plastové krabice; Nekovové háčiky na vešiaky; Nekovové háčiky na odevy; Nekovové koše; Truhlica na hračky; Oddeľovače priestoru pre zásuvky; Plastové skladovacie truhlice; Škatule na skladovanie z textílií; Kovové vešiakové háčiky na umiestnenie na dvere; Záklopky; Posuvné koľajničky pre zásuvky [nábytková výbava]; Úložné zásuvky (nábytok); Nekovové skladovacie nádoby; Háčiky na vešanie; Vešiaky, remienka na odevy, stojany na šaty [nábytok], háčiky na odevy; Zásuvky; Nekovové skladacie boxy; Plastové odkladacie stohovateľné priehradky; Vývesné štíty z dreva alebo plastov; Panely na vešanie kľúčov; Vozíky (nábytok); Snímateľné kryty na drezy; Stojany na časopisy; Novinové stojany; Príborníky; Písacie stoly; Nekovové debny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Škatle iz lesa ali plastike; Kljuke za obešanje garderobe, nekovinske; Kljuke za oblačila, nekovinske; Nekovinske košare; Skrinje za igrače; Delilne pregrade za predale; Skrinje za shranjevanje iz plastike; Škatle za shranjevanje iz tekstila; Garderobni kavlji iz kovine za pritrditev na vrata; Omarice s ključavnico; Drsniki za predale [oprema za pohištvo]; Pohištvo s predali za shranjevanje; Nekovinske posode za shranjevanje; Kljuke za obešanje oblačil; Obešalniki za oblačila, stojala za oblačila [pohištvo] in kavlji za obešanje oblačil; Predalnik za čevlje; Zložljive škatle, nekovinske; Pladnji za zlaganje, iz plastike; Označevalne table iz lesa ali plastike; Table za obešanje ključev; Servirne mizice [pohištvo]; Odstranljive podloge za pomivalna korita; Stojala za revije; Stojala za časopise; Vzidne omare; Pisalne mize; Skrinje, nekovinske.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Lådor av trä eller plast; Krokar för ytterkläder, inte av metall; Klädhängare, inte av metall; Korgar, inte av metall; Leksakslådor; Avdelare för byrålådor; Kistor av plast för lagringsändamål; Förvaringsboxar av textilier; Garderobskrokar av metall för applicering på dörrar; Förvaringsskåp; Glidskenor för byrålådor [metallvaror för möbler]; Förvaringslådor [möbler]; Behållare och containrar, inte av metall, för förvaring; Klädkrokar; Klädhängare, klädställ [möbler] och klädkrokar; Skåp med lådor; Vikbara boxar, ej av metall; Stapelbara plastbrickor; Skyltar av trä eller plast; Nyckeltavlor; Serveringsvagnar [möbler]; Lösa mattor för diskhoar; Tidningshyllor; Skyltställ för tidningar; Skåp; Skolbänkar; Kistor, inte av metall.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Кофи за боклук; Съдове за домакински или кухненски цели [с изключение на такива от благороден метал]; Съдове за домакински или кухненски цели [с изключение на такива от благороден метал]; Кутии от стъкло; Кошове за домакински цели; Кухненски съдове, не от благороден метал; Подложки за маса, не от хартия или текстил; Кошчета за изхвърляне на хартия; Детски касички, не от метал; Детски касички, не от метал; Тоалетни чанти; Поставки за тоалетна хартия; Поставки за тоалетна хартия; Четки за миене на съдове; Държачи за четки за миене на съдове; Чистачки [уреди за почистване]; Панерчета за хляб; Кошници за хляб за домакински цели; Поставки за гъби; Кутии за сапун; Кутии за сапун; Дозатори за сапун; Поставки за пакетчета чай; Сушилни стойки за пране; Кофи за изхвърляне на пелени; Метли; Дъски за гладене; Кутии за масло; Чашки за варени яйца, не от благороден метал; Ведра; Гарафи; Комплекти тенджери за готвене; Готварски принадлежности, неелектрически; Кухненски прибори; Подложки за хранене, не от хартия или текстил; Подложки за предпазване на повърхността на масата, не от хартия или текстил; Чаши от хартия или пластмаса; Порцеланови изделия; Кофи с приспособление за изстискване на парцали за под; Купи; Дъски за рязане, кухненски; Обувалки; Обувалки за обувки; Калъп за обувки [за опъване]; Съдове; Салфетници за маса; Парцали за миене; Бърсалки от плат; Подноси за домакински цели; Подноси от хартия, за домакински цели; Сервизи и прибори за маса [с изключение на ножове, вилици и лъжици], не от благороден метал; Плоски шишенца (за джоб); Чаши; Кутийки за съхранение на чай; Метални топки с дупки за запарване на чай; Чайници; Калъфи за чайници; Сервизи за чай, не от благороден метал; Цедки за чай, не от благороден метал; Чинии; Дъски за пране; Корита за пране; Приспособление за изстискване на парцалите за миене; Изстисквачки за паста за зъби; Захарници.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nádoby na odpad; Dózy, boxy a nádoby pro použití v domácnosti a kuchyni; Dózy, boxy a nádoby pro použití v domácnosti a kuchyni; Krabičky ze skla; Koše pro použití v domácnosti; Kuchyňské dózy a krabičky; Podtácky, ne papírové nebo textilní; Odpadní koše na papír; Prasátka (pokladničky); Prasátka (pokladničky); Toaletní taštičky; Držáky toaletního papíru; Dávkovače na toaletní papír; Kartáčky na mytí nádobí; Držáky na kartáče na nádobí; Stahovače [čisticí nástroje]; Nádoby na chleba; Košíky na chleba pro použití v domácnosti; Držáky na houby; Krabičky na mýdlo; Držáky na mýdlo; Dávkovače mýdla; Tácky na odkládání čajových sáčků; Sušáky na prádlo; Kbelíky na likvidaci plen; Košťata; Žehlicí prkna; Máselničky; Pohárky na vejce; Kbelíky; Dekantéry; Sady hrnců; Nářadí pro vaření, ne elektrické; Kuchyňské náčiní; Prostírání, ne papírové nebo textilní; Podložky pod (horké) nádobí, ne papírové nebo textilní; Papírové nebo plastové kelímky; Výrobky z porcelánu; Kbelíky s nástavci na ždímání mopů; Misky; Prkénka kuchyňská na krájení; Lžíce na boty; Lžíce na boty; Napínáky na obuv; Nádobí; Stojánky na ubrousky (stolování); Utěrky na nádobí; Utěrky [hadry] na utírání prachu; Podnosy pro použití v domácnosti; Papírové podnosy pro použití v domácnosti; Stolní nádobí, nikoliv nože, vidličky a lžíce; Kapesní lahve; Šálky; Krabičky na čaj; Sítka na louhování čaje; Čajové konvice; Textilní obaly na čajové nádoby sloužící k udržení teploty nápoje; Čajové servisy [stolní nádobí]; Sítka na slévání čaje; Stolní talíře; Valchy; Vaničky na praní; Ždímače mopů; Pomůcky na vytlačování obsahu tub; Cukřenky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Skraldebøtter; Beholdere til husholdnings- eller køkkenbrug; Beholdere til husholdnings- eller køkkenbrug; Glasæsker; Kurve til husholdningsbrug; Køkkenbeholdere; Bordskånere, ikke af papir eller tekstil; Papirkurve; Sparebøsser; Sparebøsser; Rejsenecessaire; Toiletrulleholdere; Toiletpapir dispensere; Opvaskebørster; Holdere til opvaskebørster; Aftrækkere (rengøringsredskaber); Brødkasser; Brødkurve til husholdningsbrug; Svampeholdere; Sæbeæsker; Sæbeholdere; Sæbedispensere; Teposeholdere; Tørrestativer til vasketøj; Blespande; Koste; Strygebrætter; Smørskåle; Æggebægre; Spande; Karafler; Grydesæt; Madlavningsredskaber, ikke-elektriske; Køkkenredskaber; Dækkeservietter, ikke af papir eller tekstiler; Bordskånere, ikke af papir eller tekstiler; Krus af pap eller plastic; Porcelænsvarer; Mop wringer buckets; Spølkum; Skærebrætter til køkkenbrug; Skohorn; Skohorn; Skolæste; Fade; Servietholdere; Viskestykker; Støveklude; Bakker til husholdningsbrug; Bakker af papir til husholdningsformål; Bordservice, undtagen knive, gafler og skeer; Lommelærker; Kopper; Tedåser; Teæg; Tepotter; Tehætter; Teservicer [bordservice]; Tesier; Tallerkner; Vaskebrætter; Vaskebaljer; Moppevridere; Klemmer til tandpastatuber; Sukkerskåle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Abfalleimer; Behälter für Haushalt oder Küche; Gefäße für Haushalt oder Küche; Glasbehälter; Körbe für den Haushalt; Küchengefäße; nicht aus Papier oder Stoff bestehende Untersetzer; Papierkörbe; Sparbüchsen; Sparschweine; Toilettenecessaires; Toilettenpapierhalter; Toilettenpapierspender; Spülbürsten; Halterungen für Spülbürsten; Abzieher [Reinigungsgeräte]; Brotkästen; Brotkörbe für den Haushalt; Schwammhalter; Seifendosen; Seifenhalter, -schalen; Seifenspender; Teebeutelablagen; Wäscheständer; Windelentsorgungseimer; Besen; Bügelbretter; Butterdosen; Eierbecher; Eimer aller Art; Karaffen; Kochgeschirr; Kochutensilien; Küchengeschirr; nicht aus Papier oder Stoff bestehende Platzdeckchen [Sets]; nicht aus Papier oder Stoff bestehende Tischdeckchen; Papier- oder Plastikbecher; Porzellan; Putzeimer mit Auswringer; Schalen; Schneidbretter für die Küche; Schuhanzieher; Schuhlöffel; Schuhspanner; Schüsseln; Serviettenhalter; Spüllappen; Staubtücher; Tabletts für den Haushalt; Tabletts für den Haushalt aus Papier; Tafelgeschirr; Taschenflaschen; Tassen; Teedosen; Tee-Eier; Teekannen; Teemützen, -wärmer; Teeservice [Tafelgeschirr]; Teesiebe; Teller; Waschbretter; Waschwannen; Wischmopppressen; Zahnpastatubenquetscher; Zuckerdosen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δοχεία απορριμμάτων· Δοχεία οικιακά ή μαγειρικά· Δοχεία οικιακά ή μαγειρικά· Κουτιά γυάλινα· Καλάθια για οικιακή χρήση· Δοχεία μαγειρικής χρήσης· Βάσεις για ποτήρια (σουβέρ), όχι από χαρτί ή ύφασμα· Κάλαθοι απορριμμάτων χαρτιού· Κουμπαράδες· Κουμπαράδες· Σετ τουαλέτας σε τσαντάκι· Θήκες χαρτιού τουαλέτας· Θήκες χαρτιού τουαλέτας· Βουρτσάκια για το πλύσιμο των πιάτων· Βάσεις για βούρτσες πλυσίματος πιάτων· Μάκτρα καθαρισμού [συσκευές καθαρισμού]· Ψωμιέρες· Καλάθια για το ψωμί, για οικιακή χρήση· Σπόγγοι (σπογγοθήκες)· Κουτιά συσκευασίας σαπουνιών· Σαπουνοθήκες [διακοσμητικά μπάνιου]· Σαπουνιού διανεμητές· Υποδοχές για φακελάκια τσαγιού· Φορητές απλώστρες για το στέγνωμα πλυμένων λευκών ειδών και ρούχων· Κάδοι απόρριψης βρεφικών πανών· Σκούπες· Σιδερώστρες· Βουτυριέρες· Αυγοθήκες· Κάδοι· Καράφες· Σκεύη μαγειρικής χρήσης· Μαγειρικά σκεύη μη ηλεκτρικά· Σκεύη μαγειρικής χρήσης· Επιτραπέζιες προστατευτικές βάσεις σερβίτσιων, όχι από χαρτί ή ύφασμα· Επιτραπέζιες προστατευτικές βάσεις σερβίτσιων, όχι από χαρτί ή ύφασμα· Κύπελλα από χαρτί ή πλαστικό· Πορσελάνης είδη· Κουβάδες στιψίματος σφουγγαρίστρας· Γαβάθες· Κοπής (Σανίδες -) για την κουζίνα· Κόκαλα για παπούτσια· Κόκαλα για υποδήματα· Καλαπόδια για υποδήματα· Πιατικά· Υποδοχές για πετσέτες φαγητού· Πανιά για το σκούπισμα πιάτων· Ξεσκόνισμα (μάκτρα) [πανιά] --ος· Δίσκοι για οικιακή χρήση· Χάρτινοι δίσκοι, για οικιακή χρήση· Επιτραπέζια σκεύη, εκτός από μαχαίρια, πιρούνια και κουτάλια· Παγούρια· Κύπελλα (όχι από πολύτιμα μέταλλα)· Κουτιά τσαγιού· Συσκευές παρασκευής τσαγιού· Τσαγιέρες· Καλύμματα τσαγιέρας· Σερβίτσια τσαγιού [επιτραπέζια σκεύη]· Σουρωτήρια τσαγιού· Πιατέλες· Μπουγάδα (Σανίδες -)· Λεκάνες πλυσίματος ρούχων· Διατάξεις στυψίματος σφουγγαρίστρας· Πιεστήρια για σωληνάρια οδοντόπαστας· Ζαχαριέρες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Dustbins; Containers for household or kitchen use; Containers for household or kitchen use; Boxes of glass; Baskets for household purposes; Kitchen containers; Coasters, not of paper or textile; Waste paper baskets; Piggy banks; Piggy banks; Toilet cases; Toilet roll holders; Toilet roll dispensers; Dishwashing brushes; Holders for dishwashing brushes; Squeegees (cleaning apparatus); Bread bins; Bread baskets for household purposes; Sponge holders; Soap boxes; Soap dishes; Soap dispensers; Tea bag rests; Laundry drying racks; Diaper disposal pails; Brooms; Ironing boards; Butter dishes; Egg cups; Buckets; Decanters; Cooking pot sets; Cooking utensils, non-electric; Kitchen utensils; Place mats, not of paper or textile; Tablemats, not of paper or textile; Cups of paper or plastic; Porcelain ware; Mop wringer buckets; Basins [bowls]; Cutting boards for the kitchen; Shoe horns; Shoe horns; Shoe trees; Dishes; Table napkin holders; Dishcloths; Dusting cloths; Trays for household purposes; Trays of paper, for household purposes; Tableware, other than knives, forks and spoons; Hip flasks; Cups; Tea caddies; Tea infusers; Teapots; Tea cosies; Tea services [tableware]; Tea strainers; Plates; Washing boards; Washtubs; Mop wringers; Toothpaste squeezers; Sugar bowls.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cubos de basura; Recipientes para uso doméstico o culinario; Recipientes para uso doméstico o culinario; Cajas de vidrio; Cestas para uso doméstico; Recipientes de cocina; Posabotellas y posavasos que no sean de papel ni de materias textiles; Papeleras; Huchas de cerdito; Huchas de cerdito; Neceseres de tocador; Portarrollos de papel higiénico; Distribuidores de papel higiénico; Cepillos para lavar la vajilla; Soportes para cepillos de fregar la vajilla; Extractores [equipos de limpieza]; Cajas para el pan; Cestas para el pan de uso doméstico; Portaesponjas [esponjeras]; Jaboneras [estuches]; Portajabones [jaboneras]; Dispensadores de jabón; Reposabolsas de té; Tendederos de ropa; Cubos para la eliminación de pañales; Escobas; Tablas de planchar; Mantequeras [vajilla]; Hueveras; Cubos; Decantadores; Baterías de cocina; Utensilios de cocción no eléctricos; Utensilios de cocina; Manteles individuales que no sean de papel ni de materias textiles; Salvamanteles que no sean de papel ni de materias textiles; Vasos de papel o materias plásticas; Artículos de porcelana; Cubos escurridores de fregonas; Tazones (cuencos); Tablas de cortar para la cocina; Calzadores; Calzadores para zapatos; Hormas para calzado; Fuentes [vajilla]; Servilleteros de mesa; Balletas de cocina; Trapos para quitar el polvo; Bandejas para uso doméstico; Bandejas de papel para uso doméstico; Vajilla; Petacas [botellas de bolsillo]; Tazas; Cajas para té; Difusores de té; Teteras; Cubiertas para teteras; Servicios de té [vajilla]; Coladores de té; Platos; Tablas de lavar; Tinas para lavar la ropa; Escurridores de mopas; Utensilio para apretar tubos de dentífricos; Azucareros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Prügikastid; Köögi- või majapidamismahutid; Köögi- või majapidamismahutid; Klaaskarbid; Majapidamiskorvid; Köögimahutid; Jooginõualused, v.a paberist või tekstiilist; Paberikorvid; Hoiupõrsad; Hoiupõrsad; Tualett-tarvete kotid; Tualettpaberihoidlid; Tualettpaberijaoturid; Nõudepesuharjad; Nõudepesuharjade hoidikud; Kaabitsad [puhastusvahendid]; Leivakastid; Leivakorvid [majatarbed]; Pesukäsnaalused; Seebikarbid; Seebialused; Seebijaoturid; Teekottide alused; Kuivatusrestid (Pesu -), pesukuivatusrestid; Prügiämbrid mähkmetele; Luuad; Triikimislauad; Võitoosid; Munapeekrid, munatopsid; Panged, ämbrid; Karahvinid; Poti- ja pannikomplektid; Keedunõud, v.a elektrilised; Köögitarbed; Sööginõude alusmatid, v.a paberist või tekstiilist; Lauamatid, v.a paberist või tekstiilist; Paber- või plasttopsid; Portselantooted; Mopi kuivaks väänamise süsteemiga ämbrid; Kausid, vaagnad; Lõikelauad [köögitarbed]; Kingalusikad; Kingalusikad; Kingaliistud [venitid]; Nõud; Salvrätihoidlid lauale; Loputuslapid; Tolmulapid; Majapidamiskandikud; Paberist majapidamiskandikud; Lauanõud, v.a noad, kahvlid ja lusikad; Lapikud pudelid [plaskud]; Tassid; Teetoosid; Teetõmbekuulid; Teekannud; Teekannusoojendajad; Teeserviisid [lauanõud]; Teesõelad; Taldrikud; Pesulauad; Pesupalid; Mopiväänajad ämbritele; Hambapastatuubi pigistusvahendid; Suhkrutoosid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Roska-astiat; Säiliöt koti- tai keittiökäyttöön; Säiliöt koti- tai keittiökäyttöön; Lasikotelot; Korit kotitalouskäyttöön; Keittiön säilytysastiat; Lasinaluset, muut kuin paperiset tai kankaiset; Paperikorit; Säästöpossut; Säästöpossut; Toalettilaukut; Pidikkeet WC-paperirullille; Pidikkeet WC-paperirullille; Astianpesuharjat; Astiaharjatelineet; Ulosvetimet (puhdistuslaitteet); Leipälaatikot; Leipäkorit kotitalouskäyttöön; Pesusienten pitimet; Saippuatelineet; Saippuarasiat; Saippuanjakelulaitteet; Teepussien aluset; Pyykkitelineet; Vaipparoskikset; Luudat; Silityslaudat; Voiastiat; Munakupit; Sangot; Viinikarahvit; Keittokattilasarjat; Keittovälineet, ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Keittokattilasarjat; Ruokailualustat, ei paperia eikä tekstiiliä; Tabletit, ei paperia eikä tekstiiliä; Mukit (Paperi- tai muovi -); Posliinitavarat; Moppisangot; Vadit [astiat]; Leikkuulaudat keittiökäyttöön; Kenkälusikat; Kenkälusikat; Kenkälestit [pingottimet]; Ruoka-astiat; Lautasliinarenkaat; Pesulaput; Pölyrievut; Tarjottimet kotitalouskäyttöön; Paperitarjottimet, kotitalouskäyttöön; Pöytätarvikkeet, muut kuin veitset, haarukat ja lusikat; Taskumatit; Kupit; Teetölkit; Teehauduttimet; Teepannut; Teemyssyt; Teeserviisit [astiastot]; Teesiivilät; Lautaset; Pesulaudat; Pesupaljut; Moppipuristimet; Hammastahnaputkilon puristimet; Sokeriastiat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Poubelles; Récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine; Récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine; Boîtes en verre; Corbeilles à usage ménager; Récipients de cuisine; Dessous de carafes, ni en papier ni en matières textiles; Corbeilles à papier; Cochons tirelires; Cochons tirelires; Nécessaires de toilette; Supports pour papier hygiénique; Distributeurs de papier hygiénique; Brosses pour laver la vaisselle; Fixations pour brosses à vaisselle; Extracteurs [équipements de nettoyage]; Boîtes à pain; Corbeilles à pain à usage ménager; Porte-éponges; Boîtes à savon; Porte-savon; Distributeurs de savon; Repose-sachets de thé; Étendoirs à linge; Poubelles pour langes; Balais; Planches à repasser; Beurriers; Coquetiers; Seaux; Carafes; Batteries de cuisine; Ustensiles de cuisine non électriques; Ustensiles de cuisine; Sets de table, ni en papier ni en matières textiles; Ronds de table, ni en papier ni en matières textiles; Gobelets en papier ou en matières plastiques; Porcelaines; Seaux pour l'essorage de balais à franges; Bols; Planches à découper pour la cuisine; Chausse-pieds; Chausse-pieds; Formes [embauchoirs] pour souliers; Plats; Porte-serviettes de table; Lavettes; Torchons [chiffons] pour épousseter; Plateaux à usage domestique; Plateaux en papier à usage domestique; Vaisselle; Flasques [gourde de poche]; Tasses; Boîtes à thé; Boules à thé; Théières; Cosys pour théières; Services à thé; Passe-thé; Assiettes; Planches à laver; Cuves de lavage; Essoreuses de balais à franges; Presse-tubes de dentifrice; Sucriers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kante za smeće; Posude za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju; Posude za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju; Kutije, staklene; Košarice za kućanstvo; Kuhinjske posude; Podmetači za čaše, nepapirnati i netekstilni; Koševi za otpadni papir; Štedne kasice prasice; Štedne kasice prasice; Toaletni neseseri; Držači za toaletni papir u roli; Dispenseri higijenskog papira u roli; Četke za pranje posuđa; Držači za četke za pranje; Čistači stakla [uređaji za čišćenje]; Kutije za kruh; Košare za kruh [za kućanstvo]; Dršci spužvi; Kutije za sapun; Kutije za sapun; Držači sapuna [naprave za izdavanje sapuna]; Držači za vrećice čaja; Stalci za sušenje odjeće; Kante za zbrinjavanje pelena; Metle; Daske za glačanje; Posude za maslac; Čašice za jaja; Vedra [drvene posude]; Dekanteri; Kuhinjsko posuđe; Pribor za kuhanje, neelektrični; Kuhinjski pribor; Podmetači za stolove, osim od tekstila i papira; Podmetači za stolove, osim od papira i tekstila; Čaše, papirnate ili plastične; Porculansko posuđe; Kante s ocjeđivačem za resaste metle; Plitice [zdjelice]; Daske za rezanje [kuhinjski pribor]; Žlice za obuvanje; Žlice za cipele; Kalupi za rastezanje cipela; Posude; Držači ubrusa; Krpe za posuđe; Krpe za prašinu; Polsužavnici za kućanstvo; Poslužavnici od papira za kućanstvo; Stolni predmeti, osim noževa, vilica i žlica; Pljoske za piće; Šalice; Kutije za čaj; Jaja za kuhanje čaja; Čajnici; Navlake za čajnike; Čaj [servisi za čaj]; Filtri za čaj; Tanjuri; Daske za pranje rublja; Lužnice [posude za pranje rublja]; Ocjeđivači krpa za mop; Pomagala za istiskivanje zubne paste; Posude za šećer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szemeteskukák; Tárolók, tároló edények háztartási vagy konyhai célokra; Tárolók, tároló edények háztartási vagy konyhai célokra; Dobozok üvegből; Kosarak háztartási használatra; Konyhai dobozok, tárolók; Poháralátétek, nem papírból vagy textilből; Papírkosarak; Malacperselyek; Malacperselyek; Piperetáskák, neszesszerek; Toalettpapír-tartók; Toalettpapír-tartók; Edénymosó kefék; Edénymosó kefékhez való tartók; Lehúzók [tisztítóeszközök]; Kenyértartók; Kenyérkosarak, háztartási célokra; Szivacstartók; Szappantartók; Szappantartók; Szappanadagolók; Teafilter-tartók; Ruhaszárító állványok; Pelenka eltakarítására való szemetesládák; Seprűk; Vasalódeszkák; Vajtartók; Tojástartók; Vödrök; Dekantálók; Konyhai eszközök, kis méretű; Főzőeszközök, nem elektromos; Konyhai eszközök, kis méretű; Tányéralátétek, nem papírból vagy textilből; Asztali alátétek, nem papírból vagy textilből; Poharak papírból vagy műanyagból; Porcelánok; Felmosófej-kifacsarós vödrök; Mosdótálak, lavórok; Konyhai vágódeszkák; Cipőkanalak; Cipőkanalak; Sámfák [tágítók]; Edényáruk; Asztali szalvétatartók; Edénytörlő ruhák; Porrongyok; Tálcák háztartási használatra; Tálcák papírból, háztartási használatra; Étkészlet, a kések, villák és kanalak kivételével; Ivópalackok sportoláshoz; Csészék; Teásdobozok; Teafőző tojások; Teáskannák; Tea cozy [teáskanna melegítő]; Teáskészletek [terítékek]; Teaszűrők; Tányérok; Mosódeszkák; Dézsák; Felmosó vödör kicsavaróval; Fogkrémtubus-kinyomók; Cukortartók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pattumiere; Recipienti per la casa o per la cucina; Recipienti per la casa o per la cucina; Scatole di vetro; Cestini per uso domestico; Recipienti per la cucina; Sottocaraffe, non di carta o di tessuto; Cestini per rifiuti; Salvadanai; Salvadanai; Nécessaire per la toilette; Portarotoli per carta igienica; Distributori di carta igienica; Spazzole per lavare le stoviglie; Supporti per spazzole per stoviglie; Estrattori [apparecchi per la pulizia]; Recipienti per il pane; Cestini per il pane per uso domestico; Porta-spugne; Scatole per sapone; Porta-sapone; Distributori di sapone; Poggia sacchetti da tè; Stenditoi per biancheria; Pattumiere per pannolini; Scope; Assi da stiro; Burriere; Portauova; Secchi; Decanter; Batterie da cucina; Utensili da cottura non elettrici; Utensili da cucina; Tovagliette, non di carta o di tessuto; Centrini per tavoli, non di carta o di tessuto; Bicchieri in carta o in materie plastiche; Porcellane; Secchi per strizzare scope frangiate; Bacinelle; Assi per tagliare per la cucina; Calzascarpe; Calzascarpe; Allargastivali; Piatti da portata; Porta-tovaglioli da tavolo; Strofinacci per lavare i piatti; Strofinacci per spolverare; Guantiere per uso domestico; Vassoi di carta, per uso domestico; Vasellame; Fiaschette da tasca; Tazze; Scatole per il tè; Bocce per il tè; Teiere; Copriteiere; Servizi da tè; Filtri per il tè; Piatti; Assi per lavare; Tinozze per il bucato; Strizzatori per scope a frange; Spremitori di tubetti di dentifricio; Zuccheriere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Atliekų dėžės; Buitinės ar virtuvinės talpyklos; Buitinės ar virtuvinės talpyklos; Stiklinės dėžutės; Buitiniai krepšeliai; Virtuviniai konteineriai; Ropinių [grafinų] padėkliukai (ne popieriniai ar ne tekstiliniai); Šiukšliadėžės popieriui; Taupyklės; Taupyklės; Tualeto reikmeninės; Tualetinio popieriaus dalytuvai; Tualetinio popieriaus dalytuvai; Indų plovimo šepečiai; Plovimo šepečių laikikliai; Valytuvai su gumos sluoksniu [valymo reikmenys]; Duoninės; Duonos krepšeliai (buities reikmėms); Kempinių laikikliai; Muilinės; Muilinės; Muilo dalytuvai; Arbatos maišelių padėkliukai; Drabužių džiovyklos; Sauskelnių utilizavimo kibirai; Šluotos; Lyginimo lentos; Sviestinės; Kiaušinių puodeliai; Kibirai; Ropinės [grafinai]; Virtuvės reikmenys; Ne elektriniai valgių gaminimo reikmenys; Virtuviniai indai; Ne popieriniai ir ne tekstiliniai patiesalai; Ne popieriniai ir ne tekstiliniai stalo aptiesalai; Popieriaus ar plastiko puodeliai; Porceliano dirbiniai; Kibirai su nugręžimo mechanizmu ir šepečiu; Katiliukai; Virtuvinės pjaustymo lentelės; Batų liežuvėliai; Batų šaukšteliai; Avalynės laikymo kurpaliai; Indai; Stalo servetėlių laikikliai; Plovimo šluostės; Dulkių šluostės; Padėklai (buities reikmėms); Popieriniai padėklai (buities reikmėms); Valgomieji reikmenys [išskyrus peilius, šakutes ir šaukštus]; Plokščios gertuvės (alkoholiniams gėrimams); Puodukai; Arbatos dėžutės; Arbatos plikytuvai; Arbatinukai; Arbatinukų apdangalai; Arbatos servizai [valgomieji reikmenys]; Arbatos koštuvėliai; Lėkštės; Skalbimo lentos [rintės]; Skalbimo dubenys; Grindų šluosčių gręžtuvai; Dantų pastos tūbelių išspaudimo įtaisai; Cukrinės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Atkritumu tvertnes; Tilpnes mājturības vai virtuves nolūkiem; Tilpnes mājturības vai virtuves nolūkiem; Stikla kārbas; Grozi mājsaimniecības vajadzībām; Virtuves kārbas; Glāžu paliktņi, kas nav no papīra vai auduma; Papīrgrozi; Krājkasītes cūciņas formā; Krājkasītes cūciņas formā; Tualetes maciņi; Tualetes papīra ruļļu turētāji; Tualetes papīra ruļļu turētāji; Trauku birstes; Trauku mazgājamo birstu turētāji; Lobītāji [tīrīšanas ierīces]; Maizes kastes; Maizes groziņi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Sūkļu turētāji; Ziepju trauki (ar vāku); Ziepju trauki (ar vāku); Ziepju dozatori; Tējas maisiņu paliktņi; Veļas žāvēšanas statīvi; Atkritumu spaiņi izlietotajiem autiņiem; Slotas; Gludināmie dēļi; Sviesta trauki; Olu trauciņi; Spaiņi; Karafes; Virtuves trauki; Ēdienu gatavošanas piederumi (neelektriskie); Virtuves trauki; Individuālie galda paliktņi, kas nav no papīra vai auduma; Galda paliktņi, kas nav no papīra vai auduma; Papīra un plastmasas tases; Porcelāna trauki; Virvju slotu spaiņi; Bļodas [tvertnes]; Virtuves dēlīši, paredzēti griešanai; Kurpju lāpstiņas; Apavu lāpstiņas; Kurpju nostiepēji; Šķīvji; Salvešu gredzeni; Skalošanas lupatas; Auduma putekļu lupatas; Paplātes mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Papīra paplātes mājsaimniecības vajadzībām; Galda piederumi, izņemot nažus, dakšiņas un karotes; Dzērienu pudeles sportam; Tases; Tējas kārbiņas; Tējas sietiņi; Tējkannas; Tējkannu sildītāji; Tējas servīzes [galda piederumi]; Tējas sietiņi; Šķīvji; Veļas dēļi; Veļas toveri; Mazgāšanas slotu nospiedēji; Zobu pastas tūbiņu saspiedēji; Cukura trauki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Landi taż-żibel; Kontenituri għal użu domestiku jew għal użu fil-kċina; Kontenituri għal użu domestiku jew għal użu fil-kċina; Kaxxi tal-ħġieġ; Basktijiet għal użu domestiku; Reċipjenti tal-kċina; Gabarrejiet żgħar għal użu taħt it-tazzi, mhux tal-karta u jew tat-tessut; Laned għall-karti għar-rimi; Karus forma ta' qażquż; Karus forma ta' qażquż; Kaxxi fejn jitpoġġew l-oġġetti tat-twaletta; Distributuri tat-toilet paper; Distributuri tat-toilet paper; Xkupilji għall-ħasil tal-platti; Ħowlders għal xkupilji għall-ħasil tal-platti; Estratturi [tagħmir tat-tindif]; Laned tal-ħobż; Basktijiet tal-ħobż għal skopijiet domestiċi; Kontenituri tal-isponoż; Kontenituri tas-sapun; Kontenituri tas-sapun; Dispenser tas-sapun; Strumenti għall-appoġġ ta' boroż tat-te; Xtillieri għall-ħwejjeġ, għat-tnixxif; Bramel għar-rimi ta' ħrieqi; Xkupi; Twavel tal-mogħdija; Butirieri; Uvieri; Bramel; Karaffi; Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir; Għodod tat-tisjir, mhux tal-elettriku; Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir; Matts ta' taħt il-platti, mhux tal-karta jew tat-tessut; Matts ta' fuq il-mejda, mhux tal-karta jew tat-tessut; Tazzi tal-karti jew tal-plastik; Oġġetti tal-porċellana; Bramel li jinkludu apparat li jagħsar il-mopp; Friskaturi [skutelli]; Bords li fuqhom jitqattgħu l-affarijiet, għall-kċina; Alzaturi taż-żraben; Alzaturi taż-żraben; Tagħmir biex twessa' l-bwiez; Reċipjenti tal-mejda; Tagħmir li jżomm is-srievet għal fuq il-mejda; Paljazzi; Biċċiet tat-tfarfir [ċraret]; Gabarrès għal skopijiet domestiċi; Gabarrejiet tal-karti, għal skopijiet domestiċi; Tagħmir ta' fuq il-mejda, minbarra skieken, frieket u mgħaref; Fliexken żgħar għall-ispirti li jitqegħdu fil-but ta' wara; Kikkri; Kaxxetti tat-te; Infużorji tat-te f'forma ta' ballun; Tettieri; Drapp, ġeneralment tas-suf, li żżomm il-kitla tat-tè sħuna; Servizzi tat-tè [oġġetti tal-mejda]; Passaturi tat-te; Platti li fihom jisserva l-ikel; Bords tal-ħasil; Banjijiet jew friskaturi tal-ħasil; Bramel b'apparat għat-tagħsir tal-moppijiet; Tagħmir għall-għafis tat-tubi tad-dentifriċi; Zukkarieri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Vuilnisbakken; Houders voor de huishouding of de keuken; Houders voor de huishouding of de keuken; Doosjes van glas; Mandjes voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Houders voor de keuken; Onderzetters, niet van papier of linnen, voor karaffen; Papiermanden; Spaarpotten; Spaarpotten; Toiletnecessaires; Toiletrolhouders; Toiletroldispensers; Afwasborstels; Houders voor afwasborstels; Trekkers [reinigingsinstrumenten]; Broodtrommels; Broodmanden voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Sponzenbakjes; Zeepdozen; Zeephouders; Zeepdispensers; Houders voor theezakjes; Wasrekken; Afvalemmers voor luiers; Bezems; Strijkplanken; Botervlootjes; Eierdopjes; Kuipjes; Karaffen; Pannensets; Kookgerei, niet elektrisch; Keukengerei; Placemats, niet van papier of textiel; Tafelmatjes, niet van papier of textiel; Bekers van papier of plastic; Porseleinwerk; Emmers voor het uitwringen van zwabbers; Kommen; Snijplanken voor de keuken; Schoenlepels; Schoenlepels; Schoenleesten; Schotels; Servethouders; Vaatdoeken; Stofdoeken; Dienbladen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Dienbladen van papier, voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Vaatwerk; Heupflessen; Kopjes; Theedozen; Thee-eieren; Theepotten; Theemutsen; Theeserviezen; Theezeefjes; Borden; Wasborden; Waskuipen; Wringers voor zwabbers; Uitknijpers voor tandpastatubes; Suikerpotten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kosze na śmieci; Pojemniki do użytku domowego lub kuchennego; Pojemniki do użytku domowego lub kuchennego; Pudełka szklane; Kosze do użytku domowego; Pojemniki kuchenne; Podkładki pod szklanki, nie z papieru i nie z materiałów tekstylnych; Kosze na papier; Skarbonki-świnki; Skarbonki-świnki; Kosmetyczki na przybory toaletowe; Dozowniki papieru toaletowego; Dozowniki papieru toaletowego; Szczotki do mycia naczyń; Uchwyty do szczotek do mycia zębów; Szczypce płaskie [narzędzia do czyszczenia]; Pojemniki na chleb; Kosze na chleb do użytku domowego; Uchwyty na gąbki; Mydelniczki; Mydelniczki; Dozowniki mydła; Podstawki na torebki herbaty; Suszarki na pranie; Kosze na zużyte pieluchy; Miotły; Deski do prasowania; Maselniczki; Kieliszki do jajek; Kubły; Karafki [na alkohol]; Przybory kuchenne; Przybory kuchenne nieelektryczne; Przybory kuchenne; Maty na stół, nie z papieru ani materiałów tekstylnych; Podkładki na stół, nie z papieru ani materiałów tekstylnych; Kubki z papieru lub z tworzyw sztucznych; Porcelana; Wiadra z wyciskarkami do mopów; Miseczki; Deski do krojenia do kuchni; Łyżki do butów; Łyżki do obuwia; Prawidła do butów; Naczynia; Serwetniki; Zmywaki; Ściereczki do kurzu; Tace do użytku domowego; Tace papierowe, do użytku domowego; Zastawa stołowa, inna niż noże, widelce i łyżki; Piersiówki; Filiżanki; Pudełka na herbatę; Sitka do zaparzania herbaty; Czajniczki do herbaty; Przykrycia na czajniczek; Serwisy do herbaty; Sitka do herbaty; Talerze; Deski do prania [tary]; Balie; Wyżymaczki do mopów; Wyciskarki do pasty do zębów; Cukiernice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Caixotes do lixo; Recipientes para uso doméstico ou para cozinha; Recipientes para uso doméstico ou para cozinha; Caixas em vidro; Cestos para fins domésticos; Recipientes para cozinha; Bases para copos, não sendo em papel ou têxteis; Cestos para papeis; Porquinhos mealheiros; Porquinhos mealheiros; Bolsas de toucador; Suportes para rolos de papel higiénico; Dispensadores de papel higiénico; Escovas para lavar louça; Suportes para escovas para lavar louça; Rodos [instrumentos de limpeza]; Caixas para pão; Cestos para pão, para uso doméstico; Suportes para escovas; Saboneteiras [caixas]; Saboneteiras; Dispensadores de sabonete; Suportes para sacos de chá; Estendais para a roupa; Baldes de fraldas; Vassouras; Tábuas de engomar; Manteigueiras; Taças para ovos; Baldes; Decantadores; Trens de cozinha; Utensílios para cozinhar, não elétricos; Utensílios para cozinha; Individuais de mesa, não sendo em papel ou têxteis; Toalhas de mesa, não sendo em papel ou têxteis; Copos em papel ou em plástico; Loiça de porcelana; Baldes com espremedores para esfregonas; Bacias [pias]; Tábuas de cortar para a cozinha; Calçadeiras; Calçadeiras para sapatos; Formas para calçado [alargadores]; Pratos; Suportes para guardanapos de mesa; Panos de lavagem; Panos para limpeza de pó [trapos]; Tabuleiros para uso doméstico; Bandejas em papel, para uso doméstico; Serviços de mesa, exceto facas, garfos e colheres; Garrafas de bolso; Taças; Caixas para chá; Infusores para chá; Chaleiras [bules para chá]; Abafadores para bules de chá; Serviços de chá [louça de mesa]; Coadores de chá; Louça; Tábuas para lavar; Tanques para lavar roupa; Espremedores para esfregonas; Dispositivos para apertar tubos de pastas dentífricas; Açucareiros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Lăzi de gunoi; Recipiente pentru menaj sau bucătărie; Recipiente pentru menaj sau bucătărie; Cutii de sticlă; Coşuri de uz casnic; Bucătărie (Recipiente pentru -); Suporturi pentru pahare, nu din hârtie sau material textil; Coşuri de hârtii; Puşculiţe; Puşculiţe; Truse de toaletă; Suporturi pentru role de hârtie igienică; Suporturi pentru role de hârtie igienică; Perii pentru spălarea veselei; Suporturi pentru perii de spălat; Raclete [instrumente de curățare]; Cutii pentru pâine; Coşuri de pâine de uz casnic; Suporturi pentru bureţi; Savoniere; Savoniere; Dozatoare de săpun; Suporturi pentru pliculeţe de ceai; Suporturi de uscat rufe; Coșuri de gunoi pentru aruncarea scutecelor; Mături; Mese de călcat; Untiere; Suporturi pentru ouă; Doniţe; Carafe; Ustensile de bucătărie; Ustensile de gătit, neelectrice; Ustensile de bucătărie; Individualuri de masă, nu din hârtie sau material textil; Şervete de masă, nu din hârtie sau material textil; Pahare din plastic sau hârtie; Porţelanuri; Găleţi cu storcător pentru mop; Chiuvete; Tocătoare din lemn pentru bucătărie; Limbi de încălţat pantofii; Lingură pentru pantofi; Calapoade pentru pantofi [sisteme de întindere]; Veselă; Suporturi pentru şerveţele de masă; Cârpe de spălat; Ştergerea prafului (Cârpe pentru -); Tăvi de uz casnic; Tăvi de uz casnic, din hârtie; Veselă, altele decât cuţite, furculiţe şi linguri; Ploşti; Ceşti; Ceai (Cutii pentru -); Infuzoare de ceai; Ceainice; Huse pentru ceainice; Servicii de ceai [veselă]; Strecurători de ceai; Farfurii; Scânduri de spălat rufe; Căzi; Storcătoare de găleată pentru mop; Dispozitive pentru presat tubul de pastă de dinți; Zaharniţe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Smetné nádoby; Nádoby na použitie v domácnosti alebo v kuchyni; Nádoby na použitie v domácnosti alebo v kuchyni; Sklené schránky; Koše pre domácnosť; Kuchynské nádoby; Tanieriky pod fľaše (nie papierové, nie textilné); Odpadkové koše na papier; Pokladničky; Pokladničky; Tašky alebo kufríky na toaletné potreby; Držiaky na toaletný papier; Dávkovače toaletného papiera; Kefky na umývanie riadu; Držiaky pre kefky na umývanie riadu; Stierky [prostriedky a pomôcky na čistenie]; Schránky na chlieb; Košíky na chlieb pre domácnosť; Držiaky na špongie; Obaly na mydlá; Obaly na mydlá; Dávkovače mydla; Tácky na odkladanie použitých čajových vrecúšok; Stojany na sušenie bielizne; Odpadkové koše na plienky; Metly; Dosky (Žehliace -); Nádobky na maslo (maselničky); Stojany na vajíčka; Kade, putne; Karafy; Kuchynský riad; Potreby na prípravu jedál (nie elektrické); Kuchynský riad; Prestieranie na stolovanie okrem textilného a papierového; Podložky na stôl (anglické prestieranie) okrem textilných a papierových; Papierové alebo plastové poháre; Porcelán; Vedrá s košom na žmýkanie mopu; Misy; Dosky na krájanie (Kuchynské -); Lyžice na obúvanie, obuváky; lyžice na topánky; Napínadlá obuvi; Kuchynský riad na podávanie jedál; Stojany na obrúsky; Oplachovacie handry; Prachovky; Podnosy na použitie v domácnosti; Papierové podnosy pre domácnosť; Kuchynský riad (okrem príborov); Cestovné, turistické fľaše; Šálky; Dózy na čaj; Čajové naparovacie sitká; Čajníky; Poklopy z textílií na udržanie teploty v čajníkoch; Čajové súpravy (stolový riad); Cedidlá na čaj; Taniere; Dosky na pranie; Vane na pranie; Žmýkačky na mopy; Pomôcky na vytláčanie túb; Cukorničky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Smetnjaki; Posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo; Posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo; Steklene posode (s pokrovom); Košare za gospodinjske namene; Kuhinjske posode; Podstavki, ne iz papirja ali blaga; Koši za odpadni papir; Hranilniki; Hranilniki; Toaletne torbice; Nosilci za WC papir; Nosilci za WC papir; Krtače za pomivanje posode; Držala za krtače za pomivanje posode; Brisalke [čistilne naprave]; Posode za shranjevanje kruha; Košarice za kruh za gospodinjske namene; Podstavki za gobice; Posodice za milo; Posodice za milo; Dozirniki mila; Držala za čajne vrečke; Stojala za sušenje perila; Vedra za odlaganje plenic; Metle; Likalne mize; Posode za maslo; Podstavki za jajca; Vedra; Karafe; Kuharski pripomočki; Neelektrični pripomočki za kuhanje; Kuharski pripomočki; Pogrinjki, ne iz papirja ali blaga; Namizni pogrinjki, ne iz papirja ali blaga; Kozarci iz papirja ali plastike; Posoda iz porcelana; Vedra za ožemanje mopov; Umivalniki (sklede); Kuhinjske deske za rezanje; Žlice za obuvanje; Žlice za obuvanje; Napenjalniki čevljev; Posoda; Stojala za serviete; Krpe za pomivanje; Cunje za brisanje prahu; Pladnji za gospodinjske namene; Papirnati pladnji, za gospodinjske namene; Namizna posoda (razen nožev, vilic in žlic); Žepne čutarice; Skodelice; Škatle za čaj; Filtri za čaj v obliki bunke; Čajniki; Grelci iz blaga za čajnike; Čajni servisi; Cedila za čaj; Krožniki; Perilniki (ribežni za perilo); Kadi za pranje perila; Ožemalniki za mope; Pripomočki za stiskanje zobne paste; Sladkornice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Soptunnor; Behållare för hushålls- eller köksändamål; Behållare för hushålls- eller köksändamål; Askar av glas; Korgar för hushållsbruk; Köksbehållare; Underlägg, inte av papper eller textil; Papperskorgar; Spargrisar; Spargrisar; Resenecessärer (inredda); Toalettpappersautomat; Toalettpappersautomat; Diskborstar; Hållare för diskborstar; Avdragare [rengöringsredskap]; Brödskrin; Brödkorgar för hushållsändamål; Svamphållare; Tvålkoppar; Tvålkoppar; Tvålautomater; Fat för tepåsar; Torkställningar för tvätt; Blöjsophinkar; Kvastar; Strykbrädor; Smöraskar; Äggkoppar; Hinkar; Karaffer; Köksgeråd; Icke-elektriska kokkärl; Köksgeråd; Bordstabletter, inte av papper eller textil; Bordsunderlägg, inte av papper eller textil; Muggar av papper eller plast; Porslinsvaror; Hinkar med moppurvridare; Bunkar [skålar]; Skärbrädor för köket; Skohorn; Skohorn; Stövelblock [sträckare]; Uppläggningsfat; Servetthållare; Disktrasor; Dammtrasor; Brickor för hushållsändamål; Pappersbrickor för hushållsändamål; Bordserviser (inte knivar, gafflar och skedar); Dryckesflaskor för sport; Bägare; Teburkar; Tekulor; Tekannor; Tekannehuvar; Teserviser [bordsserviser]; Tesilar; Fat; Tvättbrädor; Tvättbaljor; Moppurvridare; Klämmor för tandkrämstuber; Sockerskålar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Метални куки за портманто, Кутии, Сандъци от метал, Метални кукички за дрехи, Метални кошове, Куки [метална кинкалерия], Метална пощенска кутия, Кутии от неблагородни метали; Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Стоки от хартия, Торби за боклук (от хартия или пластмасови материи), Папки за книжа, Документни папки [канцеларски принадлежности], Кошове за писма, Контейнери за съхранение, изработени от хартия, Контейнери за съхранение, изработени от картон, Моливи (поставки за -), Преспапиета, Офис принадлежности (с изключение на мебели), Поставки за писалки и моливи, Подложки за документи с щипка, Гравюри, Бележници [канцеларски принадлежности], Книжки, Книговезки телчета за офиси; Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Клипсове за поставяне на баджове [офисни артикули], Джобове за документи, Държачи за значки [офис артикули], Пликове [канцеларски принадлежности], Календари, Разделители за книги, Перфоратори [офисни принадлежности], Маркери [канцеларски принадлежности], Баджове с имена [oфис консумативи], Тефтери, Кламери, Гуми за изтриване, Канцеларски принадлежности, Принадлежности за писане, Дъсчици за писане,; Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Шкафове за работни маси [офис принадлежности]; Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Кутии от дърво или пластмаса, Закачалки за дрехи, Не от метал, Решения с кукички за облекло, Не от метал, Кошници, Не от метал, Кутия за играчки, Разделения за чекмеджета, Пластмасови кутии за съхранение, Кутии, изработени от плат, Куки от метал за окачалки за дрехи, за закрепване на врати, Шкафчета с ключ, Слайдове за шкафчета, Кутии за съхранение [мебели]; Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Контейнери, Не от метал, За целите на съхранението, Закачалки за щендери за дрехи, Закачалки за дрехи, Поставки за костюми [мебели] и закачалки (кукички) за дрехи, Шкаф с плъзгащи чекмеджета, Сгъваеми кутии, Не от метал, Поставящи се една върху друга кутии за съхранение от пластмаса, Табели от дърво или пластмаса, Табла за окачване на ключове, Колички [мебели]; Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Подложки, сменяеми, за мивки, Поставки за списания, Стелажи за вестници, Шкафове, Писалища, Кутии, Кутии, Не от метал; Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Кошчета за боклук, Домакински или кухненски поставки, Съдове за домакински или кухненски цели [с изключение на такива от благороден метал], Кутии от стъкло, Кошници за битови цели, Кухненски съдове, Подложки за чаши, различни от тези от хартия или текстил, Кошове за отпадъчна хартия, Кутии за пари, Прасенца касички, Тоалетни чанти, Държачи за тоалетна хартия, Прибори за автоматично осигуряване на тоалетна хартия, Четки за миене на съдове, Държачи за четки за миене на съдове, Чистачки [уреди за почистване], Панерчета за хляб; Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Кошници за хляб за домашна употреба, Съдове за гъби, Кутии за сапун, Поставки за сапун, Поставки за сапун, Дозатори за течен сапун, Четки за миене на съдове, Поставки за пакетчета чай, Сушилници, Кофи за изхвърляне на пелени, Метли, Дъски за гладене, Буталки за избиване на масло, Чашки за варени яйца, Кофи, Гарафи, Комплекти тенджери за готвене, Уреди за печене, Комплекти тенджери за готвене, Подложки за хранене, състоящи се не от хартия или текстил (комплекти); Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Подложки за предпазване на повърхността на масата, не от хартия или текстил, Книжни и пластмасови чаши, Продукти от порцелан, Кофи с приспособление за изстискване на бърсалки, Купи, Дъски за рязане за кухнята, Обувалки, Обувалки, Калъпи за обувки, Купи, Релси за закачване на хавлии, Парцали за миене, Бърсалки от плат, подноси за домакини цели, Подноси за домакински цели, от хартия, Изкуството на масата, Плоски бутилки, Чаши, Кутийки за съхранение на чай, Съдове за запарване на чай, Чайници; Продажба на едро и на дребно на плодове, Продажба по пощата, включително по интернет, по отношение на Калъфи за чайници, Калъфи (чай- ), Сервизи за чай, не от благороден метал, Решетки за чай, Дискове, Дъски за пране, Корита за пране, Приспособление за изстискване на парцалите за миене, Притискачи за туби с паста за зъби, Захарници, не от благороден метал, Представяне на стоки и услуги на големи пазари, в супермаркети, в маганизи за търговия на дребно, универсални магазини и он-лайн магазини.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Kovové háčky pro věšáky, Pouzdra, Bedny (kovové), Kovové háčky na věšení šatů, Kovové koše, Háčky [kovové potřeby klempířské], Dopisní schránky z kovu, Krabice z obecných kovů; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Papírové zboží, Sáčky na odpadky z papíru nebo umělých hmot, Pouzdra na doklady, Pořadače [spisové obaly], Koše na poštu, Ukládací krabice z papíru, Ukládací nádoby z lepenkového kartonu, Tužky (držátka na-), Těžítka, Kancelářské potřeby (s vyjímkou nábytku), Stojany na pera a tužky, Desky (psací -) sklipsem [na přidržování papíru], Obrazy, Bloky [papírnické výrobky], Knížky (brožované), Kancelářské sponky; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Spony na visačky [psací potřeby], Desky na dokumenty, Panely na visačky [psací potřeby], Obálky (papírnické výrobky), Kalendáře, Knihy (záložky do-), Děrovačky (kancelářské potřeby), Zvýrazňovače [papírnictví], Jmenovky [kancelářské potřeby], Poznámkové bloky, Kancelářské sponky, Gumy na mazání, Psací potřeby, Psací potřeby, Psací podložky na stůl; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Skříňky do pracovních stolů [kancelářské potřeby]; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Bedny ze dřeva nebo z umělých hmot, Háčky k věšákům na oděvy, Nikoli z kovu, Věšáky [háčky] na oděvy, Nikoli z kovu, Košíky, Nikoli z kovu, Skříňky na hračky, Oddělovače pro zásuvky, Úložné nádoby z plastické hmoty, Boxy z látky, Háčky na šaty z kovu pro umístění na dveře, Zásuvky, Zásuvkové kolejnice, Ukládací krabice [nábytek]; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Bedny, Nikoli z kovu, Pro ukládání, Háčky pro tyče na oděvy, Ramínka na oděvy, Stojany na oděvy [nábytek] a ramínka na šaty, Skříně se zásuvkami, Skládací boxy, Nikoli z kovu, Stohovatelné odkládací skříňky z plastické hmoty, Vývěsní štíty ze dřeva nebo umělých hmot, Tabule s háčky na zavěšení klíčů, Vozíky [nábytek]; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Snímatelné kryty nebo vložky pro dřezy, Stojany na časopisy, Stojany na noviny, Skříně, Psací stoly, Pouzdra, Bedny laťové přepravní, Nikoli z kovu; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Kbelíky na smetí, odpadky, Nádoby pro použití v domácnosti nebo v kuchyni, Nádoby pro použití v domácnosti a v kuchyni, Schránky ze skla, Koše pro použití v domácnosti, Kuchyňské nádoby, Podložky pod sklenice, jiné než papírové nebo textilní, Koše na papír, Pokladničky, Prasátka (pokladničky), Kosmetické neceséry, Držáky na toaletní papír, Dávkovače toaletního papíru, Kartáče na umývání nádobí, Držáky na kartáče na nádobí, Stahovače [čisticí nástroje], Schránky na chléb; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Košíky na chléb pro použití v domácnosti, Misky na mycí houby, Pouzdra na mýdlo, Držáky na mýdlo, Misky na mýdlo, Dávkovače mýdla, Kartáče na umývání nádobí, Tácky na odkládání čajových sáčků, Sušáky na prádlo, Kbelíky na likvidaci plen, Smetáky, Prkna žehlicí, Máselnice, Kalíšky na vajíčka, Štoudve, Karafy, stolní lahve, Soupravy kuchyňského nádobí, Nástroje na pečení, Kuchyňské potřeby, Prostírání jiné než papírové (sady); Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Prostírání jiné než papírové nebo textilní, Pohárky z papíru nebo umělých hmot, Porcelán, Kbelíky s nástavci na ždímání mopu, Mísy, Krájecí podložky pro použití v kuchyni, Nazouvací lžíce, Lžíce na obouvání, Napínáky na obuv (kopyta), Koule (hra), Držáky na ubrousky, Utěrky na nádobí, Prachovky, Podnosy pro domácnost, Tácky papírové k použití v domácnosti, Stolování, Kapesní lahve (čutory), Šálky, Dózy na čaj, Čajová nálevka, Čajové konvice; Velkoobchodní a maloobchodní služby, Služby v oblasti poštovních objednávek, i přes internet, pokud jde o Přikrývky, Čajové panenky, Čajové servisy [stolní nádobí], Sítka na čaj, Talíře, Valchy, Dřezy na praní (škopek), Ždímače mopů, Pomůcky pro vymačkávání zubních past, Cukřenky, Prezentace zboží a služby ve velkoobchodech, supermarketech, maloobchodech, obchodních domech a online obchodech.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Metalhager til knagerækker, Huse, Bokse af metal, Knager af metal, Kurve af metal, Metalkroge, Postkasser af metal, Kasser af uædle metaller; Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Papirvarer, Affaldsposer af papir eller plastic, Dokumentmapper, Ringbind til løsblade, Brevkurve, Opbevaringsbeholdere af papir, Opbevaringsbeholdere af papkarton, Blyantholdere, Papirvægte, Kontorartikler (dog ikke møbler), Holdere til blyanter og penne, Clipboards, Billeder, Blokke [papirvarer], Brochurer, Clips til kontorbrug; Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Clips til navneskilteholdere [kontorartikler], Mapper til papirer, Navneskilteholdere [kontorartikler], Kuverter, Kalendere, Bogmærker, Hulleredskaber (kontorrekvisitter), Markeringspenne [kontorartikler], Navneskilte (kontorrekvisitter), Notesbøger, Papirclips, Viskelædere, Skriveredskaber, Skriveredskaber [kontorartikler], Skrivebordsunderlag; Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Skriveborde [kontorudstyr]; Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Æsker af træ eller plastic, Kroge til knagerækker, ikke af metal, Kroge til tøjstativer, ikke af metal, Kurve, ikke af metal, Legetøjskasser, Rumadskillelser til skuffer, Opbevaringsbeholdere af syntetiske materialer, Bokse af stof, Garderobeknager af metal til anbringelse på døre, Opbevaringsskabe, Glideskinner til skuffer, Opbevaringskasser (møbler); Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Beholdere, ikke af metal, Til opbevaringsformål, Kroge til stænger til beklædningsgenstande, Bøjler, Tøjstativer (møbler) og tøjknager, Skab med skuffer, Sammenklappelige bokse, ikke af metal, Stabelbare aflæggekasser af plastic, Skilte af træ eller plastic, Brætter til ophængning af nøgler, Rulleborde (møbler); Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Løse måtter til køkkenvaske, Tidsskrifthylder, Udstillingsstativer til aviser, Dækketøjsskabe, Skriveborde, Huse, Kasser, ikke af metal; Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Dåser, Husholdnings- og køkkenbeholdere, Beholdere til husholdnings- eller køkkenbrug, Glasæsker, Kurve til husholdningsbrug, Køkkenbeholdere, Bordskånere, dog ikke af papir eller stof, Papirkurve, Pengekasser, Sparegrise, Toiletnecessaire, Toiletpapirholdere, Toiletpapirdispensere, Opvaskebørster, Holdere til opvaskebørster, Aftrækkere (rengøringsredskaber), Brødkrukker; Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Brødkurve til husholdningsbrug, Svampeholdere, Sæbeetuier, Sæbeholdere, Sæbeskåle, Sæbedispensere, Opvaskebørster, Teposeholdere, Tørrestativer, Blespande, Koste, Strygebrætter, Smørskåle, Æggebægre, Spande, Bundfældningsbeholdere, Kogekar, Kogegrej, Køkkenredskaber, Dækkeservietter, ikke af papir eller tekstiler (sæt); Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Bordskånere, ikke af papir eller tekstiler, Kopper af papir eller plastic, Porcelænsvarer, Spande med moppevridere, Skåle, Skærebrætter til køkkenbrug, Skohorn, Skohorn, Skoholdere, Skåle, Napkin holders, Viskestykker, Støveklude, Bakker til husholdningsformål, Bakker af papir til husholdningsformål, Gastronomi, Lommelærker, Kopper, Tedåser, Teæg, Tepotter; Engros- og detailvirksomhed, Postordrevirksomhed, inklusive over internettet, med hensyn til Tehætter, Tehætter, Teservice [bordservice], Tesi, Tallerkener, Vaskebrætter, Ludbehandlede vaskebaljer, Moppevridere, Klemmer til tandpastatuber, Sukkerskåle, Præsentation af varer og tjenesteydelser i hypermarkeder, supermarkeder, detailhandelsforretninger, varehuse og onlieshops.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf Garderobenhaken aus Metall, Kästen, Kisten aus Metall, Kleiderhaken aus Metall [Einrichtungsartikel], Körbe aus Metall, Haken [Kleineisenwaren], Briefkästen aus Metall, Kästen aus unedlen Metallen; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf Papierwaren, Abfallsäcke aus Papier oder Kunststoff, Aktenhüllen, Aktenordner, Briefkörbe, Aufbewahrungsbehälter aus Papier, Aufbewahrungsbehälter aus Pappkarton, Bleistifthalter, Briefbeschwerer, Büroartikel [ausgenommen Möbel], Halter für Schreibfedern und Bleistifte, Klemmtafeln [Büroartikel], Bilder, Blöcke [Papier- und Schreibwaren], Booklets, Büroklammern; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf Clips für Halter von Namensschildern [Büroartikel], Dokumentenhüllen, Halter für Namensschilder [Büroartikel], Hüllen [Papier- und Schreibwaren], Kalender, Lesezeichen, Locher [Büroartikel], Markierstifte, Namensschilder [Büroartikel], Notizbücher, Notizklemmen [Papeteriewaren], Radiergummis, Schreibgeräte, Schreibmappen [Papeteriewaren], Schreibtischunterlagen; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf Tischbehälter und -kästen für Papier- und Schreibwaren; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf Boxen aus Holz oder Kunststoff, Garderobenhaken, nicht aus Metall, Kleiderhaken [Einrichtungsartikel], nicht aus Metall, Körbe, nicht aus Metall, Spielzeugkisten, Trenneinlagen für Schubladen, Aufbewahrungskisten aus Kunststoff, Boxen aus Stoff, Garderobenhaken aus Metall zur Anbringung an Türen, Schubladen, Schubladenführungen, Aufbewahrungskisten [Möbel]; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf Behälter, nicht aus Metall, zu Aufbewahrungszwecken, Haken für Kleiderstangen, Kleiderbügel, Kleiderständer [Möbel] und Kleiderhaken, Schubladenschrank, faltbare Boxen, nicht aus Metall, Stapelbare Ablagekästen aus Kunststoff, Schilder aus Holz oder Kunststoff, Schlüsselbretter, Servierwagen [Möbel]; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf Spülsteinmatten, Zeitungshalter, Zeitungsständer, Schränke, Schreibtische, Kästen, Kisten, nicht aus Metall; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf Abfalleimer, Behälter für Haushalt oder Küche, Gefäße für Haushalt oder Küche, Glasbehälter, Körbe für den Haushalt, Küchengefäße, nicht aus Papier oder Stoff bestehende Untersetzer, Papierkörbe, Sparbüchsen, Sparschweine, Toilettenecessaires, Toilettenpapierhalter, Toilettenpapierspender, Spülbürsten, Halterungen für Spülbürsten, Abzieher [Reinigungsgeräte], Brotkästen; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf Brotkörbe für den Haushalt, Schwammhalter, Seifendosen, Seifenhalter, Seifenschalen, Seifenspender, Spülbürsten, Teebeutelablagen, Wäscheständer, Windelentsorgungseimer, Besen, Bügelbretter, Butterdosen, Eierbecher, Eimer aller Art, Karaffen, Kochgeschirr, Kochutensilien, Küchengeschirr, nicht aus Papier oder Stoff bestehende Platzdeckchen [Sets]; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf nicht aus Papier oder Stoff bestehende Tischdeckchen, Papier- oder Plastikbecher, Porzellan, Putzeimer mit Auswringer, Schalen, Schneidbretter für die Küche, Schuhanzieher, Schuhlöffel, Schuhspanner, Schüsseln, Serviettenhalter, Spüllappen, Staubtücher, Tabletts für den Haushalt, Tabletts für den Haushalt aus Papier, Tafelgeschirr, Taschenflaschen, Tassen, Teedosen, Tee-Eier, Teekannen; Groß- und Einzelhandelsdienstleistungen und Versandhandelsdienstleistungen, auch über das Internet in Bezug auf Teemützen, Teewärmer, Teeservice [Tafelgeschirr], Teesiebe, Teller, Waschbretter, Waschwannen, Wischmopppressen, Zahnpastatubenquetscher, Zuckerdosen; Präsentation von Waren und Dienstleistungen in Großmärkten, Supermärkten, Einzelhandelsgeschäften, Warenhäusern und Onlineshops.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Μεταλλικά άγκιστρα για σωλήνες ερμαρίων ενδυμάτων, Περιβλήματα, Μεταλλικά κουτιά, Μεταλλικά άγκιστρα για ενδύματα, Μεταλλικά καλάθια, Άγκιστρα (είδη σιδηροπωλείου), Μεταλλικά γραμματοκιβώτια, Κουτιά από κοινά μέταλλα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Είδη από χαρτί, Σάκοι απορριμμάτων (από χαρτί ή πλαστικές ύλες), Φάκελοι από χαρτί, Αρχειοθέτες εγγράφων, Θήκες διανομής αλληλογραφίας, Χάρτινοι περιέκτες αποθήκευσης, Χάρτινοι περιέκτες αποθήκευσης, Υποδοχές για μολύβια, Χαρτοστάτες, Είδη γραφείου (εκτός των επίπλων), Βάσεις για πένες και μολύβια, Πινάκια (είδη γραφείου), Φωτογραφιών, Σημειωματάρια [μπλοκ] είδη χαρτοπωλείου, Φυλλάδια, Συνδετήρες γραφείου· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Κλιπ για καρτελάκια - κονκάρδες [είδη γραφείου], Θήκες για έγγραφα, Καρτελάκια - κονκάρδες [είδη γραφείου], Θήκες [είδη χαρτοπωλείου], Ημεροδείκτες, Σελιδοδείκτες, Στιγείς (είδος γραφείου), Μαρκαδόροι [είδη γραφείου], Ταμπελίτσες ονόματος (είδη γραφείου), Τετράδια, Συνδετήρες σημειώσεων [είδη χαρτοπωλείου], Γόμες, Εργαλεία γραφής, Εργαλεία γραφής, Χαλάκια για γραφεία· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Ντουλαπάκια γραφείου [είδη γραφείου]· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Θήκες από ξύλο ή πλαστικό, Άγκιστρα για κρεμάστρες ενδυμάτων, Μη μεταλλικά, Άγκιστρα [γάντζοι] για ενδύματα, Μη μεταλλικά, Καλάθια, Μη μεταλλικά, Κουτιά για παιχνίδια, Διαχωριστικά συρταριών, Πλαστικά δοχεία αποθήκευσης, Κουτιά από ύφασμα, Άγκιστρα ανάρτησης ενδυμάτων από μέταλλο για τοποθέτηση σε θύρες, Φοριαμοί, Ολισθητήρες συρταριών, Κουτιά αποθήκευσης [έπιπλα]· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Δοχεία, Μη μεταλλικά, Για σκοπούς αποθήκευσης, Γάντζοι για φορέματα, Κρεμάστρες για ενδύματα, Κρεμάστρες (καλόγεροι) [έπιπλα] και κρεμάστρες, Ντουλάπα με συρτάρια, Πτυσσόμενα κουτιά, Μη μεταλλικά, Στοιβαζόμενα κουτιά αποθήκευσης από πλαστικό, Ταμπέλες από ξύλο ή πλαστικές ύλες, Πίνακες ανάρτησης κλειδιών, Καροτσάκια (έπιπλα)· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Χαλάκια για νεροχύτες, Θήκες για περιοδικά, Βάσεις παρουσίασης για εφημερίδες, Ντουλάπες, Γραφεία (σεκρετέρ), Περιβλήματα, Κιβώτια, Μη μεταλλικά· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Κάδοι, Δοχεία οικιακής ή μαγειρικής χρήσης, Δοχεία οικιακά ή μαγειρικά, Γυάλινα δοχεία, Καλάθια για οικιακή χρήση, Δοχεία μαγειρικής χρήσης, Επιτραπέζιες προστατευτικές βάσεις για ποτήρια, εκτός από τις χάρτινες ή τις υφασμάτινες, Κάλαθοι απορριμμάτων χαρτιού, Κουμπαράδες (παιχνίδια), Κουμπαράδες, Τσαντάκια για καλλυντικά είδη (διακοσμημένα), Βάσεις για χαρτί υγείας, Διανεμητές χαρτιού τουαλέτας, Βουρτσάκια για το πλύσιμο των πιάτων, Βάσεις για βούρτσες πλυσίματος πιάτων, Μάκτρα καθαρισμού [συσκευές καθαρισμού], Ψωμιέρες· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Καλαθάκια για το ψωμί για οικιακή χρήση, Θήκες για σφουγγάρια, Σαπουνοθήκες, Βάσεις για σαπούνι, Σαπουνοθήκες, Διανομείς σαπουνιών, Βουρτσάκια για το πλύσιμο των πιάτων, Υποδοχές για φακελάκια τσαγιού, Διατάξεις στήριξης για στέγνωμα, Κάδοι απόρριψης βρεφικών πανών, Σάρωθρα, Σιδερώστρες, Βουτυριέρες, Αυγοθήκες, Κάδοι, Καράφες, Μαγειρικά σκεύη, Σκεύη για ψήσιμο, Μαγειρικά σκεύη, Επιτραπέζιες προστατευτικές βάσεις σερβίτσιων (σετ) όχι από χαρτί ή ύφασμα· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Επιτραπέζιες προστατευτικές βάσεις σερβίτσιων, όχι από χαρτί ή ύφασμα, Κύπελλα από χαρτί ή πλαστικό, Είδη από σινική πορσελάνη, Κουβάδες στιψίματος σφουγγαρίστρας, Γαβάθες, Επιφάνειες κοπής για την κουζίνα, Εργαλεία για το φόρεμα των υποδημάτων, Γλώσσες παπουτσιών, Καλαπόδια για υποδήματα, Γαβάθες, Υποδοχές για πετσέτες φαγητού, Πανιά για το σκούπισμα πιάτων, Ξεσκονόπανα (πανιά), Δίσκοι για οικιακές χρήσεις, Δίσκους για οικιακή χρήση, από χαρτί, Της τέχνης του σερβιρίσματος, Φλασκιά τσέπης, Κύπελλα, Μεταλλικά δοχεία για τσάι, Συσκευές έγχυσης τσαγιού, Τσαγιέρες· Υπηρεσίες λιανικής και χονδρικής πώλησης, Αγορές μέσω του ταχυδρομείου, συμπεριλαμβανομένου του Διαδικτύου, σε σχέση με Καλύμματα τσαγιέρας, Καλύμματα τσαγιέρας, Σερβίτσια τσαγιού [επιτραπέζια σκεύη], Σουρωτήρια τσαγιού, Πιάτα, Μπουγάδα (Σανίδες -), Σκάφες για πλύσιμο, Διατάξεις στυψίματος σφουγγαρίστρας, Συσκευή πίεσης σωληναρίου οδοντόκρεμας, Ζαχαριέρες, Παρουσίαση ειδών και υπηρεσιών σε υπεραγορές, σούπερ μάρκετ, καταστήματα λιανικής πώλησης, εμπορικά κέντρα και καταστήματα επί γραμμής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of Hooks of metal for clothes rails, Boxes, Metal boxes, Clothes hooks of metal, Baskets of metal, Hooks (metal hardware), Letter boxes of metal, Boxes of common metal; Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of paper goods, Rubbish bags of paper or of plastic, Folders for papers, Organiser files, Letter trays, Storage containers of paper, Storage containers made of cardboard, pencil holders, Paperweights, Office requisites (except furniture), Stands for pens and pencils, Clipboards, pictures, Pads [stationery], Booklets, Clips for offices; Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of Clips for name badge holders (office requisites), Document sleeves, Name badge holders (office requisites), Envelopes (stationery), Calendars, book marks, Punches [office requisites], Marking pens [stationery], Name badges [office requisites], Notebooks, Paper clips, Rubber erasers, Writing instruments, Writing cases (stationery), desk mats; Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of Desktop cabinets for stationery [office requisites]; Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of Bins of wood or plastic, hooks for clothes rails, not of metal, Clothes hooks, not of metal, baskets, not of metal, Chests for toys, dividers for drawers, Storage boxes of plastic, Boxes of materials, Hooks of metal for clothes rails for attaching to doors, Lockers, Drawer slides, Storage boxes (furniture); Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of Containers, not of metal, For storage, Hooks for clothing racks, Coathangers, Clothes stands [furniture] and clothes hooks, Chest of drawers, Collapsible boxes, not of metal, Stackable filing boxes of plastic, Signboards of wood or plastics, Keyboards for hanging keys, Trolleys (furniture); Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of Removable mats or covers for sinks, Magazine racks, Newspaper display stands, Cabinets (furniture), Writing desks, Boxes, Crates, not of metal; Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of Dustbins, Containers for household or kitchen use, Containers for household or kitchen use, Glass receptacles, baskets, for domestic use, Kitchen jars, Coasters, other than of paper or textile, Waste paper baskets, Money boxes, piggy banks, Toilet cases, Toilet paper holders, Toilet paper dispensers, Dishwashing brushes, Holders for dishwashing brushes, Pullers [cleaning apparatus], Bread bins; Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of Bread baskets for household purposes, Sponge holder, soap boxes, Soap holders, Dishes for soap, Dispensers for soap, Dishwashing brushes, tea bag rests, Clothes horses, Diaper disposal pails, brooms, Ironing boards, Butter dishes, Egg cups, pails, Decanters, Cooking pot sets, Bake ware, kitchenware, Place mats, not of paper or textile (sets); Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of Tablemats, not of paper or textile, Paper and plastic cups, Articles of porcelain, mop wringer buckets, bowels, Cutting boards for kitchen use, Shoe horns, Shoehorn, Shoe-trees, bowls, napkin holders, Dishcloths, Dusting cloths, Trays for domestic purposes, trays for domestic purposes, of paper, Dinnerware, hip-flasks, Cups, Tea caddies, Tea infusers, Teapots; Wholesaling and retailing services, Mail order sale services, including over the Internet, in respect of tea cosies, Tea cosies, Tea services (tableware), Tea strainers, Plates, Washing boards, Washtubs, Mop wringers, Toothpaste tube squeezers, Sugar bowls, Presentation of goods and services in hypermarkets, supermarkets, retail outlets, department stores and online shops.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Ganchos de percheros metálicos, Carcasas, Cajas metálicas, Páteras [colgadores] para vestidos metálicas, Cestas metálicas, Ganchos [ferretería metálica], Buzón de metal, Cajas de metales comunes; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Artículos de papel, Bolsas de basura (de papel o de materias plásticas), Carpetas para documentos, Expedientes [legajos] [papelería], Bandejas de escritorio, Recipientes de papel, Contenedores de almacenamiento de cartón, Portalápices, De pisa-papeles, Artículos de oficina (excepto muebles), Soportes para plumas y lápices, Portapapeles de clip [artículos de oficina], Imágenes, Blocs [artículos de papelería], Cartillas [cuadernillos], Clips; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Clips para sujetar insignias [artículos de oficina], Carpetas para documentos, Soportes para insignias [artículos de oficina], Sobres [artículos de papelería], Calendarios, Marcapáginas, Sacabocados [artículos de oficina], Marcadores [artículos de papelería], Insignias de identificación [artículos de oficina], Cuadernos de notas, Pinzas para sujetar papeles [clips], Gomas de borrar, Instrumentos de escritura, Útiles de escritura, Alfombrillas de escritorio; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Archivadores [armarios] de escritorio para artículos de papelería [artículos de oficina]; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Cajas de madera o de materias plástica, Ganchos de percheros, no de metal, Perchas para prendas de vestir, no de metal, Cestas, no de metal, Cajones de juguetes, Divisiones para cajones, Contenedores de almacenamiento de plástico, Cajas de tela, Ganchos metálicos para prendas de vestir para su aplicación en puertas, Cajones, Guías de deslizamiento para cajones, Cajas de almacenamiento [muebles]; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Depósitos, no de metal, Para fines de almacenamiento, Ganchos para barras de ropa, Percheros para ropa, Colgadores de ropa [muebles] y ganchos de ropa, Armario de cajones, Cajas plegables, no de metal, Cajas archivadoras apilables de plástico, Letreros de madera o de materias plásticas, Tableros para colgar las llaves, Carros [mobiliario]; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Revestimientos amovibles para fregaderos, Revisteros, Expositores para periódicos, Aparadores, Escritorios, Carcasas, Cajas, no de metal; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Cubos, Recipientes para el hogar o la cocina, Recipientes para uso doméstico o culinario, Cajas de cristal, Cestos para uso doméstico, Recipientes para la cocina, Posavasos distintos de aquellos de papel o tela, Papeleras, Huchas, Huchas, Estuches de productos de tocador, Portarrollos de papel higiénico, Distribuidores de papel higiénico, Cepillos para lavar la vajilla, Soportes para cepillos de fregar la vajilla, Extractores [aparatos de limpieza], Paneras; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Cestas para el pan de uso doméstico, Porta-esponjas (esponjeras), Cajas para jabón, Jaboneras, Porta jabón (jaboneras), Distribuidores de jabón, Cepillos para lavar la vajilla, Soportes para bolsas de té, Tendederos, Cubos para la eliminación de pañales, Escobas, Soportes de planchas, Mantequeras, Hueveras, Baldes de todas clases, Decantadores, Baterías de cocina, Utensilios para la cocción, Artículos de cocina, Manteles individuales (juegos) que no sean de papel ni de materias textiles; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Tapetes que no sean de papel ni de materias textiles, Tazas de papel o de plástico, artículos de porcelana, Cubos escurridores de fregonas, Cuencos, Tablas para trinchar para la cocina, Calzadores para zapatos, Calzadores, Conformadores del calzado, Cuencos, Portaservilletas, Balletas de cocina, Paños [trapos] para limpiar el polvo, Bandejas para uso doméstico, Bandejas de papel para uso doméstico, las artes de la mesa, Frascos de bolsillo, Tazas, Latas de té, Bolas para el té, Teteras; Servicios de venta al por mayor y al por menor, Servicios de ventas por correo, incluso a través de Internet, con respecto a Cubiertas para teteras, Cubiertas para teteras, Servicios de té [vajilla], Colador para el té, Platos, Tablas de lavar, Tinas para la colada, Estrujadores de mopas, Prensas para tubos de pasta de dientes, Azucareros, Presentación de productos y servicios en grandes almacenes, supermercados, comercios minoristas, almacenes y tiendas en Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Riidepuude konksud (metallist), Korpused, Metallkastid, Riidenagid (metallist), Metallkorvid, Konksud, haagid (peenrauakaubad), Metallist kirjakastid, Kastid, karbid (lihtmetallist); Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Paberikaubad, Prügikotid (paberist või plastist), Kaaned (dokumentide või akti- ), Dokumendimapid, aktimapid [kantseleitarbed], Paberikorvid, Paberist valmistatud mahutid, Kartongist hoiumahutid, Pliiatsihoidlid, Paberipresside hulgimüük, Bürootarvikud v.a.büroomööbel, Sulepea- ja pliiatsihoidlid, Kirjutusalused [kontoritarbed], Pildid, Plokid [kirjatarbed], Brošüürid, Kirjaklambrid (kontoritarbed); Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Nimesildihoidikute klambrid [kontoritarbed], Dokumendimapid, Nimesildihoidikud [kontoritarbed], Ümbrikud [kirjatarbed], Kalendrid, Järjehoidikud, Augurauad, mulgustid, perforaatorid (kantseleitarbed), Markerid [kontoritarbed], Nimesildid [kontoritarbed], Märkmeraamatud, Kirjaklambrid, Kustutuskummid, Kirjutusvahendid, Kirjatarbed, Lauamatid; Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Paberi ja kirjatarvete mahutid ja karbid laudadele; Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Puit- või plastkarbid, Riidevarnad, mittemetallist, Rõivanagid, mittemetallist, Korvid, mittemetallist, Mänguasjakastid, Sahtlijaoturid, Plastist hoiukastid, Riidest kastid, Ustele paigaldatavad metallist riidenagid, Sahtlid, Sahtliliugurid, Säilituskastid [mööbel]; Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Mahutid, mittemetallist, Hoidmiseks, Rõivasiinide konksud, Riidepuud, Rõivanagid [mööbel] ja rõivakonksud, Sahtlitega kapid, Kokkupandavad kastid, mittemetallist, Virnastatavad plastkastid, Kuulutustahvlid (puidust või plastist), Võtmekilbid (võtmete riputamiseks), Serveerimislauad [mööbel]; Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Eemaldatavad valamumatid, Ajakirjaalused, Ajalehehoidlid, ajalehealused, Kapid (riiulitega), Kirjutuslauad, Korpused, Kastid, mittemetallist; Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Prügikorvid, Köögi- või majapidamismahutid, Maja- ja köögimahutid, Klaasanumad, Majapidamiskorvid, Köögikonteinerid, Klaasialused, muud kui paberist või tekstiilist, Kirjakorvid, Rahakarbid, Hoiupõrsad-rahakassad, Tualett-tarvete karbid, Tualettpaberihoidikud, Tualettpaberihoidikud, Nõudepesuharjad, Nõudepesuharjade hoidikud, Tõmmitsad [puhastusseadmed], Leivakastid; Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Leivakorvid majatarvetena, Pesukäsnaalused, Seebikarbid, Seebialused, Seebialused, Seebijaoturid, Nõudepesuharjad, Teekottide alused, Pesukuivatusrestid, Prügiämbrid mähkmetele, Luuad, Triikimislauad, Võitoosid, Munapeekrid, Ämbrid, Karahvinid, Keedupotikomplektid, Küpsetusnõud, Kööginõud, Paberist või tekstiilist valmistatud lauakatted (komplektid); Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Lauamatid, v.a paberist või tekstiilist, Paber- või plasttopsid, Portselannõud, Mopiväänutiga ämbrid, Kausid, Lõikelauad (köögitarbed), Kingalusikad, Kingalusikad, Kingavormid, Kausid, Salvrätikuhoidjad, Loputuslapid, Tolmulapid, Majapidamiskandikud, Paberist majapidamiskandikud, Lauanõud, Põuepudelid, Tassid, Teetoosid, Teetõmbenõud, Teekannud; Hulgi- ja jaekaubandusteenused, Postitellimisteenused, sealhulgas Interneti kaudu: Teekannusoojendajad, Teekannusoojendid, Teeserviisid [lauanõud], Teesõelad, Taldrikud, Pesulauad, Pesupalid, Mopiväänajad ämbritele, Hambapastatuubi pigistusvahendid, Suhkrutoosid, Toodete ja teenuste esitlemine suurtes kaubamajades, kaubahallides, jaekaubandusettevõtetes, kauplustes ja Internetipoodides.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Metalliset vaatekoukut, Kotelot, Metalliset lippaat, Metalliset vaatekoukut, Metallikorit, Koukut [metalli-], Metalliset postilaatikot, Epäjalosta metallista valmistetut laatikot; Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Paperitavarat, Roskapussit (paperiset tai muoviset), Paperikansiot, Kansiot, Kirjekorit, Paperiset säilytysastiat, Pahviset säilytysastiat, Kynätelineet, Paperipainot, Konttoritarvikkeet (paitsi huonekalut), Mustekynänterien ja lyijykynien telineet, Ilmoitustaulut, Kuvat, Lehtiöt, Kirjaset, Nipistimet toimistokäyttöön; Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Nipistimet nimikorttipidikkeille (toimistotarvikkeet), Asiakirjasuojukset, Nimikorttipidikkeet (toimistotarvikkeet), Kirjekuoret, Kalenterit, Kirjanmerkit, Rei´ityslaitteet (konttoritarvikkeet), Korostuskynät [toimistotarvikkeena], Nimitunnukset (toimistotarvikkeet), Muistikirjat, Paperiklemmarit, Pyyhekumit, Kirjoitusvälineet, Kirjoitusvälineet, Kirjoitusalustat; Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Työpöytien laatikostot [paperitavarat]; Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Puu- tai muovikotelot, Vaatekoukut, ei-metalliset, Vaatekoukut, ei-metalliset, Korit, ei-metalliset, Leikkikalulaatikot, Vetolaatikoiden välilevyt, Muoviset säilytyslaatikot, Kankaiset laatikot, Metalliset naulakkokoukut oviin kiinnitettäviksi, Laatikot, Vetolaatikkojen liukukiskot, Säilytyslaatikot [huonekalut]; Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Vesialtaat, ei-metalliset, Säilytystarkoituksiin, Vaatetankojen koukut, Vaateripustimet, Vaatetelineet [huonekalut] ja vaatekoukut, Laatikostokaappi, Taitettavat laatikot, ei-metalliset, Pinottavat säilytyslaatikot muovista, Puiset tai muoviset kilvet, Avaintaulut avainten ripustamiseen, Kärryt (huonekalut); Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Matot pesualtaisiin, irrotettavat, Lehtitelineet, Sanomalehtien myyntitelineet, Hyttihuonekalut, Kirjoituspöydät, Kotelot, Laatikot, ei-metalliset; Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Roskapöntöt, Talouskäyttöön tarkoitetut tai keittiön säilytysastiat, Säiliöt koti- tai keittiökäyttöön, Lasiset säilytysastiat, Korit kotitalouskäyttöön, Keittiöastiat, Lasinaluset muusta kuin paperista tai kankaasta, Paperikorit, Rahalippaat, Säästölippaat, Toilettilaukut, WC-paperitelineet, WC-paperiautomaatit, Tiskiharjat, Astiaharjatelineet, Ulosvetimet (puhdistuslaitteet), Leipälaatikot; Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Leipäkorit kotitalouskäyttöön, +sienenpidikkeet, Saippuarasiat, Saippuapidikkeet, Saippuatelineet, Saippuanannostelulaitteet, Tiskiharjat, Teepussien aluset, Kuivaustelineet, Vaipparoskikset, Harjat, Silityslaudat, Voivadit, Munakupit, Saavit, Karahvit, Keittoastiat, Leivontavälineet, Keittiötarvikkeet, Muusta kuin paperista tai kankaasta koostuvat ruokailualustat; Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Tabletit, ei paperia eikä tekstiiliä, Paperi- tai muovikupit, Posliinitavarat, Moppisangot, Kulhot, Leikkuulaudat keittiökäyttöön, Kenkälusikat, Kenkälusikat, Lestit, Altaat, Lautasliinapidikkeet, Pesulaput, Pölyrievut, Tarjottimet kotitalouskäyttöön, Paperitarjottimet kotitalouskäyttöön, Kattaukseen liittyvät tuotteet, Taskumatit, Kupit, Teepurkit, Pallonmuotoiset teesiivilät, Teepannut; Vähittäiskauppa- ja tukkukauppapalvelut, Postimyyntipalvelut, mukaan lukien Internetin välityksellä: Teemyssyt, Teemyssyt, Teeastiastot, Teesihdit, Lautaset, Pesulaudat, Pesuammeet, Moppipuristimet, Hammastahnatuubin puristimet, Sokerikulhot, Tavaroiden ja palvelujen esittely hypermarketeissa, supermarketeissa, vähittäiskaupoissa, tavarataloissa ja online-kaupoissa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne Crochets de portemanteaux métalliques, boîtiers, Boîtes métalliques, Patères [crochets] métalliques pour vêtements, Paniers métalliques, Crochets [quincaillerie métallique], boîte à lettres en métal, Boîtes en métaux commun; Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne Articles en papier, sacs à ordures (en papier ou en matières plastiques), Chemises pour documents, Dossiers (papeterie), Corbeilles à papier, Récipients en papier, Récipients de rangement en carton, Porte-crayons, de presse-papiers, Articles de bureau (à l'exception des meubles), Supports pour plumes et crayons, Planchettes à pince [articles de bureau], D'images, Blocs [papeterie], Livrets, Agrafes de bureau; Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne Pinces pour porte-badge d'identification [articles de bureau], Chemises pour documents, Porte-badge d'identification [articles de bureau], Enveloppes [papeterie], Calendrier, Signets de livres, Emporte-pièce [articles de bureau], Marqueurs [articles de papeterie], Badges d'identification [articles de bureau], Cahiers, Pince-notes, Gommes, instruments d' écriture, Instruments d'écriture, Tapis de bureaux; Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne Récipents et boîtes [articles de bureau] destinés à la papeterie; Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne caisses en bois ou en matières plastiques, Crochets de portemanteaux, non en métal, Patères [crochets] pour vêtements, non en métal, Paniers, non en métal, Coffres à jouets, Cloisons pour tiroirs, Coffres de rangement en plastique, Caisses en tissu, Crochets à vêtements métalliques à poser sur des portes, Tiroirs, Glissières de tiroirs, Caisses de rangement [meubles]; Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne Conteneurs, non en métal, Pour le rangement, Crochets pour tringles à vêtements, Cintres pour vêtements, Porte-manteaux [meubles] et patères pour vêtements, Armoires à tiroirs, Caisses pliantes, non en métal, Étagères empilables en matières plastiques, enseignes en bois ou en matières plastiques, Tableaux accroche-clés, Chariots [mobilier]; Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne Revêtements amovibles pour éviers, Porte-revues, présentoirs pour journaux, armoires, Secrétaires (meubles), boîtiers, Caisses, non en métal; Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne Poubelles, Récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine, Récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine, Bocal, Paniers, à usage domestique, Récipients pour la cuisine, dessous de verre autres qu'en papier ou en tissu, Corbeilles à papier, Tirelires, Tirelires, Trousses de toilette, Distributeurs de papier hygiéniques, Distributeurs de papier hygiénique, Brosses pour laver la vaisselle, Fixations pour brosses à vaisselle, Extracteurs [équipements de nettoyage], Boîtes à pain; Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne Corbeilles à pain à usage ménager, Porte-éponges, Boîtes à savons, Porte-savons, Porte-savon, Distributeurs de savons, Brosses pour laver la vaisselle, Supports pour sachets de thé, Séchoirs, Poubelles pour langes, Balais, Planches à repasser, Beurriers, Coquetiers, Seilles, Carafes, Batteries de cuisine, Ustensiles de cuisson, Ustensiles de cuisine, Sets de table, ni en papier ni en matières textiles; Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne Ronds de table, ni en papier ni en matières textiles, Gobelets en papier ou en plastique, Articles en porcelaine, Seaux pour l'essorage de balais à franges, Bols, Planches à découper pour la cuisine, Cornes à chaussures, Chausse-pieds, Formes (embauchoirs) pour souliers, Bols, Porte-serviettes, Lavettes, Lingettes pour épousseter, Plateaux à usage domestique, Plateaux à usage domestique, en papier, Les arts de la table, Gourdes (à porter à la taille), Tasses, Boîtes à thé, Boules à thé, Théières; Services de vente en gros et au détail, Services de vente par correspondance, y compris sur Internet, en ce qui concerne Couvre-théières, Couvre-théières, Services à thé, passoires à thé, Assiettes, Planches à laver, Cuviers, Essoreuses de balais à franges, Dispositifs pour presser les tubes de dentifrice, Sucriers, Présentation de marchandises et de services dans le marché de gros, les supermarchés, les magasins de détail, les grands magasins et les boutiques en ligne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Kuke (metalne kuke vješalica za kapute), Škrinje, Metalne kutije, Odjeća (metalne vješalice za odjeću), Košarice (metalne košarice), Kuke [željezna metalna roba], Pisma (metalni sandučići za pisma), Kutije od običnih metala; Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Papirnati proizvodi, Vrećice za smeće od papira ili plastike, Mape za spise, Fascikli [papirnati proizvodi], Košare za pisma, Spremnici od papira za spremanje, Spremnici za pohranu od kartona, Nastavci za olovke, Predmeti koji se stave na papir da ne odleti sa stola, Uredski pribor [osim namještaja], Stalci za pera i olovke, Pločice s hvataljkom za listove papira [uredski pribor], Slike, Blokovi [papirnati proizvodi], Knjižice, Uredske spajalice; Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Kvačice za držače za značke [uredski pribor], Spisi (držači spisa) [uredski pribor], Držači za značke [uredski pribor], Omotnice [papirnati proizvodi], Kalendari, Oznake za knjige, Bušilice za uredske potrebe, Markeri [pisaći pribor], Bedževi s imenima [uredske potrepštine], Bilježnice, Kvačice za papire, Gumice za brisanje, Oprema za pisanje, Pribor za pisanje, Podloge za radne stolove; Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Ormarići za papir i uredski pribor; Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Kutije, drvene ili plastične, Kuke za stalke za odjeću, ne od metala, Zidne vješalice [kuke] za odjeću, ne od metala, Košare, ne od metala, Sanduci za igračke, Pregrade za ladice, Plastični spremnici za pohranu, Tekstilne kutije, Metalne kuke za odjeću za postavljanje na vrata, Ladice, Vodilice za ladice, Kutije za odlaganje [namještaj]; Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Spremnici, ne od metala, Za potrebe pohrane, Kuke za šipke za vješanje odjeće, Vješalice za odjeću, Stalci za odjeću [pokućstvo] i kuke za vješanje odjeće, Ormar s ladicama, Sklopive kutije, ne od metala, Plastične kutije za odlaganje koje se slažu jedne na druge, Natpisi firmi na drvu ili plastici, Ploče za vješanje ključeva, Kolica [pokućstvo]; Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Sudoperi (prostirači za sudopere), Stalci za časopise, Novine (stalci za izlaganje novina), Ormara, Pisaći stolovi, Škrinje, Kutije, ne od metala; Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Kante za smeće, Kućanske ili kuhinjske posude, Posude za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju, Kutije, staklene, Košarice za kućanstvo, Kuhinjske posude, Podmetači za čaše osim od papira ili tkanine, Košarice za otpatke, Štedne tikvice, nemetalne, Štedne kasice, Toaletni neseseri, Higijenski papir (držači smotaka higijenskog papira), Držači higijenskog papira [napravice], Četke za pranje posuđa, Držači za četke za pranje, Čistači stakla [uređaji za čišćenje], Kutije z kruh; Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Košare za kruh za uporabu u kućanstvu, Dršci spužvi, Kutije za sapun, Posudica za sapun, Posude za sapun, Držači sapuna [napravice za izdavanje sapuna], Četke za pranje posuđa, Držači za vrećice za čaj, Sušila, Kante za zbrinjavanje pelena, Metle, Daske za glačanje rublja, Maslac (posudice za maslac), Čašice za jaja, Vedra [drvene posude], Boce širokog dna i uskog grla, Kompleti kuhinjskih lonaca, Pribor za kuhanje, Kuhinjsko posuđe, Podmetačima (setovima) za jelo koji nisu od papira ili tkanine; Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Podmetači za stolove, osim od papira i tekstila, Čaše, papirnate ili plastične, Porculanski proizvodi, Kante s ocjeđivačem za resaste metle, Plitice [zdjelice], Daske za rezanje [kuhinjski pribor], Žlice za obuvanje, Žlice za obuvanje, Napinjači za cipele, Zdjelice plitkog dna, Stalci za ubruse, Krpe za posuđe, Prašina [krpe za brisanje prašine], Polsužavnici za kućanstvo, Poslužavnici od papira za kućanstvo, Posuđe, Ploske, Šalice, Kutije za čaj, Jaja za kuhanje čaja, Čajnici; Veleprodajne i maloprodajne usluge, Prodaja putem pošte, uključujući putem Interneta, u pogledu: Navlake za čajnike, Navlake za čajnike, Čaj [servisi za čaj], Filtri za čaj, Tanjuri, Daske za pranje, Lužnice [posude za pranje rublja], Ocjeđivači za resaste metle, Istiskivači zubne paste iz tube, Šećer (posudice za šećer), Prezentacija proizvoda i usluga u veleprodajnim trgovinama, supermarketima, maloprodajnim trgovinama, trgovačkim kućama i online trgovinama.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Fémakasztók ruhafogasokhoz, Ládák, Fémdobozok, Ruhaakasztók fémből, Fémkosarak, Kampók [fém tömegcikkek], Leveles ládák fémből, Dobozok fémből; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Papíráru, Szemeteszsákok (papírból vagy műanyagból), Iratgyűjtők, dossziék, Dossziék [papíráruk], Irattartó tálcák, Papír tárolóedények, Kartondobozos tárolódobozok, Ceruzatoldók, ceruzahosszabbítók, Papírnyomók, Irodai kellékek (a bútorokon kívül), Toll- és ceruzatartók, Csipeszes írótáblák, Képek, Blokkok [papíráruk], Könyvecskék, füzetek, Iratkapcsok, iratfűzők; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Jelvénytartó csipeszek [irodai cikkek], Irattartók, Jelvénytartó [irodai cikkek], Tasakok [papír- írószer], Naptárak, Könyvjelzők, Lyukasztók (irodai cikkek), Szövegkiemelők[filctollak], Névkitűzők [irodai felszerelések], Noteszek, jegyzetfüzetek, Jegyzetkapcsok [papíráru], Radírgumik, Íróeszközök, Írószerek, Könyöklők; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Munkapadok [irodai kellékek]; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Dobozok fából vagy műanyagból, Fogasok (bútorok), nem fémből, Ruhaakasztók [kampók], nem fémből, Kosarak, nem fémből, Dobozok játékokhoz, Elválasztók fiókokhoz, Tárolódobozok műanyagból, Szövet dobozok, Fém fogaskampók ajtókhoz, Fiókok, Fiókcsúszkák, Tárolóládák [bútorok]; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Tárolóedények, nem fémből, Tárolási célokra, Akasztókampók ruhatartó rudakhoz, Vállfák, Ruhaállványok [bútorok] és ruhafogasok, Fiókos szekrények, Összehajtható dobozok, nem fémből, Tapadó tároló dobozok műanyagból, Cégtáblák, cégérek fából vagy műanyagból, Kulcstartó táblák, Kézikocsik [bútorzat]; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Lefolyókhoz eltávolítható burkolatok, Folyóirattartók, Újságtartó állványok, Szekrények, Íróasztalok, Ládák, Tokok, nem fémből; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Szemetesládák, szemetesedények, Háztartási vagy konyhai tartók, Tartályok háztartási vagy konyhai célokra, Üveg tárolóedények, Házi használatú kosáráru, Konyhai tartályok/tárolók, Nem papírból vagy textilből készült poháralátétek, Levélkosarak, Pénzes kazetta, Malacperselyek, Neszesszerek, Egészségügyipapír-tartók, vécépapírtartók, Vécépapírtartók, Edénymosó kefék, Edénymosó kefékhez való tartók, Lehúzók [tisztítóeszközök], Dagasztóteknők; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Kenyérkosarak, háztartási célokra, Szivacstartók, Szappandobozok, Szappantartók, Szappantartók, Szappanadagolók, Edénymosó kefék, Teafilter-tartók, Ruhaszárítók, Pelenka eltakarítására való szemetesládák, Seprűk, Vasalódeszkák, Vajtartók, Tojástartók, Vödrök, Üvegkancsók, Konyhai edénykészletek, Főzőedények, Konyhai cikkek, Tányéralátétek, nem papírból vagy textilből; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Asztali alátétek, nem papírból vagy textilből, Poharak papírból vagy műanyagból, Porcelán árucikkek, Felmosófej-kifacsarós vödrök, Tálak, Konyhai vágódeszkák, Cipőkanalak, Cipőkanál, Sámfák, Tálak, öblös edények, Szalvétatartók, Edénytörlő ruhák, Porrongyok, Tálcák otthoni használatra, Tálcák papírból, háztartási használatra, Asztaldíszek, Laposüvegek, Csészék, Teásdobozok, Teafőző tojások, Teáskannák; Nagy- és kiskereskedelmi szolgáltatások, Posta rendelési szolgáltatások, beleértve az interneten keresztül, a Teababák (melegítők), Teababák (melegítők), Teáskészletek [terítékek], Teaszűrők, Tányérok, Mosódeszkák, Lúgozókádak, Mop-facsarók, Fogkrémestubus-nyomók, Cukortartók, Árubemutatók és szolgáltatások nagypiacokon, szupermarketekben, kiskereskedelmi üzletekben, áruházakban és online shopokban.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Vendita all'ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda Ganci per attaccapanni [in metallo], Casse, Cassette metalliche, Patere [ganci] per abbigliamento [in metallo], Ceste metalliche, Uncini [chincaglieria in metallo], Cassette per lettere in metallo, Scatole in metalli comuni; Vendita all’ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda Articoli di carta, Sacchi per la spazzatura (di carta o di materie plastiche), Cartelle per documenti, Raccoglitori, Cestini per corrispondenza, Contenitori di carta, Contenitori da deposito di cartone, Portamatite, Di fermacarte, Articoli per ufficio (esclusi i mobili), Sostegni per penne e matite, Tavolette a pinza [articoli per l'ufficio], Illustrazioni, Blocchi [cartoleria], Libretti, Fermagli per ufficio; Vendita all’ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda clips per porta badge [articoli per ufficio], Cartelle per documenti, porta badge [articoli per ufficio], Buste [cartoleria], Calendari, Segnalibri, Fustelle [articoli per ufficio], Evidenziatori [cartoleria], Distintivi recanti il nome [articoli per ufficio], Blocchi per appunti, Punti da ufficio, Gomma per cancellare, Strumenti per scrivere, Strumenti per scrivere a mano, Tappetini da scrivania; Vendita all’ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda Contenitori per cancelleria; Vendita all’ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda Scatole di plastica o legno, Ganci d'attaccapanni, non in metallo, Patere [ganci] per abbigliamento, non in metallo, Cestini, non in metallo, Ceste per i giocattoli, Divisori per cassetti, Recipienti in plastica per riporre oggetti, Scatole in tessuto, Ganci per attaccapanni in metallo per l'applicazione a porte, Cassetti, Guide di scorrimento per cassetti, Scatole per conservare oggetti [mobili]; Vendita all’ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda Serbatoi, non in metallo, Per scopi di deposito, Ganci per aste attaccapanni, Portabiti, Attaccapanni a stelo (mobili) e grucce per indumenti, Cassettiera, Scatole pieghevoli, non in metallo, Vaschette di plastica impilabili, Insegne in legno o materie plastiche, Pannelli appendi-chiavi, carrelli [mobili]; Vendita all’ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda Rivestimenti amovibili per acquai, Portariviste, Espositori per giornali, Armadietti, Scrivanie, Casse, Casse, non in metallo; Vendita all’ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda Bidoni, Recipienti per la casa o la cucina, Recipienti per la casa o per la cucina, Scatole di vetro, Ceste per uso domestico, Contenitori da cucina, Sottobicchieri non di carta o materie tessili, Cestini per la carta straccia, Salvadanai, Salvadanai, Necessaire per la toilette, Distributori di carta igienica, Distributori di carta igienica, spazzole per lavare le stoviglie, Supporti per spazzole per stoviglie, Estrattori [apparecchi per la pulizia], Cassette portapane; Vendita all’ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda cestini per il pane per uso domestico, Portaspugne, Scatole per sapone, Porta-sapone, Piattini portasapone, Distributori di sapone, spazzole per lavare le stoviglie, Porta-bustine da tè, Stendibiancheria, Pattumiere per pannolini, Scope, Assi da stiro, Burriere, Portauova, Secchi, Caraffe, Batterie da cucina, utensili per la cottura, Utensili da cucina, Tovagliette (set), non di carta o di tessuto; Vendita all’ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda Centrini per tavoli, non di carta o di tessuto, Bicchieri di carta o di plastica, Articoli in porcellana, Secchi per sciacquare scope frangiate, Ciotole, Assi per tagliare per la cucina, Corni per scarpe, Calzascarpe, Forme (gambali) per scarpe, Vasche di lavello, Porta-tovaglioli, Strofinacci per lavare i piatti, Strofinacci per spolverare, Vassoi per uso domestico, Vassoi per uso domestico, in carta, Dell'arte della tavola, Fiaschette da tasca, Tazze, Scatole di tè, Boccette per infusi di tè, Teiere; Vendita all’ingrosso e al dettaglio, Servizi di vendita per corrispondenza, anche su Internet, per quanto riguarda Copriteiere, Copriteiere, Servizi da tè, Colini per il tè, piatti, Asse per lavare, Tinozza per bucato, Strizzatore per spazzoloni, Spremitori di tubetti di dentifricio, Zuccheriere, Presentazione di merci e servizi in mercati all'ingrosso, supermercati, negozi di vendita al dettaglio, grandi magazzini e negozi on-line.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Metaliniai drabužių pakabų kabliai, Dėklais, Metlainės dėžės, Drabužių kabliukai (metaliniai --- ), Metaliniai kaušai, Kabliukai [metalo gaminiai], Metalinėmis laiškų dėžutėmis, Dėžutės (Paprastųjų metalų -); Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Popieriaus prekės, Maišai (plastikiniai arba popieriniai šiukšlių --- ), Segtuvai (popieriaus --- ), Dokumentų segtuvai [raštinės reikmenys], Laiškų padėklai, Popierinė tara, Kartoninė tara, Pieštukų koteliai, Prespapjė, Biuro reikmenys (ne tik baldai), Stoveliai (Plunksnakočių ir pieštukų -), Rašomosios lentelės su spaustuku, Paveikslai, Bloknotai [raštinės reikmenys], Bukletai, Sąvaržėlės (raštinės reikmenys); Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Vardinių kortelių laikiklių segtukai (raštinės reikmenys), Dėžutės dokumentams, Vardinių kortelių laikikliai (raštinės reikmenys), Vokai [raštinės reikmenys], Kalendoriai, Knygos žymekliai, Skylmušos (raštinės reikmenys), Žymikliai [raštinės reikmenys], Identifikacinės kortelės (biuro reikmenys), Užrašų knygutės, Popieriaus sąvaržėlės, Guminiai trintukai, Rašikliai, Rašomųjų reikmenų rinkiniai [raštinės reikmenys], Rašomojo stalo kilimėliai; Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Darbo stalo raštinės reikmenų dėklai; Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Medinių arba plastikinių dėžių, Rūbinių kabliukai, ne metalo, Drabužių kabinimo įtaisai [kabliukai], ne metalo, Pintinės, ne metalo, Žaislų dėžės, Pertvaros stalčiams, Plastikinės sandėliavimo dėžės, Medžiaginėmis dėžėmis, Metaliniai drabužinių kabliukai, tvirtinami prie durų, Rakinamosios spintelės, Slankiaisiais stalčiaus mechanizmais, Saugojimo dėžės [baldai]; Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Tara, ne metalo, Laikymo reikmėms, Drabužių pakabų kabliai, Drabužių pakabos, Drabužių kabyklos [baldai] ir drabužių pakabos, Komodos, Sulankstomomis dėžėmis, ne metalo, Plastikinės sandėlių dėžės, kraunamos viena ant kitos, Iškabos (medžio ar plastikinės --- ), Raktų kabinimo lentos, Vežimėlių [baldų]; Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Įdėklai (Išimamieji plautuvių -), Žurnalų padėklai, Laikraščių stendai, Spintos, Rašomieji stalai, Dėklais, Dėžės, ne metalo; Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Atliekų dėžės, Buitinės arba virtuvinės talpyklos, Buitinė arba virtuvinė tara, Stiklinės dėžutės, Krepšeliai namų reikmėms, Virtuvės indai, Stiklinių padėkliukai, išskyrus popierinius arba tekstilinius, Popierinių šiukšlių krepšiai, Pinigų dėžutės, Kiaulės taupyklės, Tualeto reikmeninės, Tualetinio popieriaus laikikliai, Laikikliai (tualetinio popieriaus --- ), Indų plovimo šepečiai, Plovimo šepečių laikikliai, Valytuvai su gumos sluoksniu [valymo reikmenys], Duoninės; Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Duonos krepšeliai (buities reikmėms), Kempinių laikikliai, Dėžutės (muilo --- ), Muilinės padėklai, Muilinės, Muilo dalytuvai, Indų plovimo šepečiai, Arbatos maišelių laikikliai, Skalbinių džiovyklos, Sauskelnių utilizavimo kibirai, Šluotos, Lyginimo lentos, Sviestinės, Kiaušinių indeliai, Kibirai, Ropinės (grafinai), Virimo puodų komplektai, Valgio virimo reikmenimis, Virtuvės rakandai, Padėkliukais (rinkiniais) ne iš popieriaus ar audinio; Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Ne popieriniais ir ne tekstiliniais stalo užtiesalais, Popieriaus ar plastiko puodeliai, Porceliano dirbiniai, Kibirai su nugręžimo mechanizmu ir šepečiu, Dubenys, Virtuvinės pjaustymo lentelės, Batų liežuvėliai, Batų šaukštai, Kurpaliai, Dubenys, Servetėlių laikikliai, Šluostėmis, Dulkių šluostukai, Padėklai namų reikmėms, Popieriniai padėklai buities reikmėms, Stalo serviravimo reikmenys, Juosmens gertuvės, Puodeliai, Arbatos dėžutės, Arbatos plikytuvai, Arbatinukai; Didmeninės prekybos ir mažmeninės prekybos paslaugos, Prekyba paštu, įskaitant internetą, susijusius su: Arbatinukų apdangalai, Arbatinukų apdangalais, Arbatos servizai [valgomieji reikmenys], Arbatos sietelių, Lėkštės, Skalbimo lentos [rintės], Skalbimo geldos (vonelės), Grindų šluosčių gręžtuvai, Dantų pastos spaustukais, Cukrinės (ne brangiųjų metalų), Prekių ir paslaugų pristatymas didmeninės prekybos parduotuvėse, prekybos centruose, mažmeninės prekybos parduotuvėse, universalinėse parduotuvėse ir internetinėse parduotuvėse.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Drēbju pakaramo āķi no metāla, Korpusi, Kastes no metāla, Metāla drēbju pakaramie, Metāla grozi, Āķi (nelieli metāla izstrādājumi), Metāla pastkastes, Kastes no parastajiem metāliem; Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Papīra preces, Atkritumu maisi (no papīra vai plastikāta), Dokumentu mapes, Dokumentu mapes [kancelejas preces], Vēstuļu grozi, Papīra glabāšanas tilpnes, Uzglabāšanas tilpnes no kartona kārbām, Zīmuļu penāļi, Presēšana, Kancelejas preces (izņemot mēbeles), Statīvi pildspalvām un zīmuļiem, Planšetes, Attēli, Bloknoti [kancelejas preces], Bukleti, Papīra spraudes; Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Skavas nozīmīšu turekļiem [biroja rekvizīti], Dokumentu mapes, Nozīmīšu turētāji [biroja rekvizīti], Aploksnes [rakstāmpiederumi], Kalendāri, Grāmatzīmes, Caurumsitēji (biroja rekvizīti), Marķieri [kancelejas preces], Žetoni ar vārdu (biroja piederumi), Piezīmju grāmatiņas, Papīra saspraudes, Dzēšgumijas, Rakstīšanas instrumenti, Rakstāmlietas, Galda paliktņi; Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Uz darbvirsmas novietojamas kancelejas piederumu kastītes (biroja piederumi); Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Koka vai plastmasas kastes, Drēbju pakaramo āķi, nav no metāla, Āķi apģērbu pakāršanai, nav no metāla, Grozi, nav no metāla, Rotaļlietu kastes, Atvilkņu sadalītāji, Glabāšanas tvertnes no plastmasas, Kastes no auduma, Drēbju pakaramo āķi no metāla piestiprināšanai pie durvīm, Atvilktnes, Atvilktņu vadotnes, Uzglabāšanas kastes [mēbeles]; Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Trauki, nav no metāla, Uzglabāšanas nolūkiem, Āķi drēbju pakaramajiem, Mēteļu pakaramie [mēbeles], Apģērbu statīvi [mēbeles] un apģērbu pakaramie, Atvilktņu skapis, Salokāmas kastes, nav no metāla, Krautņojamas arhīva kārbas no plastmasas, Izkārtnes no koka vai plastmasas, Atslēgu pakaramie, Ratiņi [mēbeles]; Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Izlietņu maināmi paliktņi, Žurnālu plaukti, Žurnālu plaukti, Skapji, Rakstāmgaldi, Korpusi, Kastes, kārbas, nav no metāla; Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Atkritumu spaiņi, Ietvari izmantošanai mājsaimniecībā vai virtuvē, Tilpnes mājturības vai virtuves vajadzībām, Stikla trauki, Grozi mājsaimniecības vajadzībām, Virtuves konteineri, Glāžu paliktņi, kas nav no papīra vai no auduma, Papīrgrozi, Krājkasītes, Krājkasītes, Tualetes maciņi, Tualetes papīra turētāji, Tualetes papīra turētāji, Trauku birstes, Trauku mazgājamo birstu turētāji, Ekstraktori [tīrīšanas ierīces], Maizes kastes; Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Maizes groziņi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem, Sūkļu turētāji, Ziepju kastes, Ziepju turētāji, Ziepju trauki, Ziepju dozatori, Trauku birstes, Tējas maisiņu paliktņi, Veļas stendi, Atkritumu spaiņi izlietotajiem autiņiem, Slotas, Gludināmie dēļi, Sviesta trauki, Olu trauciņi, Spaiņi, Karafes, Katlu komplekti, Ugunsizturīgi trauki, Virtuves piederumi, Galda paliktņi, kas nav no papīra vai auduma (komplekti); Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Galda sedziņas, kas nav no papīra vai auduma, Papīra vai plastmasas tasītes, Porcelāns, Virvju slotu spaiņi, Bļodas, Virtuves dēļi, paredzēti griezšanai, Kurpju lāpstiņas, Apavu lāpstiņas, Kurpju statīvi, Bļodas, Mazo salvešu turētāji, Trauku lupatas, Auduma putekļu lupatas, Mājsaimniecībā izmantojamas paplātes, Papīra paplātes mājsaimniecības vajadzībām, Rokdarbi, Plakanpudeles, Kausi, Tējas kārbas, Tējas stipruma kanniņas, Tējkannas; Vairumtirdzniecības un mazumtirdzniecības pakalpojumi, Pasta pasūtījumu pārdošana, tostarp internetā attiecībā uz Tējkannu sildītāji, Tējkannu sildītāji, Tējas servīzes [galda piederumi], Tējas sietiņi, Trauki, Veļas dēļi, Veļas bļoda, Ierīce sukas izgriešanai, Zobu pastas tūbiņu saspiedējs, Cukurtrauki, Preču un pakalpojumu prezentēšana lielajos tirgos, tirdzniecības centros, mazumtirdzniecības veikalos, preču namos un tiešsaistes veikalos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta' ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ' Ganċijiet tal-gwardarobbi tal-metall, Kaxxetti protettivi, Kaxex tal-metall, Ganċijiet tal-ħwejjeġ, Kontenituri tal-iskart magħmula mill-metall, Ganċijiet [oġġetti żgħar tal-metall], Kaxxi tal-ittri tal-metall, Kaxxi tal-metall komuni; Servizzi ta’ bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta’ ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ‘ Oġġetti tal-karti, Xkejjer ta' l-iskart tal-karti jew tal-metarjal sintetiku, Kaxex għad-dokumenti, Fajls tad-dokumenti [kartolerija], Trejs tal-ittri, Kontenituri tal-karti għall-ħażna, Kaxxi tal-ħżin tal-kartun, Kontenituri għall-lapsijiet, Paperweights, Oġġetti neċessarji għall-uffiċju (apparti l-għamara), Sostenn għall-pinen u għall-lapsijiet, Klippbord, Stampi, Folji tal-karti mehmużin flimkien [kartolerija], Kotba żgħar, Klipps ta' l-uffiċċju; Servizzi ta’ bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta’ ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ‘ Klips għal appoġġi tal-beġis [oġġetti għall-uffiċċju], Kaxex għad-dokumenti, Appoġġi tal-beġis [oġġetti għall-uffiċċju], Envelops [kartoleriji], Kalendarji, Sinjal ta' ktieb li jurik fejn trid tkompli taqra, Tnalji tat-titqib [oġġetti neċessarji għall-uffiċċju], Pinen li jimmarkaw [kartolerija], Beġis tal-ismijiet [rekwiżiti tal-uffiċċju], Takkwini, Klipps tal-karti, Gomom għat-tħassir, Għodod għall-kitba, Kaxxi tal-istrumenti tal-kitba, Matt għall-iskrivanija; Servizzi ta’ bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta’ ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ‘ Bankijiet tax-xogħol għall-affarijiet ta' kartollerija [oġġetti neċessarji għall-uffiċċji]; Servizzi ta’ bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta’ ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ‘ Kaxxi tal-injam jew tal-plastik, Ganċijiet tal-gwardarobbi, mhux tal-metall, Ganċijiet tal-ħwejjeġ, mhux tal-metall, Basktijiet, mhux tal-metall, Kaxex tal-mużika tal-logħob, Diviżorji għall-kxaxen, Kaxxi tal-ħżin magħmula mill-plastik, Kaxxi tad-drapp, Ganċijiet għall-kowtijiet magħmula mill-metall għall-iffissar mal-bibien, Lockers, Kxaxen li jiżżerżqu, Kaxxi għall-ħżin [għamara]; Servizzi ta’ bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta’ ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ‘ Kontenituri, mhux tal-metall, Għal skopijiet ta' ħżin, Ganċijiet għar-rejls tal-ilbies, Spallieri tal-kowtijiet, Stend tal-ħwejjeġ [għamara] u spallieri, Armarji bil-kxaxen, Kaxxi jintwew, mhux tal-metall, Kaxxi tal-plastik għall-ħżin li jistgħu jiġu stivati fuq xulxin, Tabelli ta' l-injam jew sintetiċi, Plakka mal-ħajt li fuqha jiddendlu iċ-ċwievet, Trolis [għamara]; Servizzi ta’ bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta’ ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ‘ Mattijiet, li jitneħħew, b'tappijiet porużi għas-sinkijiet, Xtillieri tal-magazins, Xtilliera għall-magażinijiet, Armarji, Skrivaniji għall-kitba, Kaxxetti protettivi, Kaxex, mhux tal-metall; Servizzi ta’ bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta’ ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ‘ Qfief tal-karti ħżiena, Kontenituri għall-użu domestiku jew għall-kċina, Reċipjenti għal użu domestiku jew għal użu fil-kċina, Reċipjent tal-ħġieġ, Qfief għall-użu domestiku, Kontenituri tal-kċina, Mattijiet tat-tazzi minbarra tal-karti jew tat-tessuti, Trejs ta' l-ittri, Karusijiet, PIGGY BANKS, Kaxxi fejn jitpoġġew l-oġġetti tat-twaletta, Kontenituri għaż-żamm tat-toilet paper, Kontenituri għaż-żamm tat-toilet paper, Xkupilji għall-ħasil tal-platti, Ħowlders għal xkupilji għall-ħasil tal-platti, Estratturi [tagħmir tat-tindif], Laned tal-ħobż; Servizzi ta’ bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta’ ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ‘ Basktijiet għall-ħobż għal skopijiet domestiċi, Sostenn ta' l-isponoż, Sapunieri, Kontenitur għaż-żamm tas-sapun, Reċipjenti għas-sapun, Dispenser tas-sapun, Xkupilji għall-ħasil tal-platti, Strumenti għall-appoġġ ta' boroż tat-te, Aċċessorji għad-dendil tal-ħwejjeġ għall-ħasil, Bramel għar-rimi ta' ħrieqi, Xkupi, Twavel tal-mogħdija, Butirieri, Ovieri, Bramel, Fliexken tal-kristall għax-xorb, Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir, Għodda għall-ħami, Għodod tal-kċina, Sottoplatti, mhux tal-karta jew tat-tessuti; Servizzi ta’ bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta’ ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ‘ Matts ta' fuq il-mejda, mhux tal-karta jew tat-tessut, Tazzi tal-kari jew tal-plastik, Oġġetti magħmula mill-porċellana, Bramel li jinkludu apparat li jagħsar il-mopp, Bowels, Twavel għat-tqattigħ għall-kċina, Alzaturi taż-żraben, Għadma taż-żraben, Forma li żżomm id-dehra taż-żarbun, Bwieqi, Tagħmir li jżomm is-srievet, Paljazzi, Ċraret tat-tfarfir, Trejs għall-użu domestiku, Trejs tal-karti għal skopijiet domestiċi, L-arti tal-armar tal-mejda, Fliexken ta' mal-qadd, Kikkri, Kaxxi tat-te, Infużorji tat-te, Tipottijiet; Servizzi ta’ bejgħ bl-ingrossa u bl-imnut, Bejgħ permezz ta’ ordni bil-posta, inkluż fuq l-Internet, fir-rigward ta ‘ Tagħmir li jgħatti t-tettiera, Għata għat-tettieri, Servizzi tat-tè [oġġetti tal-mejda], Passatur għat-te, Dixxijiet, Twavel tal-injam għal-ħasil, Banjijiet tal-ħasil, Bramel b'apparat għat-tagħsir tal-moppijiet, Tagħmir għall-għafis tat-tubi tad-dentifriċi, Kaxxi taz-zokkor, Preżentazzjoni ta' l-affarijiet u servizzi fi swieq kbar, supermarkits, ħwienet tal-bejgħ bl-imnut, ħwienet tal-bejgħ bil-grossa. ħwienet kbar li jbiegħu kollox u ħwienet online.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Kapstokhaken van metaal, Behuizingen, Kisten van metaal, Kleerhaken van metaal, Manden van metaal, Haken van metaal, Brievenbussen van metaal, Dozen van onedele metalen; Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Producten van papier, Vuilniszakken (van papier of plastic), Map voor papieren, Dossiers [kantoorbehoeften], Brievenmandjes, Opslaghouders van papier, Opslagdozen van karton, Potloodhouders, Presse-papiers, Kantoorartikelen (uitgezonderd meubelen), Houders voor pennen en potloden, Klemborden [kantoorartikelen], Prenten, Blocnotes, Boekjes, Nietjes voor kantoordoeleinden; Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Clips voor badgehouders [kantoorartikelen], Archiefzakken, Badgehouders [kantoorartikelen], Enveloppen [kantoorartikelen], Kalenders, Bladwijzers, Ponsmachines (kantoorartikelen), Markeerpennen [kantoorbehoeften], Naamkaartjes en -speldjes [kantoorbenodigdheden], Notitieboekjes, Paperclips, Gommen, Schrijfinstrumenten, Schrijfbehoeften, Bureauleggers; Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Kastjes voor werktafels [kantoorartikelen]; Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Dozen van hout of plastic, Kapstokhaken, niet van metaal, Kleerhaken, niet van metaal, Manden, niet van metaal, Kisten voor speelgoed, Indelers voor laden, Opbergcontainers van kunststof, Boxen van textiel, Kapstokhaken van metaal voor bevestiging aan deuren, Laden, Glij-inrichtingen voor laden, Opbergkisten [meubelen]; Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Containers, niet van metaal, Voor opbergdoeleinden, Kapstokhaken, Klerenhangers, Kledingrekken [meubelen] en kleerhaken, Ladenkast, Vouwbare boxen, niet van metaal, Stapelbakken van plastic, Uithangborden van hout of plastic, Sleutelophangborden, Wagentjes [meubilair]; Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Afneembare bekledingen voor gootstenen, Tijdschriftenstandaards, Krantenstandaards, Salonkastjes, Secrétaires, Behuizingen, Kratten, niet van metaal; Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Bakken, Houders voor de huishouding of de keuken, Houders voor de huishouding of de keuken, Bakjes van glas, Manden voor de huishouding, Keukenvaatwerk, Onderzetters, niet van papier of van textiel, Prullenmanden, Spaarpotten, Spaarpotten, Toiletnecessaires, Afgifteapparaten voor toiletpapier, Toiletpapierdispensers, Afwasborstels, Houders voor afwasborstels, Trekkers [reinigingsinstrumenten], Broodkasten; Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Broodmanden voor huishoudelijk gebruik, Sponzebakjes, Zeepdozen, Zeepbakjes, Zeepbakjes, Zeepafgifte-apparaten, Afwasborstels, Steunen voor theezakjes, Wasmolens, Afvalemmers voor luiers, Bezems, Strijkplanken, Botervlootjes, Eierdopjes, Tobbes, Karaffen, Keukengerei (potten en pannen), Bakgerei, Keukengerei, Placemats, niet van papier of textiel; Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Tafelmatjes, niet van papier of textiel, Kopjes van papier of plastic, Artikelen van porselein, Emmers voor het uitwringen van stokdweilen, Schalen, Snijplanken voor keukengebruik, Schoenlepels, Schoenlepels, Schoenspanners, Kommen, Servethouders, Keukendoekjes voor de vaat, Stofdoeken, Dienbladen voor huishoudelijk gebruik, Dienbladen van papier, voorhuishoudelijk gebruik, Tafelgerei, Heupflessen, Kopjes, Theeblikken, Thee-eieren, Theepotten; Groot- en detailhandel, Postorderdiensten, inclusief via internet, met betrekking tot Theemutsen, Theemutsen, Theeserviezen, Theezeefjes, Borden, Wasborden, Waskuipen, Wringers voor zwabbers, Tandpastapersers, Suikerpotten, Presentatie van goederen en diensten in groothandels, supermarkten, detailhandelszaken, warenhuizen en on-lineshops.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Haki metalowe do drążków do wieszania odzieży, Obudowy, Skrzynie metalowe, Haki metalowe do wieszania odzieży, Kosze metalowe, Haki metalowe, Skrzynki na listy metalowe, Pudełka z metali nieszlachetnych; Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Artykuły papierowe, Torby na śmieci (z papieru lub z tworzyw sztucznych), Teczki na papiery, Segregatory na dokumenty (artykuły biurowe), Kosze na listy, Pojemniki do przechowywania wykonane z papieru, Pojemniki do przechowywania wykonane z kartonu, Ołówki (oprawy do -), Przyciski do papieru, Sprzęt biurowy (inny niż meble), Podstawki do długopisów i ołówków, Notesy podręczne, Obrazy, Bloki listowe [papeteria], Broszury, Spinacze biurowe; Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Klipsów do identyfikatorów [artykuły biurowe], Skoroszyty na dokumenty, Etui na identyfikatory [artykuły biurowe], Koperty [artykuły piśmienne], Kalendarze, Zakładki do książek, Dziurkacze [artykuły biurowe], Flamastry, Identyfikatory [artykuły biurowe], Notesy, Spinacze do papieru, Gumki do ścierania, Przyrządy do pisania, przybory do pisania, Podkłady na biurko; Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Pojemniki i szafki biurkowe na artykuły papiernicze i biurowe; Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Kasety drewniane lub z tworzyw sztucznych, Wieszaki na ubrania, nie z metalu, Haki metalowe do wieszania ubrań, nie z metalu, Kosze, nie z metalu, Skrzynki na zabawki, Przegródki do szuflad, Pojemniki na rzeczy z tworzyw sztucznych, do przechowywania, Pudła materiałowe, Haki do wieszania ubrań z metalu do mocowania na drzwiach, Szuflady, Prowadnice do szuflad, Pudełka do przechowywania (meble); Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Pojemniki, nie z metalu, Do celów przechowywania, Haczyki do wieszaków na ubrania, Wieszaki na płaszcze, Stojaki na odzież [meble] i wieszaki na ubrania, Szafki z szufladami, Składane pudła, nie z metalu, Skrzynki do ustawiania na sobie z tworzywa sztucznego, Szyldy z drewna lub tworzyw sztucznych, Klucze (tablice do zawieszania -), Wózków [meble]; Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Maty wyjmowane do zlewów, Stojaki na czasopisma, Gazety (stojaki do wystawiania -), Spiżarki, Biurka, Obudowy, Skrzynie kratowe, nie z metalu; Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Odpadki (kosze na -), Pojemniki do użytku w domu lub w kuchni, Pojemniki do użytku w gospodarstwie domowym, Pojemniki ze szkła, Koszyki do użytku domowego, Pojemniki kuchenne, Podstawki pod szklanki, inne niż z papieru lub z tkaniny, Listy (kosze na -), Skarbonki, Świnki skarbonki, Kosmetyczki, Papier toaletowy (dozowniki -), Dozowniki papieru toaletowego, Szczotki do mycia naczyń, Uchwyty do szczotek do mycia zębów, Szczypce płaskie [narzędzia do czyszczenia], Pojemniki na chleb; Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Koszy na chleb do użytku domowego, Uchwyty do gąbek, Mydelniczki, Mydelniczki, Mydło (naczynia na -), Mydło (dozowniki -), Szczotki do mycia naczyń, Podstawki na herbatę w torebkach, Suszarki, Kosze na zużyte pieluchy, Miotły, Deski do prasowania, Maselniczki, Kieliszki do jajek, Cebrzyki, Karafki, Garnki kuchenne [komplety], Przybory do gotowania, Sprzęt kuchenny, Mat na stół, nie z papieru ani materiałów tekstylnych; Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Podkładki na stół, nie z papieru ani materiałów tekstylnych, Kubki z papieru lub z tworzyw sztucznych, Wyroby z porcelany, Wiadra z wyciskarkami do mopów, Donice, Deski do krojenia do kuchni, Łyżki do butów, Łyżka do butów, Prawidła do butów, Miseczki, Serwetkownice, Szmatki do zmywania naczyń, Ściereczki do wycierania kurzu, Tace do użytku w gospodarstwie domowym, Tace do użytku domowego, papierowe, Zastawa i elementy do dekoracji stołu, Manierki, Filiżanki, Puszki na herbatę, Sitka do zaparzania herbaty, Czajniczki do herbaty; Usługi handlu hurtowego i detalicznego, Sprzedaż wysyłkowa, w tym przez Internet, w odniesieniu do Ocieplacze na czajniczki do herbaty, Czajniczki do herbaty (ocieplacze na -), Serwisy do herbaty, Sitka do herbaty, Talerze, Deski pralnicze, Balie, Wyżymaczki do mopów, Przybory do wyciskania pasty do zębów z tubki, Cukiernice, Prezentacja towarów i usług w dużych sklepach, supermarketach, sklepach detalicznych, domach towarowych i sklepach internetowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Ganchos de cabides [metálicos], Caixas, Cofres metálicos, Cabides metálicos, Cestos metálicos, Ganchos [quinquilharia metálica], Caixas de correio metálicas, Caixas em metais comuns; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Artigos em papel, Sacos de lixo (em papel ou em matérias plásticas), Pastas desdobráveis para documentos, Arquivadores para escritório, Cestos para a correspondência, Recipientes de armazenamento em papel, Recipientes de armazenamento em cartão, Porta-lápis, De pisa-papéis, Artigos para escritório (com excepção dos móveis), Suportes para canetas e lápis, Pranchetas de pinça [artigos de escritório], Gravuras, Blocos [papelaria], Livretes [livrinhos], Agrafos para escritório; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Clips para porta-crachás [artigos de escritório], Capas para documentos, Porta-crachá [artigos de escritório], Sobrescritos [papelaria], Calendários, Marcas para livros, Saca-bocados [artigos de escritório], Marcadores [artigos de papelaria], Distintivos de identificação [artigos de escritório], Cadernos de apontamentos, Molas para papel, Borrachas para apagar, Instrumentos de escrita, Instrumentos de escrita, Marcadores de secretária; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Caixas de arrumação de secretária para papelaria [artigos de escritório]; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Caixas em madeira ou em plástico, Ganchos de bengaleiros, não em metal, Cabides para vestuário, não em metal, Cestos, não em metal, Caixas de jogos, Organizadores para gavetas, Caixas de arrumação em matérias plásticas, Caixas em tecido, Ganchos de bengaleiros em metal para aplicar em portas, Gavetas, Suportes para gavetas, Caixas de arrumação [mobiliário]; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Recipientes, não em metal, Para armazenamento, Ganchos para varões de cabides, Cruzetas para a roupa, Suportes [mobiliário] e cabides para roupa, Armário com gavetas, Caixas dobráveis, não em metal, Caixas com gavetas empilháveis em matérias plásticas, Sinalizadores em madeira ou em matérias plásticas, Quadros-chaveiros, Carrinhos [mobiliário]; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Revestimentos amovíveis para pias de despejo, Porta revistas, Expositores [escaparates] para jornais, Móveis com gavetas e prateleiras, Secretárias, Caixas, Caixas, não em metal; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Caixotes, Recipientes para uso doméstico ou para a cozinha, Recipientes para uso doméstico ou para a cozinha, Recipientes em vidro, Cestos para uso doméstico, Recipientes para a cozinha, Bases para copos, sem ser em papel ou em tecido, Cestos de papéis, Caixas para guardar dinheiro (mealheiros), Mealheiros, Estojos para artigos de toilette, Distribuidores de papel higiénico, Distribuidores de papel higiénico, Escovas para lavar a louça, Suportes para escovas para lavar louça, Rodos [instrumentos de limpeza], Caixas para o pão; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Cestos para pão para uso doméstico, Esponjeiras, Saboneteiras, Saboneteiras, Saboneteiras, Distribuidores de sabão, Escovas para lavar a louça, Recipientes para pousar as saquetas de chá usadas, Estendais de roupa, Baldes de fraldas, Vassouras, Tábuas de engomar, Manteigueiras, Oveiros, Selhas, Garrafas (de base larga), Trem de cozinha, Utensílios de cozinha, Louça de cozinha, Individuais de mesa, não sendo de papel ou têxtil (individuais); Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Toalhas de mesa, não sendo de papel ou têxtil, Chávenas em papel ou em plástico, Artigos em porcelana, Baldes com espremedor para esfregonas, Taças, Tábuas para trinchar para a cozinha, Calçadeiras para sapatos, Calçadeiras para calçado, Formas para sapatos, Bacias, Porta guardanapo, Panos de lavagem, Esfregões [panos] para limpeza de pó, Tabuleiros para uso doméstico, Bandejas de papel para uso doméstico, Da decoração da mesa, Frascos de trazer à cintura, Taças, Latas para chá, Bules para chá, Bules de chá; Serviços de venda por grosso e a retalho, Serviços de encomendas postais, inclusive pela Internet, em relação a Abafadores ("cosys") para chaleiras, Abafadores ("cosys") para chaleiras, Serviços de chá, Coadores para chá, Placas, Tábuas de lavar, Bacias para a roupa, Baldes com espremedores para esfregonas, Dispositivos para apertar tubos de pastas dentífricas, Açucareiros, Apresentação de produtos e serviços em hipermercados, supermercados, lojas, armazéns e lojas on-line.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Cuiere metalice pentru haine, Cutii, Lăzi metalice, Cârlige metalice pentru haine, Coşuri metalice, Cârlige [articole de feronerie], Cutii poştale din metal, Cutii din metale comune; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Produse din hârtie, Saci de gunoi (din hârtie sau din materiale plastice), Dosare de papetărie, Dosare [papetărie], Coşuri pentru corespondenţă, Recipiente din hârtie pentru depozitare, Recipiente de depozitare din carton, Creioane (suport de -), De prese de hârtie, Rechizite pentru birou [cu exceptia mobilierului], Suporturi pentru peniţe şi creioane, Planşete cu clamă pentru hârtii, Gravuri, Blocuri [papetărie], Carnete, Agrafe de birou; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Cleme pentru suporturi de legitimații [articole de birou], Mape pentru documente, Suporturi pentru legitimații [articole de birou], Plicuri [papetărie], Calendare, Semne de carte, Perforatoare [birotică], Stilouri de marcare [papetărie], Ecusoane pentru nume [articole de birou], Bloc notes, Cleme pentru hârtie, Radiere de sters, Instrumente de scris, Instrumente de scris, Suporturi pentru birou; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Suporturi cu sertare pentru articole de papetărie [birotică]; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Cutii din lemn sau din materiale plastice, Cârlige pentru şine de agăţat haine, nu din metal, Cuiere [cârlige] pentru îmbrăcăminte, nu din metal, Coşuri, nu din metal, Lăzi de jucării, Separatoare pentru sertare, Recipiente de depozitare din material sintetic, Cutii din stofă, Cuiere metalice pentru montare pe uși, Sertare, Elemente de culisare pentru sertare, Cutii de depozitare [mobilier]; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Hârdaie, nu din metal, Pentru depozitare, Cârlige pentru bare pentru umerașe, Centuri pentru îmbrăcăminte, Busturi pentru croitorie [mobilier] şi cuiere pentru îmbrăcăminte, Dulapuri cu sertare, Cutii pliabile, nu din metal, Lăzi de depozitare care pot fi stivuite, din material plastic, Tăbliţe din lemn sau plastic, Tablouri de agatat chei, Cărucioare [mobilier]; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Covoraşe de protecţie, detaşabile, pentru chiuvete, Suporturi pentru reviste, Standuri pentru ziare, Dulapuri, Dulapuri de scris, Cutii, Cutii, nu din metal; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Cosuri de gunoi, Suporturi pentru menaj sau bucătărie, Recipiente pentru menaj sau bucătărie, Cutie din sticlă, Coşuri, de uz casnic, Veselă de bucătărie, Suporturi de pahare, nu din hârtie sau materiale textile, Cosuri de gunoi pentru hartie, Cutii pentru bani, Puşculiţe, Truse de toaletă, Suporturi pentru şerveţele de toaletă, Distribuitoare pentru hârtie igienică, Perii pentru spălarea veselei, Suporturi pentru perii de spălat, Raclete [instrumente de curățare], Cutii de pâine; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Coșuri de pâine de uz casnic, Suporturi de bureţi, Cutii pentru săpun, Suporturi pentru săpun, Suporturi pentru săpunuri, Distribuitoare de săpun, Perii pentru spălarea veselei, Suporturi pentru pliculeţe de ceai, Uscătoare, Coșuri de gunoi pentru aruncarea scutecelor, Mături, Scânduri de călcat, Untiere, Ouare, Găleţi, Decantoare, Seturi de vase de bucătărie, Articole pentru copt, Seturi de vase de bucătărie, Naproane, cu excepția celor din hârtie sau material textil; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Șervete de masă, nu din hârtie sau material textil, Pahare de hârtie şi plastic, Articole de porţelan, Găleţi cu storcător pentru mop, Castroane, Funduri de tăiat pentru bucătărie, Încălţător, Încălțătoare, Şanuri pentru pantofi, Vase, Grilaje pentru prosoape, Cârpe de spălat, Ştergerea prafului (Cârpe pentru -), Tăvi pentru uz menajer, Platouri de uz casnic din hârtie, Articole de masă, Sticluţe plate, Ceşti, Cutii pentru depozitarea ceaiului, Infuzoare de ceai, Ceainice; Servicii de vânzare cu ridicata şi cu amănuntul, Vanzare prin posta, inclusiv pe internet, în ceea ce privește Învelitoare pentru ceainice, Învelitoare pentru ceainice, Servicii de ceai [veselă], Strecurătoare pentru ceai, Farfurii, Scânduri de spălat rufe, Căzi, Găleţi pentru mop, Cleme pentru golirea tuburilor de pastă de dinți, Zaharniţe, Prezentarea de bunuri si servicii in magazine mari, supermarketuri, magazine de vanzare cu amanuntul, depozite de bunuri, magazine online.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Háčiky (kovové vešiakové -), Puzdrá, Kontajnery (kovové -), kovové háčiky na šaty, koše kovové, Háčiky [železiarsky tovar], Kovové poštové schránky, Skrinky, škatule (Kovové -); Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Papierové tovary, Vrecká na odpadky z papiera alebo plastických materiálov, Obaly na spisy (papierové -), Spisové obaly [papiernický tovar], Koše na listy, Obalové nádoby z papiera, Nádoby na skladovanie z lepenky, Puzdra na ceruzky, Ťažidiel na spisy, Kancelárske pomôcky (iné ako nábytok), Stojany na perá a ceruzky, Tabule na zapichovanie oznamov, Obrazy, Útržkové bloky, Brožované knihy, Kancelárske svorky; Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Spony na držiaky na menovky [kancelárske potreby], Puzdra na doklady, Držiaky na menovky [kancelárske potreby], Obálky [papiernický tovar], Kalendáre, Záložky do knihy, Dierovačky, Značkovacie perá [papiernický tovar], Menovky [kancelárske potreby], Notebooky, Kancelárske spinky, Gumy na gumovanie, Potreby (písacie-), Písacie potreby, Podložky na písací stôl; Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Skrinky do pracovných stolov [kancelárske potreby]; Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Drevené alebo plastové debny, Háčiky pre vešiaky na odevy, nie z kovu, Kovové háčiky na zavesenie šiat, nie z kovu, Koše, nie z kovu, Hračky (skrinka na-), Oddeľovače priestoru pre zásuvky, Skladovacie kontajnery z umelej hmoty, Boxy z textílií, Kovové vešiakové háčiky na umiestnenie na dvere, Boxerské šortky, boxerky, Posuvné prvky pre zásuvky, Úložné zásuvky (nábytok); Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Nádoby, nie z kovu, Na skladovanie, Háky pre tyče na šaty, Vešiaky na odevy, Stojany na šaty [nábytok], háčiky na odevy, Zásuvky, Skladacie boxy, nie z kovu, Stohovateľné skrinky na odkladanie z plastu, Štíty (vývesné -) z dreva alebo plastických hmôt, Vešiaky na kľúče, Servírovacie vozíky [nábytok]; Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Kryty na drezy, Časopisy (držadlá na -), Novinové stojany, Skrine, Písacie stoly, Puzdrá, Latkové debny, nie z kovu; Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Nádoby, nádoby na použitie v domácnosti alebo kuchyni, Nádoby na použitie v domácnosti alebo v kuchyni, Sklenené nádoby, Koše na použitie v domácnosti, kuchynské nádoby, Podložiek pod poháre, nie z papiera ani z textilu, Podnosy na listy, Pokladne, Sporiteľničky, Toaletné potreby (puzdrá na -), Držiaky na toaletný papier, Držiaky na toaletný papier, Kefy na umývanie riadu, Držiaky pre kefky na umývanie riadu, Stierky [prostriedky a pomôcky na čistenie], Nádoby na chlieb; Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Košíky na chlieb na použitie v domácnosti, Držiaky na špongie, Obaly na mydlá, Držiaky na mydlo, Misky na mydlo, dávkovače mydla, Kefy na umývanie riadu, Tácky na odkladanie použitých čajových vrecúšok, Stojany na prádlo, Odpadkové koše na plienky, Metly, Žehliace dosky, maselničky, Kalíšky na vajíčka, Vedrá, Karafy, Súpravy kuchynských hrncov, Nádoby na pečenie, Náčinie kuchynské, Podložky (súpravy), okrem z papiera alebo z textílií; Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Prestieranie, nie z papiera ani z textilu, Poháriky z papiera alebo plastu, Výrobky z porcelánu, Vedrá so žmýkačom na mop, Misky, Dosky na krájanie (kuchynské -), lyžice na obúvanie, obuváky", Obuváky, Obuvnícke kopytá, Misky, Stojan na obrúsky, Oplachovacie handry, Prachovky, Podnosy na domáce účely, Podnosy na použitie v domácnosti, papierové, Stolové dekorácie, Čutory, Šálky, Čajové dózy, Čajové naparovacie sitká, Konvice na čaj; Veľkoobchodné a maloobchodné služby, Predaj na dobierku, aj prostredníctvom internetu, pokiaľ ide o Čajníky (látkové poklopy na udržanie teploty -), Látkové poklopy na udržanie teploty čaju v čajníku, Čajové súpravy [stolový riad], Čajové sitká, Taniere, Dosky na pranie, Vane na pranie, Žmýkačka na mopy, Pomôcky na vytláčanie túb, Cukorničky, Prezentácia tovaru a služieb vo veľkoobchodoch, v supermarketoch, maloobchodoch, v obchodných domoch a v obchodoch online.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Kljuke (kovinske) za obešanje oblek, Ohišja, Kovinske škatle, Kljuke za obleke iz kovine, Kovinske košare, Kljuke [drobna železnina], Poštni nabiralnik iz kovine, Zaboji iz navadnih kovin; Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Papirnato blago, Vreče za odpadke iz papirja ali plastike, Ovojnice za spise, Fascikli, Košarice za pisma, Shranjevalne posode iz papirja, Vsebniki za shranjevanje iz kartona, Držala za svinčnike, Obtežilnikov za papir, Pisarniške potrebščine (razen pohištva), Stojala za pisala [nalivna peresa in svinčniki], Ploščice za pritrjevanje (pisarniški rekvizit), Slike, Bloki [pisarniški], Knjižice, Pisarniške zaponke (pisarniški pripomočki); Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Sponke za značke [pisarniški pripomočki], Etuiji za dokumente, Trakovi za vizitke [pisarniški pripomočki], Ovoji [pisalne potrebščine], Koledarji, Označevalni trakovi za knjige, Luknjači [pisarniški pripomočki], Pisala za označevanje, Priponke z imeni [pisarniški pripomočki], Beležnice, Papirne sponke, Radirke, Priprave za pisanje, Pisalne potrebščine, Namizni podstavki; Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Omarice za pisalne mize [pisalne potrebščine]; Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Posode iz lesa ali plastike, Garderobni kavlji, nekovinsko, Patere [kljuke] za obleke, nekovinsko, Košare, nekovinsko, Skrinje za igrače, Delilne pregrade za predale, Škatle za shranjevanje iz umetne snovi, Škatle iz blaga, Garderobni kavlji iz kovine za pritrditev na vrata, Predali, Drsniki za predale, Škatle za shranjevanje [pohištvo]; Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Vsebniki, nekovinsko, Za shranjevanje, Kavlji stojal za obleke, Obešalniki za oblačila, Stojala za oblačila [pohištvo] in kljuke za oblačila, Predalnik za čevlje, Zložljive škatle, nekovinsko, Naložni odlagalniki iz umetnih snovi, Izveski iz lesa ali plastike, Table za obešanje kjučev, Vozički [pohištvo]; Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Pokrovi za pomivalna korita, Stojala za revije, Stojala za časopise, Omare, Pisalne mize, Ohišja, Zaboji iz letev, gajbe, nekovinsko; Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Posode za smeti, Posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo, Posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo, Steklene posode, Košare za domačo uporabo, Kuhinjske posode, Podstavki za kozarce, razen iz papirja ali tekstila, Odlagalne košarice za pisma, Hranilniki, Hranilniki, Toaletni neseserji, Držala za toaletni papir, Držala za toaletni papir, Krtače za pomivanje posode, Držala za krtače za pomivanje posode, Brisalke [čistilne naprave], Posode za shranjevanje kruha; Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Košarice za kruh za gospodinjske namene, Podstavki za gobice, Škatlice za milo, Posodice za milo, Posodice za milo, Lončki za tekoče milo, Krtače za pomivanje posode, Držala za čajne vrečke, Stojala za perilo, Vedra za odlaganje plenic, Metle, Likalne mize, Posode za maslo, Podstavki za jajca, Vedra, Karafe, Kuhinjska posoda, Priprave za peko, Kuhinjska posoda, Pogrinjki (seti), ne iz papirja ali blaga; Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Namizni pogrinjki, ne iz papirja ali blaga, Lončki iz papirja ali umetnih snovi, Porcelan, Vedra za ožemanje mopov, Skled, Kuhinjske deske za rezanje, Žlice za obuvanje, Žlica za čevlje, Čevljarska kopita, Krogle za balinanje, Stojala za prtičke, Krpe za pomivanje, Cunje za brisanje prahu, Pladnji za gospodinjstvo, Papirnati pladnji za gospodinjstva, Namiznih umetnin, Čutare, Skodelice, Doze za čaj, Filtri za čaj v obliki bunke, Čajniki; Storitve prodaje na debelo in prodaje na drobno, Storitve poštnega naročanja, tudi preko interneta v zvezi z Grelci iz blaga za čajnike, Grelci iz blaga za čajnike, Čajni servisi, Cedilo za čaj, Krožniki, Perilniki (ribežni za perilo), Kadi za pranje perila, Mopi (ožemalniki za mope), Stiskalnik za tube za zobno pasto, Sladkornice, Predstavitev izdelkov in storitev v velikih trgovinah, samopostrežnicah, trgovinah na drobno, blagovnicah in e-trgovinah.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Krokar, metall-, för klädstänger, Höljen, Lådor av metall, Klädkrokar av metall, Papperskorgar av metall, Krokar [metallvaror], Brevlådor av metall, Askar av oädel metall; Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Pappersvaror, Soppåsar (av papper eller plast), Aktkappor, Dokumentmappar, Brevkorgar, Förvaringsbehållare av papper, Förvaringsbehållare av pappkartong, Pennhållare, Papperspressar, Tryckta skrifter och trycksaker, Ställ för bläckpennor och blyertspennor, Skrivskivor, Tavlor, Block [pappersvaror], Häften, Häftklamrar för kontorsändamål; Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Klämmor för namnbrickshållare [kontorsmaterial], Dokumentfodral, Namnbrickshållare [kontorsmaterial], Kuvert, Kalendrar, Bokmärken, Hålslag [kontorsartiklar], Märkpennor [kontorsmaterial], Namnskyltar [kontorsmaterial], Anteckningsböcker, Gem, Radergummin, Skrivredskap, Skrivredskap, Skrivbordsunderlägg; Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Arbetsbordslådor [kontorsartiklar]; Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Fodral av trä eller plast, Rockhängare, ej av metall, Klädkrokar [krokar], ej av metall, Korgar, ej av metall, Leksakslådor, Avdelare för byrålådor, Förvaringslådor av syntetmaterial, Boxar av tyg, Garderobskrokar av metall för applicering på dörrar, Skrivbordslådor, Glidskenor för byrålådor, Förvaringslådor [möbler]; Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Reservoarer, ej av metall, För förvaringsändamål, Krokar för klädstänger, Klädgalgar, Klädställ [möbler] och klädkrokar, Skåp med lådor, Vikbara boxar, ej av metall, Stapelbara förvaringslådor av plast, Skyltar av trä eller plast, Nyckeltavlor, Serveringsvagnar (möbler); Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Diskhoar, lösa mattor för, Tidningshyllor, Skyltställ för tidningar, Skåp, Sekretärer, Höljen, Askar, ej av metall; Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Slasktunnor, Behållare för hushålls- och köksändamål, Behållare för hushålls- eller köksändamål, Askar av glas, Korgar, för hushållsbruk, Köksbehållare, Glasunderlägg (ej av papper eller tyg), Papperskorgar, Kassaskrin, Spargrisar, Beautyboxar (inredda), Toalettpappershållare, Toalettpappershållare, Diskborstar, Hållare för diskborstar, Avdragare [rengöringsredskap], Brödlådor; Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Brödkorgar för hushållsändamål, Svamphållare, Tvålaskar, Tvålhållare, Tvålkoppar, Tvålautomater, Diskborstar, Hållare för tepåsar, Torkställningar, Blöjsophinkar, Kvastar, Strykbrädor, Smöraskar, Äggkoppar, Ämbar, Karaffer, Kokkärlsuppsättningar, Bakredskap, Köksvaror, Bordstabletter, inte av papper eller textil (satser); Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Bordsunderlägg, inte av papper eller textil, Muggar av papper eller plast, Porslinsvaror, Hinkar med moppurvridare, Inälvor, Skärbrädor [köksredskap], Skohorn, Skohorn, Skoblock, Skålar, Servetthållare, Disktrasor, Dammtrasor, Brickor för hushållsbruk, Pappersbrickor för hushållsändamål, Bordsattiraljer, Fickpluntor, Koppar, Teburkar, Tekulor, Tekannor; Gross- och detaljhandelstjänster, Postorderförsäljning, inklusive över Internet, med avseende på Huvar för tekannor, Huvar för tekannor, Teserviser [bordsserviser], Tesilar, Tallrikar, Tvättbrädor, Tvättbaljor, Moppurvridare, Klämmare för tandkrämstuber, Sockerskålar, Presentation av varor och tjänster i stormarknader, snabbköp, detaljistaffärer, varuhus och direktanslutna butiker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/092</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-18</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/163</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-27</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079026</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>35260</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
