<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-28T09:52:43</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224168</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224168</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-28</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="12" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-28</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Molouen</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162202872</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/224/018224168/000162202872.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.25</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Немедицински препарати за баня; Почистващи средства за целите на интимната лична хигиена, нелечебни; Почистващи средства за домакински цели; Сапуни; Памучна вата за козметични цели; Козметични средства; Ароматизатори за въздух; Вода за плакнене на уста, не за медицински цели; Химически почистващи препарати за домакински цели; Етерични масла; Сапуни за ръце.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Koupelové přípravky, ne pro léčebné účely; Neléčivé mycí přípravky pro intimní hygienu; Čisticí přípravky; Mýdla; Vata pro kosmetické účely; Kosmetické přípravky; Osvěžovače vzduchu; Ústní vody, ne pro lékařské účely; Chemické čisticí přípravky pro použití v domácnosti; Éterické oleje; Mýdla na ruce.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Badepræparater, ikke til medicinsk brug; Rensemidler til intimhygiejne, ikke-medicinske; Præparater til rengøring; Sæbe; Vat til kosmetisk brug; Kosmetik; Duftpræparater til luft; Mundskyllemidler, ikke til medicinske formål; Kemiske rengøringspræparater til husholdningsbrug; Æteriske olier; Håndsæbe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Badezusätze, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Nicht medizinische Reinigungsmittel zur Intimpflege; Reinigungsmittel; Seifen; Watte für kosmetische Zwecke; Kosmetika; Luftbeduftungsmittel; Mundspülungen, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Chemische Reinigungsmittel für Haushaltszwecke; Ätherische Öle; Handseifen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μη φαρμακευτικά παρασκευάσματα για το μπάνιο· Προϊόντα καθαρισμού της ευαίσθητης περιοχής για ατομική χρήση, μη φαρμακευτικά· Παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού· Σαπούνια· Φαρμακευτικό βαμβάκι για καλλυντική χρήση· Καλλυντικά· Παρασκευάσματα αρωματισμού του αέρα· Στοματικά διαλύματα μη προοριζόμενα για ιατρική χρήση· Χημικά παρασκευάσματα καθαρισμού για οικιακή χρήση· Αιθέρια (Έλαια -)· Σαπούνια χεριών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Bath preparations, not for medical purposes; cleansers for intimate personal hygiene purposes, non medicated; cleaning preparations; soap; cotton wool for cosmetic purposes; cosmetics; air fragrancing preparations; mouthwashes, not for medical purposes; chemical cleaning preparations for household purposes; essential oils; hand soap.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Preparaciones para el baño que no sean para uso médico; Preparaciones limpiadoras no medicinales para la higiene íntima; Productos de limpieza; Jabones; Algodón para uso cosmético; Cosméticos; Productos para perfumar el ambiente; Enjuagues bucales que no sean para uso médico; Preparaciones químicas de limpieza para uso doméstico; Aceites esenciales; Jabones de manos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Vannipreparaadid, v.a meditsiinilised; Ravitoimeta intiimpuhastusained isikliku hügieeni tarbeks; Puhastusained; Seep; Kosmeetiline vatt; Kosmeetikavahendid; Õhulõhnastusained; Ravitoimeta suuveed; Keemilised puhastuspreparaadid kodumajapidamises kasutamiseks; Eeterlikud õlid; Käteseebid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kylpyvalmisteet (ei-lääkinnälliset); Lääkeaineita sisältämättömät puhdistusaineet intiimihygieniaan; Puhdistusaineet kotitaloustarkoituksiin; Saippuat; Pumpuli kosmeettisiin tarkoituksiin; Kosmetiikka; Ilmanraikastusvalmisteet; Suuhuuhteet muihin kuin lääkinnällisiin tarkoituksiin; Kemialliset puhdistusvalmisteet kotitalouskäyttöön; Eteeriset öljyt; Käsisaippuat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Préparations pour le bain, non à usage médical; Nettoyants non médicamenteux pour l'hygiène intime; Produits de nettoyage; Savons; Ouate à usage cosmétique; Cosmétiques; Parfums d'ambiance; Bains de bouche non à usage médical; Produits chimiques de nettoyage à usage domestique; Huiles essentielles; Savons pour les mains.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Nemedicinski preparati za kupanje; Sredstva za čišćenje za intimnu osobnu higijenu, nemedicinski; Sredstva za čišćenje u kućanstvu; Sapuni; Vata za kozmetičke svrhe; Kozmetički proizvodi; Parfimiranje zraka (pripravci za-); Vodice za ispiranje usta, za nemedicinsku uporabu; Kemijski pripravci za čišćenje u kućanstvu; Esencijalna ulja; Sapuni za ruke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Nem gyógyhatású fürdőkészítmények; Intim lemosók személyi higiéniai célokra, nem gyógyszeres; Tisztítószerek háztartási használatra; Szappan; Vatta kozmetikai használatra; Kozmetikai szerek; Levegőillatosító készítmények; Szájvizek, nem gyógyászati célra; Vegyi tisztítókészítmények háztartási célokra; Esszenciális olajok; Kézmosó szappanok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Preparati per il bagno, non per uso medico; Detergenti per uso igienico intimo personale, non medicanti; Prodotti per la pulizia; Saponi; Ovatta per uso cosmetico; Cosmetici; Profumi per ambiente; Collutori non per uso medico; Preparati chimici per la pulizia per uso domestico; Oli essenziali; Saponi per le mani.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vonių preparatai (ne medicinos reikmėms); Negydomieji intymios higienos prausikliai; Valymo preparatai; Gabalinis prausiamasis [tualetinis] muilas; Vata (kosmetikos reikmėms); Kosmetika; Oro kvėpinimo preparatai; Burnos skalavimo preparatai (ne medicinos reikmėms); Cheminiai valymo preparatai (buities reikmėms); Eteriniai aliejai; Rankų muilas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vannas līdzekļi, ne medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Mazgāšanas līdzekļi intīmai higiēnai, ne medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Tīrīšanas līdzekļi; Ziepes; Vate kosmētiskiem nolūkiem; Kosmētikas līdzekļi; Gaisa iesmaržināšanas līdzekļi; Mutes skalošanas līdzekļi, ne medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Ķīmiskie tīrīšanas līdzekļi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Ēteriskās eļļas; Roku ziepes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Preparazzjonijiet għall-banju, mhux medikat; Sustanzi li jnaddfu għal skopijiet ta' iġjene personali intima, mhux medikati; Aġenti tat-tindif għal skopijiet domestiċi; Sapun; Tajjar għal skopijiet kosmetiċi; Kożmetiċi; Preparazzjonijiet biex tfewwaħ l-arja; Likwidi għat-tlaħliħ tal-ħalq, mhux għal skopijiet mediċi; Preparazzjonijiet kimiċi tat-tindif għal skopijiet domestiċi; Żjut meħudin minn pjanti; Sapun tal-idejn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Badpreparaten, niet voor medisch gebruik; Reinigingsmiddelen voor de intieme persoonlijke hygiëne, niet medicinaal; Reinigingsmiddelen; Zepen; Watten voor cosmetisch gebruik; Cosmetica; Producten voor het parfumeren van de omgevingslucht; Mondverzorgingsproducten, niet voor medicinaal gebruik; Chemische reinigingspreparaten voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Etherische oliën; Handzepen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Preparaty do kąpieli, nielecznicze; Środki czyszczące do higieny intymnej, nielecznicze; Środki czyszczące do celów gospodarstwa domowego; Mydła; Wata do celów kosmetycznych; Kosmetyki; Środki odświeżające powietrze [zapachowe]; Płyny do płukania ust do celów niemedycznych; Preparaty chemiczne do czyszczenia do użytku domowego; Olejki eteryczne; Mydła do rąk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Preparações para o banho, não sendo para fins medicinais; Produtos de limpeza para fins de higiene íntima pessoal, não medicados; Preparações para limpeza; Sabão; Algodão para uso cosmético; Cosméticos; Fragrâncias para perfumar; Preparações para bochechar, sem ser para uso médico; Produtos quimicos de limpeza para uso doméstico; Óleos essenciais; Sabões para as mãos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Preparate cosmetice pentru baie [nu de uz medical]; Produse de curățare pentru igiena personală intimă, nemedicinale; Curățat (Produse de -); Săpunuri; Vată de uz cosmetic; Cosmetice; Preparate odorizante pentru împrospătarea aerului; Ape de gură, nu pentru uz medical; Preparate chimice de curățare pentru uz casnic; Uleiuri eterice; Săpunuri pentru mâini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Prípravky do kúpeľa (nie na lekárske použitie); Neliečivé umývacie prípravky na osobnú hygienu; Čistiace prípravky; Mydlá; Vata na kozmetické použitie; Kozmetické prípravky; Osviežovače vzduchu; Ústne vody (nie na lekárske použitie); Chemické čistiace prípravky do domácnosti; Esenciálne (éterické) oleje; Mydlá na ruky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pripravki za kopanje, ne za medicinske namene; Čistila za intimno osebno higieno, brez zdravilnih učinkovin; Čistilni pripravki za gospodinjske namene; Mila; Vata za kozmetične namene; Kozmetični izdelki; Sredstva za odišavljanje zraka; Ustne vodice, ne za medicinske namene; Kemični čistilni pripravki za gospodinjske namene; Eterična olja; Mila za roke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Icke-medicinska badpreparat; Preparat för personlig intimhygien, icke-medicinska; Rengöringspreparat; Tvålar; Bomull för kosmetiska ändamål; Kosmetika; Välluktande luftpreparat; Munsköljmedel, inte för medicinska ändamål; Kemiska rengöringspreparat för hushållsändamål; Flyktiga oljor; Handtvålar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Защитни маски; Защитни работни маски за лице; Ръкавици за защита от злополуки; Филтри за респираторни маски; Очила за спорт; Облекла за защита от злополуки, радиация и огън; Защитни устройства за лично ползване за защита при злополуки; Термометри, с изключение на такива за медицински цели; Апарати за анализ на въздуха; Компютърни програми, записани; Защитни очила; Защитни устройства срещу рентгенови лъчи, с изключение на такива за медицински цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Ochranné masky; Pracovní ochranné obličejové štíty; Ochranné rukavice (k ochraně před úrazy a nehodami); Filtry do dýchacích masek; Ochranné brýle pro sportovní účely; Ochranné obleky k ochraně před úrazem, radiací a ohněm; Osobní ochranné prostředky k prevenci nehod; Teploměry, ne lékařské; Přístroje na analýzu vzduchu; Počítačový software (nahraný); Bezpečnostní brýle; Ochranné prostředky proti rentgenovému záření, ne pro lékařské účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beskyttelsesmasker; Beskyttende ansigtsskærme til arbejdere; Handsker til beskyttelse mod ulykker; Filtre til åndedrætsmasker; Sportsbriller; Tøj til beskyttelse mod ulykker, bestråling og ild; Beskyttelsesindretninger til personlig brug mod ulykker; Termometre [ikke til medicinsk brug]; Luftanalyseapparater; Software til computere, optaget; Beskyttelsesbriller; Beskyttelsesindretninger mod røntgenstråler, ikke til medicinske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Schutzmasken; Gesichtsschutzschirme für Arbeiter; Unfallschutzhandschuhe; Filter für Atemmasken; Sportbrillen; Unfall-, Strahlen- und Feuerschutzbekleidungsstücke; Unfallschutzvorrichtungen für den persönlichen Gebrauch; Thermometer, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Luftanalysegeräte; Gespeicherte Computersoftware; Korbbrille; Schutzvorrichtungen gegen Röntgenstrahlen, nicht für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Προστατευτικές μάσκες· Προστατευτικές ασπίδες προσώπου· Γάντια για προστασία από ατυχήματα· Φίλτρα για μάσκες αναπνευστικές· Γυαλιά προστατευτικά για αθλήματα· Ενδύματα για προστασία από ατυχήματα, ακτινοβολία και πυρκαγιά· Ατυχημάτων (Μηχανισμοί ατομικής προστασίας κατά των -)· Θερμόμετρα όχι ιατρικά· Αέρα (Συσκευές για την ανάλυση του -)· Η/Υ (Προγράμματα -) εγγεγραμμένα· Προστατευτικά γυαλιά· Διατάξεις προστασίας από τις ακτίνες Χ, όχι για ιατρική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Protective masks; workmen's protective face-shields; gloves for protection against accidents; filters for respiratory masks; goggles for sports; clothing for protection against accidents, irradiation and fire; protection devices for personal use against accidents; thermometers, not for medical purposes; air analysis apparatus; computer software, recorded; protective goggles; protection devices against X-rays, not for medical purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Máscaras de protección; Pantallas de protección facial para obreros; Guantes de protección contra accidentes; Filtros para máscaras respiratorias; Gafas de deporte; Trajes de protección contra los accidentes, las radiaciones y el fuego; Dispositivos de protección personal contra accidentes; Termómetros que no sean para uso médico; Aparatos analizadores de aire; Software [programas grabados]; Gafas protectoras; Dispositivos de protección contra los rayos X que no sean para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kaitsemaskid; Tööliste näokaitsesirmid; Kaitsekindad; Respiraatorifiltrid; Spordiprillid; Kaitserõivad, sh kiirgus- ja tulekindlad; Individuaalkaitsevahendid; Termomeetrid, v.a meditsiinilised; Õhuanalüsaatorid; Salvestatud arvutitarkvara; Ohutusprillid; Röntgenikiirgusvastased vahendid, v.a meditsiinilised.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Suojanaamarit; Työntekijöiden kasvonsuojukset; Käsineet suojaksi onnettomuuksilta; Suodattimet kaasunaamareihin; Suojalasit urheilemiseen; Vaatteet suojaksi tapaturmilta, säteilyltä ja tulelta; Suojalaitteet onnettomuuksien varalta, henkilökohtaiset; Lämpömittarit, ei-lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Ilman analysointilaitteet; Tietokoneohjelmat [tallennetut]; Turvasuojalasit; Suojalaitteet röntgensäteitä vastaan, ei-lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Masques de protection; Écrans de protection faciaux pour ouvriers; Gants pour la protection contre les accidents; Filtres pour masques respiratoires; Lunettes de sport; Vêtements de protection contre les accidents, les radiations et le feu; Dispositifs de protection personnelle contre les accidents; Thermomètres, non à usage médical; Appareils pour l'analyse de l'air; Logiciels [programmes enregistrés]; Lunettes de protection; Dispositifs de protection contre les rayons X non à usage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Zaštitne maske; Zasloni za zaštitu lica radnika; Zaštitne rukavice; Filtri za maske za disanje; Sportske zaštitne naočale; Odjeća za zaštitu od nesreća, zračenja i vatre; Nesreće na radu (uređaji za osobnu zaštitu na radu); Toplomjeri nisu za medicinsku uporabu; Uređaji za analizu zraka; Računalni programi [snimljeni]; Zaštitne naočale; X zrake (uređaji za zaštitu od X zraka) za nemedicinske potrebe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Védőálarcok/-maszkok; Munkavédelmi arcvédő pajzsok; Balesetek elleni védőkesztyűk; Szűrők légzőmaszkokhoz; Védőszemüvegek sportoláshoz; Védőruhák balesetek, sugárzás és tűz ellen; Védőeszközök személyek balesetvédelmére; Hőmérők, nem gyógyászati használatra; Levegő elemzésére szolgáló készülékek; Számítógépes programok, rögzített; Védőszemüvegek; Röntgensugarak elleni védőeszközök, nem gyógyászati használatra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Maschere di protezione; Schermi per la protezione del viso degli operai; Guanti per la protezione contro gli infortuni; Filtri per maschere respiratorie; Occhiali da sport; Indumenti di protezione contro gli infortuni, le irradiazioni e il fuoco; Dispositivi di protezione personale contro gli infortuni; Termometri non per uso medico; Apparecchi per analisi dell'aria; Software [programmi registrati]; Occhiali di protezione; Dispositivi di protezione contro i raggi X non per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Apsauginės kaukės; Apsauginiai darbininkų veido skydeliai; Apsauginės pirštinės; Respiratorių filtrai; Apsauginiai sportiniai akiniai; Apsauginiai drabužiai nuo nelaimingų atsitikimų, jonizuojančios spinduliuotės ir ugnies; Asmeninės apsaugos priemonės nuo nelaimingų atsitikimų; Termometrai (išskyrus medicininius); Oro analizės aparatai; Kompiuterių programinė įranga [įrašyta]; Apsauginiai akiniai; Apsaugos priemonės nuo rentgeno spindulių (ne medicinos reikmėms).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Aizsargmaskas; Aizsargmaskas strādniekiem; Cimdi aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem; Respiratoru filtri; Sporta brilles; Apģērbi aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem, starojumu un uguni; Ierīces individuālai aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem; Termometri, ne medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Aparāti gaisa sastāva analīzei; Ierakstīta programmatūra; Brilles acu aizsardzībai; Ierīces aizsardzībai pret rentgenstariem, ne medicīniskiem nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Maskri protettivi; Lqugħ protettiv tal-wiċċ għal ħaddiema; Ingwanti għall-protezzjoni kontra l-inċidenti; Filtri għal maskri respiratorji; Nuċċalijiet għall-isport; Ilbies għall-protezzjoni kontra l-inċidenti, irradjazzjoni u n-nar; Tagħmir ta' protezzjoni għall-użu personali kontra l-inċidenti; Termometri [mhux għal skopijiet mediċi]; Apparat għall-analiżi tal-arja; Programmi tal-kompjuter irrekordjati; Nuċċalijiet protettivi; Tagħmir ta' protezzjoni kontra r-raġġi X, mhux għal skopijiet mediċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Beschermende maskers; Gezichtsbeschermers [schermen] voor werklieden; Handschoenen ter bescherming tegen ongevallen; Filters voor ademhalingsmaskers; Sportbrillen; Beschermende kleding tegen ongevallen, straling en vuur; Inrichtingen voor de bescherming van personen tegen ongevallen; Thermometers, niet voor medisch gebruik; Apparaten voor het analyseren van lucht; Software [geregistreerde programma's]; Beschermende brillen; Inrichtingen ter bescherming tegen röntgenstralen, niet voor medisch gebruik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Maski ochronne; Osłony ochronne na twarz dla robotników; Rękawice do ochrony przed wypadkami; Filtry do masek do oddychania; Okulary ochronne do uprawiania sportu; Odzież chroniąca przed wypadkami, napromieniowaniem i ogniem; Urządzenia do ochrony osobistej przed wypadkami; Termometry nie do celów medycznych; Analizatory powietrza; Programy komputerowe nagrane; Okulary ochronne; Urządzenia zabezpieczające przed promieniowaniem rentgenowskim, nie do celów medycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máscaras de proteção; Telas para a proteção do rosto de operários; Luvas para proteção contra acidentes; Filtros para máscaras respiratórias; Óculos para desporto; Vestuário de proteção contra acidentes, radiações e fogo; Dispositivos de proteção pessoal contra os acidentes; Termómetros, não sendo para uso médico; Aparelhos para a análise do ar; Software [programas de computador gravados]; Óculos de proteção; Dispositivos de proteção contra raios-x, não sendo para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Măști de protecție; Măști de protecție pentru muncitori; Mănuși de protecție împotriva accidentelor; Filtre pentru măști respiratorii; Ochelari de protecție pentru sport; Îmbrăcăminte de protecție contra accidentelor, iradierii și incendiilor; Dispozitive de protecție, de uz personal, împotriva accidentelor; Termometre, altele decât cele de uz medical; Aparate pentru analiza aerului; Programe de calculator înregistrate; Ochelari de protecție; Dispozitive de protecție contra razelor X, cu excepția celor de uz medical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ochranné masky; Tvárové štíty (ochranné pracovné prostriedky); Ochranné rukavice; Filtre na dýchacie masky; Okuliare na športovanie; Ochranné odevy proti úrazom, proti rádioaktívnej kontaminácii a protipožiarne ochranné odevy; Osobné ochranné prostriedky proti nehodám; Teplomery (nie na lekárske použitie); Prístroje na rozbor vzduchu; Počítačový softvér (nahraté počítačové programy); Bezpečnostné okuliare; Ochranné zariadenia proti röntgenovým lúčom (nie na lekárske použitie).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zaščitne maske; Zaščita za obraz za delavce; Rokavice za zaščito pred nesrečam; Filtri za dihalne maske; Očala za šport; Zaščitna oblačila proti nesrečam, sevanju in ognju; Zaščitne naprave proti poškodbam, za osebno uporabo; Termometri, ne za medicinske namene; Aparati za analizo zraka; Računalniški programi, posneti; Zaščitni naočniki; Zaščitne naprave proti rentgenskim žarkom, ne za medicinske namene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Skyddsmasker; Skyddsvisir för arbetare; Handskar för skydd mot olyckor; Filter för andningsmasker; Glasögon för sport; Skyddskläder mot skador, strålning och eld; Skyddsanordningar mot olyckor för personligt bruk; Termometrar, inte för medicinska ändamål; Luftanalysapparater; Registrerade datormjukvaror; Skyddsglasögon; Skyddsanordningar mot röntgenstrålar, inte för medicinska ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Санитарни маски за медицински цели; Ръкавици за медицински цели; Маски за медицински персонал; Терапевтични маски за лице; Облекло специално за операционни зали; Подложки за медицински цели; Медицински апарати и инструменти; Бебешки шишета; Термометри за медицински цели; Колани за пристягане на корема; Защитно облекло за медицински цели; Защитни маски за дишане от нетъкан текстил при медицински уреди; Защитни съоръжения срещу рентгенови лъчи за медицински цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Hygienické masky pro lékařské účely; Rukavice pro lékařské účely; Roušky pro lékařský personál; Terapeutické obličejové masky; Oděvy určené pro operační sály; Podušky pro lékařské účely; Lékařské přístroje a nástroje; Dětské láhve; Teploměry pro lékařské účely; Břišní pásy; Ochranné oděvy pro lékařské účely; Ochranné dýchací masky vyrobené z netkaných materiálů pro lékařské použití; Ochranná zařízení proti rentgenovým paprskům pro lékařské účely.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sanitære masker til medicinske formål; Handsker til medicinske formål; Masker til brug for medicinsk personel; Terapeutiske ansigtsmasker; Beklædning specielt til operationsstuer; Puder til medicinske formål; Medicinske apparater og instrumenter; Sutteflasker; Termometre til medicinsk brug; Hypogastriske bælter; Beskyttelsesbeklædning til medicinske formål; Beskyttende respirationsmasker af ikke-vævede materialer til medicinske formål; Beskyttelsesindretninger mod røntgenstråler til medicinske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Mundschutz für medizinische Zwecke; Handschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Masken für medizinisches Personal; Therapeutische Gesichtsmasken; OP-Kleidung; Kissen für medizinische Zwecke; Medizinische Apparate und Instrumente; Saugflaschen; Thermometer für medizinische Zwecke; Leibbinden; Schutzbekleidung für medizinische Zwecke; Vlies-Atemschutzmasken für medizinische Anwendungen; Schutzvorrichtungen gegen Röntgenstrahlen für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μάσκες υγιεινής για ιατρική χρήση· Γάντια ιατρικής χρήσης· Μάσκες για το ιατρικό προσωπικό· Θεραπευτικές μάσκες προσώπου· Ενδύματα (Ειδικά για χειρουργεία -)· Μαξιλάρια για χρήση ιατρική· Ιατρικά (Συσκευές και όργανα -)· Υποδοχείς για θήλαστρα· Θερμόμετρα ιατρικά· Κοιλιακές ζώνες· Προστατευτικά ενδύματα για ιατρική χρήση· Προστατευτικές αναπνευστικές μάσκες από μη υφασμένα υλικά για ιατρικές εφαρμογές· Διατάξεις προστασίας από τις ακτίνες Χ, για ιατρική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Sanitary masks for medical purposes; gloves for medical purposes; masks for use by medical personnel; therapeutic facial masks; clothing especially for operating rooms; cushions for medical purposes; medical apparatus and instruments; feeding bottles; thermometers for medical purposes; abdominal belts; Protective clothing for medical purposes; Protective breathing masks made of non-woven materials for medical applications; protection devices against X-rays, for medical purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Mascarillas sanitarias para uso médico; Guantes para uso médico; Mascarillas para personal médico; Máscaras faciales terapéuticas; Ropa especial para quirófano; Cojines para uso médico; Aparatos e instrumentos médicos; Biberones; Termómetros para uso médico; Cinturones abdominales; Ropa protectora para fines médicos; Mascarillas de respiración de protección hechas con materiales sin tejer para aplicaciones médicas; Dispositivos de protección contra los rayos X para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meditsiinilised hügieenilised maskid; Meditsiinilised kindad; Maskid meditsiinipersonalile; Ravinäomaskid; Eririietus operatsioonisaalides viibimiseks, operatsiooniriietus; Meditsiinilised padjad; Meditsiiniseadmed ja -riistad; Lutipudelid; Meditsiinilised termomeetrid; Kõhuvööd; Meditsiinis kasutatavad kaitserõivad; Mittekootud materjalidest valmistatud kaitsvad hingamismaskid meditsiiniliseks kasutamiseks; Röntgenikiirguse vastased meditsiinilised kaitsevahendid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Saniteettinaamarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Käsineet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Suojanaamarit lääkintähenkilökuntaa varten; Hoitavat kasvonaamiot; Vaatteet leikkaussaleja varten, erikoisvalmisteiset; Tyynyt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Lääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Tuttipullot; Kuumemittarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Palleavyöt; Suojavaatteet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Suojaavat hengitysnaamarit kuitumateriaaleista lääketieteellisiin sovelluksiin; Röntgensäteilysuojavarusteet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Masques d'hygiène à usage médical; Gants à usage médical; Masques utilisés par le personnel médical; Masques thérapeutiques à porter sur le visage; Vêtements spéciaux pour salles d'opération; Coussins à usage médical; Appareils et instruments médicaux; Biberons; Thermomètres à usage médical; Ceintures abdominales; Vêtements de protection à usage médical; Masques respiratoires de protection en matériaux non tissés à usage médical; Dispositifs de protection contre les rayons X à usage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sanitarne maske za medicinske svrhe; Rukavice za medicinsku uporabu; Maske za medicinsko osoblje; Terapeutske maske za lice; Specijalna odjeća za operacijske dvorane; Jastuci za medicinske potrebe; Medicinski uređaji i instrumenti; Spremnici dječjih bočica; Toplomjeri za medicinske potrebe; Trbušni [abdominalni] pojasevi; Zaštitna odjeća za medicinske namjene; Zaštitne maske za disanje od netkanih materijala za medicinske primjene; X zrake (uređaji za zaštitu od X zraka) za medicinske potrebe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Gyógyászati célú egészségügyi maszkok; Kesztyűk gyógyászati használatra; Maszkok egészségügyi személyzet általi használatra; Terápiás arcmaszkok; Speciális műtőruházat; Párnák gyógyászati használatra; Gyógyászati készülékek és eszközök; Cumisüvegtartók; Hőmérők gyógyászati célokra; Haskötők; Védőruházat orvosi célokra; Nem szőtt anyagokból készült légzésvédő maszkok orvosi alkalmazásokhoz; Röntgensugárzás elleni védőfelszerelések orvosi használatra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Maschere igieniche per uso medico; Guanti per uso medico; Maschere utilizzate dal personale medico; Maschere terapeutiche per il viso; Vestiti speciali per sale operatorie; Cuscini per uso medico; Apparecchi e strumenti medici; Poppatoi; Termometri per uso medico; Cinture addominali; Abbigliamento protettivo per uso medico; Maschere respiratorie protettive in materiali non tessuti per applicazioni mediche; Dispositivi di protezione contro i raggi X per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Higieninės kaukės (medicinos reikmėms); Pirštinės (medicinos reikmėms); Kaukės medicinos personalui; Terapinės veido kaukės; Specialieji operaciniai drabužiai; Medicininės pagalvėlės; Medicinos aparatai ir instrumentai; Žindymo buteliukai; Medicininiai termometrai; Pilvo diržai; Apsauginiai drabužiai medicininėms reikmėms; Apsauginės kvėpavimo kaukės iš neaustinių medžiagų medicinos reikmėms; Apsaugos nuo rentgeno spinduliuotės priemonės (medicinos reikmėms).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Sanitārās maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Cimdi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Medicīnas personālam paredzētās maskas; Ārstnieciskas sejas maskas; Speciālie apģērbi operāciju zālēs; Medicīniskie spilveni; Medicīniskā aparatūra un instrumenti; Barošanas pudelītes; Medicīniskie termometri; Abdominālās jostas; Aizsargtērpi medicīniskām vajadzībām; No neaustiem materiāliem izgatavotas elpošanas aizsargmaskas lietošanai medicīnā; Medicīniskās ierīces aizsardzībai pret rentgena starojumu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Maskri sanitarji għal skopijiet mediċi; Ingwanti għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri għal personal mediku; Masks tal-wiċċ terapewtiċi; Ilbies speċjali għas-swali tal-operazzjonijiet; Kuxxini għal skopijiet mediċi; Apparat u strumenti mediċi; Reċipjenti bħala fliexken għat-tmigħ tat-trabi; Termometri għal skopijiet mediċi; Ċinturini addominali; Ħwejjeġ protettivi għall-użu mediku; Maskri respiratorji protettivi magħmula minn materjali mhux minsuġa għall-applikazzjonijiet mediċi; Tagħmir ta' protezzjoni kontra r-raġġi-X, għal skopijiet mediċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Hygiënische maskers voor medisch gebruik; Handschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Maskers te gebruiken door medisch personeel; Therapeutische gezichtsmaskers; Operatiekleding; Kussens voor medisch gebruik; Medische apparaten en instrumenten; Zuigflessen; Thermometers voor medisch gebruik; Buikgordels; Beschermende kledingstukken voor medische doeleinden; Beschermende ademhalingsmaskers gemaakt van non-woven materialen voor medische toepassingen; Inrichtingen ter bescherming tegen röntgenstralen, voor medisch gebruik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Maski sanitarne do celów medycznych; Rękawice do celów medycznych; Maski stosowane przez personel medyczny; Maski terapeutyczne na twarz; Odzież specjalna używana w salach operacyjnych; Poduszki do celów medycznych; Urządzenia i instrumenty medyczne; Pojemniki na butelki do karmienia; Termometry do celów medycznych; Pasy brzuszne; Odzież ochronna do celów medycznych; Ochronne maski do oddychania wykonane z materiałów nietkanych do użytku medycznego; Urządzenia zabezpieczające przed promieniami rentgenowskimi do celów medycznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máscaras higiénicas para uso médico; Luvas para uso médico; Máscaras para pessoal médico; Máscaras faciais terapêuticas; Vestuário especial para salas de operação; Almofadas para uso medicinal; Aparelhos e instrumentos médicos; Biberons [biberões]; Termómetros para uso médico; Cintas abdominais; Vestuário de proteção para uso médico; Máscaras de respiração de proteção em materiais não tecidos para aplicações médicas; Dispositivos médicos de proteção contra raios-x.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Măşti sanitare de uz medical; Mănuși de uz medical; Măști utilizate de personalul medical; Măști faciale terapeutice; Haine speciale pentru săli de operație; Perne de uz medical; Aparate și instrumente medicale; Recipiente pentru biberoane; Termometre de uz medical; Centuri abdominale; Îmbrăcăminte de protecție de uz medical; Măști de protecție respiratorie confecționate din materiale nețesute de uz medical; Dispozitive de protecție contra razelor X, pentru uz medical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Sanitárne masky na lekárske účely; Rukavice na lekárske použitie; Rúška (pre nemocničný personál); Terapeutické masky na tvár; Odevy do operačných sál; Podušky na lekárske použitie; Lekárske prístroje a nástroje; Detské fľaše; Lekárske teplomery; Brušné pásy; Ochranné odevy na lekárske účely; Ochranné dýchacie masky z netkaných materiálov na lekárske použitie; Ochranné zariadenia proti röntgenovému žiareniu na lekárske použitie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Higienske maske za medicinske namene; Rokavice za medicinske namene; Maske za medicinsko osebje; Terapevtske maske za obraz; Posebna oblačila za operacijske prostore; Blazine za medicinske namene; Medicinski aparati in instrumenti; Posodice za stekleničke za hranjenje; Termometri za medicinske namene; Trebušni pasovi; Zaščitna oblačila za medicinske namene; Zaščitne dihalne maske iz netkanih materialov za medicinsko uporabo; Zaščitne naprave pred rentgenskimi žarki, za medicinske namene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Sanitetsmasker för medicinska ändamål; Handskar för medicinska ändamål; Munskydd för medicinsk personal; Terapeutiska ansiktsmasker; Kläder för användning i operationsrum; Kuddar för medicinska ändamål; Medicinska apparater och instrument; Nappflaskor; Termometrar för medicinska ändamål; Maggördlar; Skyddskläder för medicinska ändamål; Skyddande andningsmasker av icke-vävda material för medicinska ändamål; Skyddsanordningar mot röntgenstrålar för medicinska ändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/073</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-17</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>996033</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017950422</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15039</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-05-27</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
