<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-31T08:41:08</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224932</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224932</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-28</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-31</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>KIMINO</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>8</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ръчни инструменти, ръчнодействащи; Комплекти за педикюр; Комплекти за маникюр; Комплекти за маникюр, електрически; Ножички за почистване на кожичките около ноктите; Пилички за нокти; Ножици; Ножици за коса за лично ползване [електрически и неелектрически]; Пинцети за отстраняване на косми; Щипки за извиване на мигли; Маши за къдрене; Обезкосмяващи уреди, електрически и неелектрически; Уреди за подстригване на брада; Маши за къдрене; Нокти (Инструменти за полиране на -) [електрически или неелектрически].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nástroje na ruční pohon; Soupravy na pedikůru; Soupravy na manikúru; Elektrické manikúrní soupravy; Kleštičky na kůži; Pilníky na nehty; Nůžky; Strojky na stříhání vlasů pro osobní potřebu, elektrické i neelektrické; Epilační pinzety; Kleštičky na řasy; Ruční nástroje na kadeření vlasů; Zařízení na depilaci, elektrická i neelektrická; Zastřihovače vousů; Kulmy na vlasy; Leštičky na nehty, elektrické i neelektrické.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Håndværktøj, hånddrevet; Pedicuresæt; Manicuresæt; Manicuresæt, elektriske; Neglebåndstænger; Neglefile; Sakse; Hårklippere til personlig brug, elektriske og ikke-elektriske; Pincetter til hårfjerning; Øjenvippebukker; Håndredskaber til hårkrølning; Hårfjerningsapparater, elektriske og ikke- elektriske; Skægtrimmere; Krøllejern; Neglepolerere, elektriske eller ikke elektriske.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Handbetätigte Handwerkzeuge; Pedikürenecessaires; Manikürenecessaires; Elektrische Maniküre-Sets; Nagelhautzangen; Nagelfeilen; Scheren; Elektrische oder nicht elektrische Haarschneidemaschinen; Pinzetten zum Epilieren; Wimpernzangen; Handbetätigte Frisiergeräte; Haarentfernungsgeräte [elektrische und nicht elektrische]; Bartschneidemaschinen; Haarbrenneisen; Fingernagelpolierer [elektrisch oder nicht elektrisch].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εργαλεία χειρός χειροκίνητα· Σετ ποδοκομίας (πεντικιούρ)· Περιποίησης χεριών (Θήκες οργάνων -)· Περιποίησης νυχιών (Σετ με είδη -) ηλεκτρικά· Παρωνυχίδες (πένσες -ων)· Νυχιών (Λίμες -)· Ψαλίδι· Μαλλιά (ψαλίδια κοπής για κούρεμα -ών) ηλεκτρικά και μη· Αποτρίχωση (τσιμπιδάκια -ης)· Πενσάκια για γυριστές βλεφαρίδες· Εργαλεία χειρός για δημιουργία κυματισμών στα μαλλιά· Αποτρίχωση (συσκευές -ης) ηλεκτρικές ή μη· Γενειάδας (Ψαλίδες κοπής -)· Εργαλεία χειρός για δημιουργία κυματισμών στα μαλλιά· Εργαλεία για γυάλισμα των νυχιών, ηλεκτρικά ή μη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hand tools, hand-operated; Pedicure sets; Manicure sets; manicure sets, electric; Cuticle nippers; Nail files; Scissors; Hair clippers for personal use, electric and non-electric; Hair-removing tweezers; Eyelash curlers; Hand implements for hair curling; Depilation appliances, electric and non-electric; Beard clippers; Curling tongs; Nail buffers, electric or non-electric.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Herramientas de mano accionadas manualmente; Estuches de pedicura; Estuches de manicura; Neceseres de instrumentos de manicura eléctricos; Alicates para cutículas; Limas de uñas; Tijeras; Maquinillas eléctricas o no para cortar el cabello; Pinzas de depilar; Rizadores de pestañas; Aparatos de mano para rizar el cabello; Aparatos de depilación eléctricos o no; Maquinillas para cortar la barba; Rizadores; Pulidores de uñas [eléctricos o no].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Käsitsi käitatavad käsi-tööriistad; Pediküürikomplektid; Maniküürikomplektid; Elektrilised maniküürikomplektid; Kraatide, lõikeserva kidade lõiketangid, pintsetid; Küüneviilid; Käärid; Elektrilised ja mitteelektrilised juukselõikusmasinad; Karvaärastuspintsetid; Ripsmekoolutajad; Juukselokkimisvahendid [käsi-tööriistad]; Elektrilised ja mitteelektrilised karvaeemaldusvahendid; Habemepügamismasinad; Lokitangid; Elektrilised või mitteelektrilised küünepoleerijad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Käsityökalut, käsikäyttöiset; Pedikyyrivälineet; Manikyyrivälineet; Manikyyrivälineet, sähkökäyttöiset; Kynsinauhapinsetit; Kynsiviilat; Sakset; Hiusleikkurit henkilökohtaiseen käyttöön [sähkö- tai käsikäyttöiset]; Karvanpoistopinsetit; Kihartimet silmäripsiä varten; Hiuskihartimet, käsikäyttöiset; Karvanpoistolaitteet, sähkö- ja ei-sähkökäyttöiset; Partaleikkurit; Hiuskihartimet, käsikäyttöiset; Kynsien kiillottimet [sähkö- tai käsikäyttöiset].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Outils à main actionnés manuellement; Trousses de pédicures; Trousses de manucures; Nécessaires de manucure électriques; Pinces à cuticules; Limes à ongles; Ciseaux; Tondeuses pour la coupe des cheveux, électriques et non électriques; Pinces à épiler; Recourbe-cils; Appareils à main à friser les cheveux; Épilateurs électriques ou non électriques; Tondeuses à barbe; Fers à friser; Polissoirs d'ongles électriques ou non électriques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Ručni alat [ručno pokretani]; Torbe s pedikerskim priborom; Torbe s priborom za manikiranje; Manikerski pribor (električni mankerski pribor); Škarice za zanoktice; Turpijice za nokte; Škare; Kosa (naprave za šišanje kose) električne i neelektrične; Pincete za uklanjanje dlačica; Uvijači za trepavice; Ručne sprave za kovrčanje kose; Električni i neelektrični depilacijski uređaji; Brada (sprave za šišanje brade); Kosa (ručne sprave za kovrčanje kose); Četke za poliranje noktiju, električne ili obične.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kézzel működtetett kéziszerszámok; Pedikűr készletek; Manikűrkészletek; Manikűrkészletek, elektromos; Körömágybőr vágó csipeszek; Körömreszelők; Ollók; Elektromos és nem elektromos hajnyíró gépek; Szőrtelenítő csipeszek; Szempillagöndörítők; Kézi hajsütővasak; Elektromos és nem elektromos szőrtelenítő eszközök; Szakállnyírók; Kézi hajsütővasak; Elektromos vagy nem elektromos körömfényesítők, körömpolírozók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Utensili a mano azionati manualmente; Astucci da pedicure; Astucci da manicure; Servizi per manicure elettrici; Pinzette per pipite; Lime per unghie; Forbici; Macchine per il taglio dei capelli elettriche e non elettriche; Pinzette per depilare; Piegaciglia; Apparecchi manuali per arricciare i capelli; Apparecchi per la depilazione elettrici e non elettrici; Macchinette per tagliare la barba; Ferri per arricciare; Lucidatrici per unghie elettriche o non elettriche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Rankiniai įrankiai; Pedikiūro įrankių komplektai; Manikiūro įrankių komplektai; Elektriniai manikiūro įrankių komplektai; Odos žnyplelės (pincetai); Nagų dildės; Žirklės; Elektriniai ir ne elektriniai plaukų kirpimo įrankiai; Plaukų šalinimo žnyplės; Blakstienų rietikliai; Žnyplės (Plaukų sukimo -); Elektriniai ir ne elektriniai plaukų šalinimo reikmenys; Rankinės barzdos kirpimo mašinėlės; Plaukų sukimo žnyplės; Elektriniai ar ne elektriniai nagų poliravimo prietaisai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ar roku darbināmi instrumenti; Pedikīra piederumu komplekti; Manikīra piederumu komplekti; Manikīra piederumu komplekti, elektriski; Kutikulas knaiblītes; Smirģeļi; Šķēres; Matu griešanas ierīces personiskai lietošanai, elektriskas un ne elektriskas; Pincetes matiņu likvidēšanai; Skropstu atliecēji; Lokšķēres; Depilācijas ierīces, elektriskas un ne elektriskas; Bārdas trimeri; Lokšķēres; Elektriski vai neelektriski nagu pulētāji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Għodda tal-idejn, operati bl-idejn; Settijiet tal-pedikjur; Settijiet tal-manikjur; Settijiet tal-manikjur, tal-elettriku; Pinzetti tar-rita; Limi tad-dwiefer; Imqassijiet; Apparat li jaqta' x-xagħar għal użu personali, elettriku u mhux elettriku; Pinzetti għat-tneħħija tax-xagħar; Tagħmir għall-brim tax-xagħar tal-għajnejn; Tnalji li jobormu; Tagħmir depilatorju (elettriku u mhux elettriku); Magni tal-qtugħ tal-leħja; Tnalji li jobormu; Bafers tad-dwiefer, elettriċi jew mhux elettriċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Handgereedschappen, met de hand te bedienen; Etuis voor pedicures; Etuis voor manicures; Elektrische manicure-sets; Nagelriemtangetjes; Nagelvijlen; Scharen; Tondeuses voor het haar, elektrisch en niet-elektrisch; Epileertangetjes; Tangen voor het krullen van de wimpers; Haarkrulapparaten, handbediend; Epileerapparaten, elektrisch of niet-elektrisch; Tondeuses voor de baard; Friseerijzers; Nagelpolijsters, elektrisch of niet-elektrisch.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Narzędzia ręczne o napędzie ręcznym; Zestawy do pedicure; Zestawy do manicure; Zestawy do manicure, elektryczne; Cążki do skórek; Pilniki do paznokci; Nożyczki; Maszynki do strzyżenia włosów do użytku osobistego, elektryczne i nieelektryczne; Pęsety do depilacji; Zalotki do rzęs; Lokówki; Przybory do depilacji, elektryczne lub nieelektryczne; Maszynki do strzyżenia brody; Lokówki; Polerki do paznokci, elektryczne lub nieelektryczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Ferramentas manuais acionadas manualmente; Estojos de pedicuras; Estojos de manicure; Kits elétricos de manicura; Alicates de unhas; Limas para unhas; Tesouras; Máquinas de corte de cabelo, elétricas ou não; Pinças para depilar; Pinças para curvar as pestanas; Utensílios manuais para frisar os cabelos; Aparelhos para a depilação, elétricos e não elétricos; Máquinas para o corte da barba; Pinças para ondular; Polidores de unhas, elétricos ou não.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Unelte de mână, acţionate manual; Truse de pedichiură; Truse de manichiură; Truse de manichiură [electrice]; Instrumente pentru îndepărtarea cuticulelor; Unghii (Pile pentru -); Foarfece; Maşini de tuns părul, electrice şi neelectrice; Pensete pentru îndepărtarea părului; Cleşti pentru întors genele; Aparate manuale pentru ondularea părului; Aparate pentru epilat, electrice sau neelectrice; Barba (Maşini de tuns -); Aparate manuale pentru ondularea părului; Pile de unghii, electrice sau neelectrice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ručné nástroje a náradie (na ručný pohon); Pedikúrové súpravy; Manikúrové súpravy; Manikúrové súpravy (Elektrické -); Klieštiky; Pilníky na nechty; Nožnice; Nožnice na strihanie vlasov (elektrické alebo neelektrické); Epilačné pinzety; Klieštiky na očné riasy; Kulmy na vlasy; Depilačné strojčeky (elektrické alebo neelektrické); Nožnice na strihanie fúzov a brady; Kliešte na kučeravenie vlasov; Leštičky na nechty (elektrické alebo neelektrické).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Ročno orodje za ročno uporabo; Pribor (garniture) za pedikuro; Garniture za manikiro; Garniture za manikiro, električne; Pincete za odstranjevanje kožice pri nohtih; Pilice za nohte; Škarje; Strojčki za rezanje las za osebno uporabo (električni ali ne električni); Pincete za odstranjevanje dlak; Klešče za vihanje trepalnic; Klešče za kodranje las; Aparati za depiliranje, električni in ne električni; Aparati za striženje brade; Klešče za kodranje las; Naprave za poliranje nohtov (električne ali ne električne).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Handdrivna handverktyg; Pedikyrset; Manikyrset; Elektriska manikyrset; Nagelbandstänger; Nagelfilar; Saxar; Hårklippningsmaskiner för personligt bruk (elektriska och icke elektriska); Hårborttagningspincetter; Ögonfransböjare; Handredskap för lockning av hår; Elektriska och icke-elektriska hårborttagningsredskap; Skäggklippare; Locktänger; Nagelpolerare (elektriska eller icke-elektriska).</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Козметични принадлежности; Тоалетни чанти; Тоалетни чанти; Гъбички за нанасяне на грим; Пухчета за пудра; Четки за вежди; Четки за бръснене; Поставки за четки за бръснене; Козметични четки; Четки за мигли; Бутилки; Пулверизатори за парфюм; Разделители от пяна, за пръсти на крака, за употреба при педикюр; Приспособления за отстраняване на грим; Козметични шпатули.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kosmetické pomůcky; Toaletní taštičky; Toaletní taštičky; Houbičky na nanášení líčidel; Labutěnky na pudrování; Kartáčky na obočí; Štětky na holení; Stojánky na štětky na holení; Štětce na nanášení líčidel; Kartáčky na řasy; Lahve; Rozprašovače na parfémy; Pěnové pedikérní separátory prstů; Zařízení na odličování; Kosmetické špachtle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Redskaber til kosmetisk brug; Rejsenecessaire; Rejsenecessaire; Makeupsvampe; Pudderkvaster; Øjenbrynsbørster; Barberkoste; Holdere til barberkoste; Kosmetikbørster; Øjenvippebørster; Flasker; Parfumeforstøvere; Tåskillere af skum til brug ved pedicure; Make-up fjerneapparater; Kosmetiske spatler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kosmetische Geräte; Toilettenecessaires; Toilettenecessaires; Schminkschwämme; Puderquasten; Augenbrauenbürsten; Rasierpinsel; Rasierpinselhalter; Kosmetikpinsel; Wimpernbürsten; Flaschen; Parfümzerstäuber; Zehentrenner aus Schaumstoff für die Pediküre; Abschminkgeräte; Kosmetische Spatel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καλλυντικά (Σκεύη -)· Σετ τουαλέτας σε τσαντάκι· Σετ τουαλέτας σε τσαντάκι· Σφουγγαράκια για μακιγιάζ· Σφουγγαράκια πουδραρίσματος· Βουρτσάκια για τα φρύδια· Βούρτσες ξυρίσματος· Βάσεις πινέλων ξυρίσματος· Καλλυντικές βούρτσες· Βουρτσάκια για τις βλεφαρίδες· Φιάλες· Αρώματος (Ψεκαστήρες -)· Διαχωριστικά για τα δάχτυλα των ποδιών από αφρώδες υλικό για χρήση στην ποδοκομία (πεντικιούρ)· Συσκευές αφαίρεσης μακιγιάζ· Σπάτουλες για καλλυντικά.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">cosmetic utensils; Toilet cases; Fitted vanity cases; Make-up sponges; Powder puffs; Eyebrow brushes; Shaving brushes; Shaving brush stands; Make-up brushes; Eyelash brushes; Bottles; Perfume sprayers; Foam toe separators for use in pedicures; Make-up removing appliances; Cosmetic spatulas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Utensilios cosméticos; Neceseres de tocador; Neceseres de tocador; Esponjas para aplicar maquillaje; Borlas de polvera; Cepillos para las cejas; Brochas de afeitar; Portabrochas de afeitar; Cepillos para uso cosmético; Cepillos para pestañas; Botellas; Pulverizadores de perfume; Separadores interdigitales de espuma para la pedicura; Aparatos para desmaquillar; Espátulas para uso cosmético.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kosmeetikatarbed; Tualett-tarvete kotid; Tualett-tarvete kotid; Jumestuskäsnad; Puudritupsud; Kulmuharjad; Habemeajamispintslid; Habemeajamispintslite hoidlid; Kosmeetikaharjad; Ripsmepintslid; Pudelid; Parfüümipihustid, parfüümipulverisaatorid; Vahtplastist varbavahekud pediküüris kasutamiseks; Meigieemaldustarvikud; Kosmeetilised spaatlid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kosmetiikkavälineet; Toalettilaukut; Toalettilaukut; Meikkisienet; Puuterihuiskut; Kulmakarvasiveltimet; Partasudit; Partasutitelineet; Harjat kosmeettisiin tarkoituksiin; Silmäripsiharjat; Pullot; Parfyymisuihkepullot; Jalkahoidossa käytettävät vaahtomuoviset varpaanerottelijat; Ehostuksen poistovälineet; Lastat kosmeettiseen käyttöön.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Ustensiles cosmétiques; Nécessaires de toilette; Nécessaires de toilette; Éponges pour le maquillage; Houppes à poudrer; Brosses à sourcils; Blaireaux à barbe; Porte-blaireaux; Pinceaux de maquillage; Brosses à cils; Bouteilles; Vaporisateurs à parfum; Séparateurs d'orteils en mousse pour soins de pédicurie; Appareils pour le démaquillage; Spatules à usage cosmétique.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kozmetički pribor; Toaletni neseseri; Toaletni neseseri; Spužvice za nanošenje šminke; Jastučići za nanošenje pudera; Četkice za obrve; Četkice za brijanje brade; Držači za četke za brijanje; Kozmetičke četke; Četkice za trepavice; Boce; Raspršivači mirisa [parfema]; Separatori nožnih prstiju od pjene za uporabu u pedikuri; Pribor za skidanje šminke; Kozmetičke lopatice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Kozmetikai eszközök; Piperetáskák, neszesszerek; Piperetáskák, neszesszerek; Sminkszivacsok; Púderpamacsok; Szemöldökkefék; Borotvapamacsok, borotvaecsetek; Borotvapamacs tartók; Kozmetikai ecsetek, pipere ecsetek; Szempilla kefék; Palackok; Parfümpermetezők, illatszerpermetezők; Szivacsos lábujjszétválasztók pedikűrözéshez; Sminkeltávolító termékek; Kozmetikai spatulák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Utensili cosmetici; Nécessaire per la toilette; Nécessaire per la toilette; Spugnette da make-up; Piumino della cipria; Spazzole per sopracciglia; Pennelli per la barba; Porta-pennelli per la barba; Spazzole per usi cosmetici; Spazzole per le ciglia; Bottiglie; Vaporizzatori di profumi; Separatori per le dita dei piedi per pedicure; Apparecchi elettrici per togliere il trucco; Spatole ad uso cosmetico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kosmetikos reikmenys; Tualeto reikmeninės; Tualeto reikmeninės; Makiažo kempinėlės; Pudrinukai; Antakių šepetėliai; Skutimosi šepetėliai; Skutimosi šepetėlių laikikliai; Kosmetiniai šepetėliai; Blakstienų šepetėliai; Buteliai; Kvepalų garintuvai; Putplasčio kojų pirštų skirtukai (pedikiūro reikmėms); Grimo valymo reikmenys; Kosmetinės mentelės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kosmētikas piederumi; Tualetes maciņi; Tualetes maciņi; Kosmētiskie sūkļi; Pūdera spilventiņi; Uzacu birstītes; Skūšanās otiņas; Skūšanās otiņu statīvi; Kosmētikas otiņas; Skropstu birstītes; Pudeles; Parfīma pulverizatori; Putu materiāla ieliktņi pirkstu atdalīšanai, paredzēti izmantošanai pedikīrā; Piederumi dekoratīvās kosmētikas noņemšanai; Lāpstiņas kosmētiskiem nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Utensili kożmetiċi; Kaxxi fejn jitpoġġew l-oġġetti tat-twaletta; Kaxxi fejn jitpoġġew l-oġġetti tat-twaletta; Sponoż tal-mejkapp; Peds għat-terra; Xkupilji tal-ħuġbejn; Pniezel tal-leħja; Sostenn għall-pinzell tal-leħja; Pniezel kożmetiċi; Pniezel tax-xagħar ta' xfar l-għajnejn; Fliexken; Sprejers tal-fwieħa; Separaturi tal-fowm għas-subgħajn tas-saqajn għall-użu fil-pedikjur; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tneħħija tal-irtokk; Spatulas kosmetiċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Cosmetisch gerei; Toiletnecessaires; Toiletnecessaires; Sponsjes voor make-up; Poederkwasten; Wenkbrauwborsteltjes; Scheerkwasten; Scheerkwasthouders; Borstels voor cosmetische doeleinden; Borstels voor de oogwimpers; Flessen; Parfumverstuivers; Schuimvormen voor het uit elkaar houden van de tenen voor gebruik bij voetverzorging; Elektrische apparaten voor het verwijderen van make-up; Spateltjes voor cosmetisch gebruik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przybory kosmetyczne; Kosmetyczki na przybory toaletowe; Kosmetyczki na przybory toaletowe; Gąbki do makijażu; Puszki do pudru; Szczoteczki do brwi; Pędzle do golenia; Stojaki na pędzle do golenia; Pędzle kosmetyczne; Szczoteczki do rzęs; Butelki; Rozpylacze do perfum; Separatory piankowe do palców stóp do użytku podczas pedicure; Przyrządy do demakijażu; Szpatułki kosmetyczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Utensílios cosméticos; Bolsas de toucador; Bolsas de toucador; Esponjas para maquilhagem; Esponjas de pó-de-arroz; Escovas para sobrancelhas; Pincéis para barbear; Porta-pincéis para barbear; Escovas para fins cosméticos; Escovas para pestanas; Garrafas; Pulverizadores de perfume; Esponjas para separar dedos dos pés, para uso em pedicura; Aparelhos para remover maquilhagem; Espátulas para uso cosmético.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cosmetice (Ustensile -); Truse de toaletă; Truse de toaletă; Bureţei pentru machiaj; Pămătufuri pentru pudrat; Sprâncene (Periuţe pentru -); Bărbierit (Pămătufuri pentru -); Suporturi pentru pămătufuri de bărbierit; Pensule de uz cosmetic; Periuţe pentru gene; Sticle; Pulverizatoare de parfum; Separatoare din spumă pentru degetele de la picioare folosite în pedichiură; Dispozitive de demachiere; Spatule cosmetice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kozmetické pomôcky; Tašky alebo kufríky na toaletné potreby; Tašky alebo kufríky na toaletné potreby; Špongie na nanášanie líčidiel; Labutienky; Štetce na obočie; Štetky na holenie; Stojany na štetky na holenie; Kozmetické štetce; Kefky na očné riasy; Fľaše; Rozprašovače na voňavky; Penové oddeľovače prstov na nohách (pedikérske potreby); Odličovacie pomôcky; Kozmetické špachtle.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kozmetični pripomočki; Toaletne torbice; Toaletne torbice; Gobice za nanašanje ličil; Pudrne blazinice; Krtačke za obrvi; Čopiči za britje; Stojala za čopiče za britje; Čopiči za kozmetične namene; Ščetke za trepalnice; Steklenice; Uparjalniki za parfume; Razdelilci iz penaste gume za uporabo v pedikuri; Aparati za odstranjevanje ličil; Kozmetične lopatice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kosmetikutensilier; Resenecessärer (inredda); Resenecessärer (inredda); Svampar för make-up; Pudervippor; Ögonbrynsborstar; Rakborstar; Ställ för rakborstar; Sminkborstar; Borstar för ögonfransar; Flaskor; Raffräschissörer för parfym; Tåseparatorer av skum för användning i pedikyr; Redskap för sminkborttagning; Kosmetiska spatlar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/095</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-21</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/165</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-31</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079140</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>32203</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
