<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-16T12:20:04</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224697</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224697</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-28</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>fr</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Bisous de lapin</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>3</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Козметични тоалетни принадлежности; Почистващи и ароматизиращи препарати; Етерични масла и ароматни екстракти.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Toaletní přípravky; Čistící prostředky a vonné přípravky; Vonné oleje a aromatické výtažky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Toiletartikler; Rengørings- og duftpræparater; Æteriske olier og aromatiske udtræk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Körperpflegemittel; Reinigungs- und Duftpräparate; Ätherische Öle und aromatische Extrakte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καλλυντικά· Καθαριστικά και αρωματικά παρασκευάσματα· Αιθέρια έλαια και αρωματικά εκχυλίσματα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Toiletries; Cleaning and fragrancing preparations; Essential oils and aromatic extracts.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Artículos de tocador; Preparaciones para limpiar y aromatizar; Aceites esenciales y extractos aromáticos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tualett-tarbed; Puhastus- ja lõhnastusained; Eeterlikud õlid ja aroomiekstraktid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kosmeettiset ja peseytymisvalmisteet; Puhdistus- ja raikastusvalmisteet; Eteeriset öljyt ja aromaattiset uutteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits de toilettes; Préparations nettoyantes et parfumantes; Huiles essentielles et extraits aromatiques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Toaletni proizvodi; Pripravci za čišćenje i osvježivanje prostora; Esencijalna ulja i aromatični ekstrakti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Testápolási cikkek; Tisztító és illatosító készítmények; Olajesszenciák és aromakivonatok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Toiletteria; Preparati per pulire e profumare; Olii essenziali ed estratti aromatici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Tualeto reikmenys; Valymo ir kvėpinimo preparatai; Eteriniai aliejai ir aromatiniai ekstraktai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Personiskās tualetes līdzekļi; Tīrīšanas un aromatizēšanas līdzekļi; Ēteriskās eļļas un aromātiskie ekstrakti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Preparazzjonijiet tat-twaletta; Preparazzjonijiet għat-tindif u għal riħa tfuħ; Żjut essenzjali u estratti aromatiċi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Preparaten voor de toiletverzorging; Reinigingsproducten en geurproducten; Essentiële oliën en aromatische extracten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Środki toaletowe; Preparaty do czyszczenia i odświeżania; Olejki esencjonalne i ekstrakty aromatyczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Produtos de toilette; Produtos para limpar e perfumar; Óleos essenciais e extratos aromáticos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Produse pentru toaletă; Preparate pentru curățare și odorizante; Uleiuri esențiale și extracte aromatice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kozmetické výrobky; Čistiace a vonné prípravky; Éterické oleje a aromatické výťažky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Toaletna sredstva; Preparati za čiščenje in odišavljanje; Eterična olja in aromatični ekstrakti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Toalettartiklar; Rengöringsmedel och välluktande preparat; Eteriska oljor och aromatiska extrakt.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Диетични храни, пригодени за новородени; Напитки за бебета; Храна за бебета; Диетични храни за употреба в клинично хранене; Диетични храни, пригодени за инвалиди; Диетични храни за лечебни цели; Хранителни продукти за диабетици; Препарати за кърмачета; Хранителни добавки и диетични препарати; Санитарни препарати и изделия; Хигиенни препарати и изделия за медицински цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Dietetické potraviny přizpůsobené pro malé děti; Nápoje pro kojence; Potraviny pro kojence a batolata; Dietetické potraviny používané v klinické výživě; Dietní potraviny přizpůsobené pro nemocné; Dietetické potraviny pro léčebné účely; Potraviny pro diabetiky; Kojenecká výživa; Potravní doplňky a dietetické přípravky; Hygienické přípravky a výrobky; Hygienické přípravky a výrobky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Diætetiske næringsmidler til spædbørn; Drikke til spædbørn; Mad til spædbørn; Diætetiske næringsmidler til brug i klinisk næring; Diætetiske næringsmidler til invalide; Diætetiske næringsmidler tilpasset medicinske formål; Fødevarer til diabetikere; Spædbørnsmad; Kosttilskud og diætetiske præparater; Hygiejniske præparater og artikler; Hygiejniske præparater og artikler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Diätnahrungsmittel für Säuglinge; Getränke für Babys; Babynahrungsmittel; Diätnahrungsmittel für die klinische Ernährung; Diätnahrungsmittel für Kranke; Diätnahrungsmittel für medizinische Zwecke; Speziell für Diabetiker hergestellte Nahrungsmittel; Babykost; Diätetische Präparate und Nahrungsergänzungsmittel; Hygienepräparate und -artikel; Hygienepräparate und -artikel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαιτητικά τρόφιμα προσαρμοσμένα για νήπια· Ροφήματα για βρέφη· Βρεφικές/Παιδικές τροφές· Διαιτητικές τροφές για χρήση στην κλινική διατροφή· Διαιτητικά τρόφιμα προσαρμοσμένα για αναπήρους· Τροφές διαιτητικές για ιατρική χρήση· Τρόφιμα για διαβητικούς· Βρεφοτροφές· Συμπληρώματα διατροφής και διαιτητικά παρασκευάσματα· Παρασκευάσματα υγειονομικά και είδη αυτών· Παρασκευάσματα υγειονομικά και είδη αυτών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Dietetic foods adapted for infants; Beverages for infants; Food for babies; Dietetic foods for use in clinical nutrition; Dietetic foods adapted for invalids; Dietetic foods adapted for medical purposes; Food for diabetics; Food for infants; Dietary supplements and dietetic preparations; Sanitary preparations and articles; Hygienic preparations and articles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Alimentos dietéticos adaptados a bebés; Bebidas para bebés; Alimentos para bebés; Alimentos dietéticos para su uso en la nutrición clínica; Alimentos dietéticos adaptados para personas inválidas; Alimentos dietéticos para uso médico; Alimentos para diabéticos; Alimentos para niños pequeños; Suplementos y preparaciones dietéticas; Preparaciones sanitarias y productos de las mismas; Preparaciones y artículos higiénicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Dieettoidud väikelastele; Imikujoogid; Imikutoit; Dieettoidud kliiniliseks toitumiseks; Invaliididele kohandatud dieettoidud; Meditsiinilised dieettoidud; Toiduained diabeetikutele; Imikutoidud; Toidulisandid ja farmatseutilised dieetained; Hügieenipreparaadid ja -tooted; Hügieenipreparaadid ja -tooted.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lapsille tarkoitetut dieettiruoat; Vauvojen juomat; Vauvanruoat; Dieettiruoat käytettäväksi kliinisessä ravitsemisessa; Invalideille tarkoitetut dieettiruoat; Dieettiravintoaineet lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Diabeetikoille tarkoitetut ruuat; Vauvanruuat; Lisäravinteet ja dieettivalmisteet; Saniteettivalmisteet ja -tarvikkeet; Hygieniavalmisteet ja -tuotteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Aliments diététiques pour nourrissons; Boissons pour bébés; Aliments pour bébés; Aliments diététiques pour la nutrition clinique; Aliments diététiques pour personnes malades; Aliments diététiques à usage médical; Aliments pour diabétiques; Aliments pour nourrissons; Compléments alimentaires et préparations diététiques; Préparation et articles d'hygiène; Préparations et articles d'hygiène.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Dijetetska hrana prilagođena za dojenčad; Napitci za dojenčad; Hrana za bebe; Dijetetska hrana za kliničku prehranu; Dijetetska hrana prilagođena za invalide; Dijetetska hrana prilagođena za medicinske potrebe; Hrana za dijabetičare; Hrana za dojenčad; Dodaci prehrani i dijetetski pripravci; Sanitarni pripravci i proizvodi; Higijenski pripravci i proizvodi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Diétás ételek csecsemők számára; Babaitalok, csecsemő italok; Bébiételek; Diétás élelmiszerek klinikai tápláláshoz; Diétás ételek betegek számára; Diétás ételek gyógyászati célokra; Ételek cukorbetegeknek; Bébiételek; Táplálékkiegészítők és diétás készítmények; Egészségügyi készítmények és cikkek; Higiéniai készítmények és cikkek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Alimenti dietetici adattati per bambini piccoli; Bevande per bambini piccoli; Alimenti per bambini (neonati); Alimenti dietetici per nutrizione clinica; Alimenti dietetici per invalidi; Alimenti dietetici per uso medico; Alimenti per diabetici; Alimenti per neonati; Integratori alimentari e preparati dietetici; Preparati e prodotti per l'igiene; Preparati ed articoli per l'igiene.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kūdikių dietinis maistas; Kūdikių gėrimai; Kūdikių maistas; Dietiniai maisto produktai, skirti naudoti klinikinės mitybos reikmėms; Neįgaliesiems pritaikyti dietiniai maisto produktai; Dietinis maistas (medicinos reikmėms); Diabetikų maisto produktai; Maistas (kūdikių); Maisto papildai ir dietiniai produktai; Higienos preparatai ir gaminiai; Higienos preparatai ir priemonės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Diētisks uzturs zīdaiņiem; Dzērieni zīdaiņiem; Maisījumi zīdaiņiem; Diētisks uzturs ēdināšanai veselības aprūpes centros; Diētisks uzturs nespējīgām personām; Diētiskā pārtika medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Pārtika diabētiķiem; Mātes piena aizstājēji zīdaiņiem; Uztura bagātinātāji un diētiskie preparāti; Sanitārie līdzekļi un izstrādājumi; Higiēnas līdzekļi un izstrādājumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ikel tad-dieta adattati għat-tfal żgħar; Xarbiet għat-tfal żgħar; Ikel għat-trabi; Ikel tad-dieta għall-użu fin-nutrizzjoni klinika; Ikel dijetetiku adattat għall-morda; Ikel djetetiku addattat għal skopijiet mediċi; Ikel għad-dijabetiċi; Ikel tat-trabi; Supplimenti tad-dieta u preparazzjonijiet dijetetiċi; Prodotti u preparazzjonijiet sanitarji; Preparazzjonijiet u oġġetti iġjenici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Dieetvoedingsmiddelen voor kleine kinderen voor medisch gebruik; Dranken voor zuigelingen; Babyvoeding; Diëtische voedingsmiddelen voor klinische voeding; Diëtische voedingsmiddelen aangepast voor zieken; Dieetvoedingsmiddelen voor medisch gebruik; Voedingsmiddelen voor diabetici; Voedingsmiddelen voor baby's; Diëtische supplementen en diëtische preparaten; Hygiënische preparaten en artikelen; Hygiënische preparaten en producten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dietetyczna żywność przystosowana dla niemowląt; Napoje dla niemowląt; Żywność dla niemowląt; Pokarmy dietetyczne używane w żywieniu klinicznym; Dietetyczna żywność przystosowana dla niepełnosprawnych; Dietetyczna żywność przystosowana do celów medycznych; Żywność dla diabetyków; Produkty żywnościowe dla niemowląt; Suplementy diety i preparaty dietetyczne; Preparaty i artykuły higieniczne; Preparaty i artykuły higieniczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Alimentos dietéticos para bebés; Bebidas para crianças; Alimentos para bebés; Alimentos dietéticos para uso em nutrição clínica; Alimentos dietéticos adaptados para pessoas inválidas; Alimentos dietéticos para uso medicinal; Alimentos para diabéticos; Alimentos para crianças; Suplementos e preparações dietéticos; Preparações e artigos de higiene; Preparações e artigos higiénicos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Alimente dietetice adaptate pentru copii; Băuturi pentru copii mici; Alimente pentru bebeluși; Alimente dietetice pentru utilizare în nutriția clinică; Alimente dietetice adaptate pentru bolnavi; Alimente dietetice de uz medical; Alimente pentru diabetici [produse speciale]; Copii mici (Alimente pentru -); Suplimente alimentare si preparate dietetice; Preparate și articole sanitare; Produse și articole pentru igienă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Dietetické potraviny upravené pre malé deti; Nápoje pre deti; Potraviny pre dojčatá; Dietetické potraviny používané v oblasti klinickej výživy; Diétne potraviny pre ľudí s postihnutím; Diétne potraviny na lekárske použitie; Potraviny pre diabetikov; Potrava pre dojčatá; Výživové doplnky a dietetické prípravky; Hygienické prípravky a výrobky; Hygienické prípravky a potreby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Dietetična živila, prirejena za dojenčke; Napitki za dojenčke; Hrana za dojenčke; Dietetična živila, ki se uporabljajo v klinični prehrani; Dietetična živila, prilagojena za invalide; Dietetična hrana, prilagojena za medicinske namene; Hrana za diabetike; Otroško mleko; Prehranska dopolnila in dietetske snovi; Sanitarni pripravki in izdelki; Izdelki in preparati za higieno.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Dietiska livsmedel anpassade för spädbarn; Drycker för spädbarn; Mat för bebisar; Dietiska livsmedel för klinisk kost; Dietiska livsmedel anpassade för sjuka personer; Dietiska födoämnespreparat anpassade för medicinska ändamål; Livsmedel för diabetiker; Mat för spädbarn; Dietiska tillskott och preparat; Sanitära preparat och -artiklar; Hygieniska preparat och artiklar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>29</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Риба, морски дарове и мекотели, неживи; Супи и бульони, месни екстракти; Млечни произведения и млечни заместители; Месо и месни продукти; Птичи яйца и яйчни продукти; Обработени плодове, гъби, зеленчуци, ядки и варива; Пилешки крилца; Охладени храни, състоящи се предимно от риба; Пърженки с извара; Панирани пилешки хапки; Биск [гъсти супи]; Телешки бульон; Силен месен бульон [супи]; Кюфтета; Булкоги [корейско ястие с телешко месо]; Приготвено говеждо месо; Сепия [готова]; Крем супа; Пържени свински кожички; Шиш кебап; Люти чушки със сирене [Chile con queso]; Ястие от чили с месо; Консомета; Рибни крокети; Сарми; Готови предястия, състоящи се предимно от морски дарове; Готови охлюви; Фалафели; Рибни филета, печени на скара; Яйчена крем супа, приготвена на пара; Готвени месни ястия; Готови сготвени ястия, състоящи се предимно от пилешко месо; Готови ястия, състоящи се предимно от пуешко месо; Готови сготвени ястия, състоящи се изцяло или в значителна степен от месо; Готови ястия, състоящи се основно от кебап; Готови сготвени ястия, състоящи се изцяло или в значителна степен от дивеч; Готови сготвени ястия, състоящи се изцяло или в значителна степен от домашни птици; Замразени ястия, състоящи се предимно от месo; Замразени ястия, състоящи се предимно от пилешко месо; Приготвени ястия, състоящи се предимно от обогатена соева паста и тофу [чонгукджанг-джиге]; Приготвени ястия, състоящи се предимно от соева паста и тофу [доенджанг-джиге]; Приготвени ястия, състоящи се предимно от пържено пилешко месо и ферментирала паста от лют червен пипер [дак-галби]; Приготвени ястия, състоящи се предимно от ферментирали зеленчуци, свинско месо и тофу [кимчи-джиге]; Приготвени ястия, състоящи се предимно от пържено говеждо месо и ферментирал соев сос [согалби]; Омлети; Яйчени мъфини; Парчета пилешко месо за употреба, като плънка на сандвичи; Черен боб в соев сос [конджабан]; Овчарски пай; Приготвени на пара или печени кексчета от рибна паста [камабоко]; Приготвени на пара кексчета от пресована риба и сладък тропически картоф [хампен]; Гуакамоле [мляно авокадо]; Бамя; Фритата; Галби [ястие от месо, приготвено на скара]; Риба с пържени картофи; Замразена приготвена риба; Замразени ястия, състоящи се предимно от месо от домашни птици; Замразени ястия, състоящи се предимно от риба; Готови ястия, приготвени от птиче месо [предимно птиче]; Готови ястия, приготвени от месо [месото преобладава]; Готови ястия от месо; Замразени приготвени ястия, състоящи се основно от зеленчуци; Сготвени ястия, състоящи се главно от месо; Приготвени ястия, съдържащи [предимно] пилешко месо; Приготвени ястия, състоящи се предимно от риба; Приготвени ястия, съдържащи [предимно] бекон; Готови ястия, състоящи се основно от морски дарове; Приготвени ястия, състоящи се основно от пуешко месо; Готови ястия, състоящи се предимно от патешко месо; Приготвени ястия, съдържащи [предимно] яйца; Готови ястия, съдържащи главно заместители на месо; Приготвени ястия, състоящи се основно от зеленчуци; Готови ястия, състоящи се основно от дивеч; Готови ястия, съставени предимно от рибени кейкове, зеленчуци, варени яйца и бульон (оден); Предварително опаковани ястия, състоящи се предимно от морски дарове; Замразени, предварително опаковани предястия, състоящи се предимно от меса; Бързо замразени зеленчукови ястия; Приготвени ястия, състоящи се предимно от пилешко месо и женшен [самгетанг]; Ястия, състоящи се основно от риба; Пълнени картофи; Супи; Пържено пиле; Пиле на грил (якитори); Печено пиле; Пиле териаки; Говежда яхния; Предварително приготвено задушено с къри; Яхния; Гювечи [храна]; Предварително опаковани ястия, състоящи се предимно от дивеч; Салата „цезар"; Картофена салата; Салати с месо от домашни птици; Салати за предястие; Зеленчукови салати; Бобови салати; Готови салати; Салати на основата на картофи; Сашими; Супа от нудели; Мисо супа; Супа топчета мацо; Предварително приготвени супи; Предварително приготвени супи мисо; Предварително приготвена супа; Сурими; Тажин [ястие от готвено месо, риба или зеленчуци]; Телешко шкембе; Приготвено месо.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Ryby, mořské plody a měkkýši, neživí; Polévky a vývary, masové výtažky; Mléčné výrobky a jejich náhražky; Maso a masné výrobky; Ptačí vejce a vaječné výrobky; Zpracované ovoce, houby a zelenina, ořechy a luštěniny; Kuřecí křídla; Chlazené potraviny obsahující převážně ryby; Smaženky ze sýru cottage; Kuřecí nugety; Bisques [francouzská krémová polévka]; Hovězí bujon; Vývar (bujón) [polévka]; Masové knedlíčky; Bulgogi [korejský pokrm z hovězího masa]; Zpracované hovězí maso; Kalamáry [upravené]; Krémová rybí polévka; Chicharrón (smažená vepřová kůže); Šiškebab; Chile con queso [sýrová omáčka s chilli papričkami]; Chili con carne; Vývary; Rybí krokety; Dolmy; Hotové předkrmy obsahující převážně plody moře; Upravení hlemýždi; Falafel; Grilované rybí filé; Polévka s vejci vařenými v páře; Vařená masová jídla; Hotová vařená jídla obsahující převážně kuřecí maso; Hotová vařená jídla obsahující převážně krůtí maso; Hotová vařená jídla obsahující výhradně nebo téměř výhradně maso; Hotová jídla sestávající především z kebabu; Hotová vařená jídla obsahující výhradně nebo téměř výhradně zvěřinu; Hotová vařená jídla obsahující výhradně nebo téměř výhradně drůbež; Mražená jídla obsahující převážně maso; Mražená jídla obsahující převážně kuřecí maso; Hotové jídlo obsahující převážně hustou sójovou pastu cheonggukjang a tofu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Hotové jídlo obsahující převážně sójovou pastu doenjang a tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Hotové jídlo obsahující převážně restované kuřecí maso a fermentovanou ostrou paprikovou pastu [dak-galbi]; Hotové jídlo obsahující převážně fermentovanou zeleninu, vepřové maso a tofu [kimči-jjigae]; Hotové jídlo obsahující převážně restované hovězí maso a fermentovanou sójovou omáčku [sogalbi]; Omelety; Vaječné muffiny; Kousky kuřecího masa jako náplň sendvičů; Fazole vařené v sójové omáčce [kongjaban]; Pastýřský koláč (Zapečená směs masa a brambor); Placičky z rybí pasty na páře nebo opečené [kamaboko]; Placičky z mletého rybího masa a jamů vařené v páře [hampen]; Guacamole [pomazánka z avokáda]; Gumbo (polévka); Frittata; Galbi [grilovaný masový pokrm]; Ryby s bramborovými hranolky; Mražené vařené ryby; Mražená jídla obsahující převážně drůbež; Mražená jídla obsahující převážně ryby; Hotová jídla vyrobené z drůbeže (převážně z drůbeže); Hotová jídla vyrobená z masa (převážně z masa); Hotová jídla z masa; Mražená hotová jídla obsahující převážně zeleninu; Hotová jídla obsahující převážně maso; Hotová jídla obsahující (převážně) kuřecí maso; Hotová jídla obsahující převážně ryby; Hotová jídla obsahující (převážně) slaninu; Hotová jídla obsahující převážně mořské plody; Hotová jídla obsahující převážně krůtí maso; Hotová jídla obsahující převážně kachní maso; Hotová jídla obsahující (převážně) vejce; Hotová jídla obsahující převážně masové náhražky; Hotová jídla obsahující převážně zeleninu; Hotové jídla obsahující převážně zvěřinu; Hotová jídla obsahující převážně rybí karbenátky, zeleninu, vařená vejce a vývar (oden); Balené večeře převážně z mořských plodů; Mražené balené předkrmy převážně z plodů moře; Hluboce zmrazené zeleninové pokrmy; Hotové jídlo obsahující převážně kuřecí maso a ženšen [samgyetang]; Vařená jídla obsahující převážně ryby; Plněné brambory ve slupce; Polévky; Smažená kuřata; Grilované kuře (Yakitori); Pečené kuře; Kuře v omáčce teriyaki; Dušené hovězí maso; Předvařená dušená jídla na kari; Dušená jídla; Zapékané pokrmy; Hotová balená jídla, převážně ze zvěřiny; Salát Caesar; Bramborový salát; Drůbeží saláty; Předkrmové saláty (antipasti); Zeleninové saláty; Luštěninové saláty; Hotové saláty (zeleninové, ovocné); Bramborové saláty; Sašimi; Nudlové polévky; Polévka miso; Polévka s macesovými knedlíčky; Polévky v konzervách; Předvařené polévky miso; Předvařené polévky; Surimi; Tajine [hotové jídlo z masa, ryb nebo zeleniny]; Hovězí dršťky; Zpracované maso.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Fisk, skaldyr og bløddyr (ikke levende); Supper og fonder, kødekstrakter; Mejeriprodukter og erstatninger for mejeriprodukter; Kød og kødprodukter; Fugleæg og æggeprodukter; Forarbejdede frugt, svampe, grøntsager, nødder og bælgfrugter; Kyllingevinger; Afkølede fødevarer hovedsageligt bestående af fisk; Beigneter med hytteost; Kyllingenuggets; Bisquéer; Oksekødsbouillon; Bouillon [suppe]; Kødboller; Bulgogi; Tilberedt oksekød; Blæksprutte [tilberedt]; Chowder (tyk fiskesuppe); Chicharrón; Shish kebab; Chili med ost; Chili con carne; Consommé [klar suppe]; Fiskekroketter; Dolmer; Tilberedte forretter hovedsageligt bestående af fisk og skaldyr; Tilberedte snegle; Falafel; Grillede fiskefileter; Sammenkog af dampede æg; Tilberedte kødretter; Tilberedte færdigretter bestående hovedsagelig af kylling; Tilberedte færdigretter hovedsagelig bestående af kalkun; Færdigretter bestående helt eller hovedsageligt af kød; Færdigretter hovedsageligt bestående af kebab; Færdigretter bestående helt eller hovedsageligt af vildt; Færdigretter bestående helt eller hovedsageligt af fjerkræ; Frosne retter, hovedsageligt bestående af kød; Frosne retter bestående hovedsagelig af kylling; Tilberedt måltid hovedsageligt bestående af kraftig sojabønnepasta og tofu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Tilberedt måltid hovedsageligt bestående af sojabønnepasta og tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Tilberedt måltid hovedsageligt bestående af lynstegt kylling og gæret chili-pasta [dak-galbi]; Tilberedt måltid hovedsageligt bestående af gærede grøntsager, svinekød og tofu [kimchi-jjigae]; Tilberedt måltid hovedsageligt bestående af lynstegt oksekød og gæret sojasauce [Sogalbi]; Omeletter; Æggemuffins; Kyllingestykker til brug som fyld i sandwich; Bønner i sojasovs [Kongjaban]; Shepherd´s pie (færdigret af hakket kød og kartoffelmos); Dampede eller ristede fiskefrikadeller [kamaboko]; Dampede kager af most fisk og yamsrod [hampen]; Guacamole; Okra; Frittataer; Galbi [retter bestående af grillet kød]; Fisk med pommes frites; Frossen tilberedt fisk; Frosne retter hovedsagelig bestående af fjerkræ; Frosne retter hovedsagelig bestående af fisk; Færdigretter fremstillet af hovedsageligt fjerkræ; Færdigretter fremstillet af kød [hovedsageligt kød]; Færdigretter fremstillet på basis af kødprodukter; Frosne færdigretter bestående hovedsageligt af grøntsager; Færdigretter bestående hovedsageligt af kød; Færdigretter indeholdende [hovedsagelig] kylling; Færdigretter bestående hovedsageligt af fisk; Færdigretter indeholdende [hovedsagelig] bacon; Færdigretter hovedsageligt bestående af fisk og skaldyr; Færdigretter bestående hovedsagelig af kalkun; Færdigretter bestående hovedsagelig af and; Færdigretter indeholdende [hovedsagelig] æg; Færdigretter hovedsageligt bestående af køderstatninger; Færdigretter hovedsageligt bestående af grøntsager; Færdigretter overvejende bestående af vildt; Færdigretter, hovedsageligt bestående af fiskefrikadeller, grøntsager, kogte æg, og kraftsky; Middagsretter i færdige pakker, overvejende bestående af fisk og skaldyr; Frosne, færdigpakkede hovedretter hovedsageligt bestående af fisk og skaldyr; Lynfrosne grøntsagsretter; Tilberedt måltid hovedsageligt bestående af kylling og ginseng [samgyetang]; Færdigretter hovedsageligt bestående af fisk; Kartofler med fyld; Supper; Stegt kylling; Grillstegt kylling (Yakitori); Ovnstegt kylling; Teriyaki-kylling; Oksekødsgryderetter; Færdiglavede gryderetter med karry; Gryderetter; Gryderetter [fødevarer]; Færdigpakkede middagsretter, hovedsageligt bestående af vildt; Cæsarsalat; Kartoffelsalat; Fjerkræsalater; Antipasto-salater; Grøntsagssalater; Salat af bælgfrugter; Tilberedte salater; Kartoffelbaserede salater; Sashimi; Nudelsuppe; Misosuppe; Suppe med matzo-boller; Supper på dåse; Forkogt misosuppe; Forkogt suppe; Surimi; Tagine [tilberedte kød-, fiske- eller grøntsagsretter]; Oksekallun; Tilberedt kød.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Nicht lebende Fische, Meeresfrüchte und Weichtiere; Suppen und Brühen, Fleischextrakte; Molkereiprodukte und deren Ersatzprodukte; Fleisch und Fleischerzeugnisse; Vogeleier und Eierprodukte; Verarbeitete Früchte, Pilze, Gemüse, Nüsse und Hülsenfrüchte; Hähnchenflügel; Vorwiegend aus Fisch bestehende, gekühlte Lebensmittel; Beignets mit körnigem Frischkäse; Hähnchenstücke [Chicken nuggets]; Bisques [Fischcremesuppen]; Fleischbouillons; Brühen [Suppen]; Fleischbällchen; Bulgogi; Verarbeitetes Rindfleisch; Verarbeitete Kalmare; Dickflüssige Fischsuppen [Chowder]; Chicharrón [Fleischgericht]; Shish Kebab [Fleischspieße]; Chile con queso; Chili con Carne [Fleisch-Chili-Gericht]; Klare Brühe; Fischkroketten; Dolmas [orientalisches Gericht]; Fertige Vorspeisen, vorwiegend aus Meeresfrüchten; Verarbeitete Schnecken [Escargots]; Falafeln; Gegrillte Fischfilets; Eintopf mit gedämpften Eiern; Gekochte Fleischgerichte; Vorwiegend aus Hähnchen bestehende vorgekochte Gerichte; Vorwiegend aus Pute bestehende vorgekochte Gerichte; Vollständig oder vorwiegend aus Fleisch bestehende gekochte Fertiggerichte; Vorwiegend aus Kebab bestehende Fertiggerichte; Vollständig oder vorwiegend aus Wild bestehende gekochte Fertiggerichte; Vollständig oder überwiegend aus Geflügel bestehende gekochte Fertiggerichte; Vorwiegend aus Fleisch bestehende Tiefkühlgerichte; Vorwiegend aus Hähnchen bestehende Tiefkühlgerichte; Fertiggericht, vorwiegend aus Tofu unter Beigabe einer nahrhaften Sojabohnenpaste [Cheonggukjang jjigae]; Fertiggericht, vorwiegend aus Tofu unter Beigabe einer Sojabohnenpaste [Doenjang jjigae]; Fertiggericht, vorwiegend aus kurz gebratenem Hähnchen und fermentierter scharfer Pfefferpaste [Dak galbi]; Fertiggericht, vorwiegend aus fermentiertem Gemüse, Schweinefleisch und Tofu [Kimchi jjigae]; Fertiggericht, vorwiegend aus kurz gebratenem Rindfleisch und fermentierter Sojasauce [Sogalbi]; Omeletten; Eiermuffins; Geflügelstückchen zur Verwendung als Sandwichfüllung; In Sojasoße gekochte Bohnen [Kongjaban]; Aufläufe aus Hackfleisch und Kartoffelbrei [Shepherd's Pie]; Fischpaste für geröstete oder gedämpfte Fladen [Kamaboko]; Fisch und Yamswurzeln für gedämpfte Fladen [Hampen]; Guacamole; Gumbo [Eintopfgericht]; Frittatas; Galbi [Grillfleischgericht]; Fisch mit Pommes Frites; Gekochter Fisch, tiefgefroren; Vorwiegend aus Geflügel bestehende Tiefgekühlgerichte; Vorwiegend aus Fisch bestehende Tiefkühlgerichte; Fertiggerichte aus Geflügel [hauptsächlich bestehend aus Geflügel]; Fertiggerichte aus Fleisch [hauptsächlich bestehend aus Fleisch]; Fleischfertiggerichte; Hauptsächlich aus Gemüse bestehende, tiefgekühlte Fertiggerichte; Fertiggerichte hauptsächlich bestehend aus Fleisch; Fertiggerichte hauptsächlich bestehend aus Hühnchen; Vorwiegend aus Fisch bestehende Fertiggerichte; Fertiggerichte hauptsächlich bestehend aus Speck; Fertiggerichte vorwiegend bestehend aus Meeresfrüchten; Vorwiegend aus Pute bestehende Fertiggerichte; Vorwiegend aus Ente bestehende Fertiggerichte; Fertiggerichte hauptsächlich bestehend aus Eiern; Vorwiegend aus Fleischersatz bestehende Fertiggerichte; Fertiggerichte vorwiegend bestehend aus Gemüse; Fertiggerichte vorwiegend bestehend aus Wild; Hauptsächlich aus Fischfrikadellen, Gemüse, gekochten Eiern und Brühe bestehende Fertiggerichte [Oden]; Abgepackte Gerichte, überwiegend aus Meeresfrüchten; Gefrorene vorverpackte Hauptgerichte, hauptsächlich bestehend aus Meeresfrüchten; Schockgefrorene Gemüsegerichte; Fertiggericht, vorwiegend aus Huhn und Ginseng [Samgyetang]; Vorwiegend aus Fisch bestehende, gekochte Gerichte; Gefüllte Kartoffeln; Kraftbrühe, Suppen; Back- und Brathähnchen; Gegrillte Hähnchen [Yakitori]; Brathähnchen; Teriyaki-Huhn; Rinderragout; Vorgekochter Curryeintopf; Eintöpfe; Aufläufe [herzhafte Speisen]; Vorverpackte Hauptmahlzeiten, hauptsächlich bestehend aus Wildfleisch; Caesar-Salate; Kartoffelsalate; Geflügelsalate; Antipasti-Salate; Gemüsesalat; Hülsenfrucht-Salate; Zubereitete Salate; Salate aus Kartoffeln; Sashimi; Nudelsuppen; Misosuppen; Matzeknödel-Suppe; Suppen in Dosen; Vorgekochte Misosuppe; Vorgekochte Suppen; Surimi; Tajine [zubereitetes Fleisch-, Fisch- oder Gemüsegericht]; Rinderkutteln; Zubereitetes Fleisch.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ψάρια, θαλασσινά και μαλάκια, μη ζωντανά· Σούπες και ζωμοί, εκχυλίσματα κρέατος· Γαλακτοκομικά προϊόντα και υποκατάστατα γαλακτοκομικών προϊόντων· Κρέας και προϊόντα κρέατος· Αυγά πουλιών και προϊόντα αυγών· Επεξεργασμένα φρούτα, μανιτάρια, λαχανικά, ξηροί καρποί και όσπρια· Φτερούγες κοτόπουλου· Ψυγμένα τρόφιμα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από ψάρι· Τηγανίτες με νωπό άπαχο τυρί (cottage)· Παναρισμένα κομμάτια κοτόπουλου· Σούπες τύπου μπισκ [βασίζονται στα οστρακόδερμα]· Ζωμός βοδινού· Ζωμός [σούπα]· Κεφτέδες· Bulgogi [κορεατικό πίατο με βοδινό κρέας]· Έτοιμο βοδινό· Καλαμάρια [παρασκευασμένα]· Κακκαβιές· Τσιτσαρόν (τηγανητό δέρμα χοιρινού)· Σις κεμπάπ [πολίτικο μπιφτέκι]· Τσίλι με τυρί· Τσίλι με κρέας· Κονσομέ [είδος σούπας]· Ψαροκροκέτες· Ντολμάδες· Έτοιμα ορεκτικά παρασκευασμένα κυρίως από θαλασσινά· Έτοιμα σαλιγκάρια· Φαλάφελ· Φιλέτα ψαριών ψημένα στο γκριλ· Πηχτή σούπα λαχανικών με αβγά στον ατμό· Μαγειρεμένα γεύματα κρέατος· Έτοιμα μαγειρεμένα γεύματα που περιέχουν κυρίως κοτόπουλο· Έτοιμα μαγειρεμένα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από γαλοπούλα· Έτοιμα μαγειρεμένα γεύματα, αποτελούμενα εξ ολοκλήρου ή σχεδόν εξ ολοκλήρου από κρέας· Έτοιμα γεύματα με κύριο συστατικό το κεμπάπ· Έτοιμα μαγειρεμένα γεύματα αποτελούμενα εξ ολοκλήρου ή σχεδόν εξ ολοκλήρου από κυνήγι· Έτοιμα μαγειρεμένα γεύματα αποτελούμενα εξ ολοκλήρου ή σχεδόν εξ ολοκλήρου από πουλερικά· Κατεψυγμένα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από κρέας· Κατεψυγμένα γεύματα που περιέχουν κυρίως κοτόπουλο· Μαγειρεμένο φαγητό παρασκευασμένο κυρίως από πυκνή πάστα σόγιας και τόφου [cheonggukjang-jjigae], κινεζική και κορεατική κουζίνα· Μαγειρεμένο φαγητό παρασκευασμένο κυρίως από πάστα σόγιας και τόφου [doenjang-jjigae], κορεατική κουζίνα· Μαγειρεμένο φαγητό παρασκευασμένο κυρίως από σοταρισμένο κοτόπουλο και πάστα καυτερής πιπεριάς που έχει υποστεί ζύμωση [dak-galbi], κορεατική κουζίνα· Μαγειρεμένο φαγητό παρασκευασμένο κυρίως με λαχανικά που έχουν υποστεί ζύμωση, με χοιρινό και με τόφου [kimchi-jjigae], κορεατική κουζίνα· Μαγειρεμένο φαγητό παρασκευασμένο κυρίως από σοταρισμένο βοδινό και σάλτσα σόγιας που έχει υποστεί ζύμωση [sogalbi], κορεατική κουζίνα· Ομελέτες· Κεκάκια αβγού· Κομμάτια κοτόπουλου για χρήση ως γέμιση σε σάντουιτς· Φασόλια μαγειρεμένα σε σάλτσα σόγιας [kongjaban], κορεατική κουζίνα· Πίτες του βοσκού· Αχνισμένοι ή ψημένοι κορμοί από πάστα ψαριού [kamaboko], ιαπωνικό παρασκεύασμα· Αχνισμένα πιτάκια από λιωμένο ψάρι και διοσκορέα [hampen], ιαπωνική κουζίνα· Γουακαμόλε [πουρές αβοκάντο]· Μπάμιες· Φριτάτες· Galbi [πιάτο από κρέας ψημένο στη σχάρα]· Ψάρι με τηγανητές πατάτες· Κατεψυγμένο μαγειρεμένο ψάρι· Κατεψυγμένα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από πουλερικά· Κατεψυγμένα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από ψάρι· Έτοιμα γεύματα από πουλερικά [με κύριο συστατικό τα πουλερικά]· Έτοιμα γεύματα από κρέας (με κύριο συστατικό το κρέας)· Έτοιμα κρέατα με κρέας· Κατεψυγμένα έτοιμα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από λαχανικά· Έτοιμα πιάτα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από κρέας· Έτοιμα γεύματα [κυρίως] με κοτόπουλο· Έτοιμα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από ψάρι· Ετοιμα γεύματα περιλαμβάνοντα [κυρίως] μπέικον· Έτοιμα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από θαλασσινά· Έτοιμα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από γαλοπούλα· Έτοιμα γεύματα που περιέχουν κυρίως πάπια· Έτοιμα γεύματα που περιέχουν [κυρίως] αυγά· Έτοιμα γεύματα που περιέχουν κυρίως υποκατάστατα κρέατος· Έτοιμα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από λαχανικά· Έτοιμα γεύματα κυρίως από κυνήγι· Έτοιμα πιάτα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από ψαροκεφτέδες, λαχανικά, βραστά αβγά και ζωμό (oden)· Προσυσκευασμένα δείπνα κυρίως από θαλασσινά· Κατεψυγμένα προσυσκευασμένα ορεκτικά αποτελούμενα κυρίως από θαλασσινά· 'Ετοιμα κατεψυγμένα γεύματα λαχανικών· Μαγειρεμένο φαγητό παρασκευασμένο κυρίως από κοτόπουλο και τζίνσενγκ [samgyetang], κορεάτικη σούπα· Μαγειρεμένα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από ψάρια· Γεμιστές πατάτες· Ζωμοί σούπας [κονσομέ]· Τηγανητό κοτόπουλο· Ψητό κοτόπουλο (γιακιτόρι)· Ψητό κοτόπουλο· Κοτόπουλο τεριγιάκι· Βραστό βοδινό· Προμαγειρεμένο βραστό με κάρι· Φαγητά της κατσαρόλας· Φαγητά μαγειρεμένα σε γάστρα· Προσυσκευασμένα δείπνα, κυρίως από κυνήγι· Σαλάτες του Καίσαρα· Πατατοσαλάτες· Σαλάτες με πουλερικά· Σαλάτες αντιπάστο [ιταλικά ορεκτικά]· Σαλάτες λαχανικών· Σαλάτες με ψυχανθή· Έτοιμες σαλάτες· Σαλάτες με βάση την πατάτα· Σασίμι· Σούπα με νούγιες· Σούπα με μίσο (καρύκευμα ιαπωνικής προέλευσης)· Σούπα ματσά [matzah] με σφαιρίδια άζυμου άρτου [εβραϊκή κουζίνα]· Σούπες σε κονσέρβα· Προμαγειρεμένες σούπες τύπου μίσο· Προμαγειρεμένες σούπες· Σουρίμι· Ταζίν [πιάτο αποτελούμενο από μαγειρεμένο κρέας, ψάρι ή λαχανικά]· Βοδινό στομάχι (πατσάς)· Έτοιμο κρέας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Fish, seafood and molluscs, not live; Soups and stocks, meat extracts; Dairy products and dairy substitutes; Meat and meat products; Birds eggs and egg products; Processed fruits, fungi, vegetables, nuts and pulses; Chicken wings; Chilled foods consisting predominately of fish; Cottage cheese fritters; Chicken nuggets; Bisques; Beef bouillon; Broth [soup]; Meatballs; Bulgogi [Korean beef dish]; Prepared beef; Squid [prepared]; Chowder; Chicharron; Shish kabobs; Chile con queso; Chili con carne; Consommes; Fish croquettes; Dolmas; Prepared entrees consisting primarily of seafood; Prepared snails [escargot]; Falafel; Grilled fish fillets; Steamed egg hotchpotch; Cooked meat dishes; Ready cooked meals consisting primarily of chicken; Ready cooked meals consisting primarily of turkey; Ready cooked meals consisting wholly or substantially wholly of meat; Prepared meals consisting primarily of kebab; Ready cooked meals consisting wholly or substantially wholly of game; Ready cooked meals consisting wholly or substantially wholly of poultry; Frozen meals consisting primarily of meat; Frozen meals consisting primarily of chicken; Cooked dish consisting primarily of rich soybean paste and tofu (cheonggukjang-jjigae); Cooked dish consisting primarily of soybean paste and tofu (doenjang-jjigae); Cooked dish consisting primarily of stir-fried chicken and fermented hot pepper paste (dak-galbi); Cooked dish consisting primarily of fermented vegetable, pork and tofu (kimchi-jjigae); Cooked dish consisting primarily of stir-fried beef and fermented soy sauce (Sogalbi); Omelettes; Egg muffins; Pieces of chicken for use as a filling in sandwiches; Beans cooked in soy sauce (Kongjaban); Shepherd's pie; Steamed or toasted cakes of fish paste (kamaboko); Steamed cakes of smashed fish and yam (hampen); Guacamole [mashed avocado]; Gumbo; Frittatas; Galbi [grilled meat dish]; Fish with chips; Frozen cooked fish; Frozen meals consisting primarily of poultry; Frozen meals consisting primarily of fish; Prepared meals made from poultry [poultry predominating]; Prepared meals made from meat [meat predominating]; Prepared meat dishes; Frozen prepared meals consisting principally of vegetables; Prepared dishes consisting principally of meat; Prepared meals containing [principally] chicken; Prepared meals consisting primarily of fish; Prepared meals containing [principally] bacon; Prepared meals consisting substantially of seafood; Prepared meals consisting primarily of turkey; Prepared meals consisting primarily of duck; Prepared meals containing [principally] eggs; Prepared meals consisting primarily of meat substitutes; Prepared meals consisting principally of vegetables; Prepared meals consisting principally of game; Prepared dishes consisting primarily of fishcakes, vegetables, boiled eggs, and broth (oden); Pre-packaged dinners consisting primarily of seafood; Frozen pre-packaged entrees consisting primarily of seafood; Quick-frozen vegetable dishes; Cooked dish consisting primarily of chicken and ginseng (samgyetang); Cooked meals consisting principally of fish; Filled potato skins; Soups; Fried chicken; Grilled chicken (Yakitori); Roast chicken; Teriyaki chicken; Beef stew; Pre-cooked curry stew; Stews; Casseroles [food]; Pre-packaged dinners consisting primarily of game; Caesar salad; Potato salad; Poultry salads; Antipasto salads; Vegetable salads; Legume salads; Prepared salads; Potato-based salads; Sashimi; Noodle soup; Miso soup; Matzo ball soup; Canned soups; Pre-cooked miso soup; Pre-cooked soup; Surimi; Tajine [prepared meat, fish or vegetable dish]; Beef tripe; Prepared meat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Pescado, mariscos y moluscos no vivos; Sopas y caldos, extractos de carne; Productos lácteos y sustitutivos de la leche; Carne y productos cárnicos; Huevos y ovoproductos; Frutos, hongos, verduras, frutos secos y legumbres procesados; Alas de pollo; Alimentos refrigerados predominantemente de pescado; Buñuelos de requesón; Nuggets de pollo; Crema de mariscos [bisque]; Caldo de ternera; Caldos [sopa]; Albóndigas; Bulgogi [plato coreano a base de carne de vacuno]; Carne de vacuno preparada; Calamares [preparados]; Sopa de pescado; Chicharrón; Shish kebab; Chile con queso; Chile con carne; Consomés [sopas]; Croquetas de pescado; Dolmas [hojas de parra rellenas]; Entrantes preparados que consisten principalmente en marisco; Caracoles preparados; Falafel; Filetes de pescado al grill; Guiso con huevos al vapor; Platos cocinados elaborados con carne; Comidas precocinadas compuestas principalmente de pollo; Comidas preparadas precocinadas principalmente a base de carne de pavo; Platos precocinados que consisten total o sustancialmente en carne; Comidas preparadas consistentes principalmente en kebab; Platos preparados que consisten total o sustancialmente en carne de caza; Comidas preparadas que consisten total o principalmente en aves de corral; Comidas congeladas principalmente a base de carne; Comidas congeladas compuestas principalmente de carne de pollo; Plato cocinado que consiste principalmente en pasta de soja espesa y tofu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Plato cocinado que consiste principalmente en pasta de soja y tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Plato cocinado que consiste principalmente en pollo frito revuelto y pasta de guindilla fermentada [dak-galbi]; Plato cocinado que consiste principalmente en verduras, hortalizas y legumbres fermentadas, cerdo y tofu [kimchi-jjigae]; Plato cocinado que consiste principalmente en ternera frita revuelta y salsa de soja fermentada [Sogalbi]; Tortilla francesa; Muffins al huevo; Trozos de pollo para usar como relleno de bocadillos; Alubias cocidas en salsa de soja [Kongjaban]; Pastel de carne y puré de patata; Pasteles al vapor o tostados de paté de pescado [kamaboko]; Pasteles al vapor de puré de pescado y ñame [hampen]; Guacamole [aguacate molido]; Sopa de quingombó; Frittatas (tortillas italianas); Galbi [platos a base de carne asada]; Pescado frito con patatas fritas; Pescados cocinados congelados; Comidas congeladas principalmente a base de carne de ave; Comidas congeladas principalmente a base de pescado; Comidas preparadas hechas de aves de corral [en las que predominan las aves de corral]; Comidas preparadas que contengan carne [donde predomina la carne]; Platos de carne preparados; Comidas congeladas preparadas que consisten principalmente en verduras; Platos preparados que consisten principalmente en carne; Platos preparados que contienen pollo [principalmente]; Comidas preparadas principalmente a base de pescado; Comidas preparadas que contienen beicon [principalmente]; Comidas preparadas que consisten sustancialmente en marisco; Comidas preparadas principalmente a base de carne de pavo; Comidas preparadas compuestas principalmente de carne de pato; Comidas preparadas que contienen huevo [principalmente]; Comidas preparadas que consisten principalmente en sucedáneos de la carne; Comidas preparadas que consisten principalmente de verduras; Comidas preparadas que consisten principalmente en carne de caza; Platos preparados que consisten principalmente en pastel de pescado, verduras, huevos cocidos y caldo (oden); Comida envasada consistente principalmente en marisco; Platos principales congelados y preenvasados compuestos principalmente de mariscos; Platos a base de verduras ultracongelados; Plato cocinado que consiste principalmente en pollo y ginseng [samgyetang]; Comidas preparadas que consisten principalmente en pescado; Patatas rellenas; Sopas; Pollo frito; Pollo a la parrilla (yakitori); Pollo asado; Pollo teriyaki; Ragú de carne de vacuno; Estofado al curry precocinado; Estofados; Estofados de carne [alimentación]; Comidas preenvasadas compuestas principalmente de carne de caza; Ensaladas césar; Ensalada de patatas; Ensaladas de carne de ave; Ensaladas de aperitivo; Ensaladas de verduras, hortalizas y legumbres; Ensaladas de legumbres; Ensaladas preparadas; Ensaladas a base de patata; Sashimi; Sopas de tallarines; Sopa de miso; Sopas de bolas de matza; Sopas en lata; Sopas de miso precocinadas; Sopas precocinadas; Surimi; Tayín [plato preparado de carne, pescado o verduras]; Tripas de bovino; Carne preparada.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kalad, mereannid ja limused, v.a elusad; Supid ja puljongid, lihaekstraktid; Piimatooted ja piima aseained; Liha ja lihatooted; Linnumunad ja munatooted; Töödeldud puuviljad, seened, köögiviljad, pähklid ja kaunviljad; Kanatiivad; Peamiselt kalast koosnevad jahutatud toidud; Kodujuustusõõrikud; Kananagitsad; Koorikloomadest püreesupid; Loomalihapuljong; Puljongid, rammuleemed [supid]; Lihapallid; Bulgogi [Korea loomalihatoit]; Töödeldud loomaliha; Töödeldud kalmaarid; Paks supp, segahautis; Chicharrón; Kebabid; Tšilli juustuga; Chilli con carne [Mehhiko oa-hakklihatoit]; Konsomeed; Kalakroketid; Riisitäidisega viinamarjaleherullid; Peamiselt mereandidest koosnevad põhiroad; Töödeldud teod (escargot); Falafel; Grillitud kalafileed; Hautatud munasupp; Küpsetatud liharoad; Peamiselt kanalihast koosnevad kuumtöödeldud valmistoidud; Peamiselt kalkuniliha sisaldavad valmistoidud; Valmistoidud ainult või peamiselt lihast; Peamiselt kebabist koosnevad valmiseined; Valmistoidud ainult või peamiselt ulukilihast; Valmistoidud ainult või peamiselt linnulihast; Peamiselt liha sisaldavad külmutatud toidud; Peamiselt kanalihast koosnevad külmutatud toidud; Peamiselt rammusast sojaoapastast ja tofust koosnev kuumtöödeldud toit [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Peamiselt sojaoapastast ja tofust koosnev kuumtöödeldud toit [doenjang-jjigae]; Peamiselt praetud kanast ja kääritatud teravast tšillipastast koosnev kuumtöödeldud toit [dak-galbi]; Peamiselt kääritatud köögiviljast, sealihast ja tofust koosnev kuumtöödeldud toit [kimchi-jjigae]; Peamiselt praetud veiselihast ja kääritatud sojakastmest koosnev kuumtöödeldud toit [Sogalbi]; Omletid; Munamuffinid; Kanalihatükid [võileivatäidised]; Sojakastmes keedetud oad [Kongjaban]; Kartuli- ja hakklihavormid; Aurutatud või röstitud kalapulgad [kamaboko]; Purustatud kalast ja jamsist aurutatud koogid [hampen]; Guacamole [avokaadopüree]; Gumbo supp; Fritatad; Galbi [grillitud lihast toit]; Praetud kala friikartulitega; Külmutatud keedetud kala; Peamiselt linnuliha sisaldavad külmutatud eined; Peamiselt kala sisaldavad külmutatud eined; Linnulihast valmisroad [põhiliselt linnulihast]; Valmistoidud lihast [põhikomponent liha]; Valmistoidud lihast; Peamiselt juurvilju sisaldavad külmutatud valmistoidud; Peamiselt lihast koosnevad valmisroad; Peamiselt kana sisaldavad valmistoidud; Peamiselt kalast koosnevad valmisroad; Peamiselt peekonit sisaldavad valmistoidud; Peamiselt mereandidest koosnevad valmistoidud; Peamiselt kalkunilihast koosnevad valmistoidud; Peamiselt pardilihast koosnevad valmistoidud; Peamiselt mune sisaldavad valmistoidud; Peamiselt liha aseaineid sisaldavad valmistoidud; Peamiselt köögiviljadest koosnevad valmistoidud; Peamiselt ulukilihast koosnevad valmistoidud; Peamiselt kalapulkadest, aedviljadest, keedetud munadest ja puljongist koosnevad valmisroad (oden); Peamiselt mereandidest koosnevad eelpakendatud eined; Peamiselt mereandidest koosnevad sügavkülmutatud pakendatud eelroad; Kiirkülmutatud köögiviljaroad; Peamiselt kanast ja ženšennist koosnev kuumtöödeldud toit [samgyetang]; Peamiselt kala sisaldavad keedetud toidud; Täidetud kartulid; Supid; Praetud kana; Grillkana (yakitori); Grillkana; Teriyaki-kanaliha; Veiselihahautis; Eelkuumutatud karrihautised; Ühepajatoidud; Vormiroad [toidud]; Peamiselt ulukiliha sisaldavad pakendatud õhtueined; Caesari salat; Kartulisalatid; Linnulihasalatid; Antipasto-salatid; Köögiviljasalatid; Kaunviljasalatid; Valmissalatid; Kartulipõhised salatid; Sashimi; Nuudlisupp; Miso-supp; Matzopallisupp; Konservsupid; Miso-supp valmistoiduna; Supp valmistoiduna; Surimi; Tajine [lihast, kalast või aedviljast valmisroog]; Veiserupskid; Töödeldud liha.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ei-elävät kalat, merenelävät ja nilviäiset; Keitot ja liemet, lihauutteet; Maitotuotteet ja maitotuotteiden korvikkeet; Liha ja lihatuotteet; Linnunmunat ja munatuotteet; Käsitellyt hedelmät, sienet, vihannekset, pähkinät ja palkokasvit; Kanansiivet; Pääosin kalaa sisältävät jäähdytetyt elintarvikkeet; Friteerattu raejuusto; Kananugetit; Rapukeitot; Häränlihanliemi; Liemet (liha -) [keitot]; Lihapyörykät; Bulgogi [korealainen liharuokalaji]; Naudanlihavalmiste; Kalmarit [käsitellyt]; Suurustetut kala-, kasvis- tai simpukkakeitot; Paistettu siankamara (Chicharron); Shish-kebabit; Juustochilit; Chili con carne; Lihaliemet; Kalakuorukat; Dolma viininlehtikääryleet; Valmiit ruoka-annokset, jotka koostuvat pääosin merenelävistä; Käsitellyt etanat; Falafelit; Grillatut kalafileet; Höyrytetty muna-lammasvihannespata; Kypsennetyt liharuoat; Valmisateriat, jotka sisältävät pääasiassa kanaa; Valmisateriat, jotka sisältävät pääasiassa kalkkunaa; Kokonaan tai pääosin lihaa sisältävät valmisateriat; Valmisateriat koostuen pääosin kebabista; Kokonaan tai pääosin riistaa sisältävät valmisateriat; Kokonaan tai pääosin siipikarjaa sisältävät valmisateriat; Pääasiassa lihasta koostuvat pakasteateriat; Pakasteateriat, jotka sisältävät pääasiassa kanaa; Kypsennetty ruokalaji, joka koostuu pääosin täyteläisestä soijapaputahnasta ja tofusta [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Kypsennetty ruokalaji, joka koostuu pääosin soijapaputahnasta ja tofusta [doenjang-jjigae]; Kypsennetty ruokalaji, joka koostuu pääosin öljyssä kypsennetystä kanasta ja hapatetusta, tulisesta pippuritahnasta [dak-galbi]; Kypsennetty ruokalaji, joka koostuu pääosin hapatetuista kasviksista, sianlihasta ja tofusta [kimchi-jjigae]; Kypsennetty ruokalaji, joka koostuu pääosin öljyssä kypsennetystä naudanlihasta ja hapatetusta soijakastikkeesta [Sogalbi]; Omeletit; Munamuffinit; Kanapalat käytettäväksi voileipien täytteenä; Soijakastikkeessa keitetyt pavut [Kongjaban]; Lihaperunasoselaatikko (Shepherd's pie); Höyrytetyt tai paahdetut kakut kalamassasta [kamaboko]; Höyrytetyt kakut jauhetusta kalasta ja jamssista [hampen]; Guacamole [avokadoseos]; Gumbo (kana- tai mereneläväkeitto); Frittatat; Galbi [grillattu liharuoka]; Kala ranskalaisilla perunoilla; Pakastettu kypsennetty kala; Pääasiassa siipikarjasta koostuvat pakasteateriat; Pääasiassa kalasta koostuvat pakasteateriat; Siipikarjasta tehdyt valmisateriat (sisältävät pääosin siipikarjaa); Valmisateriat [pääosin] lihasta; Lihapohjaiset valmisateriat; Pääosin vihanneksista koostuvat pakastetut valmisateriat; Pääosin lihasta koostuvat valmisateriat; Kanaa [pääosin] sisältävät valmisateriat; Pääasiassa kalasta valmistetut valmisateriat; Valmisateriat sisältäen [pääosin] pekonia; Valmisateriat koostuen pääosin merenelävistä; Valmisateriat, jotka sisältävät pääasiassa kalkkunaa; Valmisateriat, jotka sisältävät pääasiassa ankkaa; Valmisateriat sisältäen [pääosin] munia; Pääasiassa lihankorvikkeita sisältävät valmisateriat; Valmisruoat, jotka koostuvat pääasiassa kasviksista; Pääosin riistasta koostuvat valmisateriat; Valmisateriat, jotka koostuvat ensisijaisesti kalamurekepihveistä, vihanneksista, keitetyistä kananmunista ja keitosta (oden-keitosta); Pääosin merenelävistä koostuvat valmiiksi pakatut ateriat; Pääasiassa merenelävistä koostuvat valmiiksi pakatut pakastetut pääruoat; Pikajäädytetyt kasvisateriat; Kypsennetty ruokalaji, joka koostuu pääosin kanasta ja ginsengistä [samgyetang]; Pääosin kalasta koostuvat kypsytetyt ateriat; Täytetyt perunankuoret; Keitot; Paistettu kana; Grillattu kana (yakitori, japanilainen kanaruokalaji); Paahdettu kana; Teriyaki-kana; Naudanpaisti; Valmis currypata; Muhennokset; Vuokaruoat; Pääasiassa riistasta koostuvat valmiiksi pakatut ateriat; Caesarsalaatti; Perunasalaatti; Siipikarjasalaatit; Antipastosalaatit; Vihannessalaatit; Palkokasvisalaatit; Valmiit salaatit; Perunapohjaiset salaatit; Sashimi (raaka kala); Nuudelikeitot; Misokeitto; Matzo-leivästä tehty keitto; Purkkikeitot; Esikypsennetty misokeitto; Esikypsennetty keitto; Surimi [kalatahna]; Tajine [lihasta, kalasta tai vihanneksista valmistettu ruokalaji]; Naudan mahalaukut; Lihavalmisteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Poissons, fruits de mer et mollusques non vivants; Potages et bouillons, extraits de viande; Produits laitiers et substituts; Viande et produits à base de viande; Œufs de volaille et ovoproduits; Fruits, champignons, légumes, fruits à coque et légumineuses transformés; Ailes de poulet; Aliments réfrigérés principalement à base de poisson; Beignets de fromage blanc égoutté; Beignets de poulet; Bisques; Bouillon de bœuf; Bouillons [soupe]; Boulettes de viande; Bulgogi [plat coréen à base de boeuf]; Bœuf préparé; Calmars préparés; Chaudrée; Chicharron; Chiche-kebabs; Chile con queso [hors-d'œuvre composé de fromage fondu et de piment]; Chili con carne; Consommés; Croquettes de poisson; Dolmas; Entrées préparées composées principalement de fruits de mer; Escargots préparés [escargots]; Falafels; Filets de poissons grillés; Flan aux œufs cuit à la vapeur; Plats cuisinés à base de viande; Plats cuisinés préparés principalement à base de poulet; Plats cuisinés préparés principalement à base de dinde; Plats cuisinés entièrement ou principalement à base de viande; Plats cuisinés essentiellement composés de kebab; Plats cuisinés entièrement ou principalement à base de gibier; Plats cuisinés entièrement ou essentiellement à base de volaille; Plats congelés principalement à base de viande; Plats congelés principalement à base de poulet; Plat cuisiné principalement à base de pâte de soja riche et de tofu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Plat cuisiné principalement à base de pâte de soja et de tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Plat cuisiné principalement à base de poulet sauté et de pâte de piments forts fermentés [dak-galbi]; Plat cuisiné principalement à base de légumes fermentés, de porc et de tofu [kimchi-jjigae]; Plat cuisiné principalement à base de bœuf sauté et de sauce soja fermentée [Sogalbi]; Omelettes; Muffins aux œufs; Morceaux de poulet utilisés comme garniture de sandwiches; Haricots cuits dans de la sauce soja [Kongjaban]; Hachis Parmentier; Gâteaux à base de pâte de poisson cuits à la vapeur ou grillés [kamaboko]; Gâteaux de purée de poisson et d'igname cuits à la vapeur [hampen]; Guacamole [avocat écrasé]; Gombo; Frittatas; Galbi [plats à base de viande grillée]; Poisson-frites; Poisson cuit surgelé; Plats surgelés essentiellement à base de volaille; Plats surgelés essentiellement à base de poisson; Plats préparés à base de volaille [la volaille étant l'ingrédient principal]; Plats préparés à base de viande [la viande étant l'ingrédient principal]; Plats préparés à base de viande; Plats préparés surgelés principalement à base de légumes; Plats préparés principalement à base de viande; Plats préparés principalement à base de poulet; Plats préparés principalement à base de poisson; Plats préparés principalement à base de lard; Plats préparés principalement à base de fruits de mer; Plats préparés principalement à base de dinde; Plats préparés principalement à base de canard; Plats préparés principalement à base d'œufs; Plats préparés principalement composés de substituts de viande; Plats préparés essentiellement à base de légumes; Plats préparés essentiellement à base de gibier; Plats préparés essentiellement à base de croquettes de poisson, de légumes, d'œufs durs et de bouillon (oden); Plats préemballés essentiellement à base de fruits de mer; Plats principaux congelés pré-emballés composés principalement de fruits de mer; Plats cuisinés surgelés à base de légumes; Plats cuisinés principalement à base de poulet et de ginseng [samgyetang]; Plats cuisinés principalement à base de poisson; Pommes de terre farcies; Potages; Poulet frit; Poulet grillé (Yakitori); Poulet rôti; Poulet teriyaki; Ragoût de bœuf; Ragoût précuit au curry; Ragoûts; Ragoûts [cuits au four]; Repas pré-emballés composés principalement de gibier; Salade César; Salade de pommes de terre; Salade de volaille; Salades d'antipasti; Salades de légumes; Salades de légumineuses; Salades préparées; Salades à base de pommes de terre; Sashimi; Soupe de nouilles; Soupe miso; Soupes aux boulettes de matzo; Soupes en boîte; Soupes miso précuites; Soupes précuites; Surimi; Tajine [plat préparé à base de viande, poisson ou légumes]; Tripes de bœuf; Viande préparée.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Neživa riba, morski plodovi i mekušci; Juhe i temeljci, mesni ekstrakti; Mliječni proizvodi i njihovi nadomjesci; Meso i mesni proizvodi; Ptičja jaja i proizvodi od jaja; Prerađeno voće, gljive, povrće, orašasti plodovi i mahunarke; Pileća krilca; Rashlađena hrana koja se sastoji pretežno od ribe; Uštipci od svježeg sira; Panirani pileći medaljoni; Bisque juha; Goveđi bujon; Bujon [Juha]; Mesne okruglice; Bulgogi [korejsko jelo od govedine]; Pripremljena govedina; Lignja [pripremljena]; Gusta juha od morskih plodova ili povrća; Chicharron - pržena svinjska koža; Šiš-kebab; Umak od čilija sa sirom; Čili s mesom; Bistre juhe; Riblji kroketi; Punjeni listovi vinove loze; Gotova predjela koja se uglavnom sastoje od morskih plodova; Pripremljeni puževi [escargot]; Falafel; Riblji fileti s roštilja; Krema od jaja kuhanih na pari; Kuhana mesna jela; Gotovi kuhani obroci koji se uglavnom sastoje od piletine; Gotovi kuhani obroci koji se uglavnom sastoje od puretine; Gotova kuhana jela koja se u cijelosti ili uglavnom sastoje od mesa; Gotova jela koja se sastoje uglavnom od kebaba; Gotova kuhana jela koja se u cijelosti ili uglavnom sastoje od divljači; Gotova kuhana jela koja se u cijelosti ili uglavnom sastoje od peradi; Zamrznuta jela koja se sastoje pretežno od mesa; Smrznuti obroci koji se uglavnom sastoje od piletine; Kuhano jelo koje se sastoji uglavnom od guste paštete od soje i tofua [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Kuhano jelo koje se sastoji uglavnom od paštete od soje i tofua [doenjang-jjigae]; Kuhano jelo koje se sastoji uglavnom od piletine pržene u voku i paštete od fermentiranih ljutih papričica [Dak-galbi]; Kuhano jelo koje se sastoji uglavnom od fermentiranog povrća, svinjetine i tofua [kimchi-jjigae]; Kuhano jelo koje se sastoji uglavnom od govedine pržene u voku i fermentiranog umaka od soje [Sogalbi]; Omleti; Muffini s jajima; Komadići piletine za sendviče; Grah kuhan u umaku od soje [Kongjaban]; Pita od mljevenog mesa sa zapečenim pireom od krumpira; Pareni ili tostirani kolačići od riblje paštete [kamaboko]; Kolačići od gnječene ribe i jama spremljeni na pari [hampen]; Guacamole umak [pire od avokada]; Gumbo [gulaš porijeklom iz Louisiane]; Omleti; Galbi [jelo od mesa s roštilja]; Riba s pomfritom; Zamrznuta kuhana riba; Zamrznuta jela koja se sastoje pretežno od peradi; Zamrznuta jela koja se sastoje pretežno od ribe; Gotova jela napravljena od peradi [perad prevladava]; Gotova jela napravljena od mesa [meso prevladava]; Gotova mesna jela; Zamrznuta gotova jela koja se pretežno sastoje od povrća; Gotova jela koja se uglavnom sastoje od mesa; Gotova jela koja uglavnom sadrže piletinu; Gotova jela koja se uglavnom sastoje od ribe; Gotova jela koja uglavnom sadrže slaninu; Gotova jela koja se pretežito sastoje od morskih plodova; Pripremljeni obroci koji se uglavnom sastoje od puretine; Gotovi obroci koji se uglavnom sastoje od pačetine; Gotova jela koja uglavnom sadrže jaja; Gotova jela koja se pretežno sastoje od nadmjestaka za meso; Gotova jela koja se uglavnom sastoje od povrća; Gotova jela koja se uglavnom sastoje od divljači; Gotova jela koja se sastoje uglavnm od ribljih pogačica, povrća, kuhanih jaja i bistre juhe (oden); Pakirani obroci koji se uglavnom sastoje od morske hrane; Smrznuta pakirana predjela koja se uglavnom sastoje od morskih plodova; Brzo smrznuta jela od povrća; Kuhano jelo koje se sastoji uglavnom od piletine i ginsenga [samgyetang]; Kuhana jela koja se pretežno sastoje od ribe; Punjeni krumpir s korom; Juhe; Pržena piletina; Pileći ražnjići (Yakitori); Pečena piletina; Teriyaki piletina; Jelo od dinstanog goveđeg mesa; Gotovi gulaš s curryjem; Gulaši; Složenci [hrana]; Pakirani obroci koje se uglavnom sastoje od divljači; Cezar salata; Krumpir salata; Salate od mesa peradi; Salate za predjelo; Salate od povrća; Salate od mahunarki; Gotove salate; Salata od krumpira; Sashimi; Juha s rezancima; Miso juha; Juha s matzo knedlama; Juhe u konzervi; Unaprijed skuhana miso juha; Unaprijed skuhana juha; Surimi; Tajine [gotovo jelo od mesa, ribe ili povrća]; Goveđe tripice; Pripremljeno meso.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hal, tenger gyümölcsei és puhatestűek, nem élő; Levesek és csontlevesek, húskivonatok; Tejtermékek és tejtermék-helyettesítők; Hús és hústermékek; Tojások és tojástermékek; Feldolgozott gyümölcsök, gombák, zöldségek, diófélék és hüvelyesek; Csirkeszárnyak; Főként halat tartalmazó hűtött ételek; Túrós fánkok; Csirkedarabkák (nugget); Ráklevesek; Marhahúsleves; Húslevesek, erőlevesek; Húsgombócok; Bulgogi [koreai szarvasmarhából készült étel]; Konyhakész marhahús; Tintahal [előkészített]; Chowder; Chicharron; Sis kebab; Sajtos chili; Chili con carne (chilis bab); Erőleves; Halkrokett; Dolma, töltött szőlőlevél; Elsősorban tenger gyümölcseiből álló konyhakész előételek; Ételként elkészített csigák; Falafel; Grillezett halfilék; Gőzölt tojásos húslevesféle, egytálétel sok zöldségfélével; Főtt húsételek; Elsősorban csirkéből álló készre főzött ételek; Elsősorban pulykából álló készre főzött ételek; Teljesen vagy lényegében húsból készült készételek; Elsősorban kebabból álló készételek; Teljesen vagy lényegében vadhúsból készült készételek; Teljesen vagy lényegében baromfiból készült készételek; Elsősorban húst tartalmazó fagyasztott ételek; Elsősorban csirkéből álló fagyasztott ételek; Koreai főtt étel sűrű szójababpürével és tofuval [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Koreai ragu szójababpürével és tofuval [doenjang-jjigae]; Koreai főtt étel csirkéből és fermentált csípős csilipasztából [dak-galbi]; Koreai ragu fermentált zöldséggel, sertéshússal és tofuval [kimchi-jjigae]; Koreai főtt étel sült marhahúsból és fermentált szójaszószból [sogalbi]; Omlettek; Tojásmuffinok; Szendvicstöltelékként használt csirkehús darabok; Szójaszószban főtt bab [kongjaban]; Pásztorpite; Gőzölt vagy grillezett halpogácsa [kamaboko]; Gőzölt halpogácsa jamgyökérrel [hampen]; Guacamole [avokádószósz]; Gumbó, gombó [amerikai csirkés-rákos egytálétel]; Frittaták; Kalbi [grillezett húsétel]; Hal sültkrumplival; Fagyasztott főtt hal; Elsősorban baromfit tartalmazó fagyasztott ételek; Elsősorban halat tartalmazó fagyasztott ételek; Túlnyomórészt csirkehúsból készült készételek; Főként húst tartalmazó készételek; Készételek húsból; Főként zöldségeket tartalmazó fagyasztott készételek; Főként húsból álló készételek; Főként csirkét tartalmazó készételek; Elsősorban halból álló készételek; Főként szalonnát tartalmazó készételek; Elsősorban tenger gyümölcseiből álló készételek; Elsősorban pulykából álló készételek; Elsősorban kacsából álló készételek; Főként tojást tartalmazó készételek; Főként húspótlókat tartalmazó készételek; Elsősorban zöldségféléket tartalmazó készételek; Főként vadhúst tartalmazó készételek; Főként halvagdalékot, zöldségeket, főtt tojást és erőlevest tartalmató készételek; Elsősorban tenger gyümölcseit tartalmazó előre csomagolt ételek; Elsősorban tengeri ételeket tartalmazó előre csomagolt fagyasztott főételek; Gyorsfagyasztott zöldséges ételek; Koreai főtt étel csirkével és ginzenggel [samgyetang]; Főként halat tartalmazó főtt ételek; Töltött burgonya; Levesek; Sült csirke; Grillcsirke (yakitori [japán pálcás grillcsirke]); Sült csirke; Teriyaki csirke (japán étel); Marhahús ragu; Előfőzött curry pörkölt; Raguk, pörköltek; Tűzálló tálban készült élelmiszerek; Elsősorban vadhúst tartalmazó előre csomagolt ételek; Cézársaláta; Burgonyasaláták; Baromfi saláták; Előételként felszolgált saláták; Zöldségsaláták; Hüvelyesekből készült saláták; Kész saláták; Burgonyaalapú saláták; Sashimi; Tésztás levesek; Miso leves; Maceszgombóc leves; Leveskonzervek; Előfőzött miszóleves; Előfőzött leves; Surimi; Tajine [elkészített hús, hal vagy zöldség]; Marhagyomor; Konyhakész hús.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pesci, frutti di mare e molluschi, non vivi; Zuppe e brodi, estratti di carne; Prodotti caseari e loro succedanei; Carne e prodotti a base di carne; Uova e prodotti a base di uova; Frutta, funghi ed ortaggi lavorati (inclusi frutta a guscio e legumi); Ali di pollo; Cibi freddi principalmente a base di pesce; Frittelle di formaggio; Nuggets di pollo; Bisque [zuppa di crostacei cremosa]; Brodo di manzo; Brodo, minestra; Polpette; Bulgogi [piatto coreano a base di carne bovina]; Manzo preparato; Calamari [pronti]; Zuppa di pesce; Chicharron; Kebab shish; Chile con queso [salsa piccante a base di formaggio e peperoncino]; Chili con carne; Consommé; Crocchette di pesce; Dolmas; Antipasti pronti principalmente a base di frutti di mare; Lumache pronte; Falafels; Filetti di pesce grigliato; Hotchpotch con uova al vapore; Piatti a base di carne cotta; Piatti pronti cotti principalmente a base di carne di pollo; Piatti cotti pronti principalmente a base di tacchino; Piatti cotti pronti costituiti interamente o principalmente da carne; Piatti pronti principalmente a base di kebab; Piatti cotti pronti costituiti interamente o principalmente da selvaggina; Piatti cotti pronti costituiti interamente o principalmente da pollame; Piatti surgelati principalmente a base di carne; Pasti surgelati principalmente a base di carne di pollo; Piatto pronto principalmente a base di pasta di soia arricchita e tofu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Piatto pronto principalmente a base di pasta di soia e tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Piatto cotto principalmente a base di sauté di pollo e pasta di peperoncino piccante fermentato [dak-galbi]; Piatto pronto principalmente a base di verdure fermentate, maiale e tofu [kimchi-jjiga]; Piatto pronto principalmente a base di sauté di manzo e salsa di soia fermentata [Sogalbi]; Omelette; Muffin all'uovo; Pezzi di pollo da utilizzare in panini imbottiti; Fagioli cotti in salsa di soia [kongjaban]; Pasticcio di carne ricoperto di purè; Panetti cotti al vapore o tostati di pasta di pesce [kamaboko]; Panetti cotti al vapore di pasticcio di pesce e patate dolci [hampen]; Guacamole [purea di avocado]; Gumbo; Frittate; Galbi [piatto a base di carne grigliata]; Pesce servito con patatine fritte; Pesce cotto surgelato; Piatti surgelati principalmente a base di pollame; Pasti surgelati principalmente a base di pesce; Pasti pronti a base di pollame [con predominanza del pollame]; Piatti pronti a base di carne [in cui la carne è l'ingrediente principale]; Piatti pronti di carne; Pasti pronti surgelati principalmente a base di ortaggi; Piatti pronti principalmente a base di carne; Piatti pronti contenenti [principalmente] pollo; Pasti pronti principalmente a base di pesce; Piatti pronti contenenti [principalmente] pancetta; Pasti pronti principalmente a base di frutti di mare; Piatti preparati principalmente a base di tacchino; Piatti pronti principalmente a base di carne di anatra; Piatti pronti contenenti uova [principalmente]; Pasti pronti principalmente a base di succedanei della carne; Piatti pronti, principalmente a base di verdure; Pasti pronti principalmente a base di selvaggina; Piatti pronti principalmente a base di polpette di pesce, verdura, uova bollite e brodo (oden); Pasti preconfezionati principalmente a base di frutti di mare; Piatti principali congelati preconfezionati che principalmente a base di frutti di mare; Piatti vegetali surgelati; Piatto pronto principalmente a base di pollo e ginseng [samgyetang]; Pasti cotti principalmente a base di pesce; Bucce di patate ripiene; Brodi ristretti; Pollo fritto; Pollo alla griglia (yakitori); Pollo arrosto; Pollo Teriyaki; Stufato di manzo; Stufati di curry precotti; Stufati; Alimenti cotti in casseruola; Pasti preconfezionati principalmente a base di selvaggina; Caesar salad [insalata a base di lattuga, pollo, parmigiano e salse]; Insalata di patate; Insalate con carne di pollame; Insalate come antipasto; Macedonia di verdure; Insalate di legumi; Insalate pronte; Insalate a base di patate; Sashimi; Zuppa di spaghetti cinesi; Zuppa di miso; Zuppa di palline di matzo; Minestre in scatola; Zuppa di miso precotta; Zuppa precotta; Surimi; Tajine [piatto pronto a base di carne, pesce o verdure]; Trippa di manzo; Carni preparate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Žuvis, jūrų gėrybės ir moliuskai, negyvi; Sriubos ir sultiniai, mėsos ekstraktai; Pieno produktai ir pieno pakaitalai; Mėsa ir mėsos produktai; Kiaušiniai ir kiaušinių produktai; Apdoroti vaisiai, grybai, daržovės, riešutai ir ankštinės daržovės; Vištų sparneliai; Atšaldytas maistas [žuvies pagrindu]; Varškėčiai; Vištienos gabaliukai; Kreminė prancūziška vėžiagyvių sriuba; Jautienos sultiniai; Sultiniai [sriubos]; Mėsos kukuliai; Korėjietiškas jautienos patiekalas [bulgogi]; Paruošta jautiena; Kalmarai [paruošti]; Tiršta daržovių ir jūrų gėrybių sriuba; Traškios kiaulienos odelės; Šašlykai; Aitriosios paprikos su sūriu; Mėsos ir aitriųjų paprikų troškinys; Skaidrus sultinys; Žuvies maltinukai; Dolmos; Paruošti pirmieji patiekalai jūros gėrybių pagrindu; Paruoštos sraigės; Falafeliai; Kepta ant grotelių žuvų filė; Ant garų ruošta šiupininė su kiaušiniais; Termiškai apdoroti mėsos patiekalai; Paruošti virti ir kepti patiekalai vištienos pagrindu; Paruošti virti ir kepti maisto patiekalai kalakutienos pagrindu; Paruošti virti ir kepti maisto patiekalai [vien iš arba daugiausia iš mėsos]; Paruošti patiekalai, daugiausia sudaryti iš kebabo; Paruošti virti ir kepti maisto patiekalai [vien iš arba daugiausia iš laukinienos]; Paruošti virti ir kepti maisto patiekalai [vien iš arba daugiausia iš paukštienos]; Šaldyti patiekalai mėsos pagrindu; Šaldyti valgiai vištienos pagrindu; Paruoštas patiekalas tirštos sojų pupelių tyrės ir sojų varškės pagrindu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Paruoštas patiekalas sojų pupelių tyrės ir sojų varškės pagrindu [doenjang-jjigae]; Paruoštas patiekalas keptos vištienos ir fermentuotos aitriųjų paprikų tyrės pagrindu [dak-galbi]; Paruoštas patiekalas fermentuotų daržovių, kiaulienos ir sojų varškės pagrindu [kimchi-jjigae]; Paruoštas patiekalas keptos jautienos ir fermentuotų sojų pupelių padažo pagrindu [Sogalbi]; Omletai; Kiaušininiai keksiukai; Vištienos gabalėliai [sumuštinių įdaras]; Sojų padaže virtos pupelės [Kongjaban]; Bulvių košės ir mėsos faršo apkepas su prieskoniais (piemenėlių pyragas); Ant garų ruošti ar skrudinti gaminiai iš žuvies tyrės [kamaboko]; Ant garų ruošti trintos žuvies ir batatų pyragai [hampen]; Gvakamolė; Mėsos, vėžiagyvių ir daržovių troškinys [gumbo]; Itališkas omletas (frittata); Kepti ant grotelių mėsos patiekalai [galbi]; Žuvis su bulvių traškučiais; Užšaldyta termiškai apdorota žuvis; Užšaldyti patiekalai paukštienos pagrindu; Užšaldyti patiekalai žuvies pagrindu; Paruošti paukštienos valgiai [paukštienos pagrindu]; Paruošti mėsos valgiai [mėsos pagrindu]; Paruošti mėsos patiekalai; Užšaldyti paruošti patiekalai daržovių pagrindu; Paruošti mėsos patiekalai [mėsos pagrindu]; Paruošti valgiai iš vištienos; Paruošti patiekalai žuvies pagrindu; Paruošti valgiai iš kiaulienos šoninės; Paruošti jūros gėrybių valgiai [jūros gėrybių pagrindu]; Paruošti patiekalai, susidedantys daugiausia iš kalakutienos; Paruošti patiekalai antienos pagrindu; Paruošti valgiai iš kiaušinių; Paruošti valgiai, daugiausia sudaryti iš mėsos pakaitalų; Paruošti daržovių pagrindu patiekalai; Paruošti laukinienos patiekalai; Paruošti patiekalai, daugiausia sudaryti iš paplotėlių su žuvimi, daržovių, virtų kiaušinių ir sultinio; Supakuoti pietūs [jūros gėrybių pagrindu]; Šaldyti fasuoti pirmieji patiekalai, daugiausia iš jūrų gėrybių; Greitai užšaldyti daržovių patiekalai; Paruoštas patiekalas vištienos ir ženšenio pagrindu [samgyetang]; Termiškai apdoroti patiekalai [pagaminti žuvies pagrindu]; Įdarytos išskobtos bulvės; Sriubos; Keptas viščiukas; Kepta ant grotelių vištiena (Yakitori); Kepta vištiena; Vištiena su japonišku sojų padažu (terijakiu); Jautienos troškinys; Išvirti kario troškiniai; Troškiniai (iš mėsos, žuvies ir daržovių); Troškinti patiekalai; Fasuoti pietūs, daugiausia iš laukinienos; Cezario salotos; Bulvių mišrainės; Paukštienos salotos; Užkandžių salotos; Daržovių salotos; Ankštinių daržovių salotos; Paruoštos salotos; Bulvių salotos; Sašimis; Makaronų sriuba; Miso sriuba; Macų kukuliukų sriuba; Konservuotos sriubos [skardinėse]; Išvirta miso sriuba; Išvirtos sriubos; Surimis; Tadžinas [paruoštas mėsos, žuvies ar daržovių patiekalas]; Jautienos žarnokai; Paruošta mėsa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Nedzīvas zivis, jūras veltes un moluski; Zupas un buljoni, gaļas ekstrakti; Piena produkti un piena aizstājēji; Gaļa un gaļas produkti; Putnu olas un olu produkti; Apstrādāti augļi, sēnes, dārzeņi, rieksti un pākšaugi; Vistu spārniņi; Atdzesēti ēdieni, kas pamatā sastāv no zivīm; Biezpiena pankūkas; Vistas nageti; Biezeņzupa; Liellopa gaļas buljons; Buljoni (zupas); Kotletes; Korejiešu liellopu gaļas ēdiens (bulgogi); Sagatavota liellopu gaļa; Kalmāri [gatavi]; Bieza zupa no zivīm; Grauzdēta cūkāda [chicharron]; Šašliki; Kausētais siers ar čili pipariem [chile con queso]; Gaļas sautējums ar čili pipariem; Dzidrie buljoni; Zivju kroketes; Vīnogu lapu tīteņi [dolmas]; Gatavas uzkodas, kas sastāv galvenokārt no jūras veltēm; Pagatavoti gliemeži čaumalās ar kausēta sviesta un ķiploku mērci; Turku zirņu pīrāgs (falafels); Grilētas zivs filejas; Tvaicētu olu mistrojums; Lietošanai gatavi gaļas ēdieni; Gatavi ēdieni, kas galvenokārt sastāv no vistas gaļas; Gatavas maltītes, kas galvenokārt sastāv no tītara gaļas; Gatavie ēdieni, kas pilnībā vai daļēji sastāv no gaļas; Gatavās maltītes, kas sastāv galvenokārt no kebaba; Gatavie ēdieni, kas pilnībā vai daļēji sastāv no medījumu gaļas; Gatavie ēdieni, kas pilnībā vai daļēji sastāv no mājputnu gaļas; Saldētas maltītes, kas galvenokārt sastāv no gaļas; Saldēti ēdieni, kas sastāv galvenokārt no vistas gaļas; Gatavi ēdieni, kas sastāv galvenokārt no biezas sojas pupiņu pastas un tofu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Gatavi ēdieni, kas sastāv galvenokārt no sojas pupiņu pastas un tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Gatavi ēdieni, kas sastāv galvenokārt no strauji apceptas vistas gaļas un fermentētas aso piparu pastas [dak-galbi]; Gatavi ēdieni, kas sastāv galvenokārt no fermentētiem dārzeņiem, cūkgaļas un tofu [kimchi-jjigae]; Gatavi ēdieni, kas sastāv galvenokārt no strauji apceptas liellopu gaļas un fermentētas sojas mērces [Sogalbi]; Omlete; Olu mafini; Vistas gaļas gabaliņi sviestmaižu pildījumiem; Sojas mērcē pagatavotas pupiņas [Kongjaban]; Gaļas un kartupeļu biezputras sacepums; Tvaicēti vai grauzdēti plācenīši no zivju masas [kamaboko]; Tvaicēti plācenīši no maltas zivs un jamsa [hampen]; Avokado biezenis (gvakamole); Gumbo zupa; Fritātas (itāļu omletes); Grilētas gaļas ēdiens (galbi); Zivs ar ceptiem kartupeļiem; Saldētas pagatavotas zivis; Saldētas maltītes, kas galvenokārt sastāv no mājputnu gaļas; Saldētas maltītes, kas galvenokārt sastāv no zivīm; Gatavi ēdieni, kas pagatavoti no mājputnu gaļas (pārsvarā no mājputnu gaļas); Gatavi ēdieni, kas pagatavoti no gaļas (pārsvarā no gaļas); Pagatavoti gaļas ēdieni; Saldēti lietošanai gatavi ēdieni, kas sastāv galvenokārt no dārzeņiem; Pagatavoti ēdieni, kas galvenokārt sastāv no gaļas; Pagatavoti ēdieni, kas satur (galvenokārt) cāļa gaļu; Gatavas maltītes, kas sastāv galvenokārt no zivīm; Pagatavoti ēdieni, kas satur (galvenokārt) bekonu; Pagatavoti ēdieni, kas galvenokārt sastāv no jūras veltēm; Gatavas maltītes, kas pamatā sastāv no tītara gaļas; Gatavi ēdieni, kas sastāv galvenokārt no pīles gaļas; Pagatavoti ēdieni, kas satur (galvenokārt) olas; Pagatavoti ēdieni, kas galvenokārt sastāv no gaļas aizstājējiem; Gatavi ēdieni, kas galvenokārt sastāv no dārzeņiem; Gatavi ēdieni, kas galvenokārt sastāv no medījumu gaļas; Sagatavotas maltītes, tostarp zivju kotletes; Fasēti ēdieni, kas galvenokārt sastāv no jūras veltēm; Saldētas, fasētas uzkodas, kas galvenokārt sastāv no jūras veltēm; Strauji saldēti dārzeņu ēdieni; Gatavi ēdieni, kas sastāv galvenokārt no vistas gaļas un ženšeņa [samgyetang]; Lietošanai gatavi ēdieni, kas, galvenokārt, sastāv no zivīm; Pildīti kartupeļi; Zupas; Ceptas vistas; Grilēta cāļu gaļa; Vistas cepetis; Vista teriaki mērcē; Liellopu gaļas sautējums; Iepriekš pagatavots karija sautējums; Sautējumi; Sacepumi; Iepakotas maltītes, kas galvenokārt sastāv no medījumu gaļas; Cēzara salāti; Kartupeļu salāti; Mājputnu gaļas salāti; Priekšēdiena salāti; Dārzeņu salāti; Pākšaugu salāti; Gatavi salāti; Salāti, kas pamatā pagatavoti no kartupeļiem; Sašimi; Nūdeļu zupas; Miso zupa; Maco klimpu zupa; Zupu konservi; Pagatavota miso zupa; Pagatavota zupa; Surimi (samalta zivju masa); Tadžina (pagatavots gaļas, zivju vai dārzeņu ēdiens); Liellopu kuņģi; Sagatavota gaļa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ħut, frott il-baħar u molluski, mhux ħajjin; Sopop u stokkijiet, estratti tal-laħam; Prodotti tal-ħalib jew sostituti tal-ħalib; Laħam u prodotti tal-laħam; Bajd jew prodotti tal-bajd tal-għasafar; Frott proċessat, fungi, ħxejjex ġewż u legumi; Ġwienaħ tat-tiġieġ; Prodotti tal-ikel imkessħin li fihom prinċipalment il-ħut; Frejjeġ ta' ġobon moxx magħmul minn ħalib xkummat; Nuggets tat-tiġieġ; Bisques; Brodu taċ-ċanga; Brodu [soppa]; Blalen tal-laħam; Bulgogi [dixx taċ-ċanga Korean]; Ċanga ppreparata; Klamari [ippreparat]; Soppa tal-ħut jew tal-ħaxix magħquda; Biċċa ta' majjal moqli; Shish kebabs; Ċilì bil-ġobon; Bżar aħmar bil-kapuljat (Stuffat ta' -); Sopop; Kroketti tal-ħut; Dolmas; Platti prinċipali ppreparati li jikkonsistu primarjament minn frott tal-baħar; Bebbux imsajjar [escargot]; Felafel; Fletti tal-ħut griljati; Muntun bil-bajd imsajjar bil-fwar; Ikliet ta' laħam imsajjar; Ikliet imsajra lesti magħmula l-aktar mit-tiġieġ; Ikliet imsajra lesti magħmula l-aktar mid-dundjan; Ikliet imsajra lesti li jikkonsistu kompletament jew sostanzjalment minn laħam; Ikliet lesti li jikkonsistu primarjament minn kebabs; Ikliet imsajra lesti li jikkonsistu totalment jew sostanzjalment minn annimali kkaċċjati; Ikliet imsajra lesti li jikkonsistu totalment jew sostanzjalment fi tjur; Ikliet iffriżati li jikkonsistu prinċipalment mil-laħam; Ikliet iffriżati magħmula l-aktar mit-tiġieġ; Platt imsajjar li jikkonsisti primarjament f'pejst rikk tas-sojja u tofu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Platt imsajjar li jikkonsisti primarjament f'pejst tas-sojja u tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Platt imsajjar li jikkonsisti primarjament f'tiġieġ moqli [stir-fried] u pejst iffermentat ta' bżar jaħraq [dak-galbi]; Platt imsajjar li jikkonsisti primarjament f'ħaxix iffermentat, majjal u tofu [kimchi-jjigae]; Platt imsajjar li jikkonsisti primarjament f'ċanga moqlija [stir-fried] u zalza tas-sojja ffermentata [Sogalbi]; Frejjeġ tal-bajd; Muffins tal-bajd; Biċċiet tat-tiġieġ għall-użu bħala mili għas-sendwiċis; Fażola msajjra fiz-zalza tas-sojja [Kongjaban]; Shepherd's pie [Torta tal-laħam ikkappuljat mgħottija b'saff patata maxx u msajjra l-forn]; Kejkijiet fuq il-fwar jew mixwija tal-pejst tal-ħut [kamaboko]; Kejkijiet fuq il-fwar ta' ħut imfarrak u yam [hampen]; Guacamole [maxx tal-avokado]; Soppa magħquda magħmula bl-okra (gumbo); Frejjeġ; Galbi [platt bil-laħam mixwi]; Ħut biċ-ċipps; Ħut imsajjar iffriżat; Ikliet iffriżati li jikkonsistu prinċipalment mit-tjur; Ikliet iffriżati li jikkonsistu prinċipalment mill-ħut; Ikliet ippreparati magħmula mit-tjur [fejn jiddominaw it-tjur]; Ikliet ippreparati magħmula mil-laħam (fejn il-laħam jippredomina); Ikliet ippreparati fuq bażi ta' laħam; Ikliet ippreparati ffriżati li jikkonsistu prinċipalment mill-ħaxix; Platti preparati li jikkonsistu prinċipalment mill-laħam; Ikliet imħejjija li jkun fiha [prinċipalment] tiġieġ; Ikliet ippreparati li jikkonsistu primarjament minn ħut; Ikliet ippreparati li fihom [l-aktar] bejken; Ikliet ippreparati li jikkonsistu sostanzjalment minn frott tal-baħar; Ikliet ippreparati magħmula l-aktar mid-dundjan; Ikliet ippreparati magħmula l-aktar mill-papra; Ikliet ippreparati li fihom [l-aktar] bajd; Ikliet imsajrin li jinkludu primarjament sostituti tal-laħam; Ikliet lesti li jikkonsistu prinċipalment mill-ħxejjex; Ikliet ippreparati li jikkonsistu l-aktar mil-laħam tal-kaċċa; Ikliet lesti magħmula primarjament minn pulpetti tal-ħut, ħxejjex, bajd mgħolli, u brodu (oden); Ikliet ippakkjati minn qabel magħmulin l-aktar mill-frott tal-baħar; L-ewwel platti ffriżati ppakkjati minn qabel magħmula l-aktar minn frott il-baħar; Dixxijiet tal-ħaxix iffriżati lesti; Platt imsajjar li jikkonsisti primarjament f'tiġieġ u ġinseng [samgyetang]; Ikliet imsajra li fihom prinċipalment ħut; Qxur tal-patata mimlija; Sopop; Tiġieġ moqli; Tiġieġ iggriljat (yakitori); Tiġieġ mixwi; Tiġieġ terijaki; Stuffat taċ-ċanga; Stuffat tal-kari msajjar minn qabel; Stuffaturi; Casseroles [ikel]; Ikliet ippakkjati minn qabel magħmulin l-aktar mil-laħam tal-annimali tal-kaċċa; Insalata Caesar; Insalata tal-patata; Insalati tat-tjur; Insalati bħala antipasto; Insalati tal-ħxejjex; Insalati tal-legumi; Insalati lesti; Insalata bbażata fuq il-patata; Saximi; Soppa tat-taljarini; Soppa tal-miso; Soppa tal-pulpetta tal-Matzo; Sopop fil-laned; Sopop tal-miso msajra minn qabel; Soppa msajra minn qabel; Surimi; Tajine [laħam, ħut jew dixx ta' ħaxix ippreparat]; Kirxa taċ-ċanga; Laħam ippreparat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Vis, zeevruchten en weekdieren, niet-levend; Soepen en bouillons, vleesextracten; Zuivelproducten en vervangingsmiddelen voor zuivel; Vlees en vleesproducten; Eieren en eierproducten; Bewerkte vruchten, paddenstoelen, groenten, noten en peulvruchten; Kippenvleugels; Gekoelde voedingsmiddelen, voornamelijk bestaande uit vis; Beignets van cottagecheese; Kipnuggets; Soepen van schaaldieren; Rundvleesbouillon; Bouillon [soepen]; Gehaktballen; Bulgogi; Bereid rundvlees; Inktvis (Bereide -); Vishutspot (chowder); Chicharron [gebakken reepjes vlees]; Shish kebabs; Chili con queso; Chili con carne; Consommé; Viskroketten; Dolma's; Kant-en-klare voorgerechten voornamelijk bestaande uit zeevruchten; Bereide slakken [escargots]; Falafel; Gegrilde visfilets; Maaltijd met gestoomde eieren; Kant-en-klare vleesschotels; Geprepareerde maaltijden voornamelijk bestaande uit kip; Kant-en-klaarmaaltijden, voornamelijk bestaande uit kalkoen; Kant-en-klare maaltijden, geheel of voornamelijk bestaande uit vlees; Kant-en-klare maaltijden, hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit kebab; Kant-en-klare maaltijden, geheel of voornamelijk bestaande uit wild; Kant-en-klare maaltijden, geheel of voornamelijk bestaande uit gevogelte; Diepvriesmaaltijden voornamelijk bestaande uit vlees; Bevroren maaltijden hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit kip; Kant-en-klaargerecht, hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit stevige sojabonenpasta en tofoe [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Kant-en-klaargerecht, hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit sojabonenpasta en tofoe [doenjang-jjigae]; Kant-en-klaargerecht, hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit roergebakken kip en gefermenteerde pasta van rode pepers [dak-galbi]; Kant-en-klaargerecht, hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit gefermenteerde groenten, varkensvlees en tofoe [kimchi-jjigae]; Kant-en-klaargerecht, hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit roergebakken rundvlees en gefermenteerde sojasaus [Sogalbi]; Omeletten; Eiermuffins; Stukken kip voor gebruik als vulling voor broodjes; Bonen gekookt in sojasaus [Kongjaban]; Gehaktschotels met een korst van aardappelpuree (shepherd's pie); Gestoomde of geroosterde cakejes van vispasta [kamaboko]; Gestoomde cakejes van stukjes vis en yam [hampen]; Guacamole [geprakte avocado]; Gumbo; Frittata's; Galbi [gegrilld vleesgerecht]; Vis met frites; Diepgevroren bereide vis; Diepvriesmaaltijden voornamelijk bestaande uit gevogelte; Diepvriesmaaltijden voornamelijk bestaande uit vis; Maaltijden gemaakt van gevogelte [met gevogelte als hoofdbestanddeel] (kant-en-klare -); Maaltijden (Bereide -), voornamelijk bestaande uit vlees; Vleesmaaltijden (Kant-en-klare -); Kant-en-klare diepvriesmaaltijden voornamelijk bestaande uit groenten; Maaltijden (Kant-en-klare -), bestaande hoofdzakelijk uit vlees; Maaltijden (Kant-en-klare -), voornamelijk bestaande uit kip; Kant-en-klare maaltijden voornamelijk bestaande uit vis; Bereide maaltijden, voornamelijk bestaande uit spek; Maaltijden (Kant-en-klare -), voornamelijk bestaande uit zeevruchten; Bereide maaltijden, hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit kalkoen; Kant-en-klare maaltijden voornamelijk bestaande uit eend; Kant-en-klare maaltijden, voornamelijk bestaande uit eieren; Kant-en-klare maaltijden, hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit vleesvervangers; Kant-en-klare maaltijden voornamelijk bestaande uit groenten; Maaltijden voornamelijk bestaande uit wild (Kant-en-klare -); Kant-en-klare gerechten voornamelijk bestaande uit viscake, groenten, gekookte eieren en bouillon (oden); Voorverpakte maaltijden hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit zeevruchten; Bevroren voorverpakte voorgerechten hoofdzakelijk op basis van zeevruchten; Direct ingevroren groenteschotels; Kant-en-klaargerecht, hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit kip en ginseng [samgyetang]; Kant-en-klare maaltijden voornamelijk bestaande uit vis; Aardappelen (Gevulde -); Soepen; Gebakken kip; Gegrilde kip (yakitori); Gegrilde kip; Kip teriyaki; Runderstoofpot; Voorgekookte kerrieschotel; Stoofschotels; Stoofschotel [voeding]; Voorverpakte maaltijden hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit wild; Caesar salades; Aardappelsalades; Gevogeltesalades; Antipasti-salades; Groentesalades; Groentesalades; Salades (Bereide -); Salades op basis van aardappelen; Sashimi; Noedelsoepen; Misosoep; Matzeballensoep; Soepen (Ingeblikte -); Voorgekookte misosoepen; Voorgekookte soep; Surimi; Tajines [bereide vlees-, vis- of groenteschotel]; Runderpens; Bereid vlees.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Ryby, owoce morza i mięczaki, nieżywe; Zupy i wywary, ekstrakty mięsne; Nabiał i substytuty nabiału; Mięso i wyroby mięsne; Jaja ptasie i produkty z jaj; Przetworzone owoce, grzyby, warzywa, orzechy i nasiona roślin strączkowych; Skrzydełka kurczaka; Żywność chłodzona składająca się głównie z ryb; Smażone placuszki twarogowe; Nuggetsy z kurczaka [małe kawałki kurczaka w panierce]; Zupy bisque; Bulion wołowy; Rosół [zupa]; Pulpety; Bulgogi (koreańskie danie z wołowiny); Wołowina gotowa do spożycia; Kałamarnica [przetworzona]; Chowder (zupa rybna); Skwarki; Szaszłyki; Chili con queso; Chili con carne (chili z mięsem); Buliony; Krokiety rybne; Dolma [faszerowane warzywa]; Przystawki gotowe do spożycia, składające się przede wszystkim z owoców morza; Przygotowane ślimaki; Falafel; Grillowane filety rybne; Parzona zupa z jajek; Potrawy mięsne gotowane; Ugotowane posiłki składające się głównie z kurczaka; Gotowe posiłki gotowane składające się głównie z indyka; Gotowe posiłki gotowane składające się całkowicie lub głównie z mięsa; Gotowe posiłki składające się głównie z kebaba; Gotowe posiłki gotowane składające się całkowicie lub głównie z dziczyzny; Gotowe posiłki gotowane składające się całkowicie lub głównie z drobiu; Mrożone posiłki składające się głównie z mięsa; Mrożone posiłki składające się głównie z kurczaka; Danie gotowe, składające się głównie z pasty sojowej i tofu w gęstym sosie [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Danie gotowe, w skład którego wchodzi przede wszystkim pasta sojowa i tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Danie gotowe, w skład którego wchodzi przede wszystkim krótko smażone na dużym ogniu mięso z kurczaka i pasta ze sfermentowanych ostrych papryczek [dak-galbi]; Danie gotowe, w skład którego wchodzą przede wszystkim fermentowane warzywa, wieprzowina i tofu [kimchi-jjigae]; Danie gotowe, w skład którego wchodzi przede wszystkim krótko smażona na dużym ogniu wołowina i fermentowany sos sojowy [sogalbi]; Omlety; Muffiny jajeczne; Kawałki kurczaka do kanapek; Fasola przyrządzona w sosie sojowym [Kongjaban]; Zapiekanka mięsno-ziemniaczana (shepherd's pie); Gotowane na parze lub opiekane kotleciki z pasty rybnej [kamaboko]; Gotowane na parze kotleciki z rozdrobnionej ryby i jamsów [hampen]; Guacamole [pasta z awokado]; Zupa gumbo; Frittaty; Galbi [danie z grillowanego mięsa]; Ryba z frytkami; Mrożone gotowane ryby; Mrożone posiłki składające się głównie z drobiu; Mrożone posiłki składające się głównie z ryb; Gotowe posiłki z drobiu [drób jako główny składnik]; Gotowe posiłki z mięsa [mięso jako główny składnik]; Gotowe dania z mięsa; Mrożone gotowe posiłki składające się głównie z warzyw; Gotowe dania składające się głównie z mięsa; Gotowe posiłki zawierające [głównie] kurczaka; Gotowe posiłki składające się głównie z ryb; Gotowe posiłki zawierające [głównie] boczek; Gotowe posiłki składające się głównie z owoców morza; Gotowe posiłki składające się głównie z indyka; Gotowe posiłki składające się głównie z kaczki; Gotowe posiłki zawierające [głównie] jajka; Gotowe posiłki składające się głównie z substytutów mięsa; Potrawy gotowe składające się głównie z warzyw; Gotowe posiłki składające się głównie z dziczyzny; Gotowe dania składające się głównie z kotletów rybnych, warzyw, gotowanych jajek i bulionu (oden); Zapakowane zestawy obiadowe składające się głównie z owoców morza; Mrożone pakowane przystawki składające się głównie z owoców morza; Głęboko mrożone dania warzywne; Danie gotowe, w skład którego wchodzi przede wszystkim kurczak i żeń-szeń [samgyetang]; Posiłki gotowane składające się głównie z ryb; Nadziewane skórki z ziemniaków; Zupy; Kurczak smażony; Kurczak grillowany (yakitori); Pieczony kurczak; Kurczak teriyaki; Gulasz wołowy; Gotowy gulasz z curry; Gulasze; Zapiekanki [żywność]; Zapakowane zestawy obiadowe składające się głównie z dziczyzny; Sałatka Cezar; Sałatka ziemniaczana; Sałatki drobiowe; Sałatki podawane na przystawkę; Sałatki warzywne; Sałatki z roślin strączkowych; Sałatki gotowe; Sałatki na bazie ziemniaków; Sashimi; Zupy z makaronem; Zupa miso; Zupa z kulkami z macy; Zupy w puszkach; Wstępnie ugotowana zupa miso; Wstępnie ugotowana zupa; Surimi; Tajine [gotowe danie z mięsa, ryby lub warzyw]; Flaki wołowe; Mięso gotowe do spożycia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Peixe, marisco e moluscos, não vivos; Sopas e caldos, extratos de carne; Produtos lácteos e substitutos lácteos; Carne e produtos à base de carne; Ovos de aves e produtos à base de ovo; Frutos, fungos e vegetais processados (incluindo oleaginosas e leguminosas); Asas de galinha; Alimentos refrigerados constituídos essencialmente por peixe; Bolinhos de queijo cottage; Panados de frango; Bisques [sopas]; Caldo de carne de vaca; Caldos [sopas]; Almôndegas; Bulgogi [prato Coreano à base de carne bovina]; Carne de vaca preparada; Lulas [preparadas]; Sopa de peixe; Torresmos; Espetadas de kebabs; Chile com queijo; Chili com carne; Consommés; Croquetes de peixe; Dolmas [folhas de videira recheadas]; Entradas preparadas constituídas principalmente por marisco; Caracóis preparados; Falafel; Filetes de peixe grelhados; Carne e legumes com ovos cozidos a vapor; Pratos cozinhados à base de carne; Refeições pré-confecionadas constituídas principalmente por frango; Refeições pré-confecionadas constituídas principalmente por peru; Refeições cozinhadas prontas, constituídas total ou principalmente por carne; Refeições prontas a comer constituídas principalmente por kebab; Refeições cozinhadas prontas, constituídas total ou predominantemente por caça; Refeições cozinhadas prontas, constituídas total ou predominantemente por aves; Refeições congeladas constituídas principalmente por carne; Refeições congeladas constituídas principalmente por frango; Refeições cozinhadas, constituídas principalmente por pasta de soja espessa e tofu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Refeições cozinhadas, constituídas principalmente por pasta de soja e tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Refeições cozinhadas, constituídas principalmente por frango salteado e pasta de pimenta picante fermentada [dak-galbi]; Refeições cozinhadas, constituídas principalmente por legumes fermentados, carne de porco e tofu [kimchi-jjigae]; Refeições cozinhadas, constituídas principalmente por carne de vaca salteada e molho de soja fermentado [Sogalbi]; Omeletes; Queques de ovo; Pedaços de frango para recheio de sanduíches; Feijões cozinhados em molho de soja [Kongjaban]; Empadão de carne; Bolinhos de pasta de peixe cozidos no vapor ou torrados [kamaboko]; Bolos de peixe esmagado e inhame cozidos no vapor [hampen]; Guacamole [puré de abacate]; Sopa de quiabo; Frittatas (omeletes); Galbi [prato de carne grelhada]; Filetes de peixe com batatas fritas; Peixe cozinhado congelado; Refeições congeladas constituídas principalmente por aves; Refeições congeladas constituídas principalmente por peixe; Refeições preparadas com aves [principalmente aves domésticas]; Refeições preparadas de carne [em que predomina a carne]; Refeições de carne pré-confecionadas; Refeições preparadas congeladas constituídas essencialmente por legumes; Refeições preparadas que contêm [principalmente] carne; Refeições preparadas que contêm [principalmente] frango; Refeições preparadas constituídas essencialmente por peixe; Refeições preparadas contendo principalmente bacon; Refeições preparadas que contêm [principalmente] marisco; Refeições preparadas constituídas principalmente por peru; Refeições preparadas constituídas principalmente por pato; Refeições preparadas que contêm [principalmente] ovos; Refeições preparadas constituídas principalmente por sucedâneos de carne; Refeições preparadas constituídas principalmente por legumes; Refeições preparadas que contêm [principalmente] caça; Pratos preparados essencialmente à base de bolinhos de peixe, legumes, ovos cozidos, e caldos (oden); Refeições pré-embaladas constituídas principalmente por marisco; Pratos principais congelados pré-embalados compostos principalmente de marisco; Pratos à base de legumes ulracongelados; Refeições cozinhadas, constituídas principalmente por galinha e ginseng [samgyetang]; Refeições cozinhadas constituídas principalmente por peixe; Tiras de cascas de batata; Sopas; Frango frito; Frango grelhado (yakitori (prato japonês)); Galinha assada; Galinha teriyaki (marinada em molho de soja e grelhada); Ragu de vaca; Guisado de caril pré-cozinhado; Guisados; Alimentos preparados em caçarola; Refeições pré-embaladas compostas principalmente de carne de caça; Saladas César; Salada de batata; Saladas de aves; Saladas de entrada; Saladas de legumes; Saladas de legumes; Saladas preparadas; Saladas à base de batata; Sashimi; Sopas de talharim; Sopa de miso; Sopas de bolas de matzo; Sopas em lata; Sopas de miso pré-cozinhadas; Sopa pré-cozinhada; Surimi; Tajine [pratos preparados à base de carne, peixe, ou legumes]; Tripas de bovino; Carne preparada.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Pește, fructe de mare și moluște, nu vii; Supe și baze de supă, extracte din carne; Produse lactate și înlocuitori; Carne și produse din carne; Ouă și produse din ouă; Fructe, ciuperci, legume, nuci și leguminoase prelucrate; Aripioare de pui; Alimente refrigerate constând în principal din pește; Gogoși cu brânză proaspătă de vaci; Bucățele de piept de pui pane [nuggets]; Bisque; Concentrat din carne de vacă; Fiertură [supe]; Pârjoale din carne; Bulgogi [fel de mâncare coreeană din carne de vită]; Carne de vită preparată; Calmar preparat; Supă groasă; Chicharron (șorici de porc prăjit); Frigărui Shish Kebab; Sos de brânză Velveeta amestecat cu ardei iuți chili; Chili con carne (tocană de ardei iute și carne); Consommé-uri; Crochete de pește; Sarmale în foi de viță; Antreuri preparate constând în principal din fructe de mare; Melci preparați [escargot]; Falafel; Fileuri de pește la grătar; Ghiveci cu ouă, gătit la vapori; Mâncăruri preparate pe bază de carne; Mâncăruri gătite care conțin în principal carne de pui; Mâncăruri preparate care conțin în principal carne de curcan; Alimente gătite, constând în totalitate sau în cea mai mare parte din carne; Mâncăruri preparate care constau în principal din kebab; Mâncăruri preparate care constau integral sau în principal din vânat; Mâncăruri gătite care conțin în totalitate sau aproape în totalitate carne de pui; Mâncăruri congelate constând în principal din carne; Mâncăruri congelate care conțin în principal carne de pui; Mâncare gătită constând în principal dintr-o pastă de soia consistentă și tofu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Mâncare gătită constând în principal din pastă de soia și tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Mâncare gătită constând în principal din carne de pui prăjită fâșii și pastă de ardei iute fermentat [dak-galbi]; Mâncare gătită constând în principal din legume fermentate, carne de porc și tofu [kimchi-jjigae]; Mâncare gătită constând în principal din carne de vită prăjită fâșii și sos de soia fermentat [Sogalbi]; Omlete; Brioșe cu ouă; Bucăți de carne de pui utilizate ca umplutură pentru sandvișuri; Fasole gătită în sos de soia [Kongjaban]; Plăcintă cu carne; Turte din pastă de pește fierte în abur sau prăjite [kamaboko]; Turte din pește și cartofi dulci zdrobiți, fierte în abur [hampen]; Guacamole [avocado pasat]; Supă de bame; Frittata (omletă italiană); Galbi [mâncare pe bază de carne la grătar]; Pește cu aromă de cartofi prăjiți; Pește gătit și congelat; Mâncăruri congelate constând în principal din carne de pasăre; Mâncăruri congelate constând în principal din pește; Mâncăruri preparate obținute din carne de pui [care conțin în principal carne de pui]; Mâncăruri preparate din carne (în care predomină carnea); Feluri de mâncare preparate din carne; Mâncăruri gătite și congelate constând în principal din legume; Mâncăruri preparate constând în principal din carne; Mâncăruri gătite constând în principal din carne de pui; Mâncăruri preparate constând în principal din pește; Mâncăruri preparate care conțin [în principal] bacon; Mâncăruri preparate constând în principal din fructe de mare; Mâncăruri preparate conținând în principal curcan; Mâncăruri preparate care conțin în principal carne de rață; Mâncăruri preparate care conțin [în principal] ouă; Alimente preparate care constau în principal din înlocuitori de carne; Mâncăruri gătite constând în principal din legume; Mâncăruri preparate constând în principal din carne de vânat; Mâncăruri preparate care constau în principal din chiftele din pește, legume, ouă fierte și bulion (oden); Cine preambalate care conțin în principal fructe de mare; Aperitive congelate preambalate constând în principal din fructe de mare; Mâncăruri cu legume, congelate rapid; Mâncare gătită constând în principal din carne de pui și ginseng [samgyetang]; Mâncăruri gătite constând în principal din pește; Cartofi umpluți; Supe; Carne prăjită de pui; Pui la grătar (Yakitori); Carne prajita de pui; Pui teriyaki; Tocană de vită; Tocană cu curry semipreparată; Tocăni; Tocane [alimente]; Cine preambalate constând în principal din vânat; Salată Caesar; Salate de cartofi; Salate cu carne de pasăre; Salate aperitiv; Salate de legume; Salate de legume; Salate preparate; Salate pe bază de cartofi; Sashimi; Supă de tăieței; Supe miso; Supă cu bulete din mața; Supe la conservă; Supe miso gata-preparate; Supă gata-preparată; Surimi; Tajine [fel de mâncare preparat din carne, pește sau legume]; Burtă de vită; Carne preparată.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ryby, morské plody a mäkkýše, nie živé; Polievky, vývary, bujóny, mäsové výťažky; Mliečne výrobky a ich náhradky; Mäso a mäsové výrobky; Konzumné vtáčie vajcia a výrobky z nich; Spracované ovocie, huby, zelenina, orechy a strukoviny; Kuracie krídelká; Chladené potraviny obsahujúce hlavne ryby; Guličky a placky z bieleho tvarohového syra cottage cheese na vyprážanie; Kuracie nugety; Krémová polievka s morskými živočíchmi [Bisque]; Hovädzí bujón; Vývary (bujóny); Mäsové guľky; Bulgogi (kórejské jedlo z hovädzieho mäsa); Pripravené hovädzie mäso; Kalamáre [pripravené]; Hustá rybacia polievka; Vysmážané bravčové kožky; Shish kebab; Syrová omáčka s čili papričkami [chile con queso]; Chili con carne (mexické pikantné jedlo); Vývary; Rybacie krokety; Dolmas ako kapustové zvitky s ryžou; Hotové predjedlá obsahujúce najmä morské ryby a morské plody; Slimáky (hotové jedlá); Falafel (tradičné arabské jedlo); Grilované rybie filé; Polievka hotchpotch s vajcom pripraveným na pare; Varené mäsové jedlá; Hotové varené jedlá obsahujúce predovšetkým kura; Hotové varené jedlá obsahujúce predovšetkým morku; Hotové varené jedlá obsahujúce len alebo hlavne mäso; Hotové jedlá obsahujúce predovšetkým kebab; Hotové varené jedlá pozostávajúce úplne alebo prevažne z diviny; Hotové varené jedlá obsahujúce len alebo hlavne hydinu; Mrazené jedlá obsahujúce prevažne mäso; Mrazené jedlá obsahujúce predovšetkým kura; Varené jedlo pozostávajúce najmä z hustej sójovej pasty a tofu [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Varené jedlo pozostávajúce najmä zo sójovej pasty a tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Varené jedlo pozostávajúce najmä z prudko opečeného kuracieho mäsa a fermentovanej pasty zo štipľavej papriky [dak-galbi]; Varené jedlo pozostávajúce najmä z fermentovanej zeleniny, bravčového mäsa a tofu [kimči-ččigä]; Varené jedno pozostávajúce najmä z prudko opečeného hovädzieho mäsa a fermentovanej sójovej omáčky [Sogalbi]; Omelety; Vajíčkové mafiny; Spracované kuracie kúsky používané ako plnky do sendvičov; Fazule varené v sójovej omáčke [Kongdžaban]; Nakrájané jahňacie mäso pokryté zapečenou zemiakovou kašou (pastiersky koláč); Dusené alebo opekané placky z rybacej pasty [kamaboko]; Dusené placky z roztlačenej ryby a jamov [hampen]; Guakamola (avokádová nátierka); Gumbo (polievka); Frittata; Galbi (kórejské jedlo z grilovaného mäsa); Ryba so zemiakovými hranolčekmi; Mrazené varené ryby; Mrazené jedlá obsahujúce predovšetkým hydinu; Mrazené jedlá obsahujúce predovšetkým ryby; Hotové jedlá vyrobené z hydiny [hydina je prevažujúcou zložkou]; Hotové jedlá vyrobené z mäsa [s prevažným obsahom mäsa]; Hotové jedlá z mäsa; Mrazené hotové jedlá obsahujúce hlavne zeleninu; Hotové jedlá obsahujúce hlavne mäso; Hotové jedlá obsahujúce hlavne kura; Hotové jedlá obsahujúce prevažne ryby; Hotové jedlá obsahujúce hlavne slaninu; Hotové jedlá pozostávajúce prevažne z plodov mora; Hotové jedlá obsahujúce predovšetkým morku; Hotové jedlá obsahujúce predovšetkým kačicu; Hotové jedlá obsahujúce hlavne vajcia; Hotové jedlá zložené najmä z mäsových náhradiek; Hotové jedlá, ktoré obsahujú hlavne zeleninu; Hotové jedlá pozostávajúce prevažne z diviny; Hotové jedlá obsahujúce hlavne rybacie fašírky, zeleninu, varené vajcia a vývar (oden); Vopred balené jedlá, obsahujúce prevažne morské plody; Mrazené vopred balené predjedlá pozostávajúce predovšetkým z morských plodov; Rýchlomrazené zeleninové pokrmy; Varené jedlo pozostávajúce najmä z kuracieho mäsa a ženšenu [samgjetang]; Varené jedlá obsahujúce predovšetkým ryby; Plnené zemiakové šupky; Polievky; Vyprážané kura; Grilované kurča (yakitori) (japonský kurací špíz); Pečené kuracie mäso; Kurča v omáčke teriyaki; Dusené hovädzie mäso; Predvarené jedlá (guláš s kari korením); Guľáš (Dusené mäso); Jedlá pripravované v zapekacej nádobe; Vopred balené večere, obsahujúce prevažne zverinu; Šalát Caesar; Zemiakový šalát; Hydinové šaláty; Šalátové predjedlá; Zeleninové šaláty; Šaláty zo strukovín; Hotové šaláty; Zemiakové šaláty; Sašimi; Rezancová polievka; Miso polievka; Polievka s macesovými guľôčkami; Konzervované polievky; Predvarené polievky miso; Predvarené polievky; Surimi; Tajine [hotové jedlo z mäsa, rýb alebo zeleniny]; Hovädzie držky; Pripravené mäso.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Ribe, morski sadeži in mehkužci, neživi; Juhe in jušne osnove, mesni ekstrakti; Mlečni proizvodi in njihovi nadomestki; Meso in mesni izdelki; Ptičja jajca in jajčni proizvodi; Predelano sadje, gobe, zelenjava, oreščki in stročnice; Piščančje perutničke; Ohlajena živila, sestavljena predvsem iz rib; Skutni ocvrtki; Piščančji kroketi; Juha bisque; Goveja juha; Mesna juha; Mesne kroglice; Bulgogi [korejska goveja jed]; Pripravljena govedina; Lignji [pripravljeni]; Gosta ribja juha; Ocvirki (chicharron); Šiš kebabi; Čili s sirom; Chili con carne (Čili z mesom); Krepke goveje juhe; Ribji kroketi; Dolme [polnjena zelenjava]; Pripravljene glavne jedi, sestavljene predvsem iz morskih sadežev; Pripravljeni polži [escargot]; Falafel; Ribji fileji na žaru; Enolončnica z jajci, kuhanimi na sopari; Kuhane mesne jedi; Pripravljene kuhane jedi, sestavljene predvsem iz piščančjega mesa; Pripravljene kuhane jedi, sestavljene predvsem iz puranjega mesa; Pripravljene kuhane jedi, ki so sestavljene v celoti ali pretežno iz mesa; Pripravljeni obroki, sestavljeni predvsem iz kebaba; Pripravljene kuhane jedi, sestavljene v celoti ali pretežno iz divjačine; Pripravljene kuhane jedi, sestavljene v celoti ali pretežno iz perutnine; Zamrznjeni obroki, sestavljeni predvsem iz mesa; Zamrznjene jedi, sestavljene predvsem iz piščančjega mesa; Kuhana jed, sestavljena predvsem iz obogatene sojine paste in tofuja [cheonggukjang-jjigae]; Kuhana jed, sestavljena predvsem iz sojine paste in tofuja [doenjang-jjigae]; Kuhana jed, sestavljena predvsem iz na hitro prepraženega piščanca in fermentirane paste iz pekoče paprike [dak-galbi]; Kuhana jed, sestavljena predvsem iz fermentirane zelenjave, svinjine in tofuja [kimchi-jjigae]; Kuhana jed, sestavljena predvsem iz na hitro prepražene govedine in fermentirane sojine omake [sogalbi]; Omlete; Jajčni mafini; Kosi piščanca, ki se uporabljajo kot nadev za sendviče; Fižol, kuhan v sojini omaki [kongjaban]; Pita z mletim mesom in pire krompirjem; Na sopari kuhane ali popečene polpete iz ribje paste [kamaboko]; Na sopari kuhane polpete iz pretlačene ribe jama [hampen]; Gvakamole [pretlačen avokado]; Gumbo (vrsta začinjene enolončnice); Fritate; Galbi [jed iz mesa na žaru]; Ribe z ocvrtim krompirjem; Zamrznjene kuhane ribe; Zamrznjeni obroki, sestavljeni predvsem iz perutnine; Zamrznjeni obroki, sestavljeni predvsem iz rib; Pripravljeni obroki iz perutnine [perutnina prevladuje]; Pripravljeni obroki, izdelani iz mesa [meso prevladuje]; Pripravljene mesne jedi; Zamrznjene pripravljene jedi, sestavljene predvsem iz zelenjave; Pripravljene jedi, ki so sestavljene predvsem iz mesa; Pripravljeni obroki, ki vsebujejo [pretežno] piščanca; Pripravljeni obroki, sestavljeni predvsem iz rib; Pripravljeni obroki, ki vsebujejo [pretežno] slanino; Pripravljeni obroki, ki so sestavljeni predvsem iz morskih sadežev; Pripravljene jedi, sestavljene predvsem iz puranjega mesa; Pripravljene jedi, sestavljene predvsem iz račjega mesa; Pripravljeni obroki, ki vsebujejo [pretežno] jajca; Pripravljeni obroki, sestavljeni predvsem iz mesnih nadomestkov; Pripravljeni obroki, sestavljeni predvsem iz zelenjave; Pripravljeni obroki, ki so sestavljeni predvsem iz divjačine; Pripravljene jedi, sestavljene v glavnem iz ribjih pogačic, zelenjave, kuhanih jajc in mesne juhe (oden); Pakirani obroki (večerje), sestavljeni predvsem iz morskih sadežev; Zamrznjene pakirane predjedi, ki so sestavljene predvsem iz morskih sadežev; Hitro zamrznjene zelenjavne jedi; Kuhana jed, sestavljena predvsem iz piščanca in ginsenga [samgyetang]; Kuhani obroki, sestavljeni predvsem iz rib; Nadevan krompir; Juhe; Ocvrti piščanec; Piščanec na žaru (yakitori (japonska piščančja nabodalca)); Pečen piščanec; Piščanec terijaki; Obara iz govedine; Predkuhana enolončnica s curryjem; Enolončnice; Kozice [hrana]; Predpakirani obroki, sestavljeni predvsem iz divjačine; Cezarjeva solata; Krompirjeva solata; Solate s perutnino; Solate kot predjedi; Zelenjavne solate; Solate iz stročnic; Pripravljene solate; Solate na osnovi krompirja; Sašimi; Juhe z rezanci; Miso juha; Juha z matzo kroglicami; Juhe v konzervi; Vnaprej kuhana juha miso; Vnaprej kuhana juha; Surimi; Tajine [pripravljena jed iz mesa, rib ali zelenjave]; Goveji vampi; Pripravljeno meso.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Fisk, skaldjur och blötdjur, inte levande; Soppor och buljonger, köttextrakt; Mejeriprodukter och mejeriersättningar; Kött och köttprodukter; Fågelägg och äggprodukter; Behandlade frukter, svampar, grönsaker, nötter och baljfrukter; Kycklingvingar; Kylda livsmedel bestående i huvudsak av fisk; Fritter av kornig färskostmassa; Friterade kycklingbitar [nuggets]; Bisque [soppa]; Köttbuljong; Buljong [soppor]; Köttbullar; Bulgogi [koreansk kötträtt]; Bearbetat nötkött; Bläckfisk [tillagade]; Chowder [soppa]; Friterad fläsksvål; Shish kebab; Chili med ost; Chili con carne; Consomméer; Fiskkroketter; Dolmar; Färdiga förrätter huvudsakligen bestående av fisk och skaldjur; Tillagade sniglar; Falafel; Grillade fiskfiléer; Hotchpotch framställd av ångkokta ägg; Tillagade kötträtter; Färdiglagade måltider i huvudsak bestående av kyckling; Färdiglagade måltider i huvudsak bestående av kalkon; Färdiglagade måltider bestående helt eller i huvudsak helt av kött; Färdiglagade måltider huvudsakligen bestående av kebab; Färdiglagade måltider bestående helt eller i huvudsak av vilt; Färdiglagade måltider bestående helt eller i huvudsak av fjäderfä; Frysta måltider i huvudsak bestående av kött; Frysta måltider i huvudsak bestående av kyckling; Tillagad rätt huvudsakligen bestående av fyllig sojabönspasta och tofu [cheonggukjang -jigae]; Tillagad rätt huvudsakligen bestående av sojabönspasta och tofu [doenjang-jjigae]; Tillagad rätt huvudsakligen bestående av wokad kyckling och fermenterad het chilipepparpasta [dak-galbi]; Tillagad rätt huvudsakligen bestående av fermenterad grönsak, griskött och tofu [kimchi-jjigae]; Tillagad rätt huvudsakligen bestående av wokat oxkött och fermenterad sojasås [Sogalbi]; Omeletter; Äggmuffins; Kycklingbitar för användning som fyllning i sandwiches; Bönor tillagade i sojasås [Kongjaban]; Köttfärs med potatismos (Shepherd´s pie); Ångkokta eller rostade kakor av fiskpasta [kamaboko]; Ångkokta kakor av mosad fisk och jams [hampen]; Guacamole [mosad avokado]; Gumbo; Frittator; Galbi [grillad kötträtt]; Fisk och pommes frites; Fryst tillagad fisk; Frysta måltider i huvudsak bestående av fjäderfä; Frysta måltider huvudsakligen bestående av fisk; Tillagade måltider framställda av fjäderfä [fjäderfä dominerande]; Tillagade måltider gjorda av kött [övervägande kött]; Tillagade maträtter av kött; Frysta tillagade måltider bestående huvudsakligen av grönsaker; Tillagade rätter bestående huvudsakligen av kött; Tillagade måltider innehållande [i huvudsak] kyckling; Tillagade måltider, huvudsakligen bestående av fisk; Färdiglagade måltider innehållande [huvudsakligen] bacon; Tillagade måltider bestående huvudsakligen av skaldjur; Färdiglagade måltider huvudsakligen bestående av kalkon; Färdiglagade måltider huvudsakligen bestående av anka; Tillagade måltider innehållande ägg [huvudsakligen]; Tillagade måltider huvudsakligen bestående av köttersättningar; Tillagade måltider huvudsakligen bestående av grönsaker; Tillagade måltider huvudsakligen bestående av vilt; Tillagade maträtter huvudsakligen bestående av fiskkakor, grönsaker, kokta ägg och buljong; Färdigpackade måltider huvudsakligen bestående av fisk och skaldjur; Frusna förpaketerade förrätter i huvudsak bestående av fisk och skaldjur; Snabbfrysta grönsaksrätter; Tillagad rätt huvudsakligen bestående av kyckling och ginseng [samgyetang]; Tillagade måltider i huvudsak bestående av fisk; Fyllda potatisskal; Soppor; Stekt kyckling; Grillad kyckling (yakitori); Ugnsstekt kyckling; Teriyaki-kyckling; Gryta av oxkött; Tilllagade currygrytor; Gryträtter; Casserole [livsmedel]; Färdigpackade måltider huvudsakligen bestående av vilt; Caesarsallad; Potatissallad; Fjäderfäsallader; Antipastosallader; Grönsakssallader; Sallad av baljväxter; Färdiga sallader; Potatisbaserade sallader; Sashimi; Nudelsoppa; Misosoppa; Kneidlachsoppor; Konserverade soppor; Tillagade misosoppor; Tillagad soppa; Surimi; Tagine [färdiglagade måltider av kött, fisk eller grönsaker]; Komage; Bearbetat kött.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>30</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Захар, естествени подсладители, сладкарски покрития и пълнежи, пчелни продукти; Лед, сладолед, замразен йогурт и сорбети; Обработени зърнени храни, нишестета и стоки от тях, смеси за тестени изделия и кваси; Баодзъ [кифлички с пълнеж, приготвени на пара]; Основи за пица; Бананови бухтички; Ананасови бухтички; Бибимбап [ориз със зеленчуци и телешко месо]; Оризови бисквити; Готови пикантни хранителни продукти, направени от картофено брашно; Готови хранителни продукти под формата на сосове; Франзели с пълнеж; Сухи бисквити с вкус на билки; Крекери, овкусени с подправки; Сухи бисквити с вкус на месо; Сухи бисквити с вкус на зеленчуци; Сухи бисквити с пълнеж от сирене; Сухи бисквити с вкус на сирене; Крекери от обработени зърнени храни; Оризови кракери във формата пелети (араре); Бисквити с лук; Топки от лепкав ориз; Пухкави топчета със сирене [леки закуски от царевица]; Оризови кнедли; Оризови кнедли, покрити със сладък конфитюр (анкоро); Соленки; Меки соленки; Кръгли кифли със стафиди; Тортила (чипс); Хрупкави бисквити, приготвени от зърнени храни; Бисквити от пълнозърнесто брашно; Чоу мейн; Чоу мейн [ястия на основата на китайски макарони]; Оризови крекери; Оризови корички; Шарлота (сладкиш); Палачинки; Американски палачинки; Палачинка от зелен лук [pajeon]; Предварително опакован обяд, състоящ се предимно от ориз, както и месо, риба или зеленчуци; Продукти за леки закуски, приготвени от галета; Продукти за леки закуски, приготвени от зърнено брашно; Продукти за леки закуски, приготвени от царевично брашно; Продукти за снаксове, направени от картофено брашно; Продукти за леки закуски, приготвени от оризово брашно; Продукти за леки закуски, приготвени от соево брашно; Леки закуски (снаксове) с вкус на тортиля; Леки закуски, приготвени от царевица; Снаксове, приготвени от царевица под формата на кълба; Снаксове, приготвени от царевица под формата на пръстени; Леки закуски на многозърнеста основа; Леки закуски на оризова основа; Кекс от пържен ориз [topokki]; Солени палачинки; Кимбап [корейско ястие с ориз]; Царевични зърна, които са печени; Пуканки, покрити с карамел със сладки ядки; Китайски пълнени тестени топки (gyoza, готвени); Торти от просо; Оризов пай [кекс]; Оризови кексове с шоколадово покритие; Кексчета от лепкав ориз (Chapsalttock); Корейски традиционен оризов сладкиш [injeolmi]; Желе от елда (Memilmuk); Пълни хлебни ролца; Френски тост; Лепкави кексчета от смлян ориз, покрити с бобов прах [инджолми]; Изделия от многолистно тесто, съдържащи шунка; Замразени тестени изделия, пълнени с месо и зеленчуци; Хранителен тестен продукт с пълнеж; Консервирани макаронени храни; Предварително изпечени кори за пица; Печива, състоящи се от зеленчуци и месо от домашни птици; Яйчени рулца; Пай със свинско месо; Пирожки с пълнеж от месо; Ястия от макаронени изделия; Сухи и течни готови за употреба храни, главно съставени от ориз; Готови ястия от ориз; Сублимационно изсушени ястия с основна съставка ориз; Сублимационно изсушени ястия с основна съставка макаронени изделия; Ястия на основата на ориз; Печива, състоящи се от зеленчуци и месо; Печива, състоящи се от зеленчуци и риба; Замразени баници с пълнеж от зеленчуци; Замразени баници с пълнеж от месо; Овкусени сладки; Хрупкав овесен флейкс, съдържащ сушени плодове; Рамен [японско ястие на основата на нудълс]; Равиоли; Равиоли [приготвени]; Скаридени кнедли; Кутии с обяд, състоящи се от ориз, с добавено месо, риба или зеленчуци; Ястия на базата на нудели (макаронени храни); Готови ястия на основата на тестени варива; Готови ястия на основата на ориз; Ризото; Сладък ориз с ядки и хинап [яксик]; Лепкав ориз, опакован в бамбукови листa [Zongzi]; Приготвен ориз, завит във водорасли; Препечени сандвичи със сирене с шунка; Препечени сандвичи със сирене; Сандвичи, съдържащи салата; Сандвичи с пиле; Препечени сандвичи; Люта наденичка и кетчуп в разрязано хлебче; Оризови крекери [сенбей]; Китайски тестени топки на пара [shumai, готвени]; Кашкавален снакс на спирали [закуски]; Консервирани спагети в доматен сос; Спагети и кюфтенца; Пайове с пилешко месо; Пай със зеленчуци; Пайове, съдържащи месо; Пай, съдържащ птиче месо; Пай, съдържащ зеленчуци; Пай, съдържащ месо от дивеч; Пай, съдържащ риба; Месни пайове; Пресни пайове; Пирожки с пълнеж, пайове [сладки или пикантни]; Пайове с месо [приготвени]; Вид китайски кнедли [уон тон]; Завит сандвич [сандвич]; Пилешки дюнери.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Cukr, přírodní sladidla, sladké polevy a náplně, výrobky z včelích produktů; Led, zmrzliny, mražené jogurty a sorbety; Zpracované obilí, škrob a produkty z nich vyrobené, pečicí přípravky a droždí; Baozi [nadívané bochánky]; Pizza korpusy; Banánové smaženky; Ananasové smaženky; Bibimbap [rýže s kousky zeleniny a masa]; Rýžové sušenky; Hotová slaná jídla vyrobená z bramborové mouky; Hotové potraviny v podobě omáček; Plněné bagety; Krekry ochucené bylinkami; Krekry ochucené kořením; Krekry s masovou příchutí; Krekry ochucené zeleninou; Krekry plněné sýrem; Krekry ochucené sýrem; Krekry vyrobené ze zpracovaných cereálií/obilnin; Rýžové krekry ve tvaru pelet (arare); Cibulové bochánky; Rýžové kuličky; Extrudované sýrové kuličky [kukuřičné chuťovky]; Rýžové knedlíčky; Rýžové knedlíčky polité džemem ze sladkých fazolí (ankoro); Preclíky; Jemné preclíky; Briošky; Tortillové chipsy; Cereální lupínky; Celozrnné lupínky; Chow mein (čínské nudle); Chow mein [jídla na bázi nudlí]; Rýžové krekry; Rýžové korpusy; Drobenkový koláč; Palačinky (crepes); Lívance; Koláč se zelenou cibulí (pajeon); Balené obědy sestávající zejména z rýže a obsahující také maso, ryby nebo zeleninu; Pochutiny vyrobené ze strouhanky; Pochutiny vyrobené z obilné mouky; Pochutiny vyrobené z kukuřičné mouky; Pochutiny vyrobené z bramborové mouky; Pochutiny vyrobené z rýžové mouky; Pochutiny vyrobené ze sójové mouky; Tortila (chuťovky); Pochutiny připravené z kukuřice; Kukuřičné křupky (pochutiny); Kukuřičné kroužky (pochutiny); Vícezrnné pochutiny; Svačinové občerstvení na bázi rýže; Restované rýžové koláčky (topokki); Slané palačinky; Gimbap [korejský rýžový pokrm]; Pražená kukuřičná zrna; Karamelový popcorn s praženými ořechy; Čínské plněné knedlíky [gyoza, vařené]; Jáhlové koláče; Rýžové chlebíčky; Rýžové chlebíčky v čokoládové polevě; Koláčky z lepkavé rýže (chapsalttock); Tradiční korejský rýžový zákusek (injeolmi); Rosol z pohanky (memilmuk); Obložené housky; Sladká topinka; Koláček z drcené lepkavé rýžové mouky posypaný sušenými drcenými fazolemi [injeolmi]; Pečivo z listového těsta se šunkou; Mražené pečivo plněné masem a zeleninou; Plněné těstoviny; Konzervované těstoviny; Předpečené korpusy na pizzu; Pečivo obsahující zeleninu a drůbeží maso; Vaječné závitky; Koláče plněné vepřovým masem; Masové koláče; Těstovinová jídla; Tuhá a tekutá hotová jídla obsahující převážně rýži; Hotová jídla z rýže; Lyofilizovaná jídla s rýží jako hlavní složkou; Lyofilizovaná jídla s těstovinami jako hlavní složkou; Rýžové pokrmy; Pečivo obsahující zeleninu a maso; Pečivo obsahující zeleninu a ryby; Mražené pečivo plněné zeleninou; Mražené pečivo plněné masem; Slané pečivo; Ovesné hrudky obsahující sušené ovoce; Ramen [japonské polévky na bázi nudlí]; Ravioli; Ravioli (hotové); Knedlíčky s krevetkami; Obědy v krabičkách obsahující rýži s masem, rybami nebo zeleninou; Hotová jídla na bázi nudlí; Hotová jídla na bázi těstovin; Hotová jídla na bázi rýže; Rizoto; Sladká rýže s ořechy a jujubou [yaksik]; Lepkavá rýže zabalená do bambusových listů (Zongzi); Hotová rýže zabalená do mořské řasy; Zapečený sýrový sendvič se šunkou; Zapečený sýrový sendvič; Sendviče se salátem; Sendviče s kuřecím masem; Grilované sendviče; Horké párky s kečupem v rozkrojených rohlících; Rýžové krekry [Senbei]; Čínské knedlíčky vařené v páře (shumai); Sýrové křupky [jednohubky]; Konzervované špagety v rajčatové omáčce; Špagety a masové knedlíčky; Kuřecí koláče (páje); Zeleninové koláče; Masové koláče; Koláče s drůbeží; Koláče obsahující zeleninu; Koláče se zvěřinou; Rybí koláče; Pot pies (slané plněné koláče); Čerstvé plněné pečivo; Koláče s náplní [sladkou nebo pikantní]; Masové koláče [hotové]; Knedlíčky won ton; Wrap (zavinutý sendvič); Kuřecí wrapy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sukker, naturlige sødemidler, søde overtræk og fyld, produkter fra bier; Is, spiseis, frossen yoghurt, og sorbet; Forarbejdet korn, stivelse og varer fremstillet deraf, bagepræparater og gær; Baozi; Pizzadej; Ristede bananklatkager; Stegte ananasringe; Bibimbap [ris blandet med grøntsager og oksekød]; Riskiks; Tilberedte krydrede næringsmidler fremstillet af kartoffelmel; Tilberedte næringsmidler i form af sovser; Flutes med fyld; Kiks med urtesmag; Kiks med krydret smag; Kiks med kødsmag; Kiks med grøntsagssmag; Kiks med ostefyld; Crackers med ostesmag; Kiks fremstillet af tilberedte kornprodukter; Pilleformede riskiks (arare); Kiks med løgsmag; Klæbrige riskugler; Poppede ostekugler [majssnacks]; Risdumplings med fyld; Risboller overtrukket med sød bønnepasta (ankoro); Saltkringler; Bløde saltkringler; Briocher; Tortillachips; Chips fremstillet af korn; Fuldkornschips; Chow mein (kinesisk ret baseret på nudler); Chow mein [nudelbaserede retter]; Sprøde riskiks; Risskorper; Smuldredej; Crepes [pandekager]; Pandekager; Pandekager med forårsløg (pajeon); Færdigpakkede frokostretter, hovedsagelig bestående af ris og indeholdende kød, fisk eller grøntsager; Snackvarer fremstillet af knuste tvebakker; Snackvarer fremstillet af kornmel; Snackvarer fremstillet af majsmel; Snackvarer fremstillet af kartoffelmel; Snackvarer fremstillet af rismel; Snackvarer fremstillet af sojamel; Tortillasnacks; Majssnacks; Snackvarer fremstillet af majs og i oppustet form; Snackvarer fremstillet af majs og i form af ringe; Snackvarer fremstillet på basis af flere slags korn; Snacks baseret på ris; Lynstegte riskager (topokki); Krydrede madpandekager; Gimbap [koreansk risret]; Ristede majskerner; Karamelovertrukne popcorn med kandiserede nødder; Kinesiske fyldte boller (gyoza, kogte); Hirsekager; Riskager; Chokoladeovertrukne riskager; Kager lavet af klæbrig ris (chapsalttock); Traditionelle koreanske riskager (injeolmi); Boghvedegelé (memilmuk); Fyldte rundstykker; Arme riddere; Glutinøs, stødt riskage dækket med bønnepulver [injeolmi]; Butterdej med skinke; Frossen dej med fyld af kød og grøntsager; Fyldt pasta; Pastafødevarer (makaroni o.l.) på dåse; Forbagte pizzabunde; Konditorivarer bestående af grøntsager og fjerkræ; Æggeruller [forårsruller]; Svinetærter; Kød indbagt i dej; Pastaretter (makaroni o.l.); Tørrede færdigretter og færdigretter indeholdende væske, hovedsageligt bestående af ris; Færdigretter af ris; Frysetørrede retter hovedsageligt bestående af ris; Frysetørrede retter hovedsageligt bestående af pasta; Risbaserede retter; Konditorivarer bestående af grøntsager og kød; Konditorivarer med grøntsager og fisk; Frossen dej med grøntsagsfyld; Frossen dej med fyld af kød; Konditorivarer med krydret smag; Havregrynskugler indeholdende tørret frugt; Ramen; Ravioli; Ravioli [tilberedt]; Melboller med rejer; Madpakker bestående af ris tilsat kød, fisk eller grøntsager; Nuddelbaserede tilberedte måltider; Pastabaserede færdigretter; Færdigretter fremstillet på basis af ris; Risotto; Søde ris med nødder og brystbær [yaksik]; Glutinøse ris svøbt i bambusblade [zongzi]; Tilberedt ris rullet i tang; Ristede ostesandwicher med skinke; Ristede ostesandwicher; Sandwicher indeholdende salat; Sandwicher indeholdende kylling; Ristede sandwicher; Varm pølse og ketchup i opskåret brød; Riskiks; Dampede kinesiske boller (shumai, kogte); Ostechips [snacks]; Spaghetti i tomatsauce på dåse; Spaghetti og kødboller; Kylling indbagt i dej; Grøntsagstærter; Tærter indeholdende kød; Indbagte tærter indeholdende fjerkræ; Indbagte dejretter indeholdende grøntsager; Pie indeholdende vildt; Indbagte dejretter med fisk; Grydepier; Friske tærter; Pier [søde eller krydret]; Kødpier [tilberedte]; Wonton; Wrap [sandwich]; Kyllingewraps.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Zucker, natürliche Süßungsmittel, süße Glasuren und Füllungen sowie Bienenprodukte zu Speisezwecken; Eis, Eiscreme, gefrorener Joghurt, Sorbets; Verarbeitetes Getreide und Stärken für Nahrungsmittel sowie Waren hieraus, Backzubereitungen und Hefe; Baozi; Pizzafertigböden; Bananenbeignets; Ananasbeignets; Bibimbap [Reisgericht mit Gemüse und Rindfleisch]; Reisplätzchen; Pikante Fertignahrungsmittel aus Kartoffelmehl; Zubereitete Lebensmittel in Form von Soßen; Gefüllte Baguettes; Cracker mit Kräutergeschmack; Cracker mit würzigem Geschmack; Cracker mit Fleischgeschmack; Cracker mit Gemüsegeschmack; Mit Käse gefüllte Cracker; Cracker mit Käsegeschmack; Cracker aus verarbeitetem Getreide; Gepresste Reiskräcker [Arare]; Zwiebelkekse; Klebreisbälle; Puffkäsebällchen [Maissnacks]; Reisknödel; Reisknödel, garniert mit süßer Bohnenkonfitüre [Ankoro]; Brezeln; Weiche Brezen; Brioches; Tortillachips; Chips aus Getreide; Weizenchips; Chow Mein; Chow Mein [Nudelgerichte]; Reiskräcker; Reiskrusten; Streusel; Crêpes; Pfannkuchen [Crepes]; Pfannkuchen mit Frühlingszwiebeln [pajeon]; Überwiegend aus Reis bestehende abgepackte Mittagsgerichte mit Fleisch, Fisch oder Gemüse; Snacks aus Semmelmehl; Imbisserzeugnisse aus Getreidemehl; Snacks aus Maismehl; Aus Kartoffelmehl zubereitete Snacks; Imbisserzeugnisse aus Reismehl; Imbisserzeugnisse aus Sojamehl; Tortilla-Snacks; Aus Mais zubereitete Snacks; Imbissgerichte aus Mais in Form von Backwaren; Imbissgerichte aus Mais in Form von Ringen; Snacks auf Mehrkornbasis; Reissnacks; Frittierter Reiskuchen [topokki]; Pikante Pfannkuchen; Gimbap [Reisgericht koreanischer Art]; Geröstetes Maiskorn; Karamellisiertes Popcorn mit kandierten Nüssen; Gefüllte chinesische Klöße [Gyoza, gekocht]; Hirsekuchen; Reiskuchen; Reiswaffeln mit Schokoladenüberzug; Klebreiskuchen [Chapsalttock]; Traditioneller koreanischer Reiskuchen [injeolmi]; Buchweizengelee [Memilmuk]; Gefülltes Brot; Arme Ritter; Kuchen aus gestampftem Klebreis mit Bohnenpulver überzogen [Injeolmi]; Blätterteig mit Schinken; Tiefgekühlte feine Backwaren mit Fleisch und Gemüse gefüllt; Gefüllte Nudeln; Nudeln in Dosen; Vorgebackene Pizzaböden; Pasteten bestehend aus Gemüse und Geflügel; Frühlingsrolle; Schweinepastete; Fleischpasteten; Pastagerichte; Trockene und flüssige Fertiggerichte, überwiegend bestehend aus Reis; Reisfertiggerichte; Gefriergetrocknete Reisgerichte; Gefriergetrocknete Nudelgerichte; Gerichte auf Reisbasis; Pasteten aus Gemüse und Fleisch; Feine Backwaren mit Gemüse- und Fischfüllungen; Gefrorene, mit Gemüse gefüllte Teigwaren; Gefrorene, mit Fleisch gefüllte Teigwaren; Pikantes Gebäck; Hafercluster mit Trockenfrüchten; Ramen; Ravioli; Zubereitete Ravioli; Klößchen mit Shrimps; Verpacktes Essen bestehend aus Reis mit Fleisch, Fisch oder Gemüse; Nudelgerichte; Zubereitete Mahlzeiten aus Teigwaren; Fertiggerichte auf Reisbasis; Risotto; Süßer Reis mit Nüssen und Jujuben [Yaksik]; In Bambusblätter eingewickelter Klebreis [Zongzi]; Zubereiteter, in Meeresalgen eingerollter Reis; Getoastetes Käsesandwich mit Schinken; Getoastetes Käse-Sandwich; Sandwiches mit Salat; Sandwiches mit Hähnchen; Getoastete Sandwiches; Heiße Würstchen und Ketchup in aufgeschnittenen Brötchen; Reiscracker; Chinesische gedämpfte Teigtaschen [Shumai, gekocht]; Käseflips; Spaghetti mit Tomatensoße in Dosen; Spaghetti mit Fleischbällchen; Hähnchenpasteten; Gemüsepasteten; Fleischhaltige Pasteten; Pasteten mit Geflügel; Pasteten mit Gemüse; Pasteten mit Wild; Pasteten mit Fisch; Pot Pies [Auflauf]; Frische Pasteten; Pasteten [süß oder herzhaft]; Zubereitete Fleischpasteten; Wantans; Wraps [Sandwich]; Hühnchenwraps.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ζάχαρη, φυσικές γλυκαντικές ουσίες, γλυκιά επικάλυψη και γλυκιά γέμιση, μελισσοκομικά προϊόντα· Πάγος, παγωτά, παγωμένο γιαούρτι και γρανίτες· Επεξεργασμένα δημητριακά, άμυλα και προϊόντα που κατασκευάζονται από αυτά, ψημένα παρασκευάσματα και μαγιά· Baozi [γεμιστά ψωμάκια]· Βάσεις για πίτσα [ζύμη]· Σβίγγοι και τηγανίτες μπανάνας· Σβίγγοι ανανά· Bibimbap [ρύζι ανάμικτο με λαχανικά και βοδινό]· Ρυζιού κέικ· Έτοιμα αλμυρά τρόφιμα από άλευρο πατάτας· Έτοιμα τρόφιμα σε μορφή σαλτσών· Μπαγκέτες με γέμιση· Κράκερ με γεύση βοτάνων· Κράκερ με γεύση μπαχαρικών· Κράκερ με γεύση κρέατος· Κράκερ με γεύση λαχανικών· Κράκερ με γέμιση τυριού· Κράκερ με γεύση τυριού· Κράκερ από παρασκευασμένα δημητριακά· Στρογγυλά κράκερ ρυζιού (αράρε)· Μπισκότα, ψωμάκια, παξιμάδια και γεμιστά πιτάκια με κρεμμύδι· Γλυκές ρυζόμπαλες· Φουσκωτά τυρομπαλάκια [μικρογεύματα καλαμποκιού]· Ντάμπλινγκς [τυλιχτά και γεμιστά πιτάκια στρογγυλά ή τρίγωνα] με βάση το ρύζι· Ντάμπλινγκ ρυζιού με επικάλυψη μαρμελάδας από γλυκό φασόλι (ανκόρο)· Αλμυρά κουλούρια (τύπου πρέτσελ)· Μαλακά πρέτσελ· Μπριός (τσουρεκάκια)· Τσιπς τορτίγιας· Τραγανά τεμάχια (κρισπς) από δημητριακά· Παξιμάδια από σιτάρι ολικής αλέσεως· Τσόου μέιν (φιλετάκια με τηγανιτά κινέζικα ζυμαρικά)· Τσόου μέιν [πιάτα με βάση τις νούγιες]· Κράκερ ρυζιού· Γαλέτες ρυζιού· Γλυκά με φρούτα και επικάλυψη τριμμένη ζύμη (crumble)· Κρέπες· Τηγανίτες· Τηγανίτα με πράσινο κρεμμύδι [pajeon]· Προσυσκευασμένα γεύματα αποτελούμενα κυρίως από ρύζι,τα οποία περιλαμβάνουν κρέας, ψάρι και λαχανικά· Προϊόντα μικρογευμάτων (σνακ) από τρίμμα φρυγανιάς· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) από άλευρα δημητριακών· Προϊόντα μικρογευμάτων (σνακ) από αραβοσιτάλευρο· Προϊόντα μικρογευμάτων (σνακ) από πατατάλευρο· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) από ρυζάλευρο· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) από αλεύρι σόγιας· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) τορτίγιας· Μικρογεύματα από αραβόσιτο· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) από διογκωμένο καλαμπόκι· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) από καλαμπόκι σε μορφή ροδέλων· Μικρογεύματα με βάση διάφορα δημητριακά· Μικρογεύματα (σνακ) με βάση το ρύζι· Κέικ τηγανητού ρυζιού [topokki]· Αλμυρές τηγανίτες· Gimbap [κορεατικά πιάτα με βάση το ρύζι]· Ψημένοι σπόροι καλαμποκιού· Ποπκόρν με επικάλυψη καραμέλας και καραμελωμένους ξηρούς καρπούς· Κινέζικα γεμιστά ντάμπλινγκ (gyoza), μαγειρεμένα· Αλμυρές και γλυκές πίτες και μπιφτέκια με κεχρί· Κέικ ρυζιού· Γκοφρέτες ρυζιού με επικάλυψη σοκολάτας· Κολλώδη κέικ ρυζιού (Chapsalttock)· Παραδοσιακό κορεατικό κέικ ρυζιού [injeolmi]· Ζελέ από μαύρο σιτάρι (Memilmuk)· Ψωμί με γέμιση· Αβγόφετες· Κολλώδη ρολά από αλεσμένο ρύζι με επικάλυψη σκόνης φασολιών [injeolmi], κορεατική κουζίνα· Σφολιάτα με χοιρομέρι· Κατεψυγμένες πίτες γεμιστές με κρέας και λαχανικά· Παραγεμισμένα ζυμαρικά· Τρόφιμα ζυμαρικών σε κονσέρβα· Προψημένες βάσεις πίτσας· Πίτες με λαχανικά και κρέας πουλερικών· Εγκ ρολ (κινέζικο φαγητό με βάση ζύμη από αυγά)· Πίτες με χοιρινό κρέας· Κρεατόπιτες· Πιάτα (γέυματα) ζυμαρικών· Έτοιμα φαγητά σε ξηρή και υγρή μορφή, αποτελούμενα κυρίως από ρύζι· Έτοιμα γεύματα με ρύζι· Πιάτα ξηράς ψύξης με κύριο συστατικό το ρύζι· Πιάτα ξηράς ψύξης με κύριο συστατικό τα ζυμαρικά· Πιάτα (γεύματα) με βάση το ρύζι· Πίτες από λαχανικά και κρέας· Ζυμαρικά από λαχανικά και ψάρια· Κατεψυγμένες πίτες γεμιστές με λαχανικά· Κατεψυγμένη ζύμη με γέμιση κρέατος· Αλμυρά πιτοειδή· Σβώλοι βρώμης που περιέχουν αποξηραμένα φρούτα· Ramen [γιαπωνέζικα πιάτα με βάση τις νούγιες]· Ραβιόλια· Ραβιόλια (έτοιμα)· Ντάμπλινγκ με γαρίδες· Συσκευασμένα γεύματα αποτελούμενα από ρύζι, με προσθήκη κρέατος, ψαριού ή λαχανικών· Έτοιμα γεύματα με βάση νούγιες· Έτοιμα γεύματα με βάση τα ζυμαρικά· Έτοιμα γεύματα με βάση το ρύζι· Ριζότο· Γλυκό ρύζι με ξηρούς καρπούς και τζίτζιφα [yaksik], κορεατική ζαχαροπλαστική· Κολλώδες ρύζι τυλιγμένο σε φύλλα μπαμπού (Zongzi)· Έτοιμο ρύζι τυλιγμένο σε φύκια· Ψημένα τοστ με τυρί και ζαμπόν· Ψημένο τοστ με τυρί· Σάντουιτς με σαλάτες· Σάντουιτς με κοτόπουλο· Ψημένα τοστ· Χοτ ντογκ και κέτσαπ σε ανοιχτά μακρόστενα ψωμάκια· Κράκερ ρυζιού [σενμπέι]· Κινέζικα ντάμπλινγκ ατμού (shumai), μαγειρεμένα· Γαριδάκια τυριού (σνακ)· Σπαγγέτι με σάλτσα ντομάτας σε κονσέρβα· Σπαγγέτι και κεφτέδες· Πιτάκια με κοτόπουλο· Πίτες λαχανικών· Πίτες που περιέχουν κρέας· Πίτες με πουλερικά· Πίτες που περιέχουν λαχανικά· Πίτες που περιέχουν κρέας από κυνήγι· Πίτες που περιέχουν ψάρι· Σκεπαστές πίτες· Νωπές πίτες· Πίτες (γλυκές ή αλμυρές)· Κρεατόπιτες (έτοιμες)· Γουόν τον· Τυλιχτά σάντουιτς· Τυλιχτές πίτες με κοτόπουλο.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Sugars, natural sweeteners, sweet coatings and fillings, bee products; Ice, ice creams, frozen yogurts and sorbets; Processed grains, starches, and goods made thereof, baking preparations and yeasts; Baozi [stuffed buns]; Pizza bases; Banana fritters; Pineapple fritters; Bibimbap [rice mixed with vegetables and beef]; Rice biscuits; Prepared savory foodstuffs made from potato flour; Prepared foodstuffs in the form of sauces; Filled baguettes; Crackers flavoured with herbs; Crackers flavoured with spices; Crackers flavoured with meat; Crackers flavoured with vegetables; Crackers filled with cheese; Crackers flavoured with cheese; Crackers made of prepared cereals; Pellet-shaped rice crackers (arare); Onion biscuits; Rice glue balls; Puffed cheese balls [corn snacks]; Rice dumplings; Rice dumplings dressed with sweet bean jam (ankoro); Pretzels; Soft pretzels; Brioches; Tortilla chips; Crisps made of cereals; Wholewheat crisps; Chow mein; Chow mein [noodle-based dishes]; Rice crackers; Rice crusts; Crumble; Crepes; Pancakes; Green onion pancake [pajeon]; Pre-packaged lunches consisting primarily of rice, and also including meat, fish or vegetables; Snack food products made from rusk flour; Snack food products made from cereal flour; Snack food products made from maize flour; Snack food products made from potato flour; Snack food products made from rice flour; Snack food products made from soya flour; Tortilla snacks; Snack foods prepared from maize; Snack foods made from corn and in the form of puffs; Snack foods made from corn and in the form of rings; Multigrain-based snack foods; Rice-based snack food; Stir fried rice cake [topokki]; Savoury pancakes; Gimbap [Korean rice dish]; Corn kernels being toasted; Caramel coated popcorn with candied nuts; Chinese stuffed dumplings (gyoza, cooked); Millet cakes; Rice cakes; Chocolate-coated rice cakes; Sticky rice cakes (Chapsalttock); Korean traditional rice cake [injeolmi]; Buckwheat jelly (Memilmuk); Filled bread rolls; French toast; Glutinous pounded rice cake coated with bean powder (injeolmi); Flaky pastry containing ham; Frozen pastry stuffed with meat and vegetables; Pasta containing stuffings; Canned pasta foods; Pre-baked pizzas crusts; Pastries consisting of vegetables and poultry; Egg rolls; Pork pies; Meat pies; Pasta dishes; Dry and liquid ready-to-serve meals, mainly consisting of rice; Prepared rice dishes; Freeze-dried dishes with the main ingredient being rice; Freeze-dried dishes with the main ingredient being pasta; Rice based dishes; Pastries consisting of vegetables and meat; Pastries consisting of vegetables and fish; Frozen pastry stuffed with vegetables; Frozen pastry stuffed with meat; Savory pastries; Oat clusters containing dried fruit; Ramen [Japanese noodle-based dish]; Ravioli; Ravioli [prepared]; Shrimp dumplings; Boxed lunches consisting of rice, with added meat, fish or vegetables; Noodle-based prepared meals; Pasta-based prepared meals; Rice-based prepared meals; Risotto; Sweet rice with nuts and jujubes (yaksik); Glutinous rice wrapped in bamboo leaves (Zongzi); Prepared rice rolled in seaweed; Toasted cheese sandwich with ham; Toasted cheese sandwich; Sandwiches containing salad; Sandwiches containing chicken; Toasted sandwiches; Hot sausage and ketchup in cut open bread rolls; Senbei [rice crackers]; Chinese steamed dumplings (shumai, cooked); Cheese curls [snacks]; Canned spaghetti in tomato sauce; Spaghetti and meatballs; Chicken pies; Vegetable pies; Pies containing meat; Pies containing poultry; Pies containing vegetables; Pies containing game; Pies containing fish; Pot pies; Fresh pies; Pies [sweet or savoury]; Meat pies [prepared]; Wontons; Wraps [sandwich]; Chicken wraps.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Azúcar, edulcorantes naturales, productos dulces de cobertura y relleno y productos de apicultura; Hielo, helados, yogures helados y sorbetes; Granos preparados, almidones y productos fabricados con los mismos, productos para panadería y levaduras; Baozi [bollos rellenos]; Bases para pizzas; Buñuelos de plátano; Buñuelos de piña; Bibimbap [arroz mezclado con ternera y verduras]; Galletas de arroz; Alimentos salados preparados hechos de harina de patata; Alimentos preparados en forma de salsas; Baguettes rellenas; Galletas saladas con sabor a hierbas; Galletas saladas con sabor a especias; Galletas saladas con sabor a carne; Galletas saladas con sabor a verduras; Galletas saladas rellenas con queso; Galletas saladas con sabor a queso; Galletas saladas de cereales preparados; Galletas de arroz con forma de gránulos (arare); Galletas de cebolla; Bolas de arroz glutinoso; Bolitas de queso inflado [aperitivos de maíz]; Bolitas de arroz [dumplings]; Buñuelos de arroz recubiertos con mermelada de alubias dulces (ankoro); Pretzels (galletas saladas); Galletas saladas blandas [pretzel]; Brioches; Chips de tortilla; Aperitivos crujientes hechos de cereales; Patatas fritas de trigo integral; Chow mein [tallarines chinos salteados]; Chow mein [platos a base de fideos]; Galletas saladas de arroz; Cortezas de arroz; Crumble (postre de fruta cubierto de una mezcla de harina, mantequilla y azúcar); Crepes; Creps [filloas]; Tortitas de cebolleta [pajeon]; Comidas preparadas que consisten principalmente en arroz y también con carne, pescado o verduras; Productos de aperitivo hechos de harina de galleta; Productos alimenticios para aperitivos hechos de harina de cereales; Productos de aperitivo hechos de harina de maíz; Productos de aperitivo hechos de harina de patata; Productos de aperitivo hechos con harina de arroz; Productos de aperitivo hechos con harina de soja; Aperitivos de tortilla de harina; Aperitivos preparados a base de maíz; Aperitivos hechos de maíz en forma hinchada; Aperitivos hechos de maíz y en forma de anillos; Tentempiés multigranos; Refrigerios a base de arroz; Galletas de arroz para saltear [topokki]; Tortitas saladas; Gimbap [plato coreano a base de arroz]; Granos de maíz tostados; Palomitas recubiertas de caramelo con nueces azucaradas; Empanadillas de masa rellenas chinas (gyoza, cocinadas); Pasteles de mijo; Pastelitos de arroz; Tortitas de arroz cubiertas de chocolate; Pasteles de arroz, de textura pegajosa (Chapsalttock); Pasteles de arroz tradicionales coreanos [injeolmi]; Jalea de alforfón (Memilmuk); Bocadillos rellenos; Tostadas francesas; Pastel de arroz glutinoso molido rebozado en alubias en polvo [injeolmi]; Masa de hojaldre con jamón; Empanadas de hojaldre congeladas rellenas de carne y verduras; Pasta con relleno; Alimentos enlatados a base de pasta; Masas de pizza precocidas; Empanadillas de verduras y carne de aves; Rollitos de huevo; Empanadas de cerdo; Pasteles de carne [empanadas de carne]; Platos de pasta; Platos preparados secos y no secos, compuestos esencialmente de arroz; Platos de arroz preparados; Platos liofilizados cuyo ingrediente principal es el arroz; Platos liofilizados cuyo ingrediente principal son las pastas alimenticias; Platos a base de arroz; Empanadillas de verduras y carne; Empanadillas de verduras y pescado; Empanadas de hojaldre congeladas rellenas de verduras; Empanadas de hojaldre congeladas rellenas de carne; Pasteles salados; Aglomerados de avena que contienen fruta seca; Ramen [plato japonés a base de fideos]; Raviolis; Ravioli [preparados]; Buñuelos de camarón; Comidas envasadas a base de arroz, con carne, pescado o verduras; Comidas preparadas a base de fideos; Comidas preparadas a base de pastas; Comidas preparadas a base de arroz; Risotto; Arroz dulce con nueces y yuyubas [yaksik]; Arroz glutinoso envuelto en hojas de bambú (Zongzi); Arroz preparado enrollado en alga marina; Sándwich de queso tostado con jamón; Sándwich de queso tostado; Bocadillos que contienen ensalada; Sándwiches de pollo; Sándwiches tostados; Salchicha caliente y ketchup en panecillos abiertos; Senbei [galletas de arroz]; Bolas de masa al vapor chinas [shumai, cocidas]; Rizos con sabor a queso [aperitivos]; Espaguetis con salsa de tomate en lata; Espaguetis y albóndigas; Pasteles de pollo; Empanadas de verduras; Empanadas que contienen carne; Empanadas que contienen aves de corral; Empanadas que contienen verduras; Empanadas que contienen carne de caza; Empanadas que contienen pescado; Empanadas rellenas; Empanadas frescas; Empanadas [dulces o saladas]; Empanadas de carne [preparadas]; Wontons; Wrap [rollos de sándwich]; Rollos de pollo [wraps].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Suhkrud, looduslikud magusained, magusad katted ja täidised, meetooted; Jäätis, piima- ja koorejäätised, külmutatud jogurtid ja sorbetid; Töödeldud teraviljad, tärklis ning nendest valmistatud kaubad, küpsetuspulbrid ja pärm; Baozi [täidisega kuklid]; Pitsapõhjad; Banaanisõõrikud; Friteeritud ananass; Bibimbap [köögiviljade ja veiselihaga segatud riis]; Riisiküpsised; Kartulijahust valmistatud soolased või vürtsikad valmistoiduained; Valmistoiduained [kastmed]; Pikad täidisega Prantsuse saiad [baguette'id]; Ürdimaitselised kreekerid; Vürtsidega maitsestatud kreekerid; Lihamaitselised kreekerid; Köögiviljamaitselised kreekerid; Juustutäidisega kreekerid; Juustumaitselised kreekerid; Töödeldud teraviljast valmistatud kreekerid; Kuulikesekujulised riisiküpsised (Arare); Sibulaküpsised; Tangyuanid [Hiina riisipallid]; Pais-juustupallid [maisisuupisted]; Riisiklimbid; Magusa oakeedisega kaetud riisiklimbid (ankoro); Krõbedad soolakringlid; Pehmed soolakringlikesed; Brioche'd [Prantsuse nupsusaiad]; Tortilla krõpsud; Teraviljakrõpsud; Täisterakrõpsud; Hiinapärased wok-nuudlid [chow mein]; Chow mein [nuudliroad]; Riisikuivikud; Riisikoorikud; Krõbeda kattega ahjumagustoidud [Crumble]; Krepid [õhukesed ülepanni pannkoogid]; Pannkoogid; Rohelise sibula pannkook [pajeon]; Peamiselt riisist koosnevad ja lisaks liha, kala või aedvilju sisaldavad pakitud lõunasöögid; Kuivikujahust suupistetooted; Teraviljajahust valmistatud suupisted; Maisijahust suupistetooted; Kartulijahust valmistatud suupisted; Riisijahust suupistetooted; Sojajahust valmistatud suupisted; Tortilla-suupisted; Maisist suupisted; Paisutatud maisisuupisted; Rõngakujulised maisisuupisted; Eri teraviljade põhised suupistetoidud; Riisist valmistatud suupisted; Vokitud riisikook [topokki]; Soolased pannkoogid; Gimbap [Korea riisitoit]; Maisitõlvikud (röstitud); Karamelliga kaetud popkorn suhkurdatud pähklitega; Hiina täidetud klimbid (gyoza, keedetud); Hirsikoogid; Riisikoogid; Šokolaadikattega riisikoogid; Kleepuvad riisikoogid (Chapsalttock); Korea traditsiooniline riisikook [injeolmi]; Tatrapüreetarrend (memilmuk); Täidetud prantssaiad; Prantsusepärane röstsai; Oapulbriga kaetud kleepuv tambitud riisikook [injeolmi]; Lehttaina-singipirukad; Liha- ja köögiviljatäidisega külmutatud kondiitritooted; Täidetud makarontooted; Konserveeritud makaronitoidud; Eelküpsetatud pitsapõhjad; Köögivilju ja linnuliha sisaldavad kondiitritooted; Aasiapärased munarullid; Sealihapirukad; Lihapirukad; Makaronitoidud; Peamiselt riisist valmistatud kuivad ja vedelad valmistoidud; Riisist valmistoidud; Peamiselt riisist valmistatud külmkuivatatud toidud; Peamiselt makarontoodetest valmistatud külmkuivatatud toidud; Riisitoidud; Köögivilju ja liha sisaldavad pagaritooted; Köögivilju ja kala sisaldavad kondiitritooted; Köögiviljatäidisega külmutatud kondiitritooted; Lihatäidisega külmutatud kondiitritooted; Soolased kondiitritooted; Kuivatatud puuvilja sisaldavad kaerapätsikesed; Ramen [Jaapani nuudlitoit]; Ravioolid; Valmisravioolid; Krevetiklimbid; Liha-, kala- või aedviljalisandiga riisist koosnevad karbieined; Nuudlitel põhinevad valmistoidud; Makarontoodete põhised valmistoidud; Riisipõhised valmistoidud; Risotod; Magus riis pähklite ja jujuubidega [yaksik]; Zongzi [bambuselehtedesse keeratud kleepuv riis]; Merivetikasse keeratud küpseriis; Röstitud singi-juustuvõileivad; Röstitud juustuvõileivad; Salatit sisaldavad võileivad; Kanaliha sisaldavad võileivad; Röstitud võileivad; Lahtilõigatud kuklid kuuma vorstikese ja ketšupiga; Senbei [riisiküpsised]; Hiina aurutatud klimbid (keedetud, küpsetatud või praetud) [shumai]; Juustumaitselised maisipulgad [suupisted]; Konservitud spagetid tomatikastmes; Spagetid ja lihapallid; Kanapirukad; Aedviljapirukad; Liha sisaldavad pirukad; Linnulihapirukad; Aedvilju sisaldavad pirukad; Ulukilihapirukad; Kalapirukad; Potipirukad; Värsked pirukad; Pirukad [magusad või soolased]; Lihapirukad [tarbimiseks valmis]; Wontonid [Hiina pelmeenid]; Vrapid [võileivad]; Kanavrapid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sokerit, luontaiset makeutusaineet, makeat päällysteet ja täytteet, mehiläistuotteet; Jää, jäätelöt, jäädytetyt jugurtit ja sorbetit; Jalostetut viljat, tärkkelykset ja niistä tehdyt tuotteet, leivontavalmisteet ja hiivat; Höyrytetyt täytetyt baozi-pullat; Pitsapohjat; Taikinoidut, uppopaistetut banaanit; Taikinoidut, uppopaistetut ananaspalat; Bibimbap [riisi, johon on sekoitettu vihanneksia ja naudanlihaa]; Riisikeksit; Perunajauhosta tehdyt valmiit suolaiset elintarvikkeet; Valmiit elintarvikkeet kastikkeiden muodossa; Täytetyt patongit; Yrtinmakuiset voileipäkeksit; Maustetut voileipäkeksit; Lihanmakuiset voileipäkeksit; Kasvistenmakuiset voileipäkeksit; Juustotäytteiset voileipäkeksit; Juustolla maustetut voileipäkeksit; Jalostetuista viljoista tehdyt voileipäkeksit; Pallonmuotoiset riisikeksit (araret); Sipulikeksit; Liimamaiset riisipallot; Kuohkeat juustopallot [maissinaksut]; Riisimykyt; Makealla papuhillolla kuorrutetut riisimykyt (ankorot); Suolarinkilät; Pehmeät suolarinkelit; Briossit; Tortillalastut; Viljasta valmistetut lastut; Kokojyvävehnämurot; Chow mein -nuudeliateriat; Chow mein [nuudelipohjaiset ateriat]; Riisistä valmistetut voileipäkeksit; Riisistä tehdyt kuoret; Piirakka (Murotaikina); Ohukaiset; Pannukakut; Vihersipulipannukakut (pajeon); Pääasiassa riisistä koostuvat mutta myös lihaa, kalaa tai vihanneksia sisältävät esipakatut lounaat; Korppujauhosta valmistetut välipalatuotteet; Viljajauhosta valmistetut välipalatuotteet; Maissijauhoista valmistetut välipalatuotteet; Perunajauhosta tehdyt välipalat; Riisijauhosta tehdyt välipalatuotteet; Soijajauhosta tehdyt välipalatuotteet; Tortillavälipalat; Maissista tehdyt välipalat; Maissista valmistetut välipalaruoat kohokkaina; Maissista valmistetut välipalaruoat rinkilöinä; Moniviljapohjaiset välipalat; Pikaruoka, riisipohjainen; Uppopaistetut riisikakut [topokki]; Suolaiset pannukakut; Gimbap [korealainen riisipohjainen ruokalaji]; Paahdetut maissinjyvät; Karamellikuorrutteinen popcorn karamellisoitujen pähkinöiden kera; Kiinalaiset täytetyt mykyt (gyozat, kypsennetyt); Hirssikakut; Riisikakut; Suklaapäällysteiset riisikakut; Tahmeat riisikakut (chapsalttock); Injeolmi, perinteinen korealainen riisikakku; Tattarihyytelö (memilmuk); Voileivät, täytetyt; Köyhät ritarit; Tahmea, papujauheella päällystetty murskattu riisikakku [injeolmi]; Kuivat kinkkupasteijat; Liha- ja kasvistäytteiset pakastetut leivonnaiset; Pasta, täytetty; Purkitetut pastaruoat; Esipaistetut pitsapohjat; Kasviksia ja siipikarjanlihaa sisältävät leipomotuotteet; Munakääryleet (egg roll); Sianlihapiirakat; Lihapiirakat; Pasta-ateriat; Kuivat ja nestemäiset valmisruuat koostuen pääosin riisistä; Valmiit riisiateriat; Pakastekuivatut ateriat, joiden pääainesosa on riisi; Pakastekuivatut ateriat, joiden pääainesosa on pasta; Riisipohjaiset ateriat; Kasviksia ja lihaa sisältävät leipomotuotteet; Kasviksia ja kalaa sisältävät leipomotuotteet; Vihannestäytteiset pakasteleivonnaiset; Pakastetut leivonnaiset lihatäytteellä; Suolaiset leivonnaiset; Kuivattuja hedelmiä sisältävät kaurapallot; Ramen [japanilainen nuudelipohjainen ruokalaji]; Ravioli; Ravioli [valmistettu]; Katkarapumykyt; Pakatut lounaat, jotka koostuvat riisistä ja joihin on lisätty lihaa, kalaa tai vihanneksia; Nuudelipohjaiset valmisateriat; Pastapohjaiset valmisateriat; Riisipohjaiset valmisateriat; Risotto; Makea riisiruoka, jossa on pähkinöitä ja jujube-taateleita [yaksik]; Tahmeat bambunlehtiin käärityt kiinalaiset riisikakut (zongzi); Valmis riisi merilevän täytteenä; Kinkkua sisältävät paahdetut juustovoileivät; Paahdetut juustoleivät; Salaattia sisältävät voileivät; Kanaa sisältävät voileivät; Paahdetut voileivät; Kuumat nakkisämpylät ketsupin kanssa; Riisikeksit [senbeit]; Kiinalaiset höyrytetyt mykyt (shumait, kypsennetyt); Juustonaksut [välipalat]; Spagetti tomaattikastikkeessa säilykkeenä; Spagetti ja lihapyörykät; Kanapiirakat; Kasvispiiraat; Lihaa sisältävät piirakat; Siipikarjaa sisältävät piiraat; Vihanneksia sisältävät piirakat; Riistaa sisältävät piiraat; Kalaa sisältävät piiraat; Täytetyt piiraat; Tuorepiiraat; Piirakat [makeat tai suolaiset]; Lihapiirakat [valmiit]; Täytetyt mykyt (Wonton); Wrapit [kääritty leipä]; Kanawrapit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Sucres, édulcorants naturels, enrobages et fourrages sucrés, produits apicoles; Glace, crèmes glacées, yaourts glacés et sorbets; Grains transformés, amidons et dérivés, préparations pour boulangerie et levures; Baozi [petits pains farcis]; Bases pour pizzas; Beignets aux bananes; Beignets à l'ananas; Bibimbap [riz mélangé à du bœuf et des légumes]; Biscuits de riz; Aliments salés préparés à base de farine de pommes de terre; Aliments préparés sous forme de sauces; Baguettes fourrées; Biscuits salés [crackers] aromatisés aux herbes; Biscuits salés [crackers] aromatisés aux épices; Biscuits salés [crackers] aromatisés à la viande; Biscuits salés [crackers] aux arômes de légumes; Biscuits salés [crackers] fourrés au fromage; Biscuits salés [crackers] goût fromage; Biscuits salés [crackers] à base de céréales préparées; Biscuits à apéritif au riz sous forme de granulés [arare]; Biscuits à l'oignon; Boules de riz gluant; Boules soufflées au fromage [en-cas au maïs]; Boulettes de riz; Boulettes de riz enrobées de pâte de haricots sucrée [ankoro]; Bretzels; Bretzels mous; Brioches [pâtisserie]; Chips tortillas; Chips à base de céréales; Chips à base de farine de blé complet; Chow mein [nouilles chinoises sautées]; Chow mein [plats à base de nouilles]; Crackers au riz; Croûtes de riz; Crumble; Crêpes; Crêpes [alimentation]; Crêpes épaisses [pancakes] aux oignons verts [pajeon]; Déjeuners préemballés composés principalement de riz et incluant également de la viande, du poisson ou des légumes; En-cas à base de farine de biscotte; En-cas à base de farine de céréales; En-cas à base de farine de maïs; En-cas à base de farine de pommes de terre; En-cas à base de farine de riz; En-cas à base de farine de soja; En-cas à base de galette tortilla; En-cas à base de maïs; En-cas à base de maïs soufflé; En-cas à base de maïs sous forme d'anneaux; En-cas à base de plusieurs graines; En-cas à base de riz; Galettes de riz sautées [topokki]; Galettes salées; Gimbap [plat coréen à base de riz]; Grains de maïs grillés; Grains de maïs soufflés [pop-corn] enrobés de caramel avec des fruits à coque pralinés; Gyoza cuits [raviolis chinois farcis]; Gâteaux de millet; Gâteaux de riz; Gâteaux de riz enrobés au chocolat; Gâteaux de riz gluant (Chapsalttock); Gâteaux de riz traditionnels coréens [injeolmi]; Gélatine de sarrasin (Memilmuk); Pain fourré; Pain perdu; Pâte de riz gluante sous forme de boulette recouverte de poudre de haricot [injeolmi]; Pâte feuilletée au jambon; Pâte surgelée fourrée à la viande et aux légumes; Pâtes alimentaires farcies; Pâtes cuisinées en conserve; Pâtes à pizza précuites; Pâtisserie à base de légumes et de volaille; Pâté impérial; Pâtés de porc en croûte; Pâtés à la viande; Plats de pâtes; Plats cuisinés déshydratés ou liquides, essentiellement à base de riz; Plats de riz préparés; Plats lyophilisés dont le riz est l'ingrédient principal; Plats lyophilisés dont les pâtes alimentaires sont l'ingrédient principal; Plats à base de riz; Pâtisserie comprenant des légumes et de la viande; Pâtisserie comprenant des légumes et du poisson; Pâtisserie surgelée farcie de légumes; Pâtisserie surgelée farcie de viande; Pâtisseries salées; Pépites d'avoine contenant des fruits secs; Ramen [plat japonais à base de nouilles]; Ravioli; Raviolis [préparés]; Raviolis aux crevettes; Repas en boîte composés de riz accompagné de viande, de poisson ou de légumes; Repas préparés à base de nouilles; Repas préparés à base de pâtes alimentaires; Repas préparés à base de riz; Risotto; Riz gluant aux noix et aux jujubes [yaksik]; Riz gluant emballé en papillotte dans des feuilles de bambou [Zongzi]; Riz préparé roulé dans une feuille d'algue; Sandwichs au fromage et au jambon grillés; Sandwichs au fromage grillés; Sandwichs contenant de la salade; Sandwichs contenant du poulet; Sandwichs grillés; Saucisse chaude et ketchup dans un petit pain coupé et ouvert; Senbei [crackers au riz]; Shumai [raviolis chinois cuits à la vapeur]; Snacks soufflés au fromage; Spaghettis en boîte à la sauce tomate; Spaghettis et boulettes de viande; Tourtes au poulet; Tourtes aux légumes; Tourtes contenant de la viande; Tourtes contenant de la volaille; Tourtes contenant des légumes; Tourtes contenant du gibier; Tourtes contenant du poisson; Tourtes en pâte feuilletée [pot pies]; Tourtes fraîches; Tourtes sucrées ou salées; Tourtes à la viande [cuisinées]; Wontons [raviolis chinois]; Wrap [sandwich roulé]; Wraps de poulet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Šećeri, prirodni zaslađivači, slatke glazure i punjenja, pčelinji proizvodi; Led, sladoledi, zamrznuti jogurti i sorbeti; Prerađene žitarice, škrobovi i njihovi proizvodi, pripravci za pečenje i kvasci; Baozi [punjena peciva]; Podloge za pizzu; Uštipci s bananom; Uštipci s ananasom; Bibimbap [riža s povrćem i govedinom]; Keksi od riže; Gotova slana hrana napravljena od krumpirovog brašna; Gotova hrana - u obliku umaka; Punjeni francuski kruh; Krekeri s okusom začinskih trava; Krekeri s okusom začina; Krekeri s okusom mesa; Krekeri s okusom povrća; Krekeri punjeni sirom; Krekeri s okusom sira; Krekeri od pripremljenih žitarica; Arare [rižini krekeri u obliku kuglica]; Kolačići od luka; Rižine okruglice; Ekstrudirane kuglice s okusom sira [grickalice od kukuruza]; Rižine okruglice; Ankoro [rižine okruglice s preljevom od džema od slatkog graha]; Pereci; Mekani pereci; Brioši; Tortilla čips; Čips od žitarica; Integralni čips; Chow mein [vrsta kineskih prženih rezanaca]; Chow mein [jela na bazi rezanaca]; Krekeri od riže; Rižina kora; Crumble [britanski kolač od voća i žitarica]; Palačinke; Palačinke; Palačinke od mladog luka [pajeon]; Unaprijed zapakirani ručkovi od riže, koji mogu sadržavati meso, ribu ili povrće; Grickalice od mljevenog dvopeka; Grickalice od brašna žitarica; Grickalice od kukuruznog brašna; Grickalice od brašna krumpira; Grickalice od rižinog brašna; Grickalice od sojinog brašna; Tortilla grickalice; Grickalice pripremljene od kukuruza; Napuhane grickalice od kukuruza; Grickalice od kukuruza u obliku prstenja; Grickalice na bazi više žitarica; Grickalice od riže; Rižin kolač pržen u wok tavi [topokki]; Začinjene palačinke; Gimbap [korejsko jelo od riže]; Tostirana kukuruzna zrna; Kokice prekrivene karamelom s kandiranim oraščićima; Punjene kineske kuhane okruglice [Gyoza]; Kolači od prosa; Kolačići od riže; Kolačići od riže preliveni čokoladom; Kolači od ljepljive riže (Chapsalttock); Korejski tradicionalni rižin kolač [injeolmi]; Žele od heljde (Memilmuk); Punjene zemičke; Pohani kruh; Glutinozni rižini kolačići uvaljani u prah od graha [injeolmi]; Lisnato tijesto sa šunkom; Zamrznuto tijesto punjeno mesom i povrćem; Punjena tjestenina; Konzervirani proizvodi od tjestenine; Gotove kore za pizzu; Proizvodi od tijesta koji se sastoje od povrća i peradi; Rolice od jaja; Pite od svinjetine; Mesne pite; Jela od tjestenine; Suhi i tekući obroci spremni za posluživanje koji se uglavnom sastoje od riže; Gotova jela od riže; Jela sušena u smrznutom stanju s rižom kao glavnim sastojkom; Jela sušena u smrznutom stanju s tjesteninom kao glavnim sastojkom; Jela na bazi riže; Proizvodi od tijesta koji se sastoje od povrća i mesa; Proizvodi od tijesta koji se sastoje od povrća i ribe; Zamrznuto tijesto punjeno povrćem; Zamrznuto tijesto punjeno mesom; Slani pekarski proizvodi; Kuglice zobi sa sušenim voćem; Ramen [japansko jelo na bazi rezanaca]; Ravioli [tjestenina]; Ravioli [gotovi]; Okruglice od kozica; Gotovi ručci od riže, s dodanim mesom, ribom ili povrćem; Gotovi obroci na bazi rezanaca; Gotova jela s tjesteninom; Gotova jela s rižom; Rižoto; Slatka riža s orasima i žižulama [yaksik]; Ljepljiva riža umotana u lišće bambusa (Zongzi); Pripremljena riža omotana morskom travom; Tostirani sendvič sa sirom i šunkom; Tostirani sendvič sa sirom; Sendviči sa salatom; Sendviči s piletinom; Tostirani sendviči; Vruća hrenovka i kečap u razrezanom pecivu; Senbei [rižini krekeri]; Kineske okruglice kuhane na pari [Shumai]; Kukuruzni flips s aromom sira; Špageti u umaku od rajčice u konzervi; Špageti i mesne okruglice; Pite s piletinom; Pite od povrća; Pite koje sadrže meso; Pite koje sadrže perad; Pite koje sadrže povrće; Pite koje sadrže divljač; Pite koje sadrže ribu; Zatvorena pita od prhkog tijesta; Svježe pite; Pite [slatke ili slane]; Mesne pite [gotove]; Wonton [kineske okruglice]; Punjeni smotuljak od tijesta [vrsta sendviča]; Smotuljci od piletine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Cukor, természetes édesítőszerek, édes bevonatok és töltetek, méhészeti termékek; Jég, fagylalt, fagyasztott joghurtok és sörbetek; Feldolgozott gabonák, keményítő és az ezekből készült áruk, pékáruk és élesztők; Baozi [töltött gőzölt tészta]; Pizza alapok; Banánfánkok; Ananászfánkok; Bibimbap [zöldségfélékkel és marhahússal kevert rizs]; Puffasztott rizs szelet; Burgonyalisztből készült sós készételek; Elkészített élelmiszerek szósz formájában; Töltött bagettek; Fűszernövényekkel ízesített sós kekszek; Fűszerekkel ízesített sós kekszek; Hússal ízesített sós kekszek; Zöldségekkel ízesített sós kekszek; Sajttal töltött sós kekszek; Sajttal ízesített sós kekszek; Feldolgozott gabonafélékből készült sós kekszek; Golyócska formájú rizsropogósok (arare); Hagymás kekszek; Ragadós rizsgombócok; Puffasztott sajtgolyók [kukoricás rágcsálnivalók]; Rizsgombócok; Rizsgombócok édesbab öntettel [ankoro]; Perecek; Puha perec; Briósok; Tortilla chips; Gabonából készült ropogtatnivalók; Teljes kiőrlésű rágcsálnivalók; Chow mein [kínai pirított tésztás étel]; Chow mein [tésztaalapú étel]; Rizs rágcsálnivalók; Rizses tésztaalapok; Crumble [angol édesség, morzsasüti]; Crepe [francia palacsinta]; Palacsinták; Zöldhagymás palacsinta [pajeon]; Előre csomagolt ebéd, amely főként rizst, továbbá húst, halat vagy zöldségeket is tartalmaz; Kétszersült lisztből készült snack termékek; Gabonalisztből készült rágcsálnivalók; Kukoricalisztből készült snack termékek; Burgonyalisztből készült rágcsálnivaló termékek; Rizslisztből készült snack termékek; Szójalisztből készült rágcsálnivaló termékek; Tortilla rágcsálnivalók; Kukoricából készült snack termékek; Puffasztott kukoricából készült rágcsálnivalók; Kukoricából készült, gyűrű formájú rágcsálnivalók; Több gabonafélén alapuló rágcsálnivalók; Rizs alapú rágcsálnivalók; Wokban sült rizses tészta, sütemény [topokki]; Sós palacsinták; Gimbap [koreai rizsétel]; Pörkölt kukoricaszemek; Karamellel bevont pattogatott kukorica cukrozott diófélékkel; Kínai töltött gombócok [gyoza, főtt]; Kölesből készült sütemények; Rizssütemény; Csokoládéval bevont rizssütemények; Ragadós rizses sütemény (Chapsalttock); Hagyományos koreai rizses sütemény [injeolmi]; Hajdinazselé (Memilmuk); Töltött kenyértekercsek; Bundás kenyér; Darált babba forgatott ragadós rizspogácsa [injeolmi]; Sonkát tartalmazó leveles tészta; Hússal és zöldségekkel töltött fagyasztott sütemény; Töltött tészták; Tésztaételek konzervben; Elősütött pizzalapok; Zöldséget és baromfihúst tartalmazó sütemények; Tavaszi tekercsek; Disznóhúsos piték; Húsos piték; Tésztaételek; Főleg rizsből készült száraz és folyékony készételek; Rizses készételek; Fagyasztva szárított ételek, fő összetevőként rizzsel; Fagyasztva szárított ételek, fő összetevőként tésztával; Rizs alapú ételek; Zöldséget és húst tartalmazó sütemények; Zöldséget és halat tartalmazó sütemények; Zöldségekkel töltött fagyasztott sütemény; Fagyasztott, hússal töltött sütemény/tészta; Sós sütemények; Szárított gyümölcsöt tartalmazó zabfalatok; Ramen [japán tésztaalapú étel]; Ravioli; Félkész ravioli; Rákgombócok; Dobozolt ételek, amelyek rizsből, valamint húsból, halból vagy zöldségből állnak; Metélttészta-alapú készételek; Tésztaalapú előkészített ételek; Rizsalapú előkészített ételek; Rizottók; Édes rizs diófélékkel és jujubával [yaksik]; Bambuszlevelekbe göngyölt ragacsos rizs (Zongzi); Tengeri algába csavart, előkészített rizs; Pirított sajtos szendvics sonkával, sajtos melegszendvics sonkával; Pirított sajtos szendvics, sajtos melegszendvics; Salátát tartalmazó szendvicsek; Csirkét tartalmazó szendvicsek; Melegszendvicsek; Csípős kolbász és ketchup félbevágott kifliben; Rizskeksz [senbei]; Kínai gőzölt gombócok [shumai, főtt]; Sajtos extrudált kukoricapelyhek; Konzerv spagetti paradicsommártásban; Spagetti húsgombóccal; Csirkés pite; Zöldséges piték; Húst tartalmazó lepények; Baromfit tartalmazó piték; Zöldségeket tartalmazó lepények, piték; Vadhúst tartalmazó lepények, piték; Halas lepények; Pot pie [Töltött sós pite]; Friss lepények, piték; Gyümölcsös sütemények/torták [édes vagy ízesített]; Húsos piték [elkészített]; Wontonok; Göngyölt szendvicsek; Csirketekercsek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Zucchero, dolcificanti naturali, glasse e ripieni dolci, prodotti delle api; Ghiaccio, gelati, yogurt gelati e sorbetti; Cereali lavorati, amidi e prodotti da essi derivati, preparati da forno e lieviti; Baozi [panini farciti]; Basi per pizza; Frittelle alle banane; Frittelle di ananas; Bibimbap [riso con verdure e manzo]; Biscotti di riso; Alimenti pronti salati a base di farina di patate; Alimenti pronti sotto forma di salse; Baguette ripiene; Crackers aromatizzati alle erbe; Crackers aromatizzati alle spezie; Crackers aromatizzati alla carne; Crackers aromatizzati alle verdure; Cracker ripieni di formaggio; Cracker aromatizzati al formaggio; Crackers a base di cereali pronti; Cracker di riso in grani (arare); Biscotti alla cipolla; Polpette di farina di riso glutinoso; Palline soffiate al formaggio [spuntini a base di mais]; Budini di riso; Gnocchi di riso conditi con marmellata di fagioli dolci (ankoro); Ciambelline croccanti salate; Brezel morbidi; Brioche; Chips al mais; Sfogliatine a base di cereali; Patatine integrali; Chow mein; Chow mein [piatti a base di tagliolini]; Cracker al riso; Gallette di riso; Dolce con pasta sbriciolata; Crespelle; Crêpes; Pancake di cipollotto [pajeon]; Pranzi in scatola composti essenzialmente di riso, ma che contengono anche carne, pesce o verdure; Prodotti alimentari per snack a base di farina di pane biscottato; Snack a base di farina di cereali; Prodotti alimentari per spuntini a base di farina di mais; Snack a base di farina di patate; Snack a base di farina di riso; Snack a base di farina di soia; Snack a base di tortillas; Spuntini a base di mais; Spuntini a base di mais soffiato; Snack a base di mais e in forma di anelli; Spuntini a base di più cereali; Snack a base di riso; Torta di riso saltata in padella [topokki]; Crêpes salate; Gimbap [piatto di riso coreano]; Chicchi di mais tostati; Popcorn ricoperti di caramello con noci candite; Ravioli cinesi ripieni (gyoza, cotti); Tortine di miglio; Torte di riso; Torte di riso ricoperte di cioccolato; Dolci di riso appiccicosi (Chapsalttock); Torta di riso coreana tradizionale [injeolmi]; Farina di fagopiro (Menilmuk); Panini imbottiti; Toast alla francese; Torta di riso glutinoso avvolta in polvere di fagioli [injeolmi]; Pasta sfoglia contenente prosciutto; Paste congelate ripiene di carne e verdure; Paste alimentari ripiene; Prodotti in scatola a base di pasta; Basi precotte al forno per pizza; Paste contenenti ortaggi e pollame; Involtini primavera; Pasticci di maiale; Pasticcio di carne; Piatti a base di pasta; Piatti pronti, secchi e non, costituiti principalmente da riso; Piatti di riso pronti; Piatti liofilizzati con riso come ingrediente principale; Piatti liofilizzati con pasta come ingrediente principale; Piatti a base di riso; Paste contenenti ortaggi e carne; Paste ripiene con ortaggi e pesce; Paste congelate ripiene di verdure; Paste surgelate ripiene di carne; Pasticceria salata; Agglomerati d'avena contenenti frutta secca; Ramen [piatto giapponese a base di noodles]; Ravioli; Ravioli [pronti]; Gnocchi di gamberetti; Pranzi in scatola composti di riso con carne, pesce o verdure; Pasti preparati a base di noodle; Pasti preparati a base di pasta; Pasti preparati a base di riso; Risotto; Riso dolce con noci e giuggiole [yaksik]; Riso glutinoso avvolto in foglie di bambù [Zongzi]; Riso pronto avvolto in alghe marine; Panini imbottiti con formaggio e prosciutto tostati; Panini imbottiti al formaggio tostati; Panini contenenti insalata; Panini imbottiti contenenti pollo; Panini imbottiti tostati; Salsicce calde e ketchup contenute in un panino; Senbei [crackers di riso]; Ravioli cinesi cotti al vapore (Shumai); Riccoli al formaggio [snack]; Spaghetti in salsa di pomodoro in scatola; Spaghetti e polpette; Torte di pollo; Tortini di verdura; Pasticci contenenti carne; Pasticci contenenti pollame; Pasticci contenenti ortaggi; Pasticci contenenti selvaggina; Pasticci contenenti pesce; Pasticci pronti da cuocere; Torte fresche; Pasticcio [dolce o salato]; Pasticci di carne [pronti]; Wonton; Involtini [panini imbottiti]; Involtini di pollo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Cukrus, natūralios saldinamosios medžiagos, saldūs aptepai ir įdarai, bičių produktai; Ledas, ledai, šaldytas jogurtas ir šerbetas; Apdoroti grūdai, krakmolas ir jų gaminiai, preparatai kepimo reikmėms ir mielės; Bandelės su įdaru [baozi]; Picų papločiai; Bananai, gruzdinti tešloje; Tešloje gruzdinti ananasai; Ryžiai su daržovėmis ir jautiena [bibimbap]; Ryžių sausainiai; Paruošti sūrūs maisto produktai iš bulvių miltų; Paruošti maisto produktai (padažai); Įdaryti prancūziški batonai; Žolelėmis pagardinti krekeriai; Prieskoniais pagardinti krekeriai; Mėsa pagardinti krekeriai; Daržovėmis pagardinti krekeriai; Sūriu įdaryti krekeriai; Sūrio skonio krekeriai; Krekeriai iš paruoštų grūdų; Rutuliukų formos ryžių traškučiai [arare]; Svogūnų sausainiai; Ryžių klijų rutuliukai; Pūsti sūrio kamuoliukai [kukurūzų užkandžiai]; Ryžių koldūnai; Ryžių virtinukai užpilti saldžia pupelių uogiene [ankoro]; Druska apibarstyti riestainiukai; Minkšti bavariškieji riestainiai; Saldžios bandelės; Tortilijos traškučiai; Javainiai; Viso grūdo kviečių traškučiai; Keptų makaronų mišinys (chow mein); Chow mein [patiekalai makaronų pagrindu]; Ryžių krekeriai; Traškūs ryžiai; Trupininiai apkepai; Lietiniai; Blynai; Žaliųjų svogūnų blynai [pajeon]; Įpakuoti pietų patiekalai, kurių pagrindas ryžiai, ir juose taip pat gali būti mėsos, žuvies ar daržovių; Užkandiniai gaminiai iš maltų džiūvėsėlių; Užkandiniai gaminiai iš grūdų miltų; Užkandiniai gaminiai iš kukurūzų miltų; Užkandiniai gaminiai iš bulvių miltų; Užkandiniai gaminiai iš ryžių miltų; Užkandiniai gaminiai iš sojų miltų; Tortilijos užkandžiai; Užkandžiai iš kukurūzų; Užkandžiai iš išpūstų javų grūdų; Užkandžiai iš kukurūzų [žiedo formos]; Įvairių grūdų užkandžiai; Ryžių užkandžiai; Kepintų ryžių (pamaišant) pyragas [topokki]; Pikantiški blynai; Korėjietiškas ryžių patiekalas [gimbap]; Skrudinti kukurūzų branduoliai; Karamele glaistyti kukurūzų spragėsiai su pasaldintais riešutais; Kiniški virti įdaryti koldūnai (gyoza); Sorų papločiai; Ryžių kepiniai; Šokoladu aplieti ryžių kepiniai; Lipnūs ryžių pyragai (Chapsalttock); Tradicinis korėjiečių ryžių pyragas [injeolmi]; Grikių želatina (Memilmuk); Įdarytos bandelės; Prancūziški skrebučiai; Lipniųjų trintų ryžių gaminys, padengtas pupelių milteliais [injeolmi]; Sluoksniuotos tešlos pyragaičiai su kumpiu; Šaldyti pyragaičiai įdaryti mėsos ir daržovių įdaru; Makaronai su įdarais; Konservuoti makaronų tešlos gaminiai (skardinėse); Picų papločių pusgaminis; Kepiniai su paukštiena ir daržovėmis; Blynų vyniotiniai su daržovių ir mėsos įdaru; Pyragai su kiaulienos įdaru; Pyragai su mėsos įdaru; Makaronų patiekalai; Paruošti ryžių patiekalai (sauso ir skysto pavidalo); Paruošti ryžių patiekalai; Šalčiu džiovinti ryžių patiekalai; Šalčiu džiovinti makaronų patiekalai; Ryžių patiekalai; Mėsos ir daržovių kepiniai; Daržovių ir žuvies kepiniai; Šaldyti pyragaičiai, įdaryti daržovėmis; Šaldyti pyragaičiai, įdaryti mėsa; Sūrūs kepiniai; Avižų dribsnių gabalėliai su džiovintais vaisiais; Ramenai; Mėsėčiai [koldūnai]; Ravioliai [paruošti]; Krevečių virtiniai [koldūnai]; Dėžutėmis supakuoti pietūs iš ryžių su mėsa, žuvimi arba daržovėmis; Paruošti lakštinių patiekalai; Paruošti patiekalai makaronų pagrindu; Paruošti patiekalai ryžių pagrindu; Daugiaryžis (rizotas); Lipnieji ryžiai su riešutais ir zizifais [yaksik]; Į bambukų lapus įvynioti lipnūs ryžiai (Zongzi); Paruošti į jūros dumblius įvynioti ryžiai; Skrudintas sumuštinis su sūriu ir kumpiu; Skrudintas sumuštinis su sūriu; Sumuštiniai su salotomis; Sumuštiniai su vištiena; Skrudinti sumuštiniai; Prapjautos duonelės su karšta dešrele ir kečupu; Ryžių krekeriai [senbei]; Paruošti kinų garinti kukuliai (shumai); Kukurūzų traškučiai su sūriu [užkandžiai]; Konservuoti spagečiai pomidorų padaže; Spagečiai ir mėsos kukuliai; Pyragai su vištienos įdaru; Daržovių apkepai; Pyragai su mėsa; Pyragai su paukštiena; Pyragai su daržovėmis; Pyragai su laukiniena; Pyragai su žuvimi; Mėsos pyragai uždaru tešlos viršumi; Švieži pyragai; Pyragai [saldūs arba sūrūs]; Pyragai su mėsa [paruošti]; Vontonai; Papločių vyniotiniai su įdaru [sumuštiniai]; Vištienos suktinukai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Cukurs, dabiskie saldinātāji, saldas glazūras un pildījumi, biškopības produkti; Pārtikas ledus, saldējums, saldēts jogurts un sorbets; Apstrādāti graudi, ciete un no tiem ražoti produkti, piedevas cepšanai un raugs; Pildīti mīklas izstrādājumi (baozi); Picu pamatnes; Banānu virtuļi; Ananāsu virtuļi; Rīsi ar dārzeņiem un liellopu gaļu (bibimbap); Rīsu cepumi; No kartupeļu miltiem pagatavoti sāļie pārtikas produkti; Sagatavoti pārtikas produkti mērču veidā; Pildītas bagetes; Krekeri ar garšaugu garšu; Krekeri ar garšvielām; Krekeri ar gaļas garšu; Krekeri ar dārzeņu garšu; Krekeri, kas pildīti ar sieru; Krekeri ar siera garšu; Krekeri no pagatavotiem graudaugiem; Arare (granulu formas rīsu krekeri); Cepumi ar sīpoliem; Rīsu masas bumbiņas; Uzpūstas siera bumbiņas [kukurūzas uzkodas]; Rīsu tīteņi; Ankoro (rīsu klimpas, kas garnētas ar saldo pupiņu džemu); Sālsstandziņas; Mīkstie kliņģeri; Brioši (smalkmaizītes); Tortiljas čipsi; Čipsi no graudaugiem; Pilngraudu kviešu čipsi; Ceptas nūdeles ar piedevām (chow mein); Nūdeļu ēdiens [chow mein]; Rīsu krekeri; Rīsu pamatnes un rīsu groziņi; Drumstalu kūkas; Plānās pankūkas; Pankūkas; Pankūkas ar zaļajiem lociņiem (pajeon); Fasētas pusdienu maltītes, kuru sastāvā galvenokārt ir rīsi, kā arī gaļa, zivis vai dārzeņi; No sausiņu pulvera pagatavoti uzkodu pārtikas produkti; Uzkodu pārtikas produkti, kas gatavoti no graudaugu miltiem; No kukurūzas miltiem pagatavoti uzkodu pārtikas produkti; No kartupeļu miltiem pagatavoti uzkodu pārtikas produkti; No rīsu miltiem pagatavoti uzkodu pārtikas produkti; Uzkodu pārtikas produkti, kas pagatavoti no sojas miltiem; Tortiljas uzkodas; No kukurūzas pagatavoti uzkodu izstrādājumi; Uzkodas no uzpūstas kukurūzas; No kukurūzas pagatavotas uzkodas riņķīšu veidā; Pilngraudu uzkodas; Uzkodas, kas pamatā sastāv no rīsiem; Ātri apcepti rīsu plācenīši (topokki); Sāļās un pikantās pankūkas; Korejiešu ēdiens, kas pamatā sastāv no rīsiem (gimbap); Grauzdēti kukurūzas graudi; Karamelizēts popkorns ar sacukurotiem riekstiem; Gyoza (ķīniešu pildītās klimpas, pagatavotas); Prosas kūkas; Rīsu galetes; Rīsu galetes ar šokolādes pārklājumu; Lipīgo rīsu plācenīši (Chapsalttlock); Korejiešu tradicionālie rīsu plācenīši (injeolmi); Griķu cietes ēdiens (Memilmuk); Pildītas smalkmaizītes; Franču grauzdiņi; Ar pupiņu pulveri pārklāts saberztu lipīgu rīsu plācenītis [injeolmi]; Kārtainās mīklas izstrādājumi ar šķiņķi; Saldēti mīklas izstrādājumi ar gaļas un dārzeņu pildījumu; Pildīti makaronu izstrādājumi; Konservēti makaronu ēdieni; Pusgatavas picu pamatnes; Konditorejas izstrādājumi ar dārzeņiem un mājputnu gaļas; Pildīti mīklas rullīši; Pīrāgi ar cūkgaļu; Gaļas pīrāgi; Makaronu ēdieni; Servēšanai gatavas sausās un šķidrās maltītes, kas sastāv galvenokārt no rīsiem; Gatavi rīsu ēdieni; Liofilizēti ēdieni, kas pamatā sastāv no rīsiem; Liofilizēti ēdieni, kas pamatā sastāv no pastas (makaronu izstrādājumiem); Rīsu ēdieni; Konditorejas izstrādājumi no dārzeņiem un gaļas; Konditorejas izstrādājumi no dārzeņiem un zivīm; Saldēti mīklas izstrādājumi ar dārzeņu pildījumu; Saldēti mīklas izstrādājumi ar gaļas pildījumu; Sāļie maizes konditorejas izstrādājumi; Auzu pārslu cepumi ar žāvētiem augļiem; Japāņu ēdiens, kas pamatā sastāv no nūdelēm (ramen); Ravioli; Ravioli (sagatavoti ēšanai); Garneļu klimpas; Safasētas pusdienu kārbiņas, kas satur rīsus, gaļu, zivis vai dārzeņus; Gatavas maltītes, kas pamatā sastāv no nūdelēm; No makaroniem pagatavoti ēdieni; No rīsiem pagatavoti ēdieni; Risoto; Saldie rīsi ar riekstiem un jujubu [yaksik]; Lipīgo rīsu sainīši, kas ietīti bambusa lapās (Zongzi); Jūraszālēs ietīti pagatavoti rīsi; Grauzdētas siermaizes ar šķiņķi; Grauzdētas siermaizes; Sviestmaizes ar salātiem; Cāļa gaļas sviestmaizes; Grauzdētas sviestmaizes; Pārgrieztas maizītes ar karstu cīsiņu un tomātu pastu; Rīsu krekeri (senbei); Ķīniešu tvaicētās klimpas (šumai, pagatavotas); Siera nūjiņas (uzkodas ar siera garšu); Konservēti spageti makaroni ar tomātu mērci; Spageti ar gaļas bumbiņām; Pīrāgi ar vistas gaļu; Dārzeņu pīrāgi; Pīrāgi ar gaļu; Pīrāgi ar mājputnu gaļu; Pīrāgi ar dārzeņiem; Pīrāgi ar medījumu gaļu; Pīrāgi ar zivi; Ar gaļas sautējumu pildīti pīrāgi; Svaigi pīrāgi; Pīrāgi (saldi vai sāļi); Gaļas pīrāgi [gatavi]; Vontoni (pelmeņi); Tītās sviestmaizes; Tīteņi ar vistas gaļu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Zokkor, ħlewwiet naturali, kisi u mili bil-ħelu, prodotti tan-naħal; Silġ, ġelati, jogurts iffriżati u sorbets; Qamħ proċessat, lamtu, u prodotti magħmula minnhom, preparazzjonijiet għall-ħami u ħmira; Baozi [bans mimlijin]; Bażijiet tal-pizza; Fritturi tal-banana; Fritturi tal-ananas; Bibimbap [ross imħallat bil-ħaxix u l-laħam taċ-ċanga]; Gallettini tar-ross; Prodotti tal-ikel imħejjija minn dqiq tal-patata; Prodotti tal-ikel ippreparati fl-għamla ta' zlazi; Bziezen mimlijin; Krakers bl-essenza tal-ħwawar; Krackers imħawra; Krakers bl-essenza tal-laħam; Krakers bl-essenza tal-ħaxix; Kràkers mimlijin bil-ġobon; Krakers bl-essenza tal-ġobon; Krakers magħmula minn ċereali ppreparati; Krakers tar-ross forma ta' granelli (arare); Gallettini tal-basal; Ballun tar-ross imwaħħal; Blalen tal-ġobon minfuħa [ikel ħafif tal-qamħirrun]; Damplings tar-ross; Dumplings tar-ross miksijin bil-ġamm tal-fażola ħelu (ankoro); Pretzels [biskuttelli b'togħma mielħa jqarmċu]; Pretzels rotob; Brijoxxi; Biċċiet tat-tortillas; Krisps magħmul miċ-ċereali; Krisps tal-qamħ oħxon; Chow mein [platt tipiku ċiniż li jikkonsisti minn taljarini]; Chow mein [platti bbażati fuq it-taljarini]; Krakers tar-ross; Qxur tar-ross; Pudini tal-frott miksijin bil-frak tal-ħobż; Krepps; Pancakes; Kejkijiet tat-taġen bil-basal aħdar [pajeon]; Ikliet ippakkjati lest li jikkonsistu primarjament mir-ross, u jinkludu wkoll laħam, ħut jew ħxejjex; Prodotti tal-ikel ħafif magħmula mid-dqiq tal-biskuttelli; Prodotti bħala ikliet ħfief magħmula mid-dqiq taċ-ċereali; Prodotti tal-ikel ħafif magħmula mid-dqiq tal-qamħirrum; Prodotti tal-ikel ħfief magħmula mid-dqiq tal-patata; Prodotti tal-ikel ħafif magħmula mid-dqiq tar-ross; Prodotti tal-ikel ħafif magħmula mid-dqiq tas-sojja; Ikel ħafif tat-tortillas; Prodotti tal-ikel ħafif ippreparati mill-qamħirrum; Ikel ħafif magħmul mill-qamħirrum minfuħ; Ikel ħafif magħmul mill-qamħirrum u li għandu forma ta' ċrieket; Snekks ibbażati fuq diversi qmuħ; Ikliet ħfief ibbażati fuq ir-ross; Kejk tar-ross moqli [topokki]; Pancakes mhux tal-ħelu; Gimbap [platt tar-ross Korean]; Qlub tal-qamħirrum mixwija; Popkorn miksi bil-karamel bil-lewż biz-zokkor kandju; Blalen mill-għaġina mimlijin [gyoza, imsajrin]; Kejkijiet tad-dekkuk; Galletti (tar-ross); Gallettini tar-ross miksija biċ-ċikkulata; Kejkijiet tar-ross umdi (Chapsalttock); Kejk tar-ross tradizzjonali Korean [injeolmi]; Ġèli tal-qamħ Saraċin; Bziezen mimlija; Ħobż mixwi Franċiż; Kejk tar-ross glutinuż imfarrak miksi bit-trab tal-fażola [injeolmi]; Għaġina sfiljurata li fiha l-perżut; Għaġina ffriżata mimlija bil-laħam u l-ħaxix; Għaġin bil-mili; Għaġin ippreparat fil-bottijiet; Għagina tal-pizza moħmija minn qabel; Ikel tal-għaġina li jikkonsisti fi ħxejjex u tjur; Torta żgħira magħmula bl-għaġina tal-bajd; Torti tal-majjal; Torti tal-laħam; Ikliet tal-għaġin; Ikliet xotti jew likwidi lesti biex jisservew, l-iktar li fihom għaġin jew ross; Ikliet tar-ross lesti; Platti mnixxfa bl-iffriżar li l-ingredjent prinċipali tagħhom ikun ir-ross; Platti mnixxfa bl-iffriżar li l-ingredjent prinċipali jkun l-għaġin; Ikliet ibbażati fuq ir-ross; Ikliet bl-għaġina li jikkonsistu fi ħxejjex u laħam; Ikel tal-għaġina li jikkonsistu fi ħxejjex u ħut; Għaġina ffriżata mimlija bil-ħaxix; Għaġina ffriżata mimlija bil-laħam; Ikel tal-għaġina [mhux tal-ħelu]; Raggruppamenti tal-ħafur li fihom frott imnixxef; Ramen [platt Ġappuniż ibbażat fuq it-taljarini]; Ravjul; Ravjul [ippreparat]; Dumplings tal-gambli; Kolazzjon fil-kaxxa magħmul minn ross, bil-laħam, ħut jew ħxejjex miżjuda; Ikliet imħejjija abbażi ta' noodles; Ikliet lesti bbażati fuq l-għaġin; Ikliet lesti bbażati fuq ir-ross; Risotto; Ross ħelu bil-lewż u jujubes [yaksik]; Ross bil-gluten imgeżwer f'weraq tal-bambù (Zongzi); Ross imsajjar imkebbeb f'alka tal-baħar; Sandwiċis bil-ġobon u bil-perżut mixwija; Sandwiċis tal-ġobon mixwija; Sandwiċis li fihom insalata; Sandwiċis bil-laħam tat-tiġieġa; Sandwiċis mixwijin; Zalzett jaħraq u keċap f'bziezen maqtugħin miftuħin; Krakers tar-ross [senbei]; Blalen mill-għaġina, mfawwra (Shumai, imsajra); Ġobon imfelfel [ikel ħafif]; Spagetti tal-landa fiz-zalza tat-tadam; Spagetti u pulpetti tal-laħam; Torti tat-tiġieġ; Torti tal-ħaxix; Torti bil-laħam; Torti bil-mili tat-tajr; Torti li jkun fihom il-ħaxix; Torti bil-laħam tal-kaċċa; Torti li jkun fihom il-ħut; Torta moħmija f'borma; Torti friski; Torti (ħelwin jew bil-melħ); Torti tal-laħam (ippreparati); Wontons; Wraps [sandwiċis]; Wraps bit-tiġieġ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Suiker, natuurlijke zoetstoffen, zoete omhulsels en vullingen, bijenproducten; Ijs, roomijs, yoghurtijs en waterijs; Bewerkte granen, zetmeel en producten hiervan, preparaten voor het bakken en gist; Baozi; Bodems voor pizza's; Bananenbeignets; Ananasbeignets; Bimibap [rijst gemengd met groenten en rundvlees]; Rijstkoekjes; Aardappelmeel (Kant-en-klare hartige voedingsmiddelen bereid uit -); Sausen (Kant-en-klare voedingsmiddelen in de vorm van -); Gevulde stokbroden; Crackers met kruidensmaak; Crackers met kruidensmaak; Crackers met een vleessmaak; Crackers met een groentesmaak; Crackers gevuld met kaas; Crackers met kaassmaak; Crackers gemaakt van bewerkte granen; Rijstwafels in de vorm van bolletjes (arare); Uienkoekjes; Kleefrijstballetjes; Gepofte kaasballetjes [maïssnacks]; Rijstdumplings; Rijstmeelballetjes met zoete-bonenjam (ankoro); Zoute krakelingen; Zachte krakelingen; Brioches; Tortillachips; Chips van granen; Chips (Volkoren -); Chow mein; Chow mein [gerechten op basis van noedels]; Rijstwafels; Rijstkorsten; Kruimeltaarten; Flensjes; Pannenkoeken; Pannenkoek van groene ui [pajeon]; Voorverpakte lunchgerechten, voornamelijk bestaande uit rijst, maar ook met vlees, vis of groenten; Snacks bereid uit beschuitmeel; Snacks vervaardigd van bloem van granen; Snacks bereid uit maïsmeel; Snacks gemaakt van aardappelmeel; Snackproducten bereid uit rijstmeel; Snackproducten bereid uit sojameel; Tortillasnacks; Snacks bereid uit maïs; Snacks vervaardigd uit maïs en in de vorm van bladerdeeg; Snacks vervaardigd uit maïs en in de vorm van ringen; Snacks op meergranenbasis; Versnaperingen op basis van rijst; Roergebakken rijstcracker [topokki]; Hartige pannenkoeken; Gimbap [Koreaans rijstgerecht]; Maïskorrels (Geroosterde -); Popcorn met caramellaagje met gesuikerde noten; Meelballetjes (Chinese gevulde -) [gyoza, gekookt]; Gierstcake; Rijstcake; Rijstwafels met een chocoladelaagje; Kleefrijstcakes (chapsalttock); Koreaanse traditionele rijstcracker [injeolmi]; Boekweitgelei (memilmuk); Belegde broodjes (Gevulde -); Wentelteefjes; Cakejes van gestampte kleefrijst bedekt met een laagje bonenpoeder [injeolmi]; Banketbakkerswaren van bladerdeeg met ham; Bevroren pasteien gevuld met vlees en groenten; Deegwaren met vullingen; Pastadeegwaren in blik; Voorgebakken pizzabodems; Bakkerswaren met groenten en gevogelte; Loempiaas; Pasteien (Varkensvlees -); Vleespasteitjes; Deegwaren (Schotels met -); Droge en vloeibare kant-en-klare gerechten, hoofdzakelijk bestaande uit rijst; Rijstschotels (Kant-en-klare -); Gevriesdroogde gerechten met rijst als voornaamste ingrediënt; Gevriesdroogde gerechten met pasta als voornaamste ingrediënt; Rijstschotels; Banketbakkerswaren bestaande uit groenten en vlees; Banketbakkerswaren bestaande uit groenten en vis; Diepgevroren pastei gevuld met groenten; Bevroren banketbakkerswaren gevuld met vlees; Hartig gebak; Haverclusters met gedroogde vruchten; Ramen; Ravioli; Ravioli [bereide]; Meelballetjes van garnalen; Lunchpakketten bestaande uit rijst met vlees, vis of groenten; Maaltijden op basis van noedels; Bereide maaltijden op basis van pasta; Bereide maaltijden op basis van rijst; Risotto; Zoete rijst met noten en jujubes [yaksik]; Kleefrijst, gewikkeld in bamboebladeren (zongzi); Bereide rijst in zeewier gerold; Boterhammen (Geroosterde -) met ham en kaas; Boterhammen (Geroosterde -) met kaas; Sandwiches met salade; Sandwiches met kip; Boterhammen (Geroosterde -); Broodjes (Opengesneden -) belegd met hete worst en ketchup; Rijstwafels (senbei); Meelballetjes (Chinese gestoomde -) [shumai, gekookt]; Kaas krullen [tussendoortjes]; Spaghetti met tomatensaus in blik; Spaghetti met gehaktballen; Kippenpasteien; Groentetaarten; Hartige pasteien met vlees; Hartige pasteien met gevogelte; Pasteien met groentes; Pasteien met wild; Pasteien met vis; Pasteien (In een pot gebraden -); Pasteien (verse -) [hartige taarten]; Pasteien [hartige taarten] zoete of hartige; Vleespasteien [bereide]; Wontons; Wraps [sandwiches]; Kippenwraps.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Cukry, naturalne słodziki, polewy cukiernicze i nadzienia, produkty pszczele; Lód, lody spożywcze, mrożone jogurty i sorbety; Ziarna przetworzone, skrobia i wyroby z tych towarów, preparaty do pieczenia i drożdze; Baozi (nadziewane kluski gotowane na parze); Spody do pizzy; Banany w cieście; Ananasy w cieście; Bibimbap [ryż z warzywami i wołowiną]; Ciasteczka ryżowe; Gotowa solona żywność przyrządzona z mąki ziemniaczanej; Gotowe produkty spożywcze w postaci sosów; Bagietki z nadzieniem; Krakersy o smaku ziołowym; Krakersy o smaku przypraw; Krakersy o smaku mięsnym; Krakersy o smaku warzyw; Krakersy nadziewane serem; Krakersy o smaku sera; Krakersy z preparatów zbożowych; Chrupki ryżowe w kształcie kulek (arare); Ciasteczka cebulowe; Kleiste kuleczki ryżowe; Dmuchane kuleczki serowe [przekąski kukurydziane]; Ryżowe pierożki; Pierożki ryżowe przybrane dżemem ze słodkiej fasoli (ankoro); Precelki; Miękkie precle; Brioszki (drożdżowe bułeczki); Chipsy tortilla; Chrupki zbożowe; Chrupki z pełnego ziarna pszenicy; Chow mein [chiński smażony makaron]; Chow mein [dania na bazie makaronu]; Krakersy ryżowe; Wafle ryżowe; Owoce pod kruszonką; Naleśniki [cienkie]; Naleśniki; Naleśnik z zieloną cebulą [pajeon]; Zapakowane zestawy obiadowe składające się głównie z ryżu, ale również z mięsa, ryb lub warzyw; Przekąski wykonane ze sproszkowanych sucharów; Przekąski wykonane z mąki zbożowej; Przekąski wykonane z mąki kukurydzianej; Przekąski przyrządzone z mąki ziemniaczanej; Przekąski wykonane z mąki ryżowej; Przekąski wykonane z mąki sojowej; Przekąski na bazie tortilli; Przekąski wykonane z kukurydzy; Przekąski z kukurydzy w formie ciasta francuskiego; Przekąski z kukurydzy w formie kół; Przekąski wieloziarniste; Przekąski na bazie ryżu; Smażone ciastka ryżowe [topokki]; Naleśniki słone; Gimbap [koreańskie danie z ryżu]; Opiekane ziarna kukurydzy; Popcorn powlekany karmelem z karmelizowanymi orzechami; Chińskie pierożki nadziewane (gyoza, gotowane); Ciastka z prosa; Wafle ryżowe; Wafle ryżowe w polewie czekoladowej; Klejące się ciasteczka ryżowe (Chapsalttock); Tradycyjne koreańskie ciasto ryżowe [injeolmi]; Galareta gryczana (Memilmuk); Bułki nadziewane; Tosty francuskie; Kleiste ucierane ciasto ryżowe powlekane fasolą w proszku [injeolmi]; Ciasto kruche z szynką; Ciasta mrożone nadziewane mięsem i warzywami; Makarony zawierające nadzienia; Puszkowana żywność zawierająca makaron; Wstępnie upieczone spody na pizze; Wyroby piekarnicze składające się z warzyw i drobiu; Krokiety po chińsku; Paszteciki z wieprzowiny; Mięso zapiekane w cieście; Potrawy z makaronu; Dania gotowe suche lub w płynie, zawierające głównie ryż; Gotowe dania z ryżu; Dania liofilizowane, których głównym składnikiem jest ryż; Dania liofilizowane, których głównym składnikiem jest makaron; Dania na bazie ryżu; Wyroby piekarnicze składające się z warzyw i mięsa; Wyroby piekarnicze z warzywami i rybami; Mrożone produkty z ciasta nadziewane warzywami; Mrożone produkty z ciasta nadziewane mięsem; Solone wyroby piekarnicze; Zbitki owsiane zawierające suszone owoce; Ramen (japońskie danie na bazie makaronu); Pierożki ravioli; Ravioli [gotowe]; Pierożki z krewetkami; Gotowy lunch w pudełku składający się z ryżu, z dodatkiem mięsa, ryby lub warzyw; Gotowe potrawy na bazie makaronu; Potrawy gotowe na bazie makaronu; Gotowe potrawy na bazie ryżu; Risotto; Słodki ryż z orzechami i owocami głożyny [yaksik]; Ryż kleisty zawijany w liście bambusa [Zongzi]; Ryż preparowany zawijany w wodorosty; Opiekane kanapki z serem i z szynką; Tostowe opiekane kanapki z serem; Kanapki zawierające sałatę; Kanapki zawierające kurczaka; Kanapki tostowe opiekane; Gorąca kiełbaska i keczup w rozciętych bułkach; Senbei [ciastka ryżowe]; Chińskie pierożki gotowane na parze (shumai); Chrupki serowe [przekąski]; Spaghetti w sosie pomidorowym w puszce; Spaghetti i klopsy; Placki z kurczakiem; Placki z nadzieniem z warzyw; Ciasta zawierające mięso; Drób w cieście; Warzywa w cieście; Dziczyzna w cieście; Ryba w cieście; Mięso z warzywami w cieście [pot pie]; Świeże placki [ciasta]; Ciasta [słodkie lub słone]; Mięso w cieście [gotowe]; Wontons (rodzaj chińskich pierożków); Zawijana kanapka typu wrap; Wrapy z kurczakiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Açúcares, adoçantes naturais, revestimentos e coberturas doces, produtos apícolas; Gelo, gelados, iogurtes gelados e sorvetes; Grãos processados, amidos, e produtos feitos a partir dos mesmos, preparações de cozedura e leveduras; Baozi [pãezinhos recheados]; Bases para pizas; Sonhos de banana; Rosquinhas de ananás; Bibimbap [arroz misturado com legumes e carne]; Bolachas de arroz; Alimentos salgados preparados feitos de farinha de batata; Alimentos preparados sob a forma de molhos; Baguetes recheadas; Bolachas salgadas com sabor a ervas; Bolachas salgadas com sabor a especiarias; Bolachas salgadas com sabor a carne; Bolachas salgadas com sabor a legumes; Bolachas salgadas com recheio de queijo; Bolachas salgadas com sabor a queijo; Bolachas salgadas de cereais preparados; Bolachas de arroz glutinoso em forma de grânulos (arare); Biscoitos de cebola; Bolinhos de arroz glutinoso; Bolas de queijo tufado [snacks de milho]; Bolinhos de arroz; Bolinhos de arroz com cobertura de doce de feijão (ankoro); Pretzels; Pretzels moles; Brioches; Rodelas fritas de tortilha mexicana; Produtos estaladiços feitos de cereais; Produtos estaladiços de trigo integral; Chow mein [noodles chineses salteados]; Chow mein [pratos à base de talharins]; Bolachas estaladiças de arroz; Crosta de arroz; Crumbles; Crepes; Panquecas [crepes]; Panquecas de cebolinha [pajeon]; Almoços pré-embalados constituídos principalmente por arroz, incluindo também carne, peixe ou legumes; Aperitivos feitos de pão ralado; Aperitivos feitos a partir de farinha de cereais; Aperitivos feitos de farinha de milho; Aperitivos feitos com farinha de batata; Aperitivos feitos a partir de farinha de arroz; Aperitivos feitos de farinha de soja; Aperitivos de tortilha mexicana; Aperitivos preparados a partir do milho; Aperitivos feitos de milho e sob a forma de folhados; Aperitivos feitos de milho e sob a forma de argolas; Aperitivos à base de multicereais; Snacks à base de arroz; Bolo de arroz frito [topokki]; Panquecas salgadas; Gimbap [prato Coreano à base de arroz]; Grãos de milho torrados; Pipocas caramelizadas com frutos secos açucarados; Bolinhos de massa chineses recheados e cozidos (gyoza); Bolos de painço; Bolos de arroz; Bolos de arroz com cobertura de chocolate; Bolos de arroz glutinoso ("Chapsalttock"); Bolo de arroz tradicional coreano [injeolmi]; Geleia de trigo sarraceno (Memilmuk); Pãezinhos recheados; Rabanadas; Bolinhos de arroz glutinoso triturado cobertos com feijão em pó [injeolmi]; Pastelaria folhada que contem fiambre; Pastéis congelados recheados com carne e legumes; Massas alimentares recheadas; Massas alimentares enlatados; Bases de pizas pré-cozidas; Pastéis contendo legumes e carne de aves; Rolinhos de ovo; Empadas de carne de porco; Tartes de carne [empadas de carne]; Pratos de massa alimentar; Refeições prontas a servir, secas e líquidas, constituídas essencialmente de arroz; Pratos preparados de arroz; Pratos liofilizados com arroz como ingrediente principal; Pratos liofilizados com massa como ingrediente principal; Pratos à base de arroz; Pastéis contendo legumes e carne; Pastéis contendo legumes e peixe; Pastéis congelados recheados com legumes; Pastéis congelados recheados com carne; Pastelaria salgada; Cereais de aveia contendo frutos secos; Ramen [prato Japonês à base de noodles]; Ravioli; Ravióli [preparado]; Bolinhos de massa fresca com camarão [dumplings]; Almoços embalados compostos por arroz, com adição de carne, peixe ou legumes; Refeições preparadas à base de massas [noodles]; Refeições preparadas à base de massas; Refeições preparadas à base de arroz; Risotto; Arroz doce coreano com nozes e jujubas [yaksik]; Arroz glutinoso enrolado em folhas de bambu (Zongzi); Arroz preparado enrolado em algas; Tosta mista; Tosta de queijo; Sanduíches contendo salada; Sanduíches contendo frango; Sanduíches tostadas; Salsichas quentes com ketchup em pãezinhos abertos; Senbei [bolachas de arroz]; Shumais (bolinhos de massa chineses cozinhados a vapor); Rolinhos de queijo tufado [aperitivos]; Esparguete enlatado com molho de tomate; Esparguete e almôndegas; Empadas de frango; Quiches de legumes; Empadas contendo carne; Empadas contendo carne de aves de capoeira; Empadas contendo vegetais; Empadas contendo carnes de caça; Tartes com recheio de peixe; Empadas [salgados]; Tartes frescas; Empadas, doces ou salgadas; Empadas de carne preparadas; Wontons; Sanduíches enroladas [tipo wrap]; Wraps de frango.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Zahăr, îndulcitori naturali, glazuri dulci și umpluturi, produse apicole; Gheață, înghețată, iaurt înghețat și șerbeturi; Semințe procesate, amidon și produsele acestora, preparate coapte și drojdie; Baozi [chifle umplute]; Blaturi de pizza; Banane pané; Ananas pané; Bibimbap [orez amestecat cu legume și carne de vită]; Biscuiți de orez; Alimente sărate preparate din făină de cartofi; Produse alimentare preparate sub formă de sosuri; Baghete umplute; Biscuiți cu aromă de plante; Biscuiți crocanți condimentați; Biscuiți cu aromă de carne; Biscuiți crackers cu aromă de legume; Biscuiți umpluți cu brânză; Biscuiți cu aromă de brânză; Biscuiți crocanți din cereale; Biscuiți din orez în formă de granule (arare); Biscuiți cu ceapă; Bulete din orez; Bulete de brânză expandate [snacksuri de porumb]; Găluște de orez; Găluște din orez garnisite cu pastă de fasole dulce (ankoro); Covrigei; Covrigei moi; Brioșe; Chipsuri tortilla; Chipsuri din cereale; Chipsuri integrale de grâu; Chow mein (mâncare de tăiței cu specific chinezesc); Tăiței chow mein [mâncăruri pe bază de tăieței]; Biscuiți sărați din orez; Tartă de orez; Fulgi; Clătite; Clătite americane; Clătite cu ceapă verde [pajeon]; Mâncăruri preambalate care constau în principal în orez, dar și cu carne, pește sau legume; Produse pentru gustări preparate din pesmet; Produse pentru gustări preparate din făină de cereale; Produse pentru gustări preparate din făină de porumb; Produse pentru gustări preparate din făină de cartofi; Produse pentru gustări preparate din făină de orez; Produse pentru gustări preparate din făină de soia; Gustări din tortilla; Gustări rapide preparate din porumb; Gustări alimentare fabricate din porumb sub formă expandată; Gustări alimentare din porumb sub formă de inele; Gustări pe bază de multicereale; Gustări pe bază de orez; Turte de orez sote [topokki]; Clătite sărate; Gimbap [fel de mâncare coreean pe bază de orez]; Boabe de porumb prăjite; Floricele de porumb învelite în caramel, cu alune; Galuște chinezești umplute (gyoza, gătite); Prăjituri din mei; Turte din orez; Turte din orez învelite în ciocolată; Prăjituri din orez cleios (chapsalttock); Prăjitură de orez tradițională coreană [injeolmi]; Jeleu de hrișcă (memilmuk); Chifle umplute; Frigănele; Găluști de orez acoperite cu pudră de fasole [injeolmi]; Produse de patiserie din foitaj care conțin șuncă; Produse de patiserie congelate umplute cu carne și legume; Paste făinoase umplute; Alimente cu paste la conservă; Blaturi de pizza coapte în prealabil; Produse de patiserie conținând legume și carne de pasăre; Rulouri cu ou; Plăcinte cu carne de porc; Plăcintă cu carne; Mâncăruri care includ paste; Mâncăruri gătite, uscate și lichide, în principal pe bază de orez; Mâncăruri pregătite pe bază de orez; Mâncăruri uscate prin înghețare în care orezul este ingredientul principal; Mâncăruri criodesicate în care pastele sunt ingredientul principal; Mâncăruri pe bază de orez; Produse de patiserie din legume și carne; Produse de patiserie conținând legume și pește; Produse de patiserie congelate cu umplutură de legume; Produse din patiserie congelate umplute cu carne; Produse de patiserie aromate; Amestecuri de ovăz care conțin fructe uscate; Ramen [fel de mâncare japonez pe bază de tăiței]; Ravioli; Ravioli (preparate); Găluște de creveți; Prânzuri la cutie constând din orez, cu carne, pește sau legume adăugate; Alimente preparate pe bază de tăieței; Mâncăruri preparate pe bază de paste; Mâncăruri preparate pe bază de orez; Rizoto; Orez dulce cu nuci și jujubă, denumit și măslin dobrogean, [yaksik]; Orez glutinos învelit în frunze de bambus (Zongzi); Orez preparat învelit în alge marine; Sandviș din brânză topită și șuncă; Sandviș din brânză topită; Sandvișuri care conțin salată; Sandvișuri cu carne de pui; Sandvișuri încălzite la grill; Crenvurști calzi și ketchup în chifle deschise; Biscuiți din orez [senbei]; Găluști chinezești gătite în abur [shumai, gătite]; Snacksuri răsucite cu gust de brânză; Spaghete cu sos de roșii la conservă; Spaghetti și chiftele; Plăcinte cu carne de pui; Plăcinte cu legume; Plăcinte cu carne; Plăcinte cu carne de pasăre; Plăcinte cu legume; Plăcinte cu vânat; Plăcinte cu pește; Plăcinte gătite; Plăcinte proaspete; Plăcinte dulci sau sărate; Plăcinte cu carne (preparate); Wonton; Înveliș pentru sandvișuri; Lipii cu pui.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Cukor, prírodné sladidlá, sladké polevy a plnky, včelie produkty; Potravinársky ľad, zmrzliny, mrazené jogurty a sorbety; Spracované semená, škroby a produkty z nich vyrobené, prípravky na pečenie a droždia; Baozi (čínske parené buchty); Pizzové korpusy; Smažené cesto s kúskami banánov; Smažené cesto s kúskami ananásu; Ryža zmiešaná so zeleninou a hovädzím mäsom (bibimbap); Ryžové sušienky; Hotové lahôdkové potraviny vyrobené zo zemiakovej múky; Hotové potraviny v podobe omáčok; Plnené bagety; Krekery s bylinkovou príchuťou; Krekery s príchuťou korenia; Krekery s mäsovou príchuťou; Krekery so zeleninovou príchuťou; Krekery plnené syrom; Krekery so syrovou príchuťou; Krekery so spracovaných cereálií; Drobné ryžové krekery vo forme peliet (arare); Cibuľové sušienky; Guľôčky z lepivej ryže; Extrudované syrové guľôčky [kukuričné chuťovky]; Ryžové knedličky; Ryžové knedličky poliate omáčkou zo sladkých fazuliek (ankoro); Praclíky; Mäkké praclíky; Briošky; Tortillové lupienky; Cereálne lupienky; Lupienky z celozrnnej pšenice; Čínske rezancové jedlo chow mein; Chow mein [jedlá na báze rezancov]; Ryžové krekery; Ryžové korpusy; Ovocný koláč s posýpkou vyrobenou z masla, cukru a múky; Palacinky; Palacinky; Placka zo zelenej cibule [pajeon]; Balené hotové obedy zložené predovšetkým z ryže a obsahujúce mäso, rybu alebo zeleninu; Chuťovky vyrobené zo strúhanky; Chuťovky vyrobené z obilnej múky; Chuťovky vyrobené z kukuričnej múky; Chuťovky vyrobené zo zemiakovej múky; Chuťovky vyrobené z ryžovej múky; Chuťovky vyrobené zo sójovej múky; Tortilla - chuťovky; Chuťovky pripravené z kukurice; Chuťovky vyrobené prevažne z kukurice vo forme pukancov; Chuťovky vyrobené z kukurice v tvare krúžkov; Viaczrnné pochutinové jedlá; Ryžové chuťovky; Restované ryžové koláče (topokki); Slané palacinky; Gimbap (kórejské ryžové jedlo); Pražené kukuričné jadrá; Pukance s karamelovou polevou s orechmi obalenými v cukre; Čínske plnené knedličky (gyoza, varené); Koláče z prosa; Ryžové koláče; Ryžové chlebíčky s čokoládovou polevou; Koláče z lepkavej ryže (chapsalttock); Kórejský tradičný ryžový koláč (injeolmi); Rôsol z pohánky (Memilmuk); Plnené žemle; Sladká francúzska hrianka; Ryžová placka z lepkavej mletej ryže posypaná fazuľovým práškom [injeolmi]; Lístkové pečivo obsahujúce šunku; Mrazené pečivo s mäsovou a zeleninovou plnkou; Cestoviny obsahujúce plnku; Konzervované cestovinové jedlá; Predpečené pizzové korpusy; Pečivo obsahujúce zeleninu a hydinu; Vaječné rolky; Koláče s bravčovým mäsom; Pečivo s mäsovou náplňou; Cestovinové jedlá; Instantné jedlá pozostávajúce hlavne z ryže; Hotové ryžové jedlá; Mrazom sušené ryžové jedlá; Mrazom sušené cestovinové jedlá; Jedlá na báze ryže; Pečivo obsahujúce zeleninu a mäso; Pečivo obsahujúce zeleninu a ryby; Mrazené pečivo so zeleninovou plnkou; Mrazené pečivo plnené mäsom; Lahôdkové pečivo; Ovsené hrudky obsahujúce sušené ovocie; Ramen (japonské rezancové polievky); Ravioly; Ravioli [hotové]; Garnátové knedličky; Balené obedy obsahujúce ryžu s pridaným mäsom, rybou alebo zeleninou; Jedlá z rezancov; Cestovinové hotové jedlá; Hotové jedlá z ryže; Rizoto; Sladká ryža s orechmi a jujubou [jaksik]; Lepkavá ryža zabalená do bambusových listov (Zongzi); Hotová ryža zabalená do morských rias; Opekané syrové sendviče so šunkou; Opekané syrové sendviče; Sendviče so šalátom; Sendviče s kuracím mäsom; Opekané sendviče; Horúca klobása s kečupom v rozrezanej bagete; Ryžové krekery [senbei]; Čínske knedličky varené na pare (šumai, varené); Syrové chrumky [pochutina]; Konzervované špagety v paradajkovej omáčke; Špagety a mäsové guľky; Kuracie koláče; Zeleninové koláče; Koláče obsahujúce mäso; Koláče obsahujúce hydinu; Koláče obsahujúce zeleninu; Koláče obsahujúce divinu; Koláče obsahujúce ryby; Pot pies (slané plnené koláče); Čerstvé koláče; Koláče [so slanou alebo sladkou plnkou]; Pirôžky s mäsom [hotové]; Čínske knedličky Wonton; Wrap [zavinutý sendvič]; Kuracie wrapy [zvinuté plnené obilné placky].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Sladkorji, naravna sladila, sladki prelivi in polnila, čebelji proizvodi; Led, sladoledi, zamrznjeni jogurti in sorbeti; Predelano zrnje, škrobi, in proizvodi narejeni iz naštetega, sredstva za peko in kvasila; Baozi [polnjene žemljice]; Testo za pizzo; Bananini ocvrtki; Ananasovi ocvrtki; Bibimbap [riž, zmešan z zelenjavo in govedino]; Riževi piškoti; Pripravljena začinjena živila iz krompirjeve moke; Pripravljena živila v obliki omak; Polnjene francoske štručke; Krekerji z okusom zelišč; Krekerji z okusom začimb; Krekerji z okusom mesa; Krekerji z okusom zelenjave; Krekerji, polnjeni s sirom; Krekerji z okusom sira; Krekerji iz pripravljenih žitaric; Japonski riževi krekerji (arare); Čebulni piškoti; Kroglice iz lepljivega riža; Flips kroglice s sirom [koruzni prigrizki]; Riževi cmoki; Riževi cmoki, obliti z marmelado iz sladkega fižola (ankoro); Preste; Mehke preste; Brioši; Tortilja čips; Hrustavci iz žitaric; Polnozrnati hrustavci; Kitajski praženi rezanci (chow mein); Chow mein [jedi na osnovi rezancev]; Riževi krekerji; Riževa skorja; Drobljenec; Palačinke; Palačinke; Palačinke z mlado čebulo [pajeon]; Predhodno pakirana kosila, sestavljena v glavnem iz riža, vključujoč tudi meso, ribe ali zelenjavo; Prigrizki iz prepečenčeve moke; Prigrizki, izdelani iz žitne moke; Prigrizki iz koruzne moke; Prigrizki izdelani iz krompirjeve moke; Prigrizki iz riževe moke; Prigrizki iz sojine moke; Tortilla prigrizki; Prigrizki, pripravljeni iz koruze; Prigrizki iz koruze v obliki napihnjenčkov; Prigrizki iz koruze v obliki prstanov; Prigrizki na osnovi več žit; Prigrizki na riževi osnovi; Ocvrto riževo pecivo [topokki]; Slane palačinke; Gimbap [korejska riževa jed]; Pečena koruzna zrna; Karamelna pokovka s kandiranimi oreščki; Kitajski polnjeni cmoki (gyoza, kuhani); Torte s prosom; Riževi vaflji; S čokolado oblito riževo pecivo; Pecivo iz lepljivega riža (Chapsalttock); Tradicionalno korejsko riževo pecivo (injeolmi); Želatina iz ajde (Memilmuk); Polnjeni kruhovi zvitki; Francoski toast; Lepljivo stolčeno riževo pecivo, potreseno s fižolovim v prahu [injeolmi]; Pecivo iz listnatega testa, ki vsebuje šunko; Zamrznjeno pecivo, polnjeno z mesom in zelenjavo; Polnjene testenine; Konzervirane testenine; Predpečeno testo za pico; Pecivo z zelenjavo in perutnino; Spomladanski zavitki (tradicionalni kitajski prigrizki); Pite s svinjino; Mesne pite; Testeninske jedi; Suhi in tekoči pripravljeni obroki, pretežno sestavljeni iz riža; Pripravljene riževe jedi; Z zamrzovanjem sušene jedi z rižem kot glavno sestavino; Z zamrzovanjem sušene jedi s testeninami kot glavno sestavino; Jedi na osnovi riža; Pecivo iz zelenjave in mesa; Pecivo iz zelenjave in rib; Zamrznjeno pecivo z zelenjavnim nadevom; Zamrznjeno pecivo, polnjeno z mesom; Pikantno pecivo; Ovseni kupčki s suhim sadjem; Ramen [japonska jed na osnovi rezancev]; Ravioli; Ravioli [pripravljeni]; Cmoki iz morskih rakcev; Kosilo v škatli, ki je sestavljeno iz riža, z dodanim mesom, ribami ali zelenjavo; Pripravljene jedi na osnovi rezancev; Pripravljeni obroki na osnovi testenin; Jedi na osnovi riža, pripravljene na uživanje; Rižote; Sladek riž z oreški in žižulami [yaksik]; Lepljiv riž, zavit v bambusove liste (Zongzi); Pripravljen riž, zavit v morske alge; Toast sendvič s sirom in s šunko; Toast sendvič s sirom; Sendviči s solato; Sendviči s piščancem; Popečeni sendviči; Pekoče klobase in kečap v prerezani kruhovi štručki; Riževi krekerji [senbei]; Shumai (kitajski parjeni cmoki, kuhani); Flips s sirom [prigrizki]; Konzervirani špageti v paradižnikovi omaki; Špageti in mesne kroglice; Piščančje pite; Zelenjavne pite; Pite z mesom; Pite, ki vsebujejo perutnino; Pite z zelenjavo; Pite z divjačinskim mesom; Ribje pite; Pite z mesom in zelenjavo; Sveže pite; Pite (sladke ali slane); Mesne pite [pripravljene]; Won-tons (tradicionalne nadevane kitajske testenine); Zavitek [sendvič]; Piščančji zvitki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Socker, naturliga sötningsmedel, söta beläggningar och fyllningar, biprodukter; Is, glass, fryst yoghurt och sorbet; Bearbetat korn, stärkelse samt varor framställda av dessa, preparat för bakning samt jäst; Baozi (ångkokta fyllda bröd); Basmaterial till pizzor (deg); Bananbeignet; Ananasbeignet; Bibimbap [ris blandat med grönsaker och nötkött]; Kakor av ris; Tillredda välsmakande livsmedel gjorda av potatismjöl; Tillagade livsmedel i form av såser; Fyllda baguetter; Smörgåskex smaksatta med örter; Smörgåskex smaksatta med kryddor; Smörgåskex smaksatta med kött; Smörgåskex smaksatta med grönsaker; Smörgåskex fyllda med ost; Smörgåskex smaksatta med ost; Smörgåskex tillverkade av bearbetade spannmål; Pelletsformade riskex (arare); Lökbiskvier; Klibbiga risbollar; Pösiga ostbollar [majssnacks]; Dumplings [slags klimp] av ris; Risklimpar överdragna med söt bönmarmelad (ankoro); Salta kringlor; Mjuka saltkringlor; Briocher (bröd); Tortillachips; Chips framställda av spannmål; Chips av fullkornsvete; Chow mein (färdiglagade maträtter huvudsakligen bestående av nudlar); Chow mein [nudelbaserade rätter]; Riskex; Risskorpor; Smulpajer; Crêpes; Pannkakor; Pannkakor med salladslök [pajeon]; Färdigförpackade luncher bestående i huvudsak av ris och innehållande kött, fisk eller grönsaker; Snacksprodukter tillverkade av skorpmjöl; Snacks tillverkade av mjöl från spannmål; Snacksprodukter tillverkade av majsmjöl; Snackmatsprodukter gjorda av potatismjöl; Snackmatsprodukter framställda av rismjöl; Snackmatsprodukter tillverkade av sojamjöl; Tortillasnacks; Snacks tillagade av majs; Snacks framställda av majs och i form av puffar; Snacks framställda av majs och i form av ringar; Snacks baserade på flera slag av spannmål; Risbaserade tilltugg; Wokade riskakor [topokki]; Kryddade pannkakor; Gimbap [koreansk risrätt]; Rostade majskorn; Popcorn överdragna med karamell med kanderade nötter; Kinesiska fyllda dumplings (gyoza, tillagade); Hirskakor; Riskakor; Chokladöverdragna riskakor; Kakor av klibbigt ris (chapsalttock); Traditionell koreansk riskaka [injeolmi]; Bovetegelé (memilmuk); Fyllda smörgåsar; Fattiga riddare; Kaka av krossat glutinöst ris täckt med bönpulver [injeolmi]; Flingliknande smördeg innehållande skinka; Frusna bakverk fyllda med kött och grönsaker; Pasta innehållande fyllningar; Pastalivsmedel på burk; Förbakade pizzabottnar; Konditorivaror bestående av grönsaker och fjäderfä; Vårrulle (egg roll); Fläskpajer; Köttpajer; Pastarätter; Färdiga rätter i torr och flytande form huvudsakligen bestående av ris; Tillagade risrätter; Frystorkade rätter huvudsakligen bestående av ris; Frystorkade rätter huvudsakligen bestående av pasta; Risbaserade rätter; Konditorivaror bestående av grönsaker och kött; Konditorivaror bestående av grönsaker och fisk; Frusna bakverk fyllda med grönsaker; Frusna bakverk fyllda med kött; Kryddade bakverk; Havrekluster innehållande torkad frukt; Ramen [japansk nudelbaserad rätt]; Ravioli; Ravioli [tillagade]; Räkdumplings; Matlådor bestående av ris, med kött, fisk eller grönsaker; Nudelbaserade måltider; Pastabaserade tillagade måltider; Risbaserade tillagade måltider; Risotto; Sött ris med nötter och jujubär [yaksik]; Klibbris inrullat i bambublad (zongzi); Tillagat ris rullat i sjögräs; Grillad ost- och skinksmörgås; Grillad ostsmörgås; Smörgåsar innehållande sallad; Smörgåsar innehållande kyckling; Rostade smörgåsar; Korvbröd fylld med kryddad korv och ketchup; Riskex [senbei]; Kinesiska ångade dumplings (shumai, tillagade); Snacks som ostkrokar; Spaghetti och tomatsås på burk; Spagetti och köttbullar; Kycklingpajer; Grönsakspajer; Pajer innehållande kött; Pajer innehållande fjäderfä; Pajer innehållande grönsaker; Pajer innehållande vilt; Pajer innehållande fisk; Pajer i form; Färska pajer; Pajer [söta eller salta]; Köttpajer [tillagade]; Wontons; Wraps [smörgåsar]; Kycklingwraps.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/074</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-20</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/142</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079115</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>95742</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018461569</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Proprietor - Total transfers</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>95742</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Exam deficiency</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-08</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
