<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-06-26T15:31:07</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224691</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224691</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-02</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>NASHARIA</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Произведения на изкуството и фигурки от хартия и картон, както и архитектурни макети; Декоративни и художествени материали и средства; Оборудване за изкуства, занаяти и моделиране; Филтри и филтриращи материали от хартия; Чанти и изделия за пакетиране, опаковане и съхранение от хартия, картон или пластмаса; Канцеларски и учебни материали; Средства за писане и щамповане; Средства за коригиране и изтриване; Офис машини; Оборудване за отпечатване и подвързване; Оборудване за обучение; Албуми за снимки и колекционерски албуми; Лепила за канцеларски цели и домашна употреба; Печатни произведения; Книги; Хартия и картон; Промишлена хартия и картон; Държатели за пари.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Umělecké předměty a figuríny z papíru a lepenky a architektonické modely; Nosiče a dekorační materiály a materiály pro umělce; Potřeby pro umělecké a řemeslné použití a potřeby na modelování; Papírové filtrační materiály; Pytle a balicí a obalové materiály a materiály pro skladování z papíru, lepenky nebo z plastů; Papírnické zboží a učební pomůcky; Psací potřeby a razítka; Korekční a vymazávací pomůcky; Kancelářské stroje; Tiskárenské potřeby a potřeby pro vázání knih; Vyučovací pomůcky a potřeby; Fotoalba a alba pro sběratele; Klovatina (lepidlo) pro kancelářské potřeby nebo pro domácnost; Tiskoviny; Knihy; Papír a lepenka; Papír a lepenka pro průmyslové použití; Spony na bankovky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kunstværker og statuetter af papir og pap samt arkitektmodeller; Materialer og medier til dekoration og kunst; Kunst, kunsthåndværk og modelleringsudstyr; Filtrermaterialer af papir; Poser og artikler til emballering, indpakning og opbevaring af papir, pap eller plastic; Kontor- og uddannelsesartikler; Udstyr til skrivning og stempling; Udstyr til rettelse og sletning; Kontormaskiner; Udstyr til trykning og bogbinding; Undervisningsudstyr; Foto- og samlealbums; Gummi [klæbemiddel] til papirvarer og til husholdningsbrug; Tryksager; Bøger; Papir og karton; Industripapir og -pap; Pengeholdere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Kunstwerke und Figuren aus Papier oder Pappe sowie Architekturmodelle; Dekorations- und Künstlerbedarfsmaterialien und -mittel; Kunst-, Kunsthandwerk- und Modellierausrüstung; Filtermaterial aus Papier; Filtermaterialien aus Papier; Taschen, Beutel und Waren für Verpackungs-, Einpack- und Ablagezwecke aus Papier, Pappe oder Kunststoff; Papier- und Schreibwaren sowie Lehr- und Unterrichtsmittel; Schreib- und Stempelausrüstung; Korrektur- und Radierartikel; Bürogeräte; Druck- und Buchbindeausrüstung; Lehr- und Unterrichtsausrüstung; Foto- und Sammleralben; Klebstoffe für Papier- und Schreibwaren oder für Haushaltszwecke; Druckereierzeugnisse; Bücher; Papier und Pappe; Papier und Pappe [industriell]; Banknotenhalter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Έργα τέχνης και φιγούρες από χαρτί και χαρτόνι, και αρχιτεκτονικές μακέτες· Υλικά και μέσα διακόσμησης και τέχνης· Εξοπλισμός τέχνης, χειροτεχνίας και μοντελισμού· Φίλτρα και υλικά φιλτραρίσματος από χαρτί· Τσάντες και είδη συσκευασίας, αποθήκευσης και περιτυλίγματος από χαρτί, χαρτόνι ή πλαστικό· Γραφική ύλη και εκπαιδευτικό υλικό· Εργαλεία γραψίματος και σφράγισης· Εργαλεία διόρθωσης και διαγραφής· Μηχανές γραφείου· Εξοπλισμός εκτύπωσης και βιβλιοδεσίας· Εκπαιδευτικό υλικό· Άλμπουμ φωτογραφιών και άλμπουμ για συλλέκτες· Κολλητικές ύλες για γραφική ύλη ή για οικιακούς σκοπούς· Έντυπο υλικό· Βιβλία· Χαρτί, χαρτόνι· Βιομηχανικό χαρτί και χαρτόνι· Θήκες για κράτηση χρημάτων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Works of art and figurines of paper and cardboard, and architects' models; Decoration and art materials and media; Arts, crafts and modelling equipment; Filtering materials of paper; Bags and articles for packaging, wrapping and storage of paper, cardboard or plastics; Stationery and educational supplies; Writing and stamping implements; Correcting and erasing implements; Office machines; Printing and bookbinding equipment; Educational equipment; Photo albums and collectors' albums; Gums [adhesives] for stationery or household purposes; Printed matter; Books; Paper and cardboard; Industrial paper and cardboard; Money holders.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Piezas de arte, figuras de papel y maquetas de arquitectos de papel y cartón; Materiales para arte y decoración; Artículos para creaciones artísticas, decorativas y para modelar; Filtros y materiales filtrantes de papel; Bolsas y artículos para empaquetar, envasar y almacenar, de papel, cartón y materias plásticas; Productos de papelería y material educativo; Artículos para escribir y estampar; Artículos para corregir y borrar; Máquinas de oficina; Artículos de escritura y encuadernación; Material de enseñanza; Álbumes de fotos y para coleccionistas; Gomas [colas] de papelería o para uso doméstico; Material impreso; Libros; Papel y cartón; Papel y cartón industrial; Sujetabilletes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kunstiteosed, taiesed (Paberist ja papist) ning arhitektuursed maketid; Kunsti- ja dekoreerimismaterjalid ja -vahendid; Kunsti-, käsitöö- ja modelleerimistarbed; Paberist filtermaterjalid; Paberist, papist või plastist kotid ja muud tooted pakkimiseks ja ladustamiseks; Kantseleitarbed ja õppevahendid; Kirjutus- ja tembeldusvahendid; Korrektuuri- ja kustutusvahendid; Büroomasinad; Printimis- ja raamatuköitmisvarustus; Õppevahendid; Foto- ja kollektsioonialbumid; Kummiliimid kantseleis või majapidamises kasutamiseks; Trükitooted; Raamatud; Paber ja papp; Tööstuslik paber ja papp; Rahahoidikud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Paperista ja pahvista tehdyt taideteokset ja pienoisveistokset ja arkkitehtien pienoismallit; Koriste- ja taidemateriaalit ja -välineet; Taide-, askartelu- ja muovailuvälineet; Paperista tehdyt suodatinmateriaalit; Paperista, pahvista tai muovista tehdyt pussit ja tavarat pakkaamista, käärimistä ja säilytystä varten; Paperikauppatavarat ja opetustarvikkeet; Kirjoitus- ja leimausvälineet; Korjaustarvikkeet; Konttorikoneet; Paino- ja kirjansitomisvälineet; Opetusvälineet; Valokuva-albumit ja keräilykansiot; Liimat toimisto- ja kotitalouskäyttöön; Painotuotteet; Kirjat; Paperi ja pahvi; Teollisuuspaperi ja -pahvi; Rahanpidikkeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Objets d'art, figurines en papier et en carton, maquettes d'architecture; Matériaux de décoration et d'art et supports; Équipement artistique, d'artisanat et de réalisation de maquettes; Matériel de filtrage en papier; Sacs et articles d'emballage, d'empaquetage et de stockage en papier, carton ou plastique; Papeterie et fournitures scolaires; Instruments d'écriture et de timbrage; Instruments de correction et d'effacement; Machines de bureau; Matériel pour imprimer et relier; Équipement d'enseignement; Albums photos et albums pour collectionneurs; Gommes [colles] pour la papeterie ou le ménage; Produits de l'imprimerie; Livres; Papier et carton; Papier et carton industriels; Porte-billets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Umjetnička djela i figurice od papira i kartona i arhitektonski modeli; Dekoracije i umjetnički materijali i mediji; Oprema za umjetnost, umjetnički obrt i modeliranje; Filtrirni materijali od papira; Papirnate, kartonske i plastične vreče i artikli za pakiranje, zamatanje i skladištenje; Uredski i školski pribor; Pribor za pisanje i pečatiranje; Pribor za ispravljanje i brisanje; Uredski strojevi; Oprema za tiskanje i uvezivanje; Oprema za obrazovne namjene; Albumi za fotografije i kolekcije; Ljepila za papirnate proizvode ili kućanske potrebe; Tiskani materijali; Knjige; Papir i karton; Industrijski papir i karton; Držači za novac.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Művészeti alkotások és szobrocskák papírból és kartonból, építészmodellek; Dekorációs és művészeti anyagok és hordozók; Művészeti, kézműves és modellező eszközök; Papírból készült szűrőanyagok; Papírból, kartonból vagy műanyagból készült tasakok és cikkek árucikkek csomagolásához és tárolásához; Irodai és oktatási segédanyagok; Író és bélyegző eszközök; Javító és törlő eszközök; Irodagépek; Felszerelések nyomtatáshoz és könyvkötéshez; Oktatási felszerelések; Fotóalbumok és gyűjtő albumok; Ragasztók irodai és otthoni célokra; Nyomtatványok; Könyvek; Papír és karton; Ipari papír és karton; Pénztárolók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Produzioni artistiche e statuette in carta e cartone, e plastici per architetti; Decorazioni, materiali e mezzi di produzione artistica; Attrezzature per prodotti di arte, di manifattura e di modellismo; Materiale filtrante in carta; Sacche ed articoli per imballaggio, impacchettatura e immagazzinaggio di carta, cartone o plastica; Cartoleria e materiale di insegnamento; Attrezzi per scrivere ed affrancare; Attrezzi per correggere e cancellare; Macchine per ufficio; Attrezzatura per la stampa e la legatoria; Attrezzatura per l'insegnamento; Raccoglitori per le foto e raccoglitori per collezionisti (album per foto); Adesivi per la cartoleria o per uso domestico; Stampati; Libri; Carta e cartone; Carta e cartone industriale; Portamonete e ferma banconote.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Popieriaus, kartono meno dirbiniai ir figūrėlės bei architektūriniai modeliai; Dekoravimo ir dailės medžiagos ir reikmenys; Dailės, amatų ir modeliavimo reikmenys; Filtravimo medžiagos [popierius]; Popieriniai, kartoniniai ar plastikiniai pakavimo, vyniojimo ir laikymo maišeliai ir reikmenys; Raštinės reikmenys ir mokymo priemonės; Rašymo ir antspaudavimo priemonės; Taisymo ir trynimo priemonės; Biuro technika; Spausdinimo ir knygų įrišimo įranga; Mokymo priemonės; Nuotraukų ir kolekcijų albumai; Augaliniai klijai (raštinės ar buities reikmėms); Spaudiniai; Knygos; Popierius ir kartonas; Pramoninis popierius ir kartonas; Pinigų sąvaržėlės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mākslas darbi un statuetes no papīra un kartona, arhitektūras maketi; Materiāli un līdzekļi māksliniekiem un dekoratoriem; Mākslinieku, amatnieku un maketētāju piederumi; Filtru materiāli no papīra; Papīra, kartona vai plastmasas maisi un maisiņi (somas) iepakošanai, ietīšanai vai uzglabāšanai; Kancelejas preces un izglītojoši materiāli; Rakstāmrīki un zīmogi; Korekcijas un dzēšanas rīki; Biroja tehnika; Poligrāfijas un grāmatsiešanas ierīces; Mācību aprīkojums; Kolekciju albumi un foto albumi; Sveķi (līmvielas) kancelejas un mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Iespiedprodukcija; Grāmatas; Papīrs un kartons; Rūpnieciskais papīrs un kartons; Naudas turētāji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Xogholijiet tal-arti u figurini tal-karti u l-kartunċin, u mudelli tal-periti; Materjali tad-dekorazzjoni u l-arti u l-midja; Tagħmir għall-arti, snajja u mmudellar; Materjali filtranti tal-karta; Basktijiet u oġġetti tal-karti, kartunċin jew plastiks għall-ippakkjar, tgeżwir u ħażna; Forniment ta' kartolerija u oġġetti edukattivi; Implimenti li tikteb jew tistampa bihom; Implimenti biex tikkoreġi jew tħassar bihom; Magni għall-użu fl-uffiċċju; Tagħmir għall-istampar u l-legatura; Tagħmir edukattiv; Albums tar-ritratti u albums tal-kolletturi; Adeżivi għal skopijiet ta' kartolerija jew domestiku; Materjal stampat; Kotba; Karti u kartunċin; Karta u kartunċin industrijali; Kontenituri li żżomm il-flus fihom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kunstwerken, beeldjes en maquettes van papier en karton; Decoratiemateriaal en materialen voor kunst en media; Uitrusting voor het decoreren en modelleren; Filtreermateriaal van papier; Zakken en artikelen voor verpakking, omwikkeling en bewaring van papier, karton of plastic; Kantoorbehoeften en onderwijsbenodigdheden; Schrijf- en stempelgerei; Correctie- en uitwisgerei; Kantoormachines; Drukkerij- en boekbindapparaten; Onderwijsmateriaal (uitgezonderd toestellen); Fotoalbums en verzamelalbums; Gom [lijm] voor kantoorgebruik of voor de huishouding; Drukwerken; Boeken; Papier en karton; Industrieel papier en karton; Geldklemmen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dzieła sztuki oraz figurki z papieru i kartonu, modele architektoniczne; Materiały i środki dla artystów i do dekoracji; Wyposażenie dla artystów, rzemieślników i modelarzy; Materiały filtracyjne z papieru; Torebki oraz artykuły do pakowania i przechowywania z papieru, kartonu lub tworzyw sztucznych; Materiały piśmienne i wyposażenie edukacyjne; Artykuły do pisania i stemplowania; Artykuły do korektorowania i ścierania; Maszyny biurowe; Materiały drukarskie i introligatorskie; Materiały szkoleniowe i instruktażowe; Albumy fotograficzne i kolekcjonerskie; Kleje do materiałów papierniczych lub do użytku domowego; Materiały drukowane; Książki; Papier i karton; Przemysłowy papier i karton; Spinacze do pieniędzy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Obras de arte e estatuetas de papel e cartão, e modelos de arquitetos; Materiais e utensílios para decoração e arte; Equipamento para artes, artesanatos e modelagem; Materiais de filtragem em papel; Sacos e artigos para o acondicionamento, embrulho e armazenamento de papel, cartão ou matérias plásticas; Artigos de papelaria e material escolar; Artigos para escrever e estampar; Implementos para corrigir e apagar; Máquinas de escritório; Equipamento de impressão e encadernação; Equipamento educacional; Álbuns de fotos e álbuns de coleção; Adesivos para papelaria ou uso doméstico; Material impresso; Livros; Papel e cartão; Papel e cartão industrial; Pinças para notas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Obiecte de artă și figurine din hârtie și carton și machete arhitectonice; Materiale și mijloace pentru decorare și artă; Echipament pentru arte, mesteșuguri și de modelare; Materiale pentru filtrare din hârtie; Sacoșe și articole pentru ambalare, împachetare și depozitare din hârtie, carton sau plastic; Articole de papetărie și accesorii educative; Ustensile de scris și ștampilat; Ustensile de corectare și ștergere; Mașini de birou; Echipament pentru imprimare și legare; Echipament pentru educație/învățământ; Albume foto și albume pentru colecționari; Adezivi; Produse de imprimerie; Cărți; Hârtie și carton; Hârtie și carton industriale; Suporturi pentru bani.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Umelecké diela a figúrky z papiera alebo lepenky a architektonické modely; Ozdobné a umelecké prostriedky a materiály; Potreby pre umelcov a remeselníkov, modelovacie potreby; Filtračné materiály (papier); Papierové, lepenkové alebo plastové vrecia a výrobky na balenie, obaľovanie a skladovanie; Papierenský tovar a učebné pomôcky; Písacie potreby, potreby na pečiatkovanie; Pomôcky na opravu a vymazávanie; Kancelárske stroje; Tlačiarenské a knihárske potreby; Učebné pomôcky; Albumy na fotografie a zberateľské albumy; Lepiace gumy na kancelárske použitie alebo pre domácnosť; Tlačoviny; Knihy; Papier a lepenka; Papier a lepenka pre priemysel; Sponky na bankovky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Umetniška dela in kipi iz papirja in kartona ter arhitekturne makete; Dekorativni in umetniški materiali in oprema; Pripomočki za umetnost, umetno obrt in oblikovanje; Filtrirni proizvodi iz papirja; Vrečke in proizvodi za pakiranje, zavijanje in shranjevanje iz papirja, lepenke ali plastike; Pisalne in izobraževalne potrebščine; Pisalni pripomočki in pripomočki za žigosanje; Pripomočki za korigiranje in brisanje; Pisarniški stroji; Pripomočki za tiskanje in vezavo; Izobraževalni pripomočki; Fotografski in zbirateljski albumi; Lepila za pisarniške in gospodinjske namene; Tiskovine; Knjige; Papir in lepenka; Industrijski papir in lepenka; Držala za denar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Konstföremål och figuriner av papper och kartong samt arkitektmodeller; Dekorations- och konstnärsmaterial; Utrustning för konst, hantverk och modellering; Filtreringsmaterial av papper; Påsar och artiklar för emballering, förpackning och förvaring, av papper, kartong eller plast; Pappersvaror och undervisningsmaterial; Redskap för skrift och stämpling; Redskap för korrigering och radering; Kontorsmaskiner; Utrustning för tryckning och bokbinderi; Undervisningsmaterial; Foto- och samlaralbum; Gummi [bindemedel] för kontors- eller hushållsändamål; Trycksaker; Böcker; Papper och kartong; Industriellt papper och kartong; Hållare för pengar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Обувки; Облекло; Украшения за глава, шапки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Obuv; Oděvy; Pokrývky hlavy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Fodtøj; Beklædningsgenstande; Hovedbeklædning.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Schuhwaren; Bekleidungsstücke; Kopfbedeckungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υποδήματα· Ενδύματα· Είδη πιλοποιίας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Footwear; Clothing; Headgear.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Calzado; Prendas de vestir; Artículos de sombrerería.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Jalatsid; Rõivad; Peakatted.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Jalkineet; Vaatteet; Päähineet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Chaussures; Vêtements; Chapellerie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Obuća; Odjeća; Pokrivala za glavu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Lábbelik; Ruházati cikkek; Kalapáruk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Calzature; Abbigliamento; Cappelleria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Apavas; Drabužiai, apranga; Galvos apdangalai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apavi; Apģērbi; Galvassegas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Xedd is-saqajn; Ilbies; Xedd ir-ras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Schoeisel; Kleding; Hoofddeksels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Obuwie; Odzież; Nakrycia głowy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Calçado; Vestuário; Chapelaria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Articole de încălțăminte; Articole de îmbrăcăminte; Articole pentru acoperirea capului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Obuv; Odevy; Pokrývky hlavy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Obutev; Oblačila; Pokrivala.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Fotbeklädnader; Kläder; Huvudbonader.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<SeniorityDetails>
<Seniority>
<SeniorityCountryCode>DE</SeniorityCountryCode>
<SeniorityFilingDate>2019-09-09</SeniorityFilingDate>
<SeniorityRegistrationNumber>302019229269</SeniorityRegistrationNumber>
<SeniorityRegistrationDate>2019-09-18</SeniorityRegistrationDate>
<InternationalTradeMarkCode>EU</InternationalTradeMarkCode>
<SeniorityPartialIndicator>false</SeniorityPartialIndicator>
<SeniorityStatusCode>Accepted</SeniorityStatusCode>
</Seniority>
</SeniorityDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079105</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003122843</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-06-02</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>de</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Art. 8(4)</OppositionGroundText>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>1092379</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>95257</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
