<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-28T09:52:46</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224933</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224933</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-28</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="12" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-28</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ASLDAN</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162207452</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/224/018224933/000162207452.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>01.15.21</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.11</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.13</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>05.03.14</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>28.03</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Лекарства за хуманни цели; Дезинфектанти; Дезинфектанти за хигиенни цели; Антибактериални препарати за миене на ръце; Фармацевтични препарати; Диетични вещества за медицински цели; Вагинални промивки за медицински цели; Лаксативи [разхлабителни средства]; Пакети с билкова кал за терапевтична употреба; Санитарни кърпички за еднократна употреба; Дезинфектанти импрегнирани в кърпички; Гащи, абсорбиращи, за хора, страдащи от инконтиненция; Дамски превръзки; Пелени за изпускащи се хора; Бебешки пелени.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Humánní léčiva; Dezinfekční přípravky; Dezinfekční prostředky pro hygienické účely; Antibakteriální prostředky na mytí rukou; Farmaceutické přípravky; Dietetické látky pro léčebné účely; Léčebné vaginální výplachy; Přípravky na pročištění; Bylinné pleťové masky pro terapeutické účely; Dezinfekční ubrousky; Ubrousky napuštěné dezinfekčními přípravky; Absorpční kalhotky pro inkontinentní pacienty; Hygienické vložky; Inkontinenční pleny; Dětské plenkové kalhotky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Humanmedicin; Desinfektionsmidler; Desinfektionsmidler til hygiejniske formål; Antibakterielle håndvaskemidler; Farmaceutiske præparater; Diætetiske substanser tilpasset medicinsk brug; Vaginale skyllepræparater til medicinske formål; Udtømningsmidler; Pakker indeholdende mudder med urter til terapeutiske formål; Renseservietter; Servietter imprægneret med desinfektionsmidler; Absorberende inkontinensbenklæder; Hygiejnebind; Bleer til inkontinens; Blebukser til spædbørn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Arzneimittel für humanmedizinische Zwecke; Desinfektionsmittel; Desinfektionsmittel für hygienische Zwecke; Antibakterielle Handwaschmittel; Pharmazeutische Präparate; Diätische Substanzen für medizinische Zwecke; Vaginalspülungen für medizinische Zwecke; Blutreinigende Mittel; Kräuterschlammpackungen für therapeutische Zwecke; Desinfektionstücher für medizinische Zwecke; Tücher, getränkt mit Desinfektionsmitteln; Saugfähige Inkontinenzhosen; Damenbinden; Inkontinenzwindeln; Babyhöschenwindeln.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Φάρμακα θεραπευτικά για ανθρώπινη χρήση· Απολυμαντικά· Απολυμαντικά για υγειονομική χρήση· Αντιβακτηριακά προϊόντα για το πλύσιμο των χεριών· Φαρμακευτικά (Προϊόντα -)· Διαιτητικές ουσίες προσαρμοσμένες για ιατρικές χρήσεις· Κολπικές πλύσεις για ιατρική χρήση· Καθαρτικά· Μάσκες με πηλό και βότανα, για θεραπευτικούς σκοπούς· Μαντιλάκια καθαρισμού· Απολυμαντικά εμποτισμένα σε μαντιλάκια· Κυλόττες υγιεινής για την ακράτεια· Σερβιέτες υγιεινής· Πάνες υγιεινής για την ακράτεια· Πάνες [βρεφικές πάνες].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Medicines for human purposes; Disinfectants; Disinfectants for hygiene purposes; Antibacterial handwashes; Pharmaceutical preparations; Dietetic substances adapted for medical use; Vaginal washes; Depuratives; Herbal mud packs for therapeutic use; Sanitizing wipes; Disinfectants impregnated into tissues; Pants, absorbent, for incontinence; Sanitary napkins; Diapers for incontinents; Babies' diaper-pants.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Medicamentos para uso médico; Desinfectantes; Desinfectantes para uso higiénico; Productos antibacterianos para lavar las manos; Preparaciones farmacéuticas; Sustancias dietéticas para uso médico; Duchas vaginales para uso médico; Depurativos; Mascarillas de barros fitoterapéuticos; Paños desinfectantes; Desinfectantes impregnados en tejidos; Bragas absorbentes para la incontinencia; Compresas higiénicas; Pañales higiénicos para la incontinencia; Pañales-braga para bebés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ravimid inimestele, inimeste raviks; Desinfektsioonivahendid; Hügieenilised desinfektsioonivahendid; Antibakteriaalsed kätepesuained; Farmatseutilised preparaadid; Meditsiinilised dieetained; Meditsiinilised tupeloputusvedelikud; Verepuhastid; Terapeutilised taimemudakotid; Desinfitseerivad lapid; Salvrättidesse immutatud desinfektsioonivahendid; Pidamatushaigete imavad püksikud; Hügieenisidemed; Pidamatushaigete mähkmed; Imikute mähkmepüksid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lääkkeet ihmisille; Desinfiointiaineet; Desinfiointiaineet hygieenisiin tarkoituksiin; Antibakteeriset käsienpesuliuokset; Farmaseuttiset valmisteet; Dieettivalmisteet lääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Emätinhuuhteet lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Ulostusaineet; Muta-yrttihauteet terapeuttisiin tarkoituksiin; Desinfiointipyyhkeet; Pyyhkeisiin kyllästetyt desinfiointiaineet; Pidätyskyvyttömille tarkoitetut vaippahousut, imukykyiset; Terveyssiteet; Inkontinenssivaipat; Vauvojen vaippahousut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Médicaments pour la médecine humaine; Désinfectants; Désinfectants à usage hygiénique; Produits antibactériens pour le lavage des mains; Préparations pharmaceutiques; Substances diététiques à usage médical; Bains vaginaux à usage médical; Dépuratifs; Masques de boues phytothérapeutiques; Lingettes désinfectantes; Tissus imprégnés de désinfectants; Culottes hygiéniques pour incontinents; Serviettes hygiéniques; Couches hygiéniques pour personnes incontinentes; Couches-culottes pour bébés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Lijekovi za ljudske potrebe; Dezinfekcijska sredstva; Dezinfekcijska sredstva za higijenske namjene; Antibakterijska sredstva za pranje ruku; Farmaceutski pripravci; Dijetne tvari za medicinske potrebe; Tekućine za vaginalno ispiranje za medicinske svrhe; Čišćenje (sredstva za čišćenje) [laksativi]; Biljne maske za lice na bazi zelene gline, za terapeutsku uporabu; Dezinfekcijske maramice; Sredstva za dezinfekciju impregnirana u maramicama; Upijajuće gaćice za inkontinenciju; Higijenski ulošci; Pelene za inkontinenciju; Nepromočive gaćice-pelene za bebe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Gyógyszerek humángyógyászati használatra; Fertőtlenítőszerek; Fertőtlenítőszerek higiéniai célokra; Antibakteriális kézmosók; Gyógyszerészeti készítmények; Diétás anyagok gyógyászati használatra; Hüvelyöblítők egészségügyi célokra; Hashajtók; Gyógynövényes iszappakolások terápiás célokra; Fertőtlenítő törlőkendők; Fertőtlenítőszerrel átitatott kendők; Egészségügyi nedvszívó nadrágok inkontinenciában szenvedőknek; Menstruációs betétek; Inkontinencia pelenkák; Nadrágpelenkák babáknak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Medicamenti per la medicina umana; Disinfettanti; Disinfettanti per uso igienico; Prodotti antibatterici per lavare le mani; Preparazioni farmaceutiche; Sostanze dietetiche per uso medico; Lavaggi vaginali per uso medico; Depurativi; Impacchi di fanghi alle erbe per uso terapeutico; Salviette disinfettanti; Salviette imbevute di disinfettante; Mutande igieniche per persone incontinenti; Assorbenti igienici; Pannolini igienici per persone incontinenti; Pannolini a mutandina per bebè.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vaistai (žmonėms); Dezinfekantai; Dezinfekavimo priemonės (higienos reikmėms); Antibakteriniai rankų plovimo skysčiai; Farmaciniai preparatai; Dietinės medžiagos (medicinos reikmėms); Makšties plovimo skysčiai (medicinos reikmėms); Vidurius valantys vaistai; Žolelių ir purvo kaukės gydymo reikmėms; Dezinfekuojamosios šluostės; Dezinfekavimo priemonėmis impregnuotos servetėlės; Nelaikančiųjų sugeriamosios kelnaitės [sauskelnės]; Higieniniai rankšluostukai; Nelaikančiųjų sauskelnės; Kūdikių sauskelnės-vystyklai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Medikamenti cilvēkam; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi; Dezinfekcijas līdzekļi higiēniskiem nolūkiem; Antibakteriālie roku mazgāšanas līdzekļi; Farmaceitiskie preparāti; Diētiskas vielas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Maksts skalošanas līdzekļi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Caureju veicinoši līdzekļi; Zāļu dubļu pakas ārstnieciskām vajadzībām; Dezinfekcijas drāniņas; Salvetēs impregnēti dezinfekcijas līdzekļi; Absorbējošas biksītes inkontinences gadījumiem; Sieviešu higiēniskās paketes; Pieaugušo autiņi inkontinences gadījumiem; Autiņbiksītes bērniem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Mediċini għal skopijiet umani; Diżinfettanti; Diżinfettanti għal skopijiet ta' iġjene; Ħasil tal-idejn antibatteriku; Preparazzjonijiet farmaċewtiċi; Sustanzi djetetiċi addattati għall-użu mediku; Prodotti għat-tlaħliħ vaġinali għal skopijiet mediċi; Purganti; Pakki ta' tajn erbali għal skopijiet terapewtiċi; Biċċiet tal-imsiħ għal skop ta' iġjene; Diżinfettanti mimlija ġo karti assorbenti; Qliezet assorbenti, tal-inkontinenza; Faxex tal-mestrwazzjoni; Ħrieqi għall-inkontinenza; Ħrieqi-qliezet ta' taħt tat-trabi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Geneesmiddelen voor menselijk gebruik; Desinfectiemiddelen; Desinfecterende middelen voor hygiënisch gebruik; Antibacteriële handzeep; Farmaceutische producten; Diëtische substanties voor medisch gebruik; Vaginale baden voor medische doeleinden; Bloedzuiverende middelen; Modderpakkingen met kruiden voor therapeutische doeleinden; Hygiënische doekjes; Desinfecterende middelen geïmpregneerd in tissues; Absorberende broekjes voor incontinenten; Maandverband; Luiers voor incontinenten; Luierbroekjes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Leki dla ludzi; Środki odkażające; Środki dezynfekcyjne do celów higienicznych; Antybakteryjne środki do mycia rąk; Preparaty farmaceutyczne; Dietetyczne substancje przystosowane do celów medycznych; Płyny do przemywania pochwy do celów medycznych; Środki przeczyszczające; Ziołowe preparaty błotne do celów terapeutycznych; Chusteczki odkażające; Środki dezynfekujące, którymi nasączane są chusteczki; Majtki chłonne dla osób cierpiących na inkontynencję; Podpaski higieniczne; Pieluchy dla osób cierpiących na inkontynencję; Pieluchomajtki dziecięce.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Medicamentos para a medicina humana; Desinfetantes; Desinfetantes para uso higiénico; Preparações antibacterianas de lavagem de mãos; Preparações farmacêuticas; Substâncias dietéticas para uso medicinal; Banhos vaginais para fins medicinais; Depurativos; Envolvimentos com lamas para uso fitoterapêutico; Toalhetes higiénicos; Desinfetantes impregnados em lenços; Cuecas absorventes para incontinência; Toalhas higiénicas; Fraldas higiénicas para incontinência; Fraldas-calça para bebés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Remedii pentru medicina umană; Dezinfectante; Dezinfectante folosite pentru igienă; Soluții antibacteriene pentru spălarea mâinilor; Preparate farmaceutice; Dietetice (substanțe - de uz medical); Spălături vaginale de uz medical; Laxative; Pachete cu nămol și plante de uz terapeutic; Șervețele dezinfectante; Substanțe dezinfectante impregnate în șervețele; Chiloți absorbanți pentru incontinență; Prosoape sanitare; Incontinență (Scutece igienice pentru -); Scutece chiloței pentru bebeluși.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Lieky pre humánnu medicínu; Dezinfekčné prípravky; Dezinfekčné prípravky na hygienické použitie; Antibakteriálne tekuté mydlá; Farmaceutické prípravky; Diétne látky na lekárske použitie; Vaginálne kúpele na lekárske použitie; Preháňadlá; Bylinné bahenné zábaly na terapeutické účely; Dezinfekčné utierky; Dezinfekčné prípravky impregnované do tkanín; Absorpčné nohavičky pre osoby postihnuté inkontinenciou; Hygienické obrúsky; Hygienické vložky pre osoby postihnuté inkontinenciou; Detské plienkové nohavičky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zdravila za ljudi; Razkužila; Razkužila za higienske namene; Antibakterijska čistila za roke; Farmacevtski pripravki; Dietetične snovi za medicinsko uporabo; Vaginalna izpirala za medicinske namene; Laksativi; Vrečke z zeliščnim blatom za terapevtsko uporabo; Dezinfekcijski robčki; Robčki, prepojeni z razkužilom; Vpojne hlačke za inkontinenco; Menstruacijski vložki; Plenice za osebe z inkontinenco; Hlačne plenice za dojenčke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Läkemedel för humana ändamål; Desinfektionsmedel; Desinfektionsmedel för hygieniska ändamål; Antibakteriella handtvättmedel; Farmaceutiska preparat; Dietiska ämnen för medicinska ändamål; Preparat för vaginal hygien för medicinska ändamål; Renande laxermedel; Lerinpackning med örter för terapibruk; Steriliserande torkservetter; Servetter impregnerade med desinfektionsmedel; Byxblöjor för inkontinens; Dambindor; Blöjor för inkontinens; Blöjbyxor för spädbarn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Санитарни маски за медицински цели; Маски за медицински персонал; Стерилни чаршафи [хирургия]; Ръкавици за медицински цели; Хирургически стерилни покривки за операции; Меки подложки за пристягане на корема; Термометри за медицински цели; Облекло специално за операционни зали; Оборудване за физиотерапия; Медицински апарати и инструменти; Ортопедични изделия; Апарати за масаж; Подложки за медицински цели; Специална мебелировка за медицински цели; Бебешки шишета.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Hygienické masky pro lékařské účely; Roušky pro lékařský personál; Chirurgická sterilní prostěradla; Rukavice pro lékařské účely; Operační roušky; Břišní podložky; Teploměry pro lékařské účely; Oděvy určené pro operační sály; Fyzioterapeutické přístroje; Lékařské přístroje a nástroje; Ortopedické potřeby; Masážní přístroje; Podušky pro lékařské účely; Speciální nábytek pro lékařské účely; Dětské láhve.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sanitære masker til medicinske formål; Masker til brug for medicinsk personel; Sterile lagner, kirurgiske; Handsker til medicinske formål; Kirurgiske afdækningsstykker; Underlivsbandager; Termometre til medicinsk brug; Beklædning specielt til operationsstuer; Udstyr til fysisk terapi; Medicinske apparater og instrumenter; Ortopædiske artikler; Massageapparater; Puder til medicinske formål; Møbler, specielt udformede til medicinske formål; Sutteflasker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Mundschutz für medizinische Zwecke; Masken für medizinisches Personal; Sterile Tücher für Operationen; Handschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Operationstücher; Unterleibspelotten; Thermometer für medizinische Zwecke; OP-Kleidung; Geräte für physikalische Therapie; Medizinische Apparate und Instrumente; Orthopädische Artikel; Massagegeräte; Kissen für medizinische Zwecke; Spezialmöbel für medizinische Zwecke; Saugflaschen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μάσκες υγιεινής για ιατρική χρήση· Μάσκες για το ιατρικό προσωπικό· Αποστειρωμένα σεντόνια, χειρουργικά· Γάντια ιατρικής χρήσης· Σεντόνια χειρουργικά· Επιθέματα υπογάστρια· Θερμόμετρα ιατρικά· Ενδύματα (Ειδικά για χειρουργεία -)· Εξοπλισμός φυσικοθεραπείας· Ιατρικά (Συσκευές και όργανα -)· Ορθοπεδικά είδη· Συσκευές μασαζ· Μαξιλάρια για χρήση ιατρική· Επίπλωση ειδική ιατρικής χρήσης· Υποδοχείς για θήλαστρα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Sanitary masks for medical purposes; Medical masks; Sterile sheets, surgical; Gloves for medical purposes; Surgical drapes; Abdominal pads; Masks for use by medical personnel; Thermometers for medical purposes; Clothing especially for operating rooms; Physiotherapy apparatus; Medical apparatus and instruments; Orthopaedic articles; Massage apparatus; Cushions for medical purposes; Furniture especially made for medical purposes; Babies' bottles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Mascarillas sanitarias para uso médico; Mascarillas para personal médico; Campos quirúrgicos [sábanas estériles]; Guantes para uso médico; Sábanas quirúrgicas; Almohadillas abdominales; Termómetros para uso médico; Ropa especial para quirófano; Equipos de terapia física; Aparatos e instrumentos médicos; Artículos ortopédicos; Aparatos de masaje; Cojines para uso médico; Mobiliario especial para uso médico; Biberones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Meditsiinilised hügieenilised maskid; Maskid meditsiinipersonalile; Kirurgias kasutatavad steriilsed linad; Meditsiinilised kindad; Kirurgilised steriilsed riided; Kõhupadjad; Meditsiinilised termomeetrid; Eririietus operatsioonisaalides viibimiseks, operatsiooniriietus; Füsioteraapiaseadmed; Meditsiiniseadmed ja -riistad; Ortopeediatooted, ortopeedilised tooted; Massaažiaparaadid; Meditsiinilised padjad; Meditsiiniline mööbel; Lutipudelid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Saniteettinaamarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Suojanaamarit lääkintähenkilökuntaa varten; Steriloidut lakanat [kirurgiset]; Käsineet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Leikkausliinat; Palleatyynyt; Kuumemittarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Vaatteet leikkaussaleja varten, erikoisvalmisteiset; Fysioterapiassa käytettävät välineet; Lääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Ortopediset välineet; Hierontalaitteet; Tyynyt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Huonekalut (erikoisvalmisteiset), lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Tuttipullot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Masques d'hygiène à usage médical; Masques utilisés par le personnel médical; Champs opératoires [draps stériles]; Gants à usage médical; Draps chirurgicaux; Pelotes hypogastriques; Thermomètres à usage médical; Vêtements spéciaux pour salles d'opération; Équipement de thérapie physique; Appareils et instruments médicaux; Articles orthopédiques; Appareils de massage; Coussins à usage médical; Mobilier spécial à usage médical; Biberons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sanitarne maske za medicinske svrhe; Maske za medicinsko osoblje; Sterilne plahte, kirurške; Rukavice za medicinsku uporabu; Plahte za kirurške potrebe; Jastučići za donji trbuh; Toplomjeri za medicinske potrebe; Specijalna odjeća za operacijske dvorane; Oprema za fizikalnu terapiju; Medicinski uređaji i instrumenti; Ortopedski artikli; Uređaji za masažu; Jastuci za medicinske potrebe; Namještaj posebno izrađen za medicinsku uporabu; Spremnici dječjih bočica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Gyógyászati célú egészségügyi maszkok; Maszkok egészségügyi személyzet általi használatra; Steril sebészeti lepedők; Kesztyűk gyógyászati használatra; Sebészeti lepedők; Hasi kötések; Hőmérők gyógyászati célokra; Speciális műtőruházat; Fizikoterápiás készülékek; Gyógyászati készülékek és eszközök; Ortopédiai cikkek; Masszázsberendezések; Párnák gyógyászati használatra; Speciálisan gyógyászati használatra készült bútorok; Cumisüvegtartók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Maschere igieniche per uso medico; Maschere utilizzate dal personale medico; Lenzuola sterili per uso nel campo operatorio; Guanti per uso medico; Lenzuola chirurgiche; Compresse ipogastriche; Termometri per uso medico; Vestiti speciali per sale operatorie; Attrezzatura per terapie fisiche; Apparecchi e strumenti medici; Articoli ortopedici; Apparecchi per il massaggio; Cuscini per uso medico; Mobilia speciale per uso medico; Poppatoi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Higieninės kaukės (medicinos reikmėms); Kaukės medicinos personalui; Steriliosios paklodės [chirurgija]; Pirštinės (medicinos reikmėms); Chirurginiai drabužiai; Pilvo pagalvėlės; Medicininiai termometrai; Specialieji operaciniai drabužiai; Fizioterapijos įranga; Medicinos aparatai ir instrumentai; Ortopedijos gaminiai; Masažavimo aparatai; Medicininės pagalvėlės; Baldai (medicinos reikmėms); Žindymo buteliukai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Sanitārās maskas medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Medicīnas personālam paredzētās maskas; Sterili palagi ķirurģiskiem nolūkiem; Cimdi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Ķirurģiskie pārklāji; Abdominālās paketes; Medicīniskie termometri; Speciālie apģērbi operāciju zālēs; Fizikālās terapijas iekārtas; Medicīniskā aparatūra un instrumenti; Ortopēdiskās preces; Masāžas aparāti; Medicīniskie spilveni; Mēbeles medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Barošanas pudelītes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Maskri sanitarji għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri għal personal mediku; Lożor sterilizzati (kirurġiċi); Ingwanti għal skopijiet mediċi; Lożor bħala għata għal waqt operazzjonijiet kirurġiċi; Kuxxinetti addominali; Termometri għal skopijiet mediċi; Ilbies speċjali għas-swali tal-operazzjonijiet; Tagħmir għat-terapija fiżika; Apparat u strumenti mediċi; Oġġetti ortopediċi; Apparat għall-massaġġi; Kuxxini għal skopijiet mediċi; Għamara magħmula apposta għal skopijiet mediċi; Reċipjenti bħala fliexken għat-tmigħ tat-trabi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Hygiënische maskers voor medisch gebruik; Maskers te gebruiken door medisch personeel; Operatielakens, steriel; Handschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Chirurgische lakens; Drukkussentjes voor de onderbuik; Thermometers voor medisch gebruik; Operatiekleding; Fysiotherapeutische apparatuur; Medische apparaten en instrumenten; Orthopedische artikelen; Massageapparaten; Kussens voor medisch gebruik; Speciaal meubilair voor medisch gebruik; Zuigflessen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Maski sanitarne do celów medycznych; Maski stosowane przez personel medyczny; Prześcieradła sterylne chirurgiczne; Rękawice do celów medycznych; Okrycia chirurgiczne; Podkładki podbrzuszne; Termometry do celów medycznych; Odzież specjalna używana w salach operacyjnych; Urządzenia i przyrządy do fizjoterapii; Urządzenia i instrumenty medyczne; Artykuły ortopedyczne; Urządzenia do masażu; Poduszki do celów medycznych; Meble wykonane specjalnie do celów medycznych; Pojemniki na butelki do karmienia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máscaras higiénicas para uso médico; Máscaras para pessoal médico; Lençóis esterilizados para cirurgia; Luvas para uso médico; Lençóis para cirurgia; Almofadas hipogástricas; Termómetros para uso médico; Vestuário especial para salas de operação; Equipamento de fisioterapia; Aparelhos e instrumentos médicos; Artigos ortopédicos; Aparelhos de massagem; Almofadas para uso medicinal; Mobiliário especial para uso médico; Biberons [biberões].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Măşti sanitare de uz medical; Măști utilizate de personalul medical; Câmpuri operatorii sterile, chirurgicale; Mănuși de uz medical; Cearceafuri chirurgicale; Comprese abdominale; Termometre de uz medical; Haine speciale pentru săli de operație; Echipament pentru exerciții fizice; Aparate și instrumente medicale; Articole ortopedice; Aparate de masaj; Perne de uz medical; Mobilier special de uz medical; Recipiente pentru biberoane.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Sanitárne masky na lekárske účely; Rúška (pre nemocničný personál); Chirurgické, sterilné plachty; Rukavice na lekárske použitie; Chirurgické plachty; Podbruškové vatované ochranné vložky; Lekárske teplomery; Odevy do operačných sál; Fyzioterapeutické zariadenia; Lekárske prístroje a nástroje; Ortopedické pomôcky; Masážne prístroje; Podušky na lekárske použitie; Nábytok špeciálne na lekárske použitie; Detské fľaše.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Higienske maske za medicinske namene; Maske za medicinsko osebje; Kirurške sterilizirane rjuhe; Rokavice za medicinske namene; Kirurške rjuhe; Trebušne komprese; Termometri za medicinske namene; Posebna oblačila za operacijske prostore; Naprave za fizikalno terapijo; Medicinski aparati in instrumenti; Ortopedski izdelki; Masažne naprave; Blazine za medicinske namene; Posebej izdelano pohištvo za medicinske namene; Posodice za stekleničke za hranjenje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Sanitetsmasker för medicinska ändamål; Munskydd för medicinsk personal; Sterila lakan (kirurgiska); Handskar för medicinska ändamål; Kirurgiska skynken; Bråckbandskuddar; Termometrar för medicinska ändamål; Kläder för användning i operationsrum; Utrustning för fysioterapi; Medicinska apparater och instrument; Konstgjorda lemmar, ögon och tänder; Massageapparater; Kuddar för medicinska ändamål; Specialmöbler för medicinska ändamål; Nappflaskor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/073</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-17</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079141</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>80927</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
