<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-03T12:28:04</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224692</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224692</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-30</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-03</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ECO-WORTHY</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>7</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Електрически косачки за трева; Бензинови косачки за трева; Косачки за живи плетове [машини]; Електрически триони; Линеен задвижващ механизъм [механичен]; Въздушни турбини; Алтернатори [генератори за променлив ток]; Генератори на постоянен ток; Електрически генератори със слънчеви клетки; Мобилни генератори за електрическо захранване; Преносими електрически генератори на електричество; Пробивни глави [части на машини]; Резбонарезни машини; 3D принтери; Въздушни помпи; Центробежни помпи; Циркулационни помпи; Електрически помпи; Винтови помпи; Водни помпи; Помпи, работещи със сгъстен въздух.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Elektrické sekačky na trávu; Benzinové sekačky na trávu; Nůžky na stříhání živých plotů (stroje); Elektrické pily; Lineární aktuátory (mechanické); Větrné turbíny; Alternátory; Generátory stejnosměrného proudu; Elektrické generátory využívající solární články; Mobilní generátory elektrické energie; Přenosné generátory elektrické energie; Vrtací hlavy [části strojů]; Závitořezy (stroje); 3D tiskárny; Vzduchová čerpadla; Odstředivá čerpadla; Oběhová čerpadla; Elektrická čerpadla; Šroubová čerpadla; Vodní čerpadla; Čerpadla na stlačený vzduch.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Elektriske plæneklippere; Benzindrevne plæneklippere; Hækkeklippere [maskiner]; Eldrevne save; Lineære aktuatorer [mekaniske]; Vindmøller; Vekselstrømsgeneratorer; Jævnstrømsgeneratorer; Elektriske generatorer der anvender solceller; Mobile elektriske generatorer; Transportable elgeneratorer; Borespidser [dele af maskiner]; Gevindskærere [maskiner]; 3D-printere; Luftpumper; Centrifugalpumper; Cirkulationspumper; Elektriske pumper; Skruepumper; Vandpumper; Trykluftpumper.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Elektrische Rasenmäher; Benzinbetriebene Rasenmäher; Heckenscheren [Maschinen]; Motorsägen; Linearaktoren [mechanische]; Windturbinen; Wechselstromgeneratoren; Gleichstromdynamos; Elektrische Generatoren mit Solarzellen; Mobile Stromgeneratoren; Tragbare Elektrogeneratoren; Bohrköpfe [Maschinenteile]; Nadeleinfädler [Maschinen]; 3D-Drucker; Luftpumpen; Zentrifugalpumpen; Umwälzpumpen; Elektropumpen; Schneckenpumpen; Wasserpumpen; Druckluftpumpen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ηλεκτρικά χλοοκοπτικά· Χλοοκοπτικές μηχανές βενζίνης· Ψαλίδια μπορντούρας [μηχανές]· Μηχανοκίνητα πριόνια· Γραμμικοί ενεργοποιητές [μηχανικοί]· Ανεμογεννήτριες· Εναλλακτήρες· Γεννήτριες συνεχούς ρεύματος· Ηλεκτρικές γεννήτριες με χρήση ηλιακών κυττάρων· Φορητές γεννήτριες παραγωγής ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος· Φορητές γεννήτριες παραγωγής ηλεκτρικής ισχύος· Στεφάνες βυθομέτρησης [μέρη μηχανών]· Βελονοπεραστές [μηχανές]· Τρισδιάστατοι εκτυπωτές· Αεραντλίες· Φυγοκεντρικές αντλίες· Αντλίες κυκλοφορίας· Ηλεκτρικές αντλίες· Κοχλιωτές αντλίες· Υδραντλίες· Αέρα πεπιεσμένου (Αντλίες -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Electric lawnmowers; Gasoline lawn mowers; Hedge trimmers [machines]; Power saws; Linear actuators [mechanical]; Wind turbines; Alternators; Direct current generators; Electrical generators using solar cells; Mobile electrical power generators; Portable electric power generators; Drilling heads [parts of machines]; Threaders [machines]; 3D printers; Air pumps; Centrifugal pumps; Circulating pumps; Electrical pumps; Screw pumps; Water pumps; Compressed air pumps.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cortacéspedes eléctricos; Cortadoras de césped a gasolina; Máquinas para podar setos [máquinas]; Sierras eléctricas; Actuadores lineales [mecánicos]; Turbinas eólicas; Alternadores; Generadores de corriente continua; Generadores eléctricos que usan células solares; Generadores móviles de energía eléctrica; Generadores de energía eléctrica portátiles; Coronas de sondeo [partes de máquinas]; Roscadoras [máquinas]; Impresoras 3D; Bombas de aire; Bombas centrífugas; Bombas de circulación; Bombas eléctricas; Bombas de tornillo; Bombas de agua; Bombas de aire comprimido.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Elektrilised muruniidukid; Bensiinimootoriga muruniidukid; Hekitrimmerid [masinad]; Mootorsaed; Mehaanilised lineaarajamid; Tuulegeneraatorid; Vahelduvvoolugeneraatorid; Alalisvoolugeneraatorid, elektrigeneraatorid; Päikeseelemente kasutavad elektrigeneraatorid; Mobiilsed elektrigeneraatorid; Teisaldatavad elektrigeneraatorid; Puuripead [masinaosad]; Keermelõikurid [seadmed]; 3D-printerid; Õhupumbad; Tsentrifugaalpumbad; Ringluspumbad; Elektripumbad; Vintpumbad; Veepumbad; Suruõhupumbad, pneumopumbad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sähkökäyttöiset ruohonleikkurit; Bensiinikäyttöiset ruohonleikkurit; Pensasaitasakset (koneet); Moottorisahat; Lineaariset toimilaitteet [mekaaniset]; Tuuliturbiinit; Vaihtovirtageneraattorit; DC-generaattorit; Aurinkokennoja käyttävät sähkögeneraattorit; Siirrettävät sähkögeneraattorit; Kannettavat sähkögeneraattorit; Poran päät [koneiden osina]; Kierteityssorvit [koneet]; 3D-tulostimet; Ilmapumput; Keskipakopumput; Kierrätyspumput; Sähköpumput; Ruuvipumput; Vesipumput; Paineilmapumput.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Tondeuses à gazon électriques; Tondeuses à gazon à essence; Taille-haies [machines]; Scies électriques; Actionneurs linéaires [mécaniques]; Éoliennes; Alternateurs; Générateurs de courant continu; Générateurs électriques utilisant des cellules solaires; Générateurs électriques mobiles; Générateurs d'énergie électrique portatifs; Couronnes de sondage [parties de machines]; Taraudeuses [machines]; Imprimantes tridimensionnelles; Pompes à air comprimé; Pompes centrifuges; Pompes de circulation; Pompes électriques; Pompes à vis; Pompes à eau; Pompes à air comprimé.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Električne kosilice za travu; Benzinske kosilice; Rezači živice [strojevi]; Električne pile; Linearni aktuatori [mehanički]; Turbine na vjetar; Alternatori; Generatori istosmjerne struje; Električni generatori koji se koriste solarnim ćelijama; Pokretni generatori električne energije; Prijenosni generatori električne energije; Krune za sondiranje [dijelovi strojeva]; Narezivači navoja [strojevi]; 3D pisači; Zračne pumpe; Centrifugalne crpke; Cirkulacijske pumpe; Električne pumpe; Vijčane pumpe; Pumpe za vodu; Zračne crpke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Elektromos fűnyírók; Benzines fűnyírók; Sövénynyírók [gépek]; Motoros fűrészek; Lineáris működtető egységek [mechanikus]; Szélturbinák; Váltakozó áramú generátorok; Egyenáramú generátorok; Napelemeket használó elektromos generátorok; Mobil elektromos áramfejlesztők; Hordozható elektromos áramfejlesztők; Fúrófejek [gépalkatrészek]; Menetvágók [gépek]; 3D nyomtatók; Levegőszivattyúk; Centrifugál szivattyúk; Keringető szivattyúk; Elektromos szivattyúk; Csavarszivattyúk; Vízpumpák, vízszivattyúk; Sűrített levegős szivattyúk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Tosaerba elettrici; Tosaerba a benzina; Tosasiepi [macchine]; Seghe elettriche; Attuatori lineari [meccanici]; Turbine eoliche; Alternatori; Generatori di corrente continua; Generatori elettrici che utilizzano pile fotovoltaiche; Generatori mobili di energia elettrica; Generatori d'energia elettrica portatili; Corone di sonda [parti di macchine]; Infila aghi [macchine]; Stampanti 3D; Pompe ad aria; Pompe centrifughe; Pompe di circolazione; Pompe elettriche; Pompe a vite; Pompe per l'acqua; Pompe ad aria compressa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektrinės vejos pjovimo mašinos; Benzininės vejapjovės; Gyvatvorių genėtuvai [mašinos]; Juostiniai pjūklai; Tiesiaeigiai vykdomieji įtaisai [mechaniniai]; Vėjo turbinos; Kintamosios srovės generatoriai; Nuolatinės srovės generatoriai; Elektros generatoriai, naudojantys saulės elementus; Kilnojamieji elektros energijos generatoriai; Nešiojamieji elektros generatoriai; Gręžimo galvutės [mašinų dalys]; Sriegimo staklės [mašinos]; 3D spausdintuvai; Oro siurbliai (pompos); Išcentriniai siurbliai; Cirkuliaciniai siurbliai; Elektriniai siurbliai; Sraigtiniai siurbliai; Vandens siurbliai; Pneumatiniai siurbliai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elektriskās mauriņa pļaujmašīnas; Zālāja pļaujmašīnas ar benzīna dzinēju; Dzīvžogu trimeri (mašīnas); Motorzāģi; Lineārie aktuatori [mehāniski]; Vēja turbīnas; Maiņstrāvas ģeneratori; Līdzstrāvas ģeneratori; Saules elementu elektroģeneratori; Mobilie elektroģeneratori; Pārvietojami elektriskās strāvas ģeneratori; Urbju galviņas (mašīnu daļas); Vītņu griešanas darbagalds; Trīsdimensiju printeri; Gaisa sūkņi; Centrbēdzes sūkņi; Cirkulācijas sūkņi; Elektriskie sūkņi; Vītņsūkņi; Ūdens sūkņi; Saspiesta gaisa sūkņi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Magni elettriċi għall-qtugħ tal-ħaxix fil-lôn; Magni għall-qtugħ tal-lon li jaħdmu bil-petrol; Tagħmir għall-ittrimmjar ta' ħitan tal-ħaxix [magni]; Segi; Attwaturi lineari [mekkaniċi]; Turbini tar-riħ; Alternaturi; Ġeneraturi tal-kurrent dirett; Ġeneraturi elettriċi li jużaw ċelloli solari; Ġeneraturi tal-enerġija elettrika mobbli; Ġeneraturi tal-enerġija elettrika li jistgħu jinġarru; Irjus ta' għodod tat-titqib [partijiet ta' magni]; Qtugħ ta' kamin [Magni għall- -]; Stampaturi 3D; Pompi tal-arja; Pompi ċentrifugi; Pompi ċirkulanti; Pompi tal-elettriku; Pompi spirali; Pompi tal-ilma; Pompi tal-arja kompressata.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Grasmaaiers (Elektrische -); Benzinegrasmaaiers; Heggenscharen [machines]; Kettingzagen; Aandrijvers (rechtlijnige -) [mechanisch]; Windmolens [turbines]; Wisselstroomdynamo's; Gelijkstroomgeneratoren; Generatoren (Elektrische -) die gebruik maken van zonnecellen; Generatoren (Mobiele -) voor het opwekken van elektriciteit; Draagbare stroomopwekkers; Boorkronen voor proefboringen [machine-onderdelen]; Naald (instrumentjes voor het trekken van garen door het oog van een -) [machines]; 3D-printers; Luchtdrukpompen; Centrifugaalpompen; Circulatiepompen; Elektrische pompen; Schroefpompen; Waterpompen; Luchtdrukpompen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Elektryczne kosiarki do trawy; Kosiarki spalinowe; Nożyce do żywopłotów [maszyny]; Piły o napędzie innym niż ręczny; Siłowniki liniowe [mechaniczne]; Turbiny wiatrowe; Alternatory [generatory prądu przemiennego]; Prądnice prądu stałego; Generatory prądu wykorzystujące ogniwa słoneczne; Przenośne generatory prądu elektrycznego; Przenośne generatory energii elektrycznej; Głowice wiertarskie [części maszyn]; Gwintownice [maszyny]; Drukarki 3D; Pompy powietrza; Pompy odśrodkowe; Pompy obiegowe; Pompy elektryczne; Pompy śrubowe; Pompy wodne; Pompy na sprężone powietrze.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cortadores de relva elétricos; Cortadores de relva a gasolina; Máquinas para aparar sebes; Serras elétricas; Atuadores lineares [mecânicos]; Turbinas eólicas; Alternadores; Geradores de corrente contínua; Geradores elétricos que utilizam células solares; Geradores móveis de energia elétrica; Geradores portáteis de energia elétrica; Coroas de sondagem [partes de máquinas]; Máquinas de enroscar; Impressoras 3D; Bombas de ar; Bombas centrífugas; Bombas de circulação; Bombas elétricas; Bombas de parafuso; Bombas de água; Bombas de ar comprimido.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Mașini electrice de tăiat iarba; Mașini de tuns iarba, alimentate cu benzină; Mașini de tuns gardul viu [mașini]; Ferăstraie; Elemente de acționare liniare [mecanice]; Turbine eoliene; Alternatoare; Generatoare de curent continuu; Generatoare electrice care folosesc celule solare; Generatoare electrice mobile; Generatoare electrice portabile; Coroane de foraj [organe de mașini]; Mașini de filetat; Imprimante 3D; Pompe de aer; Pompe centrifuge; Pompe de circulație; Pompe electrice; Pompe cu spirală; Pompe de apă; Pompe de aer comprimat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Elektrické kosačky na trávu; Benzínové kosačky na trávniky; Prístroje na strihanie živých plotov [stroje]; Reťazové píly; Lineárne ovládače [mechanické]; Veterné turbíny; Alternátory; Generátory jednosmerného prúdu; Elektrické generátory využívajúce solárne články; Mobilné generátory elektrickej energie; Prenosné elektrické generátory; Vŕtacie hlavy (časti strojov); Rezače závitov [stroje]; 3D tlačiarne; Vzduchové čerpadlá; Odstredivé čerpadlá; Cirkulačné čerpadlá; Elektrické čerpadlá; Závitovkové čerpadlo; Vodné pumpy; Čerpadlá na stlačený vzduch.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Električne kosilnice; Bencinske kosilnice za travo; Obrezovalniki žive meje [stroji]; Žage s pogonom; Linearni aktuatorji [mehanski]; Vetrne turbine; Alternatorji; Generatorji enosmerne napetosti; Električni generatorji, ki uporabljajo sončne celice; Mobilni električni generatorji; Prenosni generatorji električne energije; Vrtalne glave [deli strojev]; Vrezovalniki navojev [stroji]; 3D-tiskalniki; Zračne črpalke; Centrifugalne črpalke; Cirkulacijske črpalke; Električne črpalke; Vijačne črpalke; Vodne črpalke; Črpalke na stisnjen zrak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Elektriska gräsklippare; Bensindrivna gräsklippare; Häcksaxar [maskiner]; Elektriska sågar; Linjära manöverdon [mekaniska]; Vindturbiner; Växelströmsgeneratorer; Likströmsgeneratorer; Elektriska generatorer som använder solceller; Mobila elektriska strömgeneratorer; Bärbara elektriska kraftgeneratorer; Borrhuvuden [maskindelar]; Nålpåträdare [maskiner]; 3D-skrivare; Luftpumpar; Centrifugalpumpar; Cirkulationspumpar; Elektriska pumpar; Skruvpumpar; Vattenpumpar; Tryckluftspumpar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Акумулатори за фотоволтаична енергия; Литиево-йонни батерии; Презареждащи се батерии; Слънчеви батерии; Преносими соларни панели за генериране на електроенергия; Слънчева фотоклетка за превръщане на слънчева светлина в електроенергия; Зарядно устройство на слънчеви батерии; Устройства за зареждане на акумулатори за моторни превозни средства; Кутии за батерии; Електрически батерии за захранване на електрически превозни средства; Акумулатори за автомобили; Кабели за батерии; Кристално-силициеви соларни клетки; Фотоелектрически апарати и съоръжения за генериране на слънчева електроенергия; Акумулатори за превозни средства; Зарядни устройства; Пластини за батерии; Акумулаторни клетки; Слънчеви батерии за домашна употреба; Слънчеви панели за производство на електричество.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Akumulátory pro fotovoltaickou energii; Lithium-iontové baterie; Dobíjecí baterie; Solární baterie; Přenosné solární panely na výrobu elektřiny; Solární články na výrobu elektrického proudu; Nabíječky solárních baterií; Nabíječky baterií pro motorová vozidla; Akumulátorové skříně; Elektrické baterie na pohánění elektrických vozidel; Baterie do automobilů; Kabely pro baterie; Krystalické silikonové solární energetické články; Fotoelektrické přístroje a zařízení pro výrobu elektřiny ze sluneční energie; Baterie do vozidel; Nabíječky baterií; Desky do akumulátorů (baterií); Dobíjecí články; Solární baterie k použití v domácnost; Solární panely na výrobu elektřiny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Akkumulatorer til fotovoltaisk energi; Litiumionbatterier; Genopladelige batterier; Solbatterier; Bærbare solpaneler til generering af elektricitet; Solceller til generering af elektricitet; Solbatteriopladere; Batteriopladere til motorkøretøjer; Akkumulatorkasser; Elektriske batterier til strømforsyning til elektriske køretøjer; Bilbatterier; Batterikabler; Krystallinske siliciumsolceller; Fotovoltaiske apparater og installationer til generering af solelektricitet; Batterier til køretøjer; Opladere til batterier; Plader til batterier; Genopladelige celler; Solbatterier til husholdningsbrug; Solpaneler til elproduktion.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Akkumulatoren für Solarenergie; Lithiumionen-Batterien; Wiederaufladbare Batterien; Sonnenbatterien; Tragbare Solarbatterien zur Erzeugung von Elektrizität; Solarzellen für die Stromerzeugung; Solarbatterieladegeräte; Batterieladegeräte für Kraftfahrzeuge; Akkumulatorenkästen; Elektrische Batterien für die Stromversorgung von Elektrofahrzeugen; Autobatterien; Batteriekabel; Kristalline Silizium-Solarzellen; Photovoltaische Geräte und Anlagen zur Erzeugung von Solarstrom; Akkumulatoren für Fahrzeuge; Ladegeräte für Batterien; Platten für elektrische Akkumulatoren; Wiederaufladbare Batteriezellen; Solarbatterien für den Haushalt; Solarmodule für die Stromerzeugung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσσωρευτές για φωτοβολταϊκή ισχύ· Μπαταρίες ιόντων λιθίου· Επαναφορτιζόμενες μπαταρίες· Συσσωρευτές ηλιακοί· Φορητοί ηλιακοί συλλέκτες για παραγωγή ηλεκτρισμού· Φωτοβολταϊκή κυψελίδα για την παραγωγή ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος· Ηλιακοί φορτιστές μπαταριών· Διατάξεις φόρτισης μπαταριών για μηχανοκίνητα οχήματα· Συσσωρευτών (Κιβώτια -)· Ηλεκτρικές μπαταρίες για παροχή ισχύος σε ηλεκτρικά οχήματα· Μπαταρίες αυτοκινήτων· Καλώδια μπαταρίας· Ηλιακά στοιχεία ισχύος κρυσταλλικού πυριτίου· Φωτοβολταϊκές συσκευές και εγκαταστάσεις για την παραγωγή ηλιακής ηλεκτρικής ενέργειας· Συσσωρευτές ηλεκτρικοί οχημάτων· Φορτιστές μπαταριών· Συσσωρευτών ηλεκτρικών (Πλάκες -)· Επαναφορτιζόμενα στοιχεία· Ηλιακές μπαταρίες για οικιακή χρήση· Φωτοβολταϊκά πλαίσια για παραγωγή ηλεκτρισμού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Accumulators for photovoltaic power; Lithium ion batteries; Rechargeable batteries; Solar batteries; Portable solar panels for generating electricity; Solar cells for electricity generation; Solar battery chargers; Battery charging devices for motor vehicles; Battery boxes; Electric batteries for powering electric vehicles; Car batteries; Battery leads; Crystalline silicon solar power cells; Photovoltaic apparatus and installations for generating solar electricity; Batteries for vehicles; Battery chargers; Plates for batteries; Rechargeable cells; Solar batteries for domestic use; Solar panels for the production of electricity.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Acumuladores para la energía fotovoltaica; Baterías de iones de litio; Baterías recargables; Pilas solares; Paneles solares portátiles para generar electricidad; Células solares para la producción de electricidad; Cargadores de pilas solares; Dispositivos de carga de baterías para vehículos a motor; Cajas de acumuladores; Baterías eléctricas para activar vehículos eléctricos; Baterías para coches; Cables de batería; Células de energía solar de silicio cristalino; Aparatos e instalaciones fotovoltaicos para la generación de electricidad solar; Baterías para vehículos; Cargadores de pilas y baterías; Placas para acumuladores eléctricos; Células recargables; Baterías solares para uso doméstico; Paneles solares para producir electricidad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Fotogalvaanilise päikeseenergia akud; Liitiumioonakud; Akupatareid; Päikesepatareid; Teisaldatavad päikesepaneelid elektrienergia tekitamiseks; Päikeseelemendid elektri tootmiseks; Päikeseenergial toimivad akulaadijad; Mootorsõidukite akulaadurid; Akuanumad; Elektrisõidukite elektriakud; Autode akud; Akujuhtmed; Kristallilisest ränist päikeseelemendid; Päikeseelektrienergia tootmise fotogalvaanikaseadmed ja -paigaldised; Akud (Sõiduki -), sõidukiakud, autoakud; Akulaadurid, patareilaadurid; Akuplaadid; Taaslaetavad akuelemendid; Kodus kasutatavad päikesepatareid; Päikesepaneelid elektrienergia tootmiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Fotosähköakut; Litiumioniparistot; Ladattavat akut; Aurinkoparistot; Kannettavat aurinkopaneelit sähköntuotantoon; Aurinkokennot sähköntuotantoon; Auringonvalolla toimivat akkujen laturit; Akkulaturit moottoriajoneuvoja varten; Akun kotelot; Sähköakut sähköajoneuvojen tehonsyöttöön; Auton akut; Akkukaapelit; Kiteistä piitä sisältävät aurinkokennot; Valosähkölaitteet ja -laitteistot aurinkosähkön tuottamiseen; Ajoneuvojen akut; Latauslaitteet sähköparistoille; Akkujen laatat; Ladattavat kennot; Aurinkoakut kotitalouskäyttöön; Aurinkopaneelit sähkön tuotantoon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Accumulateurs d'énergie photovoltaïque; Batteries lithium-ion; Batteries rechargeables; Piles solaires; Panneaux solaires portables pour la production d'électricité; Cellules solaires pour la production d'électricité; Chargeurs de batteries solaires; Chargeurs de batterie pour véhicules motorisés; Caisses d'accumulateurs; Batteries électriques pour véhicules électriques; Batteries pour voitures; Câbles pour batteries; Cellules à énergie solaire en silicium cristallin; Appareils et installations photovoltaïques pour la production d'électricité solaire; Batteries pour véhicules; Chargeurs de piles et batteries; Plaques pour accumulateurs électriques; Piles rechargeables; Batteries solaires à usage domestique; Panneaux solaires pour la production d'électricité.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Akumulatori za fotonaponsku energiju; Litij-ionske baterije; Punjive baterije; Solarne baterije; Prijenosni solarni paneli za proizvodnju električne struje; Solarne ćelije za stvaranje električne energije; Solarni punjači baterija; Uređaji za punjenje akumulatorskih baterija motornih vozila; Kućišta akumulatora; Električne baterije za pogon električnih vozila; Akumulatori za automobile; Baterijski vodiči; Solarne ćelije od kristalnog silicija; Fotonaponski uređaji i instalacije za proizvodnju sunčeve energije; Akumulatori za vozila; Akumulatori (punjači električnih akumulatora); Ploče za akumulatore; Punjivi galvanski elementi; Solarne baterije za kućansku uporabu; Solarne ploče za proizvodnju električne energije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Akkumulátorok fényelektromos energiához; Lítiumion-akkumulátorok; Újratölthető elemek; Napelemek, szolár akkumulátorok; Hordozható napelem panelek villamos energia generálásához; Napelemek áramtermeléshez; Napelem töltők; Akkumulátortöltők gépjárművekhez; Akkumulátor dobozok; Elektromos akkumulátorok, elemek elektromos járművek meghajtásához; Autó akkumulátorok; Akkumulátor vezetékek; Kristályos szilícium napelemek; Fényelektromos berendezések és készülékek napenergiával történő áramfejlesztéshez; Akkumulátorok járművekhez; Akkumulátor- és elemtöltők; Lemezek akkumulátorokhoz; Feltölthető, utántölthető cellák; Háztartási napelemek; Napelemek villamosenergia-termeléshez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Accumulatori di energia fotovoltaica; Batterie a ioni di litio; Batterie ricaricabili; Pile solari; Pannelli solari portatili per la generazione di elettricità; Celle solari per la produzione di energia elettrica; Caricabatteria solari; Dispositivo di ricarica della batteria per veicoli a motore; Cassette per accumulatori; Batterie elettriche per alimentazione di veicoli elettrici; Batterie per auto; Cavi di batterie; Celle solari in silicio-cristallino; Apparecchi e impianti fotovoltaici per la generazione d'elettricità solare; Batterie per veicoli; Caricabatterie; Placche per accumulatori elettrici; Celle ricaricabili; Batterie solari per uso domestico; Pannelli solari per la produzione di energia elettrica.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Fotovoltinės energijos akumuliatoriai; Ličio jonų baterijos; Įkraunamos baterijos; Saulės baterijos; Elektros generavimo nešiojamosios saulės baterijų plokštės; Saulės elementai elektros gamybos reikmėms; Saulės baterijų įkrovikliai; Motorinių transporto priemonių akumuliatorių įkrovimo prietaisai; Baterijų korpusai; Elektrinių transporto priemonių elektros akumuliatoriai; Automobilių akumuliatoriai; Akumuliatorių baterijos išvadai; Kristalinio silicio saulės elementai; Fotogalvaniniai aparatai ir įrengimai, skirti saulės energijos generavimui; Transporto priemonių akumuliatoriai; Baterijų įkrovimo įtaisai; Akumuliatorių plokštelės; Įkraunami elementai; Saulės baterijos buities reikmėms; Saulės baterijų plokštės (elektros gamybai).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Fotogalvaniskās enerģijas akumulatori; Litija-jonu baterijas; Uzlādējamas baterijas; Saules baterijas; Portatīvie saules paneļi elektrības ģenerēšanai; Saules enerģijas elementi elektroenerģijas ražošanai; Saules bateriju akumulatoru uzlādes ierīces; Akumulatora lādēšanas ierīces automobiļiem; Bateriju korpusi; Elektrisko transportlīdzekļu elektroakumulatori; Automašīnu akumulatori; Akumulatoru kabeļi; Kristāla-silikona saules baterijas; Fotogalvaniskie aparāti un iekārtas saules elektrības ģenerēšanai; Transportlīdzekļu akumulatori; Akumulatoru uzlādes ierīces; Akumulatoru plates; Uzlādējamas šūnas; Saules baterijas mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Saules enerģijas paneļi elektroenerģijas ražošanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Akkumulaturi għall-enerġija fotovoltajka; Batteriji ta' joni tal-litju; Batteriji li jistgħu jerġgħu jiġu ċċarġjati; Batteriji solari; Panewijiet solari portabbli għall-ġenerazzjoni tal-elettriku; Ċelluli solari għall-ġenerazzjoni tal-elettriċita; Apparat li jiċċarġja batteriji solari; Tagħmir ta' ċarġ tal-batterija għal vetturi bil-mutur; Kaxxi tal-batteriji; Batteriji elettriċi li jagħtu l-enerġija lill-vetturi elettriċi; Batteriji tal-karozzi; Fili konnetturi għall-batterija; Ċelloli tal-enerġija solari bis-silikon tal-kristallin; Apparat u installazzjonijiet fotovoltajċi għall-ġenerazzjoni ta' l-elettriku solari; Batteriji ta' vetturi; Karikaturi għal batteriji elettriċi; Pjanċi għall-batteriji; Ċelloli li jistgħu jerġgħu jiġu ċċarġjati; Batteriji solari għall-użu domestiku; Pannelli solari għall-produzzjoni tal-elettriku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Accumulatoren voor fotovoltaïsche stroom; Lithiumionbatterijen; Oplaadbare batterijen; Zonnecellen; Draagbare zonnepanelen voor het opwekken van elektriciteit; Zonnecellen voor stroomopwekking; Zonnebatterijopladers; Batterijopladers voor motorvoertuigen; Accukasten; Accu's (Elektrische -) voor elektrisch aangedreven voertuigen; Auto accu's; Accukabels; Zonnestroomcellen van kristallijn silicium; Fotovoltaïsche toestellen en installaties voor het opwekken van zonne-energie; Accu's voor voertuigen; Batterij-laders; Accuplaten; Cellen (Oplaadbare -); Zonnebatterijen voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Zonnepanelen voor het opwekken van elektriciteit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Akumulatory energii fotowoltaicznej; Baterie litowo-jonowe; Baterie do ponownego ładowania; Baterie słoneczne; Przenośne panele słoneczne do wytwarzania energii elektrycznej; Ogniwa słoneczne do wytwarzania energii elektrycznej; Ładowarki do baterii słonecznych; Ładowarki do akumulatorów do pojazdów silnikowych; Skrzynki akumulatorowe; Elektryczne akumulatory do zasilania pojazdów elektrycznych; Akumulatory samochodowe; Kable do baterii; Ogniwa słoneczne z krzemu krystalicznego; Fotowoltaiczne urządzenia i instalacje do wytwarzania energii elektrycznej z energii słonecznej; Akumulatory do pojazdów; Ładowarki do baterii; Płyty do akumulatorów elektrycznych; Akumulatorki do powtórnego naładowania; Baterie słoneczne do użytku domowego; Panele słoneczne do wytwarzania energii elektrycznej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Acumuladores para energia fotovoltaica; Baterias de ião de lítio; Baterias recarregáveis; Pilhas solares; Painéis solares portáteis para produção de eletricidade; Células solares para produção de eletricidade; Carregadores de baterias solares; Carregadores de baterias para veículos a motor; Caixas de acumuladores; Baterias elétricas para veículos elétricos; Baterias para automóveis; Cabos de baterias; Células de energia solar em silício cristalino; Aparelhos e instalações fotovoltaicos para produção de energia solar; Baterias de veículos; Carregadores de baterias; Placas para acumuladores elétricos; Células recarregáveis; Baterias solares para uso doméstico; Painéis solares para a produção de eletricidade.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Acumulatori pentru energie fotovoltaică; Baterii de ioni de litiu; Baterii reîncărcabile; Baterii solare; Panouri solare portabile pentru generarea de electricitate; Celule solare pentru generarea de electricitate; Redresoare pentru baterii solare; Dispozitive de încărcat baterii pentru autovehicule; Carcase de acumulatoare; Baterii electrice pentru vehiculele electrice; Baterii pentru automobile; Cabluri pentru baterii; Celule de energie solară din silicon cristalin; Aparate și instalații fotovoltaice pentru generarea de energie solară; Baterii pentru vehicule; Alimentatoare pentru acumulatoare; Plăci pentru acumulatoare electrice; Celule reîncărcabile; Baterii solare de uz casnic; Panouri solare pentru producerea energiei electrice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Akumulátory pre fotovoltaickú energiu; Lítium-iónové batérie; Dobíjateľné batérie; Solárne články; Prenosné solárne panely pre generovanie elektriny; Solárne články na výrobu elektriny; Nabíjačky solárnych batérií; Nabíjačky batérií motorových vozidiel; Skrine akumulátorov; Elektrické batérie pre poháňanie elektrických vozidiel; Batérie pre automobily; Batériové káble; Solárne energetické články z kryštalického kremíka; Solárne (fotovoltické) prístroje a zariadenia na výrobu elektriny; Batérie do vozidiel; Nabíjačky batérií; Platne akumulátorov; Dobíjateľné články; Solárne batérie na použitie v domácnosti; Solárne panely na výrobu elektrickej energie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Akumulatorji za fotovoltaično energijo; Litij-ionske baterije; Baterije za ponovno polnjenje; Solarne baterije; Prenosne sončne plošče za proizvajanje električne energije; Sončne celice za pridobivanje električne energije; Polnilniki solarnih baterij; Naprave za polnjenje baterij motornih vozil; Ohišja za akumulatorje; Električne baterije za polnjenje električnih vozil; Baterije za avtomobile; Vodila za baterije; Kristalne silicijeve sončne celice; Fotonapetostni aparati in napeljave za pridobivanje sončne električne energije; Akumulatorji za vozila; Električni polnilniki za baterije; Plošče za baterije; Celice za ponovno polnjenje; Solarne baterije za domačo uporabo; Sončne plošče za proizvodnjo električne energije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Ackumulatorer för fotovoltaisk kraft; Litiumjonbatterier; Återuppladdningsbara batterier; Solbatterier; Bärbara solpaneler för alstring av elektricitet; Solceller för alstring av elektricitet; Solbatteriladdare; Batteriladdningsanordningar för motorfordon; Batterilådor; Elektriska batterier för strömförsörjning av eldrivna fordon; Bilbatterier; Batterikablar; Solceller av kristallint kisel; Fotocellapparater och -anläggningar för alstring av solelektricitet; Batterier till fordon och farkoster; Batteriladdare; Batteriplattor; Laddningsbara celler; Solbatterier för hushållsändamål; Solpaneler för produktion av elektricitet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Осветителни апарати със слънчеви клетки; Устройства за осветяване с органични светодиоди (OLED); Електрически фиброоптични осветителни апарати; Електрически лампи за външно осветление; Светодиодни фиксирани осветителни тела; Осветителни инсталации със светодиоди (LED); Осветителни крушки; Осветителни апарати; Осветителни уреди и инсталации; Осветителни инсталации; Лампи захранвани от слънчева енергия; Филтри за питейна вода; Електрически филтри за пречистване на вода за домакински цели; Инсталации за обработка на фекални води [пречистване]; Пречиствателни инсталации за отпадъчни води; Водни филтриращи устройства; Водни пречиствателни инсталации; Светодиодни лампи за външно осветление; Крушки за осветление тип LED; Светодиоди [LED] за осветителни уреди.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Osvětlovací zařízení se solárními články; Osvětlovací zařízení s organickými světelnými diodami (OLED); Světelné přístroje a zařízení z elektrických vláken; Elektrické lampy na venkovní osvětlení; LED osvětlovací tělesa; Zařízení pro osvětlení se světelnými diodami [LED]; Žárovky; Přístroje na osvětlení; Osvětlovací přístroje a zařízení; Osvětlovací zařízení; Lampy na solární energii; Filtry na přípravu pitné vody; Elektrické filtry na čištění vody pro domácnost; Instalace na ošetřování odpadní vody (čištění); Zařízení na čištění odpadních vod; Přístroje na filtraci vody; Zařízení na čištění vody; LED lampy na venkovní osvětlení; LED žárovky; Osvětlovací zařízení vybavená elektroluminiscenčními diodami (LED).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Solcelledrevne belysningsapparater; Belysningsapparater med organiske lysdioder (OLED); Belysningsapparater med optisk fiber; Elektriske lamper til udendørs belysning; LED-belysningsarmaturer; LED-belysningsinstallationer; Pærer til belysning; Belysningsapparater; Belysningsapparater og installationer; Belysningsinstallationer; Solcellelamper; Filtre til drikkevand; Elektriske vandrensningsfiltre til husholdningsbrug; Spildevandsanlæg [vandrensning]; Renseanlæg til spildevand; Vandfiltreringsapparater; Vandrenseinstallationer; LED-lys til udendørs belysning; LED-pærer til belysning; Lysemitterende dioder [LED]-belysningsapparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Solarzellen-Beleuchtungsgeräte; Beleuchtungsgeräte mit organischen Leuchtdioden [OLED]; Elektrische faseroptische Beleuchtungsgeräte; Elektrische Lampen zur Verwendung im Freien; LED-Beleuchtungsanlagen; Leuchtdioden [LED]-Beleuchtungsanlagen; Glühbirnen für Beleuchtungszwecke; Beleuchtungsgeräte; Beleuchtungsapparate und -anlagen; Beleuchtungsanlagen; Mit Solarenergie betriebene Lampen; Trinkwasserfilter; Elektrische Wasserreinigungsfilter für Haushaltszwecke; Abwasserbehandlungsanlagen [Reinigung]; Abwasserkläranlagen; Wasserfiltriergeräte; Wasserreinigungsanlagen; LED-Landschaftsbeleuchtungen; LED-Glühlampen; Beleuchtungsgeräte mit Leuchtdioden [LEDs].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές φωτισμού που λειτουργούν με ηλιακές κυψέλες· Συσκευές φωτισμού με οργανικές φωτοδιόδους (OLED)· Ηλεκτρικές συσκευές φωτισμού με ίνες· Ηλεκτρικές λάμπες για εξωτερικό φωτισμό· Διατάξεις φωτισμού με φωτοδιόδους (LED)· Εγκαταστάσεις φωτισμού με φωτοδιόδους [LED]· Λαμπτήρες· Μονάδες φωτισμού· Φωτισμός (μηχανισμοί και εγκαταστάσεις -ού)· Εγκαταστάσεις φωτισμού· Λαμπτήρες που λειτουργούν με ηλιακή ενέργεια· Φίλτρα για ύδωρ πόσιμο· Ηλεκτρικά φίλτρα καθαρισμού νερού για οικιακή χρήση· Εγκαταστάσεις για τον καθαρισμό και την επεξεργασία των λυμάτων· Εγκαταστάσεις για το καθαρισμό των υπονόμων· Ύδωρ (συσκευές φιλτραρίσματος του -ος)· Ύδωρ (εγκαταστάσεις καθαρισμού του -ος)· Φώτα εξωτερικών χώρων με φωτοδιόδους· Λυχνίες λαμπτήρων LED· Συσκευές φωτισμού με φωτοδιόδους.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Solar cell lighting apparatus; Organic light emitting diodes (OLED) lighting devices; Electric fiber lighting apparatus; Electrical lamps for outdoor lighting; LED lighting fixtures; LED lighting installations; Light bulbs; Lighting apparatus; Lighting apparatus and installations; Lighting installations; Solar powered lamps; Filters for drinking water; Electric water purification filters for household purposes; Sewage treatment [purification] installations; Purification installations for sewage; Water filtering apparatus; Water purification installations; LED landscape lights; LED light bulbs; Light-emitting diodes [LED] lighting apparatus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de iluminación con células solares; Dispositivo de alumbrado por diodos luminiscentes orgánicos (OLED); Aparatos de alumbrado de fibra eléctrica; Luces eléctricas para alumbrado de exterior; Apliques de iluminación led; Instalaciones de iluminación con LED; Bombillas de iluminación; Aparatos de iluminación; Aparatos e instalaciones de alumbrado; Instalaciones de alumbrado; Lámparas alimentadas por energía solar; Filtros para agua potable; Filtros eléctricos depuradores de agua para uso doméstico; Instalaciones para la depuración y tratamiento de aguas residuales; Instalaciones de depuración de aguas residuales; Aparatos para filtrar el agua; Instalaciones de depuración de agua; Luces LED de paisajismo; Bombillas de iluminación LED; Aparatos de iluminación con diodos electroluminiscentes [LED].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Päikesepatareiga valgustusseadmed; Orgaaniliste valgusdioodidega (OLED) valgustusseadmed; Elektrilised kiudvalgustid; Elektrilambid õuevalgustuseks; LED-valgustiarmatuurid; Valgusdiood [LED] valgustuspaigaldised; Lambipirnid; Valgustusaparaadid; Valgustusaparaadid ja -seadised; Valgustuspaigaldised; Päikeseenergiaga töötavad lambid; Joogiveefiltrid; Elektrilised veepuhastusfiltrid majapidamises kasutamiseks; Heitveetöötlusseadmed [heitveepuhastusseadmed]; Heitveepuhastusseadmed; Veefiltrimisseadmed; Veepuhastusseadmed; LED-maastikuvalgustid; LED-lambipirnid; Valgustkiirgavatel dioodidel põhinevad (LED-) valgustid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Aurinkokennovalaistuslaitteet; OLED-valodiodivalaisinlaitteet; Sähkökuidulliset valaistuslaitteet; Sähkölamput valaisemiseen ulkona; LED-valaistuslaitteistot; Led-valaistuslaitteistot; Hehkulamput; Valaisinlaitteet; Valaistuslaitteet; Valaistuslaitteistot; Aurinkoenergialla toimivat lamput; Juomavesisuodattimet; Sähkökäyttöiset vedenpuhdistussuodattimet kotitaloustarkoituksiin; Jäteveden käsittelyyn [puhdistus] tarkoitetut laitteet; Jäteveden puhdistuslaitteet; Vedensuodatuslaitteet; Vedenpuhdistuslaitteet; Ledimaisemavalot; LED-valolamput; LED-valaistuslaitteet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils d'éclairage à cellules solaires; Appareils d'éclairage à diodes électroluminescentes organiques (OLED); Appareils d'éclairage à fibre électrique; Lampes électriques pour éclairage d'extérieur; Luminaires DEL; Installations d'éclairage à diodes électroluminescentes [DEL]; Ampoules d'éclairage; Appareils d'éclairage; Appareils et installations d'éclairage; Installations d'éclairage; Lampes à énergie solaire; Filtres pour l'eau potable; Filtres électriques de purification de l'eau à usage domestique; Installations de traitement des eaux usées [épuration]; Installations pour la purification des eaux d'égouts; Appareils à filtrer l'eau; Installations pour la purification de l'eau; Lampes à LED pour espaces verts; Ampoules LED; Appareils d'éclairage à diodes électroluminescentes [DEL].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Rasvjetni uređaji sa solarnim ćelijama; Rasvjetni uređaji s organskim svjetlećim diodama (OLED); Uređaji za električnu rasvjetu optičkim vlaknima; Električne svjetiljke za vanjsku rasvjetu; Rasvjetna LED tijela; Sustavi diodne [LED] rasvjete; Rasvjetne žaruljice; Rasvjetni uređaji; Rasvjetni uređaji i instalacije; Rasvjetne instalacije; Svjetiljke na solarni pogon; Filtri za pitku vodu; Filtri za električno pročišćavanje vode za kućanske potrebe; Instalacije za obradu otpadnih voda [pročišćavanje]; Otpadne vode (postrojenje za pročišćavanje otpadnih voda); Uređaji za filtriranje vode; Uređaj za pročišćavanje vode; LED svjetla za krajolik; LED žarulje za svjetiljke; Rasvjetni uređaji sa diodama koje emitiraju svjetlo [LED].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Napelemes világítóberendezések; Organikus fénykibocsátó diódás (OLED-es) világítóberendezések; Elektromos szálas világító berendezések; Elektromos lámpák kültéri világításhoz; LED-es világítószerelvények; Fénykibocsátó diódás [LED-es] világítóberendezések; Villanykörték; Világítókészülékek; Világító berendezések és készülékek; Világítástechnikai berendezések; Napelemmel működő lámpák; Ivóvízszűrők; Elektromos víztisztító szűrők háztartási célokra; Szennyvízkezelő [-tisztító] berendezések; Berendezések szennyvíz tisztításához; Vízszűrő berendezések; Víztisztító berendezések; Kerti, kültéri LED lámpák; LED-izzók; LED-diódás világító berendezések.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi di illuminazione a celle solari; Dispositivi di illuminazione a diodi organici elettroluminescenti (OLED); Apparecchi d'illuminazione a fibre elettriche; Lampade elettriche per illuminazione di esterni; Impianti d'illuminazione a LED; Impianti di illuminazione a LED; Lampadine per illuminazione; Apparecchi per illuminazione; Apparecchi ed impianti di illuminazione; Impianti per l'illuminazione; Lampade alimentate a energia solare; Filtri per l'acqua potabile; Filtri depuratori d'acqua elettrici per uso domestico; Impianti per il trattamento [depurazione] dei liquami; Impianti per la depurazione delle acque di fogna; Apparecchi per filtrare l'acqua; Impianti per la depurazione dell'acqua; Luci a LED per uso paesaggistico; Lampadine LED; Diodi che emettono luce [LED].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Šviestuvai su saulės elementais; Apšvietimo įrenginiai su organiniais šviesos diodais (OLED); Elektriniai skaiduliniai apšvietimo aparatai; Elektrinės lauko apšvietimo lempos; Šviesos diodų apšvietimo įranga; Šviesos diodų apšvietimo įrenginiai; Apšvietimo lemputės; Apšvietimo aparatai; Apšvietimo prietaisai ir įrenginiai; Apšvietimo įrenginiai; Saulės energija veikiančios lempos; Geriamojo vandens filtrai; Elektriniai vandens gryninimo filtrai namų apyvokos reikmėms; Nuotekų valymo įrenginiai; Nuotekų valymo įrenginiai; Vandens filtravimo aparatai; Vandens valymo įrenginiai; Šviesos diodų lauko lempos; Šviesos diodų lemputės; Šviesadiodžio [LED] apšvietimo įrenginiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Apgaismes ierīces ar saules baterijām; Apgaismes ierīces ar organiskajām gaismas diodēm (OLED); Elektriskās optisko šķiedru apgaismojuma iekārtas; Elektriskas lampas āra apgaismojumam; LED gaismekļi; Gaismas diožu [LED] apgaismes iekārtas; Spuldzes; Apgaismes ķermeņi; Apgaismošanas ierīces un to sistēmu daļas; Apgaismes ierīces; Ar saules enerģiju darbināmi gaismekļi; Dzeramā ūdens filtri; Elektriskie ūdens attīrīšanas filtri mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Notekūdeņu apstrādes [attīrīšanas] iekārtas; Notekūdeņu attīrīšanas iekārtas; Ūdens filtrēšanas iekārtas; Ūdens attīrīšanas iekārtas; Gaismas diožu lampas āra apgaismojumam; Gaismas diožu spuldzes (LED); Gaismu emitējošu diožu (LED) apgaismes iekārtas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat għat-tidwil li fihom ċelloli solari; Tagħmir li jdawwal b'dajowds organiċi li jagħtu d-dawl (OLED); Apparat tad-dawl tal-fibra elettrika; Lampi elettriċi biex idawwlu barra; Partijiet fissi tad-dawl LED; Installazzjonijiet tad-dawl bid-dajowds li jarmu d-dawl [LED]; Bozoz tad-dawl; Apparat għat-tidwil; Apparat u sistemi tad-dawl; Sistemi ta' dwal; Fanali li jaħdmu bix-xemx; Filtri għall-ilma tax-xorb; Filtri tal-purifikazzjoni tal-ilma tal-elettriku għal skopijiet domestiċi; Installazzjonijiet għat-trattament [purifikazzjoni] tad-dranaġġ; Tagħmir għall-purifikazzjoni tad-dranaġġ; Apparat li jiffiltra l-ilma; Sistemi għat-tisfija tal-ilma; Dwal LED għall-pajsaġġi; Bozoz tad-dawl tal-LED; Apparat li jdawwal b'dajowds li jarmu d-dawl [LED].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verlichtingsapparatuur met zonnecellen; Verlichtingstoestellen met organische lichtgevende dioden (oleds); Glasverzelverlichtingsapparaten (Elektrische -); Elektrische lampen voor buitenverlichting; Led-verlichtingsarmaturen; Led-verlichting; Gloeilampen; Verlichtingsapparaten; Verlichtingsapparaten en -installaties; Verlichtingsinstallaties; Lampen (op zonne-energie); Drinkwaterfilters; Elektrische waterzuiveringsfilters voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Rioolwaterbehandelingsinstallaties [waterzuivering]; Rioolwaterzuiveringsinstallaties; Waterfiltreerapparaten; Waterzuiveringsinstallaties; Led-landschapsverlichting; LED-lichtpeertjes; LED-verlichtingsapparatuur.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia oświetleniowe z ogniwami słonecznymi; Urządzenia oświetleniowe z organicznymi diodami elektroluminescencyjnymi (OLED); Elektryczne oświetlenie światłowodowe; Lampy elektryczne do oświetlenia zewnętrznego; Oprawy oświetleniowe LED; Instalacje oświetleniowe z diodami elektroluminescencyjnymi [LED]; Żarówki oświetleniowe; Urządzenia oświetleniowe; Urządzenia i instalacje oświetleniowe; Instalacje oświetleniowe; Lampy na energię słoneczną; Filtry do wody pitnej; Elektryczne filtry do oczyszczania wody przeznaczone do użytku domowego; Instalacje oczyszczania ścieków; Instalacje do oczyszczania ścieków; Urządzenia do filtrowania wody; Instalacje do uzdatniania wody; Oświetlenie typu LED zewnętrzne [ogrody, krajobrazy]; Żarówki oświetleniowe LED; Urządzenia do oświetlania za pomocą diod elektroluminescencyjnych [LED].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos de iluminação com células solares; Dispositivos de iluminação com díodos emissores de luz orgânicos (OLED); Aparelhos de iluminação de fibra elétrica; Candeeiros elétricos para iluminação de exteriores; Luminárias de LED; Instalações de iluminação por díodos eletroluminescentes [LED]; Lâmpadas de iluminação; Aparelhos de iluminação; Aparelhos e instalações de iluminação; Instalações de iluminação; Lâmpadas alimentadas por energia solar; Filtros para a água potável; Filtros elétricos de purificação de água para uso doméstico; Instalações de tratamento de esgotos [purificação das águas dos esgotos]; Instalações para a purificação das águas de esgotos; Aparelhos para filtrar a água; Instalações para a purificação da água; Luzes paisagísticas LED; Lâmpadas de iluminação LED; Díodos emissores de luz [LED].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate de iluminat cu celule solare; Dispozitive de iluminat cu diode electroluminiscente organice (OLED); Aparate de iluminat cu fibră electrică; Lămpi electrice pentru iluminare în exterior; Corpuri de iluminat cu LED; Instalații de iluminat cu diode electroluminescente [leduri]; Becuri de iluminat; Aparate de iluminat; Aparate și instalații de iluminat; Instalații de iluminat; Lămpi alimentate cu energie solară; Filtre pentru apa potabilă; Filtre electrice pentru purificarea apei, de uz menajer; Instalații de epurare a apelor uzate (purificare); Ape reziduale (Instalații de purificare pentru -); Aparate de filtrare a apei; Instalații pentru purificarea apei; Lumini LED pentru iluminatul public; Becuri cu LED; Aparate de iluminat cu diode luminescente [LED].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Osvetľovacie zariadenia so solárnymi článkami; Osvetľovacie prístroje s organickými elektroluminiscenčnými diódami (OLED); Elektrické vláknové osvetľovacie zariadenia; Elektrické lampy pre vonkajšie osvetlenie; LED osvetľovacie zariadenia; Osvetľovacie zariadenia s luminiscenčnými diódami [LED]; Žiarovky; Osvetľovacie prístroje; Osvetľovacie prístroje a zariadenia; Osvetľovacie zariadenia; Lampy na slnečnú energiu; Filtre na pitnú vodu; Elektrické filtre na čistenie vody na domáce použitie; Inštalácie na spracovanie [čistenie] kanalizačného odpadu; Čistiace zariadenia na odpadovú vodu; Zariadenia na filtrovanie vody; Zariadenia na úpravu vody; LED svetlá používané na dekoráciu v exteriéri; LED žiarovky; Elektroluminiscenčné osvetľovacie prístroje (s LED diódami).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Aparati za razsvetljavo na sončne celice; Naprave za osvetljevanje z organskimi svetlobnimi diodami (OLED); Naprave za osvetljevanje z električnimi vlakni; Električne svetilke za zunanjo razsvetljavo; Napeljave za LED osvetljavo; Napeljave za osvetljevanje z LED diodami; Žarnice za razsvetljavo; Aparati za razsvetljavo; Naprave in napeljave za razsvetljavo; Napeljave za osvetljevanje; Svetilke na sončno energijo; Filtri za pitno vodo; Električni filtri za prečiščevanje vode za gospodinjstvo; Napeljave za obdelavo odpadnih vod [prečiščevanje]; Čistilne inštalacije za odpadne vode; Aparati za filtriranje vode; Čistilne naprave za vodo; LED svetilke za pokrajino; LED žarnice; Aparati za osvetljevanje z LED diodami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Apparater för solcellsbelysning; Belysningsapparater med organiska lysdioder (OLED); Elektriska fiberbelysningsapparater; Elektriska lampor för utomhusbelysning; LED-belysningsarmaturer; Belysningsanläggningar med lysdioder [LED]; Glödlampor; Apparater för belysning; Belysningsapparater och -installationer; Belysningsinstallationer; Soldrivna lampor; Filter för dricksvatten; Elektriska vattenreningsfilter för hushållsändamål; Avloppsbehandlingsinstallationer [rening]; Reningsanläggningar för avloppsvatten; Vattenfiltreringsapparater; Vattenreningsinstallationer; LED-lampor för utomhusbelysning; LED-glödlampor; Belysningsapparater för lysdioder [LED].</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/075</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-21</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/144</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-31</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079106</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>22168</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017693451</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>22168</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-04-09</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
