<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-26T08:48:09</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224419</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224419</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>AvantiaAqua</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Горелки, отоплителни котли и нагреватели; Електрически резервоари за топла вода; Водонагреватели с топлоакумулатор; Електрически уреди за затопляне на вода.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Hořáky, kotle a ohřívače vody; Elektricky ohřívané nádrže na teplou vodu; Zásobníkové ohřívače vody; Elektrické přístroje a zařízení na ohřívání vody.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Brændere, kedler og varmere; Elektriske varmtvandsbeholdere; Varmtvandsbeholdere; Elektriske apparater til opvarmning af vand.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Brenner, Boiler und Heizgeräte; Elektrisch beheizte Warmwasserspeicher; Warmwasserspeicher; Elektrische Wassererwärmungsgeräte..</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Καυστήρες, λέβητες και θερμάστρες· Ηλεκτρικά θερμαινόμενες δεξαμενές ζεστού νερού· Θερμοσυσσωρευτές ύδατος· Ηλεκτρικές συσκευές για τη θέρμανση του νερού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Burners, boilers and heaters; Electrically heated hot water tanks; Storage water heaters; Electric water heating apparatus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Quemadores, calderas y calentadores; Depósitos de agua caliente calentados eléctricamente; Calentadores de agua por acumulación; Aparatos eléctricos para el calentamiento de agua.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Põletid, boilerid, aurukatlad ja kütteseadmed ja soojendid; Elektrisoojendusega kuumaveepaagid; Soojaveeboilerid; Elektrilised veekuumutusseadmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Polttimet, boilerit ja lämmittimet; Sähkölämmitteiset lämminvesivaraajat; Lämminvesivaraajat; Sähkökäyttöiset laitteet veden lämmittämiseen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Brûleurs, chaudières et réchauffeurs; Réservoirs d'eau chaude chauffés électriquement; Chauffe-eau à accumulation; Chauffe-eau électiques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Plamenici, bojleri i grijači; Električno zagrijavani spremnici vruće vode; Grijači vode; Električni aparati za grijanje vode.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Égők, kazánok és fűtő/melegítőkészülékek; Elektromosan melegített forróvizes tartályok; Tárolós vízmelegítők; Elektromos vízmelegítő készülékek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Bruciatori, bollitori e caloriferi; Serbatoi per l'acqua calda elettrici; Scalda acqua ad accumulo; Apparecchi elettrici per riscaldare acqua.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Degikliai, katilai ir šildytuvai; Elektra šildomos karšto vandens talpyklos; Akumuliaciniai vandens šildytuvai; Elektriniai vandens šildymo aparatai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Degļi, sildītāji un apkures katli; Elektriski sildāmas karstā ūdens tvertnes; Uzkrātā ūdens sildītāji; Elektriskās ūdens sildīšanas ierīces.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Berners, bojlers u hiters; Tankijiet għall-ilma sħun imsaħħna bl-elettriku; Ħiters għall-ħzin tal-ilma; Apparat għat-tisħin tal-ilma jaħdem bl-elettriku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Branders, ketels, boilers en verwarmingsapparaten; Elektrisch verwarmde warmwaterreservoirs; Heetwaterreservoir; Elektrische apparaten voor het verwarmen van water.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Palniki, bojlery i podgrzewacze; Elektrycznie podgrzewane zbiorniki na gorącą wodę; Akumulacyjne ogrzewacze wody; Elektryczne urządzenia do ogrzewania wody.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Queimadores, caldeiras e aquecedores; Depósitos de água quente elétricos; Aquecedores de água para armazenamento; Aparelhos elétricos para aquecer água.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Arzătoare, boilere și încălzitoare; Rezervoare de apă fierbinte încălzite electric; Boilere; Aparate acționate electric pentru încălzirea apei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Horáky, ohrievače a vyhrievače; Elektricky vyhrievané nádrže na horúcu vodu; Zásobné ohrievače vody; Elektrické zariadenia na ohrievanie vody.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Gorilniki, kotli in grelniki; Električno ogrevani rezervoarji za vročo vodo; Akumulacijski grelniki vode; Električni aparati za ogrevanje vode.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Brännare, pannor och värmare; Elektriskt uppvärmda varmvattentankar; Varmvattenberedare; Elektriskt drivna anordningar för uppvärmning av vatten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/203</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>C.3.6</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-23</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>111160</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>81676</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
