<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T08:52:44</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224701</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224701</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-28</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>fr</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>CHEERLAND</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Апликации от хартия; Декоративни хартиени украси за маса; Хартиени декорации за поставяне върху торти; Хартиени гирлянди; Хартиени украси за партита; Хартиени знамена; Флагчета от хартия; Знамена [от хартия]; Хартиени знаменца; Афиши, плакати от хартия или картон; Декорация за маса от хартия; Хартиени декорации; Декоративни гирлянди от хартия за партита; Индикаторни банери, направени от картон; Плакати за банери от хартия; Печатни хартиени знаци; Стикери за стена [декалкомания]; Хартия металик за украса на партита; Хартия за фон за снимки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Papírové nálepky; Papírové ozdoby na stůl; Papírové ozdoby na dorty; Papírové girlandy; Papírové ozdoby na večírky; Papírové bannery; Papírové vlajky; Papírové vlajky; Papírové vlajky a vlaječky; Poutače z papíru nebo lepenky; Dekorace na stůl z papíru; Papírové ozdoby na dorty; Papírové dekorativní girlandy na večírky; Reklamní tabule z lepenky; Vývěsní tabule z papíru; Tištěné papírové cedule; Nálepky na zeď; Dekorace na večírky z pokoveného papíru; Papírové pasparty na obrazy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Applikationer af papir; Borddekorationer af papir; Papirpynt til kager; Papirguirlander; Festdekorationer af papir; Papirbannere; Guirlande af papir; Flag af papir; Vimpler af papir; Plakater af papir eller pap; Papirartikler til borddekoration; Papirdekorationer til kager; Dekorative papirguirlander til fester; Udstillingsbannere af pap; Udstillingsbannere af papir; Trykte papirskilte; Overføringsbilleder til vægge; Festdekorationer af metallisk papir; Passepartouts til billedrammer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Applikationen aus Papier; Papiermittelstücke für Dekorationszwecke; Tortenaufsätze aus Papier; Papiergirlanden; Partydekorationen aus Papier; Banner aus Papier; Fähnchen aus Papier; Fahnen aus Papier; Papierwimpel; Plakate aus Papier oder Pappe; Tischdekorationen aus Papier; Kuchendekorationen aus Papier; Dekorative Papiergirlanden für Partys; Ausstellungstransparente aus Pappe [Karton]; Schautafelbanner aus Papier; Gedruckte Papierschilder; Wandabziehbilder; Partydekorationen aus metallischem Papier; Passepartouts für Fotos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διακοσμητικά επιρράμματα (απλικέ) από χαρτί· Χάρτινα διακοσμητικά για το κέντρο του τραπεζιού· Χάρτινες διακοσμητικές φιγούρες για τούρτες· Χάρτινες γιρλάντες· Χάρτινα διακοσμητικά για πάρτι· Πανό από χαρτί· Σημαιάκια από χαρτί· Σημαίες [από χαρτί]· Σημαιάκια από χαρτί· Αφίσες από χαρτί και χαρτόνι· Χάρτινα διακοσμητικά για το τραπέζι· Χάρτινα διακοσμητικά για τούρτες· Διακοσμητικές γιρλάντες από χαρτί για πάρτι· Πανό παρουσίασης από χαρτόνι· Πανό παρουσίασης από χαρτί· Τυπωμένες χάρτινες επιγραφές· Χαλκομανίες τοίχου· Μεταλλιζέ χάρτινα διακοσμητικά για πάρτι· Χάρτινες κορνίζες φωτογραφιών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Appliqués of paper; Decorative paper centerpieces; Paper cake toppers; Paper garlands; Paper party decorations; Banners of paper; Bunting of paper; Flags of paper; Paper pennants; Placards of paper or cardboard; Table decorations of paper; Paper cake decorations; Decorative paper garlands for parties; Display banners made of cardboard; Display banners of paper; Printed paper signs; Wall decals; Metallic paper party decorations; Paper picture mounts.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Apliques de papel; Centros de mesa decorativos de papel; Decoraciones de papel para tartas; Guirnaldas de papel; Decoraciones de papel para fiestas; Banderolas de papel; Guirnaldas de banderines de papel; Banderas de papel; Banderín de papel; Rótulos de papel o cartón; Decoraciones para la mesa de papel; Decoraciones de papel para pasteles; Guirnaldas decorativas de papel para fiestas; Pancartas de exposición hechas de cartón; Pancartas de exposición de papel; Letreros de papel impresos; Calcomanías de pared; Adornos de papel metalizado para fiestas; Marcos de cuadros de papel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Paberist aplikatsioonid; Dekoratiivsed paberkaunistused; Paberist tordikaunistused; Pabergirlandid; Paberist peokaunistused; Paberist ribareklaamid; Paberlipud; Paberist lipud, plagud; Paberlipud; Paberist või papist plakatid; Paberist lauakaunistused; Paberist tordikaunistused; Pidudel kasutatavad paberist dekoratiivvanikud; Kartongist valmistatud näituseplakatid; Paberist ribareklaamistendid; Trükitud pabermärgid; Seinakleebised; Metallpaberist peokaunistused; Paberist paspartuud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Paperiapplikoinnit; Paperiset koristeet pöydän keskelle; Paperiset kakun päällyskoristeet; Paperiköynnökset; Paperiset juhlakoristeet; Paperiviirit; Paperiset lippukoristeet; Liput (Paperi -); Paperiset liput; Plakaatit (Paperi- tai pahvi -); Paperiset pöydänkoristeet; Paperiset kakunkoristeet; Paperiset koristeköynnökset juhliin; Pahvista tehdyt esittelyviirit; Paperista tehdyt julisteet; Painetut paperiopasteet; Seinälle laitettavat siirtokuvat; Metallipaperista tehdyt juhlakoristeet; Paperiset valokuvakehykset.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appliques en papier; Centres de table décoratifs en papier; Décorations en papier pour gâteaux; Guirlandes en papier; Décorations de fête en papier; Bannières en papier; Fanions en papier; Drapeaux en papier; Écriteaux en papier ou en carton; Décorations de table en papier; Guirlandes décoratives en papier pour fêtes; Banderoles d'affichage en carton; Banderoles d'affichage en papier; Enseignes en papier imprimées; Décalcomanies murales; Décorations de fête en papier métallisé; Cadres photo en papier; Fanions en papier; Décorations en papier pour gâteaux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Papirnate aplikacije; Ukrasi od papira za sredinu stola; Papirnati ukrasi za tortu; Girlande od papira; Papirnate dekoracije za zabave; Papirnate zastavice; Papirnate zastavice; Papirnate zastavice; Papirnati plamenci; Plakati, papirnati ili kartonski; Papirnate stolne dekoracije; Papirnati ukrasi za kolače; Ukrasne papirnate girlande za proslave; Reklamni transparenti napravljeni od kartona; Reklamni transparenti od papira; Tiskani papirnati natpisi; Naljepnice za zid; Ukrasi za zabave od metalik papira; Papirnati okviri za slike.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Rátétek papírból; Papír asztaldíszek; Papír tortadíszek/süteménydíszek; Papírgirlandok; Ünnepi papír dekorációk [partikra]; Papír feliratok, zászlók; Zászlófüzér papírból; Zászlók papírból; Papírzászlók; Plakátok, falragaszok papírból vagy kartonból; Papírból készült asztaldíszek; Papírdíszek süteményekhez, tortákhoz; Dekoratív papír girlandok partikra; Bemutatótáblák, reklámtáblák kartonból; Papír bemutatótáblák, reklámtáblák; Nyomtatott papír feliratok; Fali matricák; Party dekoráció fémes papírból; Papír képkeretek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Applicazioni di carta; Centrotavola decorativi di carta; Decorazioni di carta per torte; Ghirlande di carta; Decorazioni in carta per feste; Striscioni di carta; Festoni in carta; Gagliardetti di carta; Bandiere di carta; Cartelli in carta o in cartone; Decorazioni da tavola di carta; Decorazioni di carta per dolci; Ghirlande decorative in carta per feste; Banner di visualizzazione in cartone; Banner di visualizzazione in carta; Insegne di carta stampate; Decalcomanie da parete; Decorazioni in carta metallizzata per feste; Supporti di carta per immagini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Popierinės aplikacijos; Dekoratyviniai popieriniai papuošimai; Popierinės tortų puošmenos; Popierinės girliandos; Popierinės švenčių dekoracijos; Popierinės reklamjuostės; Popierinės girliandos; Popierinės vėliavėlės; Popierinės vėliavėlės; Popieriniai ar kartoniniai plakatai; Popierinės stalo dekoracijos; Popieriniai tortų papuošimai; Dekoratyvinės šventinės girliandos iš popieriaus; Kartoniniai demonstravimo plakatai; Popieriniai demonstravimo plakatai; Spausdintiniai popieriniai ženklai; Sienų atspaudžiamieji paveikslėliai; Šventiniai papuošimai iš metalizuoto popieriaus; Popieriniai paveikslų stovai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Papīra aplikācijas; Novietošanai galda centrā paredzēti rotājumi no papīra; Kūku dekorācijas no papīra; Papīra virtenes; Svinību dekorācijas no papīra; Papīra reklāmplakāti; Papīra karodziņu virtenes; Papīra karodziņi; Papīra vimpeļi; Papīra vai kartona afišas; Galda dekorācijas no papīra; Papīra dekorācijas kūkām; Dekoratīvas papīra virtenes ballītēm; Kartona izkārtnes; Reklāmplakāti no papīra; Iespiestas papīra zīmes; Sienas uzlīmes; Viesību rotājumi no metāliska papīra; Attēlu rāmji no papīra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Applikes tal-karti; Dekorazzjonijiet għal fuq il-mejda magħmula mill-karti; Dekorazzjonijiet tal-karti għall-kejkijiet; Girlandi tal-karti; Dekorazzjonijiet tal-karti għal festini; Banners tal-karti; L-iffurmar tal-karta f'forom ta' bnadar; Bnadar tal-karti; Pinnuri tal-karti; Kartelluni tal-karti jew tal-kartun; Dekorazzjonijiet tal-karti, għall-mejda; Dekorazzjonijiet tal-karti għall-kejkijiet; Girlandi dekorattivi tal-karti għall-festini; Baners għall-wiri magħmulin mill-kartun; Banners tal-karta għall-wiri; Tabelli stampati tal-karti; Dekalkomanija tal-ħajt; Dekorazzjonijiet għall-festini tal-karta metallika; Immuntar għall-istampi tal-karti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Applicaties van papier; Decoratieve middenstukjes van papier; Taartversieringen van papier; Papieren guirlandes; Papieren feestdecoraties; Vaandels van papier; Vlaggetjes van papier; Vlaggen van papier; Wimpels van papier; Aanplakborden van karton of papier; Tafelversieringen van papier; Papieren taartversieringen; Decoratieve slingers van papier voor feestjes; Presentatiebanieren van karton; Presentatiebanieren van papier; Gedrukte uithangborden van papier; Overdrukplaatjes voor op wanden; Metallic papier als feestdecoratie; Houders van papier voor foto's.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Aplikacje z papieru; Dekoracje na środek stołu z papieru; Papierowe ozdoby do ciast; Girlandy papierowe; Ozdoby papierowe na przyjęcia; Transparenty z papieru; Girlandy papierowe; Chorągiewki papierowe; Proporczyki z papieru; Afisze, plakaty z papieru lub kartonu; Dekoracje na stół z papieru; Papierowe ozdoby do ciast; Papierowe dekoracyjne girlandy na przyjęcia; Banery wystawowe wykonane z kartonu; Banery wystawowe z papieru; Drukowane znaki papierowe; Kalkomanie ścienne; Dekoracje na przyjęcia z papieru metalizowanego; Oprawy do zdjęć i obrazów wykonane z papieru.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Apliques em papel; Centros de mesa decorativos de papel; Decorações em papel para bolos; Grinaldas de papel; Decorações em papel para festas; Estandartes em papel; Bandeirolas em papel; Bandeiras em papel; Bandeirolas em papel; Cartazes em papel ou em cartão; Decorações de mesa em papel; Decorações em papel para bolos; Grinaldas decorativas de papel para festas; Cartazes de exposição feitos de cartão; Cartazes de exposição em papel; Letreiros em papel impresso; Decalcomanias de parede; Decorações para festas em papel metalizado; Molduras em papel para fotografias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aplicații din hârtie; Articole decorative din hârtie pentru centrul mesei; Ornamente de hârtie pentru torturi; Ghirlande de hârtie; Decorațiuni din hârtie pentru petreceri; Bannere din hârtie; Stegulețe decorative din hârtie; Stegulețe din hârtie; Fanioane de hârtie; Pancarte din hârtie sau carton; Decorațiuni de hârtie pentru masă; Decorațiuni din hârtie pentru prăjituri; Ghirlande decorative din hârtie pentru petreceri; Bannere de afișaj fabricate din carton; Bannere de afișaj realizate din hârtie; Afișe tipărite din hârtie; Decalcomanii de perete; Decorațiuni de petreceri din hârtie metalică; Paspartuuri din hârtie pentru fotografii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Papierové aplikácie; Dekoratívne papierové ozdoby na stred stola; Papierové ozdoby na torty; Papierové girlandy; Papierové ozdoby na oslavy; Papierové stolové vlajky; Papierové trojcípe vlajočky; Papierové zástavy; Zástavky, vlajky z papiera; Papierové alebo lepenkové pútače; Papierové ozdoby na stôl; Papierové ozdoby na koláč; Papierové ozdobné girlandy na oslavy; Vývesné tabule z kartónu; Vývesné tabule vyrobené z papiera; Tlačené papierové značky; Nálepky na stenu; Pokovované papierové ozdoby na oslavy; Papierové pomôcky na upevnenie obrázkov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Aplikacije iz papirja; Papirnate dekoracije za na mizo; Papirnati okraski za torte; Girlande iz papirja; Papirnati okraski za zabave; Papirnati transparenti; Papirnate okrasne zastavice; Zastavice (papirnate); Zastavice iz papirja; Plakati iz papirja ali kartona; Namizne dekoracije iz papirja; Papirnate dekoracije za torte; Okrasne girlande iz papirja, za zabave; Reklamni transparenti iz kartona; Reklamni transparenti iz papirja; Tiskane papirnate označbe; Odtisi [dekalkomanije] za steno; Okraski za zabave iz kovinskega papirja; Papirnati okvirji za slike.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Applikationer av papper; Pappersdekorationer för bord; Papperspynt för tårtor av papper; Pappersgirlanger; Festdekorationer av papper; Pappersfanor; Flaggdekorationer av papper; Flaggor av papper; Vimplar av papper; Plakat av papper eller kartong; Bordsdekorationer av papper; Tårtdekorationer av papper; Dekorativa pappersgirlanger för fester; Banderoller tillverkade av kartong; Banderoller av papper; Tryckta pappersskyltar; Väggdekaler; Festdekorationer av metallpapper; Bakgrundspapper för bilder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Орнаменти и декорации, всички за коледни дръвчета; Украшения за коледни елхи; Играчки, произвеждащи забавни шумове, за партита; Играчки маски; Конфети; Маски за костюми; Маски за Вси Светии; Играчки маски; Украси, играчки за партита, танци; Хартиени кукли; Хартиени маски за лице; Хартиени шапки [украшения за парти]; Малки хартиени подаръци за парти; Хартиени парти шапки; Празнични шапки; Парти попърс; Шапки за парти, от пластмаса; Балони; Парцалени кукли.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Ozdoby a dekorace na vánoční stromky; Vánoční ozdoby; Drobné zvukové hračky na večírky; Karnevalové masky; Konfety; Karnevalové masky; Masky na Halloween; Masky [na hraní]; Zábavné předměty na večírky a plesy; Papírové panenky; Papírové masky na tvář; Papírové klobouky (drobné zboží na večírky); Papírové zboží na večírky; Papírové klobouky na večírky; Žertovné pokrývky hlavy na oslavy; Vystřelovací konfety na večírky; Plastové klobouky na večírky; Balónky na hraní; Hadrové panenky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Dekorationer og pynt til juletræer; Juletræspynt; Legetøj til frembringelse af støj til festbrug (festartikler); Karnevalsmasker; Konfetti; Kostumemasker; Halloweenmasker; Masker [lejetøj]; Legetøjsartikler til fester; Papirdukker; Papirmasker; Papirhatte [festartikler]; Papirmærker og -sløjfer til at bære på tøjet til fester; Festhatte af papir; Hatte til festlige lejligheder; Bordbomber [festartikler]; Festhatte af plastik; Legetøjsballoner; Kludedukker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Christbaumschmuck und -verzierungen; Christbaumschmuck; Geräusche erzeugendes Partyspielzeug; Faschingsmasken; Konfetti; Kostümmasken; Halloween-Masken; Masken [Spielzeug]; Spaßartikel für Partys; Papierpuppen; Papiermasken; Papierhüte [Partyscherzartikel]; Partyscherzartikel aus Papier; Partyhüte aus Papier; Scherzartikel in Form von Hüten; Tischfeuerwerk [Partyartikel]; Partyhüte aus Kunststoff; Luftballons [Spielwaren]; Lumpenpuppen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διακοσμητικά και στολίδια χριστουγεννιάτικων δέντρων· Διακοσμητικά χριστουγεννιάτικων δέντρων· Πρωτότυπα παιχνίδια που βγάζουν ήχο για πάρτι· Μάσκες παιχνιδιού· Χαρτοπόλεμος (κονφετί)· Μάσκες μεταμφίεσης· Αποκριάτικες μάσκες· Μάσκες παιχνιδιού· Αποκριάτικα είδη [κοτιγιόν]· Χάρτινες κούκλες· Χάρτινες μάσκες προσώπου· Χάρτινα καπέλα για πάρτι (πρωτότυπα είδη για πάρτι)· Χάρτινα ενθύμια για πάρτι· Χάρτινα καπέλα για πάρτι· Καπέλα για πάρτι· Συσκευές εκτόξευσης κομφετί για πάρτι· Πλαστικά καπέλα για πάρτι· Μπαλόνια· Πάνινες κούκλες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Decorations and ornaments for Christmas trees; Decorations for Christmas trees; Novelty noisemaker toys for parties; Carnival masks; Confetti; Costume masks; Halloween masks; Masks [playthings]; Novelty toys for parties; Paper dolls; Paper face-masks; Paper hats [party novelties]; Paper party favours; Paper party hats; Party favor hats; Party poppers [party novelties]; Plastic party hats; Play balloons; Rag dolls.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Decoraciones y adornos para árboles de Navidad; Adornos para árboles de Navidad; Juguetes sonoros de fantasía para fiestas; Máscaras de carnaval; Confetis; Máscaras de disfraz; Máscaras de Halloween (víspera de Todos los Santos); Máscaras [juguetes]; Artículos de cotillón; Muñecas de papel; Caretas de papel; Sombreros de papel [artículos para fiesta]; Artículos de papel para fiestas; Sombreros de papel para fiestas [artículos de cotillón]; Sombreros de fiesta; Lanzadores de serpentinas y confetis; Sombreros plásticos para fiestas; Globos de juego; Muñecas de trapo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Jõulupuuehted; Jõulukuuseehted; Müratekitamislelud [peotarbed]; Karnevalimaskid; Konfetid; Maskid (mänguasjad); Halloweenimaskid; Maskid (mänguasjad); Karnevalitarbed, peotarbed; Pabernukud; Paberist näomaskid; Pabermütsid [peokaubad]; Paberist peokaubad; Paberist peomütsid; Peomütsid; Serpentiinid [peokaubad]; Plastist peomütsid; Õhupallid (mänguasjad); Kaltsunukud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Joulukuusen koristeet; Joulukuusenkoristeet; Leluräikät juhliin; Leikkinaamarit; Konfetit; Naamiaispukunaamarit; Halloween-naamiot; Leikkinaamarit; Pikkulahjat kutsuja ja juhlia varten; Paperinuket; Paperinaamiot; Paperihatut (juhlatarvikkeet); Paperiset vieraslahjat juhliin; Paperiset juhlahatut; Hatut juhlissa annettaviksi; Paukkuraketit juhliin; Muoviset bilehatut; Ilmapallot; Räsynuket.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Décorations et ornements pour sapins de Noël; Décorations pour sapins de Noël; Jouets fantaisie sonores pour fêtes; Masques de carnaval; Confettis; Masques de déguisement; Masques d'Halloween; Masques [jouets]; Objets de cotillon; Poupées en carton; Masques pour le visage en papier; Chapeaux en papier [articles de fêtes]; Cotillons en papier; Chapeaux de cotillon en papier; Chapeaux de fête [accessoires de cotillon]; Bombes de table pour fêtes; Chapeaux de fête en plastique; Ballons de jeu; Poupées chiffon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Dekoracije i ukrasi za božićna drvca; Ukrasi za božićna drvca; Šaljive trubice za zabave; Karnevalske maske; Konfeti; Karnevalske maske; Maske za noć vještica; Karnevalske maske; Oprema za izvođenje pošalica; Papirnate lutke; Papirnate maske za lice; Papirnati šeširi [maštoviti predmeti za zabavu]; Papirnati artikli za zabave; Šeširi od papira za zabave; Šaljiva pokrivala za glavu; Eksplozivni konfeti; Plastični šeširi za zabave; Baloni; Lutke od krpe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Dísztárgyak és dekorációk karácsonyfákra; Karácsonyfadíszek; Zajkeltő játékkacatok partikhoz; Játékálarcok; Konfetti; Karneváli álarcok; Halloween álarcok; Játékálarcok; Parti kellékek; Papír játék babák; Papír arcmaszkok; Papírból készült parti kalapok; Papírból készült parti kellékek; Parti kalapok papírból; Fejfedők partikhoz; Parti konfettiágyúk; Műanyag partikalapok; Léggömbök; Rongybabák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Decorazioni e ornamenti per alberi di Natale; Decorazioni per alberi di Natale; Giocattoli musicali per feste; Maschere da carnevale; Coriandoli; Maschere per feste in maschera; Maschere per Halloween; Maschere [giocattoli]; Oggetti per cotillon; Bambole di carta; Maschere di carta per il viso; Cappelli di carta [oggetti per feste]; Articoli di carta per feste; Cappellini in carta per le feste; Cappelli per feste; Petardi per feste [oggetti per feste]; Cappelli in plastica per feste; Palloni da gioco; Bambole di pezza.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kalėdų eglučių papuošalai ir dekoracijos; Kalėdų eglučių papuošalai; Žaisliniai triukšmą sukeliantys vakarėlių niekučiai; Karnavalo kaukės; Konfeti; Maskaradinės kaukės; Helovino kaukės; Žaidimų kaukės; Pramoginių renginių prizai; Popierinės lėlės; Popierinės veido kaukės; Popierinės skrybėlės [pobūvių niekučiai]; Popieriniai pobūvių suvenyrai; Popierinės pobūvių kepurės; Šventinės kepurėlės; Šventinės papliauškos; Plastikinės vakarėlių kepuraitės; Žaidimų balionai; Skudurinės lėlės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ziemassvētku eglīšu ornamenti un rotājumi; Eglīšu rotājumi; Izjokojošas trokšņus radošas rotaļlietas viesībām; Karnevāla maskas; Konfeti; Kostīmu maskas; Helovīna maskas; Rotaļu maskas; Rotaļu preces ballītēm; Papīra lelles; Sejas maskas no papīra; Papīra cepures [viesību piederumi]; Svinību piederumi no papīra; Papīra cepures ballītēm; Papīra cepures sarīkojumiem; Plaukšķenes ballītēm; Viesību cepures no plastmasas; Rotaļu baloni; Lupatu lellītes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ornamenti u dekorazzjonijiet tas-siġra tal-Milied; Dekorazzjonijiet għas-siġar tal-Milied; Ġugarelli ġodda li jagħmlu l-ħsejjes għall-festini; Maskri tal-logħob; Konfetti; Maskri tal-kostumi; Maskri tal-Ħallowin; Maskri tal-logħob; Ġugarelli żgħar għal festini (Oġġetti bħala rigali żgħar lill-mistednin); Pupi tal-karti; Maskri tal-wiċċ tal-karta; Kpiepel tal-karta (rigali żgħar tal-festini); Oġġetti tal-karti għal festini; Kpiepel tal-karta għall-festini; Kpiepel tal-festini; Faqqaturi għall-festini; Kpiepel tal-festini tal-plastik; Bżieżaq; Pupi taċ-ċarruta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Decoraties en versierselen voor kerstbomen; Versierselen voor kerstbomen; Gadgets die lawaai maken voor feestjes; Carnavalsmaskers; Confetti; Kostuummaskers; Halloweenmaskers; Maskers [speelgoed]; Feestartikelen; Poppen van papier; Papieren gezichtsmaskers; Papieren hoedjes [feestartikelen]; Feestartikelen van papier; Feesthoedjes van papier; Feesthoedjes; Party-knallers; Plastic feesthoedjes; Ballen om te spelen; Lappenpoppen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dekoracje i ozdoby choinkowe; Ozdoby choinkowe; Zabawki [gadżety] na przyjęcia wydające głośne dźwięki; Maski zabawkowe; Konfetti; Maski kostiumowe; Maski na Halloween; Maski zabawkowe; Śmieszne gadżety na imprezy; Lalki papierowe; Maski papierowe; Czapeczki papierowe [akcesoria na przyjęcia]; Artykuły papierowe jako podarki dla gości na przyjęciach; Papierowe czapeczki na przyjęcia; Czapeczki na imprezę jako podarki dla gości; Tuby strzelające na imprezy; Kapelusze na przyjęcia z tworzyw sztucznych; Balony; Lalki szmaciane.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Decorações e ornamentos para árvores de Natal; Decorações para árvores de Natal; Brinquedos de fazer barulho para festas; Máscaras de carnaval; Confetti; Máscaras de disfarce; Máscaras para Halloween; Máscaras [artigos de brincar]; Brinquedos de partidas para festas; Bonecas de papel; Máscaras de papel para o rosto; Chapéus de papel [artigos para festas]; Artigos em papel para festas; Chapéus de festa em papel; Chapéus de carnaval; Artigos de estouro para festas; Chapéus de plástico para festas; Balões de brinquedo; Bonecas de trapos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ornamente pentru pomul de Crăciun; Decorațiuni (ornamente) pentru pomul de Crăciun; Jucării fantezie sonore pentru petreceri; Măști de carnaval; Confeti; Măști de carnaval; Măști de Halloween; Măști de carnaval; Cadouri surpriză pentru invitați la petreceri; Păpuși din hârtie; Măști din hârtie; Pălării din hârtie [articole pentru petreceri]; Articole din hârtie pentru petreceri; Pălării din hârtie pentru petreceri; Pălării de petrecere; Pocnitori pentru petreceri; Pălării din plastic pentru petreceri; Baloane; Păpuși făcute din cârpe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Okrasy a ozdoby na vianočné stromčeky; Ozdoby na vianočný stromček; Drobné darčeky v podobe zvukových hračiek na oslavy; Karnevalové masky; Konfety; Karnevalové masky; Masky na sviatok Halloween; Masky (hračky); Ozdoby alebo darčeky rozdávané hosťom pri večierkoch; Papierové bábiky; Papierové masky na tvár; Papierové klobúky ako zábavné drobnosti na večierky; Papierové spomienkové predmety a darčeky odovzdávané pri večierkoch; Papierové čiapky na spoločenské zábavy; Žartovné pokrývky hlavy; Vystreľovacie konfety; Plastové klobúky pre oslavy; Balóny na hranie; Handrové bábiky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Dekoracije in okraski za božična drevesca; Dekoracije za božična drevesa; Cenene igrače, ki povzročajo hrup, za zabave; Maske (igrače); Konfeti; Maske za kostume; Maske za noč čarovnic; Maske (igrače); Predmeti za potegavščine, zabavo, ples; Papirnate punčke; Papirnate obrazne maske; Papirnati klobučki [šaljivi izdelki za zabavo]; Papirnati izdelki za zabavo; Klobučki iz papirja za zabave; Pokrivala za zabave; Pokalice za zabave; Plastični klobuki za zabave; Baloni; Punčke iz cunj.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Prydnader och pynt för julgranar; Prydnader för julgranen; Skämtleksaker som ger ljud ifrån sig, för fester; Karnevalmasker; Konfetti; Utklädnadsmasker; Halloween-masker; Masker [leksaker]; Skämtartiklar för fester; Pappersdockor; Ansiktsmasker av papper; Pappershattar [festartiklar]; Pappersdekorationer för fester; Partyhattar av papper; Partyhattar; Partysmällare; Partyhattar av plast; Ballonger; Trasdockor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/074</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-20</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/142</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079124</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>22168</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017693360</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>22168</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-04-09</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
