<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-14T13:33:26</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224150</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224150</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>nl</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="2" status="1">Application under examination</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-04-15</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>HACCP-V</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>45</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Консултантски услуги, свързани със здравето и безопасността; Консултантски услуги, свързани с изготвяне на стандарти; Наблюдение на системи за сигурност; Услуги за оценка на риска във връзка със здравето и сигурността; Оценка на безопасността; Информационни услуги, свързани със здравето и безопасността; Информационни услуги свързани с безопасността; Инспекция на фабрики от съображения за сигурност; Консултации в областта на безопасността на работното място; Консултантски услуги в областта на националната сигурност; Управление на риска в областта на здравеопазването и безопасността; Консултация относно разпоредби за безопасност на труда.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Poradenské služby vztahující se k ochraně zdraví a bezpečnosti; Poradenské služby vztahující se k přípravě norem; Monitorování bezpečnostních systémů; Služby vyhodnocování rizik v oblasti zdraví a bezpečnosti; Hodnocení bezpečnosti; Informační služby týkající se zdraví a bezpečnosti; Informační služby vztahující se k bezpečnosti; Inspekce továren pro bezpečnostní účely; Konzultace v oboru bezpečnosti na pracovišti; Konzultační služby v oboru národní bezpečnosti; Řízení zdravotních a bezpečnostních rizik; Poradenství o bezpečnostních předpisech při práci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Konsulentvirksomhed vedrørende sundhed og sikkerhed; Rådgivningsvirksomhed vedrørende udarbejdelse af standarder; Overvågning af sikkerhedssystemer; Risikovurdering inden for sundhed og sikkerhed; Sikkerhedsevaluering; Information om sikkerhed i hverdagen; Information vedrørende sikkerhed; Sikkerhedsinspektion af fabrikker; Rådgivning vedrørende sikkerhed på arbejdspladsen; Rådgivning om national sikkerhed; Risikostyring inden for sundheds- og sikkerhedsrisici; Rådgivning vedrørende forskrifter om sikkerhed på arbejdspladsen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Beratungsdienste in Bezug auf Unversehrtheit und Sicherheit; Juristische Beratungsdienste betreffend der Vorbereitung von Normen; Überwachung von Sicherheitssystemen; Risikobewertung im Rahmen des Arbeitsschutzes; Sicherheitsbewertungen; Auskünfte in Bezug auf Unversehrtheit und Sicherheit; Informationen in Bezug auf Sicherheit; Überprüfung der Sicherheit von Fabriken; Beratung im Bereich der Arbeitsplatzsicherheit; Beratungsleistungen im Bereich der nationalen Sicherheit; Risikomanagement im Rahmen des Arbeitsschutzes; Beratungsdienste hinsichtlich Arbeitssicherheitsvorschriften.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σχετικά με την υγεία και την ασφάλεια· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σχετικά με την επεξεργασία προτύπων· Παρακολούθηση συστημάτων ασφαλείας· Υπηρεσίες εκτίμησης κινδύνων υγείας και ασφάλειας· Αξιολόγηση ασφάλειας· Υπηρεσίες πληροφόρησης σε σχέση με την υγεία και την ασφάλεια· Υπηρεσίες πληροφόρησης σε σχέση με την ασφάλεια· Επιθεώρηση εργοστασίων για λόγους ασφαλείας· Παροχή συμβουλών στον τομέα της ασφάλειας στον χώρο εργασίας· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών στον τομέα της εθνικής ασφάλειας· Διαχείριση κινδύνων υγείας και ασφάλειας· Παροχή συμβουλών σχετικά με προδιαγραφές ασφαλείας κατά την εργασία.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Consultancy services relating to health and safety; Advisory services relating to the preparation of standards; Monitoring of security systems; Health and safety risk assessment services; Safety evaluation; Information services relating to health and safety; Information services relating to safety; Inspection of factories for safety purposes; Consulting in the field of workplace safety; Consulting services in the field of national security; Health and safety risk management; Consultancy on regulations on safety at work.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de consultoría en materia de seguridad y salud; Servicios de asesoramiento relacionados con la preparación de normas; Control de sistemas de seguridad; Servicios de evaluación del riesgo para la salud y la seguridad; Evaluación de la seguridad; Servicios de información relacionados con la salud y la seguridad en el trabajo [prevención de riesgos laborales]; Servicios de información relacionados con la seguridad; Inspección de fábricas con fines de seguridad; Consultas en relación con la seguridad en el trabajo; Servicios de consultoría en el ámbito de la seguridad nacional; Gestión de riesgos para la salud y la seguridad; Asesoramiento sobre normas de seguridad en el trabajo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Töötervishoiu ja -ohutuse konsultatsiooniteenused; Standardite koostamise nõustamisteenused; Turvasüsteemide seire, järelevalve; Tervise- ja turvariski hindamise teenused; Ohutuse hindamine; Töötervishoiu- ja -ohutusinfoteenused; Ohutusteabeteenused; Tehaste turvakontroll; Tööohutuse konsultatsioonid; Konsultatsiooniteenused riigi julgeoleku alal; Tervise- ja truvariski juhtimine; Nõustamine tööohutuseeskirjade osas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Työsuojeluun liittyvät konsultointipalvelut; Standardien laatimiseen liittyvät neuvontapalvelut; Turvajärjestelmien seuranta; Työturvallisuusriskien arviointipalvelut; Turvallisuuden arviointi; Työsuojeluun liittyvät tiedotuspalvelut; Turvallisuuteen liittyvät tiedotuspalvelut; Tehtaiden turvallisuustarkastus; Työturvallisuuskonsultointi; Konsultointipalvelut kansallisen turvallisuuden alalla; Työturvallisuusriskien hallinta; Työturvallisuusmääräyksiä koskeva neuvonta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Consultation en matière de sécurité; Services de conseils concernant la préparation de normes [service juridique]; Surveillance de systèmes d'alarme de sécurité; Services d'évaluation des risques en matière de santé et de sécurité; Évaluation de la sécurité; Informations en matière d’hygiène et de sécurité au travail; Services d'informations liés à la sécurité; Inspection d'usines en matière de sécurité; Consultations dans le domaine de la sécurité au travail; Services de conseils dans le domaine de la sécurité nationale; Gestion des risques pour la santé et la sécurité; Conseil en matière de réglementation sur la sécurité au travail.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge savjetovanja u svezi sa zdravljem i sigurnosti; Savjetodavne usluge u svezi s pripremanjem standarda; Nadziranje [praćenje] sigurnosnih sustava; Usluge procjene zdravstvenog i sigurnosnog rizika; Procjena sigurnosti; Informativne usluge u svezi sa zdravljem i sigurnosti; Informacijske usluge u vezi sa sigurnošću; Inspekcija tvornica radi sigurnosti; Savjetovanje u području sigurnosti na radu; Usluge savjetovanja na području nacionalne sigurnosti; Upravljanje zdravstvenim i sigurnosnim rizicima; Savjetovanje o pravilima sigurnosti na radu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Egészséggel és biztonsággal kapcsolatos konzultációs szolgáltatások; Szabványok, normák kidolgozásával kapcsolatos tanácsadási szolgáltatások; Biztonsági rendszerek felügyelete; Egészséggel és biztonsággal kapcsolatos kockázatbecslési szolgáltatások; Biztonsági értékelés; Egészséggel és biztonsággal kapcsolatos információs szolgáltatások; Biztonsággal kapcsolatos tájékoztató szolgáltatások; Gyárak biztonsági célú vizsgálata; Munkavédelmi tanácsadás; Konzultációs szolgáltatások a nemzetbiztonság területén; Egészségügyi és biztonsági kockázatkezelés; Munkavédelmi előírásokra vonatkozó tanácsadás.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di consulenza in materia di salute e sicurezza; Servizi di consulenza in materia di creazione di standard; Controllo di sistemi di sicurezza; Servizi di valutazione del rischio in materia di salute e sicurezza; Valutazione della sicurezza; Servizi di informazione in materia di salute e sicurezza; Servizi di informazione in materia di sicurezza; Ispezione di fabbriche in materia di sicurezza; Consulenza in materia di sicurezza sul posto di lavoro; Servizi di consulenza in materia di sicurezza nazionale; Gestione del rischio in materia di salute e sicurezza; Consulenza su norme di sicurezza sul lavoro.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Konsultacinės paslaugos, susijusios su sveikata ir sauga; Standartų rengimo konsultacijos; Apsaugos sistemų stebėjimas; Sveikatos ir saugos rizikos įvertinimo paslaugos; Saugumo įvertinimas; Informacinės paslaugos, susijusios su sveikata ir saugumu; Informarcinės paslaugos, susijusios su sauga; Gamyklų tikrinimas saugumo tikslais; Darbo saugos konsultacijos; Konsultavimo paslaugos nacionalinio saugumo srityje; Sveikatos ir saugos rizikos valdymas; Konsultacijos darbo saugos nuostatų klausimais.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Konsultāciju pakalpojumi saistībā ar veselību un drošību; Konsultāciju pakalpojumi saistībā ar standartu sagatavošanu; Drošības sistēmu uzraudzība; Veselības un drošības riska novērtēšanas pakalpojumi; Drošības novērtēšana; Informācijas pakalpojumi saistībā ar veselību un drošību; Informācijas pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar drošību; Drošības pārbaudīšana rūpnīcās; Konsultācijas darbavietu drošības jomā; Konsultāciju pakalpojumi valsts drošības jomā; Veselības un drošības riska pārvaldība; Konsultāciju pakalpojumi darba drošības noteikumu jautājumos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' konsulenza relatati ma' saħħa u sigurtà; Servizzi ta' pariri dwar il-preparazzjoni ta' standards; Monitoraġġ ta' sistemi ta' sigurtà; Servizzi ta' valutazzjoni tar-riskju għas-saħħa u s-sigurtà; L-evalwazzjoni tas-sigurtà; Servizzi ta' informazzjoni relatati mas-saħħa u s-sigurtà; Servizzi ta' informazzjoni relatati mas-sigurtà; Spezzjoni ta' fabbriki għal skopijiet ta' sikurezza; Konsulenza fil-qasam tas-sikurezza fuq il-post tax-xogħol; Servizzi ta' konsulenza fil-qasam tas-sigurtà nazzjonali; Ġestjoni tar-riskju għas-saħħa u s-sigurtà; Konsulenza dwar regolamenti tas-sigurtà fuq il-post tax-xogħol.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Advisering inzake veilige en gezonde arbeidsomstandigheden; Advisering met betrekking tot het opstellen van normen; Controle van beveiligingssystemen; Diensten inzake risicobeoordeling met betrekking tot gezondheid en veiligheid; Evaluatie op het gebied van veiligheid; Informatie inzake veilige en gezonde arbeidsomstandigheden; Informatiediensten met betrekking tot veiligheid; Inspectie van fabrieken voor veiligheidsdoeleinden; Veiligheid op de werkplek (Advisering inzake -); Raadgeving op het gebied van nationale veiligheid; Risicobeheer op het gebied van gezondheid en veiligheid; Voorschriften met betrekking tot veiligheid op het werk (Raadgeving inzake -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi konsultacyjne w zakresie bezpieczeństwa i higieny pracy; Usługi doradztwa związane z przygotowywaniem standardów; Monitoring systemów bezpieczeństwa; Usługi szacowania ryzyka w zakresie zdrowia i bezpieczeństwa; Ocena bezpieczeństwa; Usługi informacyjne w zakresie bezpieczeństwa i zdrowia; Usługi informacyjne w zakresie bezpieczeństwa; Kontrola fabryk dla celów bezpieczeństwa; Doradztwo w zakresie bezpieczeństwa miejsca pracy; Usługi doradcze w dziedzinie bezpieczeństwa narodowego; Zarządzanie ryzykiem związanym ze zdrowiem i bezpieczeństwem; Doradztwo w zakresie norm bezpieczeństwa w pracy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de consultadoria relacionados com higiene e segurança; Serviços de assessoria em matéria de preparação de normas; Monitorização de sistemas de segurança; Serviços de avaliação de riscos para a saúde e a segurança; Serviços de avaliação de segurança; Serviços de informação relacionados com higiene e segurança; Serviços de informação relacionados com segurança; Inspeção de fábricas para fins de segurança; Consultadoria no domínio da segurança no local de trabalho; Serviços de consultadoria no domínio da segurança nacional; Gestão de riscos para a saúde e a segurança; Consultadoria em matéria de normas de segurança no trabalho.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de consultanță în materie de sănătate și siguranță; Servicii de consiliere cu privire la întocmirea de standarde; Monitorizarea sistemelor de securitate; Servicii de evaluare a riscului pentru sănătate și siguranță; Evaluarea gradului de siguranță; Servicii de informare cu privire la sănătate și siguranță; Servicii de informare referitoare la siguranță; Inspectarea uzinelor în scopuri de securitate; Consultanță în domeniul siguranței la locul de muncă; Servicii de consultanță în domeniul securității naționale; Administrarea riscurilor pentru sănătate și siguranță; Consultanță în materie de securitate în muncă.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Konzultačné služby v oblasti zdravia a bezpečnosti; Poradenské služby vzťahujúce sa k príprave noriem; Monitorovanie bezpečnostných systémov; Služby v oblasti hodnotenia zdravotného a bezpečnostného rizika; Hodnotenie bezpečnosti; Informačné služby súvisiace so zdravím a bezpečnosťou; Informačné služby týkajúce sa bezpečnosti; Bezpečnostné prehliadky tovární; Poradenstvo týkajúce sa bezpečnosti na pracovisku; Poradenské služby v oblasti národnej bezpečnosti; Riadenie zdravotných a bezpečnostných rizík; Poradenstvo o bezpečnostných predpisoch pri práci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Svetovalne storitve na področju zaščite zdravja in varnosti na delovnem mestu in na javnih prostorih; Svetovalne storitve v zvezi s pripravo standardov; Nadzor varnostnih sistemov; Storitve ocenjevanja tveganja zdravja in varnosti; Ocena varnosti; Informacijske storitve na področju zaščite zdravja in varnosti na delovnem mestu in na javnih prostorih; Informacijske storitve v zvezi z varnostjo; Nadziranje tovarn za varnostne namene; Svetovanje na področju varnosti na delovnem mestu; Svetovalne storitve na področju nacinalne varnosti; Upravljanje tveganj za zdravje in varnost; Svetovanje o predpisih za varnost pri delu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Konsulttjänster avseende hälsa och säkerhet (arbetsskydd); Rådgivningstjänster avseende utarbetande av standarder; Granskning av säkerhetssystem; Tjänster avseende bedömning av hälso- och säkerhetsrisker; Säkerhetsutvärderingar; Information avseende hälsa och säkerhet (arbetsskydd); Informationstjänster rörande säkerhet; Inspektion av fabriker för säkerhetsändamål; Rådgivande tjänster inom området arbetsplatssäkerhet; Konsulttjänster inom området för nationell säkerhet; Riskhantering för hälsa och säkerhet; Konsultation avseende föreskrifter för arbetsskydd.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
