<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-28T11:45:22</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224174</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224174</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-23</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>sv</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-09-28</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>np NORDISKA PLAST</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162203561</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/224/018224174/000162203561.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.04</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.05</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.18</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.22</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.24</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.98</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.04.99</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.01</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>26.11.08</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.22</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.14</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>27.99.16</CategoryCode>
          <CategoryCode>29.01.02</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>8</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Ножарски изделия и прибори за хранене.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nože, vidličky a lžíce.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Knivsmedevarer, gafler og skeer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Messerschmiedewaren, Gabeln und Löffel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Όργανα κοπής, Μαχαιροπήρουνα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Cutlery.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Artículos de cuchillería, tenedores y cucharas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Noad, kahvlid, lusikad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Aterimet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Coutellerie, fourchettes et cuillers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pribor za jelo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Evőeszközök.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Coltelleria, forchette e cucchiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Peiliai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Galda piederumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pożati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Messenmakerswaren, vorken en lepels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Wyroby nożownicze.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cuteleria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cuţite, furculiţe şi linguri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nožiarsky tovar a príbory.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Noži, vilice in žlice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bestick.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>20</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Складови етажерки; Папки за съхранение на списания; Кошове за съхранение; Чекмеджета за съхранение; Шкафове; Шкафчета с ключ; Рафтове за складове; Макари от пластмаса за съхранение на маркучи; Приспособления за складиране; Кутии за нуждите на съхранението [пластмасови]; Пазарски кошници; Преносими кутии [контейнери] от пластмаса; Преносими туби [контейнери] за вода от пластмаса; Пластмасови капаци за консерви; Пластмасови кошчета [друг от кофи за боклук]; Кошове, неметални; Табуретки за крака; Каци, бъчви, бурета, неметални; Кошчета от пластмаса за приготвяне на компост.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Skladovací regály a police; Stojany na časopisy; Skladovací koše; Skladovací zásuvky; Skříně (kuchyňské); Uzamykatelné skříňky; Regály [nábytek]; Cívky z plastů pro ukládání hadic; Skladovací jednotky; Plastové krabice na skladování; Nákupní koše; Plastové přenosné boxy (nádoby); Plastové přenosné nádoby na vodu; Plastová víčka na plechovky; Plastové nádoby (s výjimkou odpadkových košů); Košíky, ne kovové; Stoličky; Sudy, ne kovové; Plastové kontejnery na výrobu kompostu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Opbevaringsstativer; Samlebind til opbevaring af blade; Kurve til opbevaring; Opbevaringsskuffer; Skabe; Skuffer; Reoler [møbler]; Ruller af plastik til opbevaring af slanger; Lagerenheder; Kasser af plastik til opbevaringsformål; Indkøbskurve; Bærbare æsker [beholdere] af plastic; Transportable vandbeholdere fremstillet af plastik; Plasticlåg til dåser; Plasticspande [andre end skraldespande]; Kurve, ikke af metal; Fodskamler; Tønder, ikke af metal; Plasticspande til kompostering.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Lagerregale; Zeitschriftenordner; Aufbewahrungskörbe; Kommoden für Aufbewahrungszwecke; Schränke; Schubladen; Regale; Haspeln aus Kunststoff für die Aufbewahrung von Schläuchen; Lagereinheiten; Kunststoffkästen für Aufbewahrungszwecke; Einkaufskörbe; Tragbare Kunststoffboxen [Behälter]; Tragbare Wasserbehälter aus Kunststoff; Kunststoffdeckel für Dosen; Kunststoffbehälter [ausgenommen Mülltonnen]; Körbe, nicht aus Metall; Schemel; Fässer [kleine], nicht aus Metall; Kunststoffbehälter zum Kompostieren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ράφια φύλαξης· Αρχειοθέτες αποθήκευσης περιοδικών· Καλάθια αποθήκευσης· Συρτάρια φύλαξης αντικειμένων· Ντουλάπια· Φοριαμοί· Ράφια για αποθήκευση· Πλαστικά έλικτρα αποθήκευσης εύκαμπτων σωλήνων· Μονάδες αποθήκευσης· Κουτιά για αποθηκευτική χρήση (από πλαστικό)· Καλάθια για τα ψώνια· Φορητά κιβώτια (δοχέια) από πλαστικό· Δοχεία μεταφοράς ύδατος κατασκευασμένα από πλαστικές ύλες· Πλαστικά καπάκια για κουτιά· Πλαστικοί κάδοι (εκτός από σκουπιδοτενεκέδες)· Καλάθια, μη μεταλλικά· Σκαμπό· Κάδοι μη μεταλλικοί· Δοχεία από πλαστικό για την παρασκευή κοπροχώματος.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Storage racks; magazine storage files; storage baskets; storage drawers; cupboards; lockers; shelves; reels of plastic for the storage of hose; storage units; plastic boxes for storage purposes; shopping baskets; portable boxes (containers) of plastic; portable water carriers (containers) made of plastics; plastic lids for cans; plastic bins (other than dust bins); baskets, non-metallic; stools; barrels, not of metal; bins of plastics for making compost.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Estanterías de almacenamiento; Archivos para guardar revistas; Cestas de almacenamiento; Cajones de almacenamiento; Armarios empotrados; Cajones; Estantes [muebles]; Carretes de plástico para el almacenamiento de mangueras; Unidades de almacenaje; Cajas para almacenaje [plástico]; Cestas para la compra; Cajas portátiles de materias plásticas [recipientes]; Recipientes portátiles para llevar agua hechos de materias plásticas; Tapas de plástico para latas; Cubos de plástico [exceptuando los cubos de basura]; Cestos no metálicos; Taburetes; Barriles no metálicos; Cubos de plástico para hacer compost.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ladustamisriiulid; Ajakirjahoidlid; Hoiukorvid; Hoiusahtlid; Seinakapid; Lukustatavad hoiukapid; Väikesed riiulid [mööbel]; Plastist voolikupoolid; Hoiuvahendid; Plastist ladustuskarbid, -kastid; Kandekotid; Teisaldatavad plastkastid, -karbid [mahutid]; Teisaldatavad plastmahutid vee kandmiseks [konteinerid]; Purkide plastkaaned; Plastist kastid, konteinerid, v.a prügikastid; Korvid, v.a metallist; Taburetid; Tünnid, v.a metallist; Plastist kompostikastid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Varastointitelineet; Aikakauslehtien säilytyskansiot; Korit säilyttämistä varten; Säilytyslaatikot; Kaapit; Lukittavat kaapit; Hyllyt [kaluste]; Muoviset kelat letkujen säilytykseen; Säilytysyksiköt; Muovilaatikot varastointitarkoituksiin; Ostoskorit; Siirrettävät muovilaatikot [säiliöt]; Kannettavat vedenkuljetusvälineet (säilytysastiat) muovista; Muovikannet kannuihin; Muovikorit [muut kuin roskakorit]; Korit, ei-metalliset; Jakkarat; Ei-metalliset tynnyrit; Muovisäiliöt kompostointiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Étagères de rangement; Classeurs pour le rangement de magazines; Paniers de rangement; Tiroirs de rangement; Placards; Tiroirs; Étagères; Dévidoirs en matières plastiques pour le rangement de tuyaux flexibles; Unités de stockage; Boîtes de rangement en matières plastiques; Paniers à provisions; Boîtes portatives [récipients] en plastique; Récipients à eau portables en matières plastiques [conteneurs]; Couvercles en plastique pour boîtes de conserve; Boîtes en plastique autres que poubelles; Paniers non métalliques; Tabourets; Barils non métalliques; Récipients en matières plastiques pour la production de compost.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Police za skladištenje; Police za skladištenje časopisa; Košare za skladištenje; Skladišne ladice; Ormari; Ormari s bravama; Stalaže; Plastična vitla za spremanje crijeva; Police; Kutije za pohranu [plastične]; Košare za kupovinu; Prijenosne kutije [spremnici] od plastike; Prijenosni spremnici za vodu [posude] od plastike; Plastični poklopci za limenke; Plastične kante [osim kanti za smeće]; Košare, nemetalne; Stolice bez naslona; Nemetalne bačve; Spremnici od plastike za kompost.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tároló állványok; Folyóirattartó mappák; Tárolókosarak; Fiókos tárolók; Gardróbszekrények; Fiókok; Állványok, polcok; Műanyag orsók tömlő tárolására; Tároló egységek; Dobozok raktározási célra [műanyag]; Bevásárlókosarak; Hordozható műanyag dobozok [tárolók]; Hordozható vízhordók [tárolók] műanyagból; Műanyag fedők, tetők konzervdobozokhoz; Műanyag tárolók [kivéve szemetesedények]; Nem fém kosarak; Zsámolyok; Nem fémből készült hordók; Műanyagládák komposztáláshoz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Scaffalature per magazzini; Schedari per conservazione di riviste; Cestini per riordino; Cassetti per riporre articoli; Stipi; Armadietti con serratura; Scaffalature; Bobine di plastica per lo stoccaggio di tubi flessibili; Unità di deposito; Scatole per magazzinaggio [plastica]; Cestelli per la spesa; Scatole trasportabili [contenitori] di plastica; Recipienti portatili per acqua [contenitori] in plastica; Coperchi in plastica per lattine; Bidoni di plastica [non bidoni della spazzature]; Cesti, non in metallo; Sgabelli; Barili non metallici; Bidoni in plastica per compostaggio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Sandėliavimo stelažai; Žurnalų laikymo aplankai; Sandėliavimo pintinės; Komodos; Spintos; Rakinamosios spintelės, dėžės, stalčiai; Lentynos [baldai]; Plastikinės ritės žarnoms laikyti; Sandėliavimo įtaisai; Dėžės sandėliavimo reikmėms [plastikinės]; Pirkinių krepšiai; Kilnojamosios plastikinės dėžės [talpyklos]; Nešiojamosios plastikinės vandens talpyklos; Plastikiniai skardinių dangteliai; Plastikinės dėžės [išskyrus šiukšliadėžes]; Ne metaliniai krepšiai; Taburetės; Ne metalinės statinės; Plastikinės talpyklos, skirtos kompostui gaminti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Uzglabāšanas plaukti; Žurnālu uzglabāšanas mapes; Mantu glabāšanas grozi; Glabāšanas atvilktnes; Skapji; Aizslēdzami skapīši; Plaukti; Plastmasas spoles šļūteņu glabāšanai; Noliktavu sekcijas; Kārbas uzglabāšanas nolūkiem (plastmasas); Iepirkumu somas; Pārvietojamas kastes [konteineri] no plastmasas; Pārnēsājamas plastmasas ūdenstvertnes; Kannu plastmasas vāki; Plastmasas tvertnes kas nav paredzētas atkritumiem; Nemetāliski grozi; Kāju soliņš; Nemetāliskas mucas; Plastmasas tvertnes komposta veidošanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Xtillieri tal-ħażna; Fajls għall-ħżin ta' magazins; Basktijiet għall-ħażna; Kxaxen għall-ħażna; Armarji; Kaxxarizzi; Xkafef; Irkiekel tal-plastik għall-ħażna ta' pajpijiet; Armarju fejn terfa'; Kaxex tal-plastik għal skopijiet ta' ħażna; Basktijiet tax-xiri; Kaxex li jistgħu jinġarru [kontenituri] tal-plastik; Ġarer tal-ilma li jistgħu jinġarru [reċipjenti] magħmula mill-plastik; Għotjien tal-plastik għal laned; Bramel tal-plastik [għajr bramel taż-żibel]; Basktijiet, mhux tal-metall; Banketti; Btieti, mhux tal-metall; Tankijiet tal-plastik għat-tħejjija tal-kompost.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Opbergrekken; Tijdschriftenrekken; Opslagmanden; Opslagladen; Kasten; Schuifladen; Rekken [stellingen]; Plastic slanghaspels; Opslageenheden; Dozen voor opslagdoeleinden [plastic]; Boodschappenmanden; Draagbare dozen van plastic [containers]; Draagbare watertanks [houders] gemaakt van plastic; Dekseltjes (Plastic -) voor blikjes; Plastic bakken [anders dan vuilnisbakken]; Manden, niet van metaal; Zitkrukjes; Vaten, niet van metaal; Bakken van plastic voor het maken van compost.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Regały do przechowywania; Teczki do magazynowania czasopism; Kosze do przechowywania; Szuflady do przechowywania przedmiotów; Szafy wnękowe; Szafki zamykane; Regały [meble]; Bębny z tworzyw sztucznych do przechowywania węży ogrodowych; Szafki; Pudełka do przechowywania [z tworzyw sztucznych]; Koszyki na zakupy; Pudełka przenośne [pojemniki] z tworzyw sztucznych; Przenośne zbiorniki na wodę [pojemniki] z tworzyw sztucznych; Pokrywki z tworzyw sztucznych do puszek; Kosze z tworzyw sztucznych [inne niż kosze na śmieci]; Kosze niemetalowe; Taborety; Niemetalowe beczułki; Pojemniki z tworzyw sztucznych do wytwarzania kompostu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Estantes de armazenamento; Pastas para armazenamento de revistas; Cestos para arrumos; Gavetas de armazenamento; Closets; Cacifos; Estantes [mobiliário]; Enroladores em matérias plásticas para guardar mangueiras; Unidades de armazenamento; Caixas para armazenagem [em plástico]; Cestos de compras; Caixas portáteis em plástico [recipientes]; Bidões portáteis de plástico para transporte de água; Tampas de plástico para latas; Caixotes de plástico [sem ser caixotes de lixo]; Cestos, não metálicos; Tamboretes; Barris, não metálicos; Caixotes em matérias plásticas para compostagem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Rafturi de depozitare; Dosare pentru păstrarea revistelor; Cosuri pentru stocare; Sertare de depozitare; Dulapuri pentru haine; Dulăpioare; Etajere; Bobine din plastic pentru depozitarea furtunului; Mobile pentru depozitare; Cutii de depozitare [plastic]; Coşuri pentru cumpărături; Cutii portabile [recipiente] din plastic; Recipiente de apă portabile confecţionate din plastic; Capace din plastic pentru conserve; Coşuri din plastic [altele decât coşurile de gunoi]; Coşuri, nemetalice; Taburete; Butoiaşe nemetalice; Coşuri din plastic pentru fabricarea compostului.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Regály a police na skladovanie; Stojany na časopisy; Skladovacie koše; Skladovacie zásuvky; Príborníky; Záklopky; Police (samostatne stojaci nábytok); Plastové cievky na skladovanie hadíc; Skladovacie jednotky; Škatule na skladovacie účely [plastové]; Nákupné tašky; Plastové prenosné škatule [nádoby]; Plastové prenosné cisterny na vodu [nádoby]; Plastové viečka na plechovky; Plastové koše a nádoby [s výnimkou košov na smeti]; Nekovové koše; Taburetky; Nekovové súdky; Plastové kompostovacie nádoby.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Stojala za shranjevanje (regali); Omarice za shranjevanje revij; Koši za skladiščenje; Shranjevalni predali; Vzidne omare; Omarice s ključavnico; Regali; Koluti iz plastike za shranjevanje gumijastih cevi; Hrambne enote; Plastične škatle za shranjevanje; Nakupovalne torbe; Prenosne plastične škatle [zaboji]; Prenosne plastične posode za vodo; Plastični pokrovi za konzerve; Plastični koši [razen košev za smeti]; Nekovinske košare; Pručke; Nekovinski sodi; Zaboji iz plastike za proizvodnjo komposta.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Förvaringshyllor; förvaringsanordningar för tidskrifter; förvaringskorgar; förvaringslådor; förvaringsmöbler; förvaringsskåp; hyllor; vindor av plast för förvaring av slangar; kombimöbler för förvaring; plastaskar för förvaringsändamål; kundkorgar; bärbara behållare av plast; bärbara vattenbehållare av plast; plastlock för burkar; plasttunnor (inte soptunnor); korgar, inte av metall; pallar; tunnor, inte av metall; tunnor av plast för kompostering.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Кофи за боклук; Пластмасови кошчета [кошчета за смет]; Съдове за напитки; Контейнери за съхранение на храна; Купички за пиене за домашни любимци; Градинарски лейки; Дозиращи лъжички за кафе; Буркани; Фунии; Купи; Кухненски прибори; Сокоизстисквачки за плодови сокове; Уреди за мачкане на храна; Цедки; Подноси за храна; Дъски за рязане на месо; Стъклени чаши за пиене; Купи и халби; Чинии; Кошници за хляб за домакински цели; Разделители за прибори за хранене за чекмедже; Стойки/сушилници за сушене на чинии; Кошници за прибори за хранене; Корита за пране; Ведра; Кошчета за изхвърляне на хартия.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Nádoby na odpad; Odpadkové koše z plastu; Nádoby na nápoje; Nádoby na ukládání potravin; Misky na pití pro domácí zvířata; Konve na zalévání; Naběračky na kávu; Nádoby ze skla; Trychtýře; Misky; Kuchyňské náčiní; Ruční odšťavňovače na ovocné šťávy; Šťouchadla na jídlo; Cedníky; Jídelní podnosy; Prkénka na krájení; Sklenice na pití; Hrnky a šálky; Stolní talíře; Košíky na chleba pro použití v domácnosti; Přihrádky na příbory; Odkapávače na nádobí; Košíky na příbory; Vaničky na praní; Kbelíky; Odpadní koše na papír.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Skraldebøtter; Skraldespande i plast; Beholdere til drikkevarer; Beholdere til opbevaring af mad; Drikkeskåle til kæledyr; Vandkander; Kaffemåleskeer; Krukker; Tragte; Spølkum; Køkkenredskaber; Frugtjuicepressere; Mosere til mad [kartoffelmoser]; Sier; Madbakker; Forskærerbrætter; Drikkeglas; Kopper og krus; Tallerkner; Brødkurve til husholdningsbrug; Bestikbakker; Opvaskestativer; Bestikkurve; Vaskebaljer; Spande; Papirkurve.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Mülleimer; Abfallbehälter aus Kunststoff; Trinkbehälter; Vorratsbehälter für Lebensmittel; Trinkschalen für Haustiere; Gießkannen; Kaffeemaßlöffel; Kruggefäße; Trichter; Schalen; Küchengeräte; Reiben zur Herstellung von Fruchtsäften; Nahrungsmittelstampfer; Siebe; Tabletts; Tranchierbretter; Glaswaren für Getränke; Tassen und Becher; Geschirr; Brotkörbe für den Haushalt; Bestecktabletts; Abtropfständer; Besteckkörbe; Waschwannen; Eimer aller Art; Papierkörbe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δοχεία απορριμμάτων· Πλαστικοί κάδοι [σκουπιδοτενεκέδες]· Δοχεία ποτών· Δοχεία αποθήκευσης τροφίμων· Γαβάθες πόσης για κατοικίδια ζώα· Ποτιστήρια· Κουτάλια για τον καφέ· Κανάτα· Χωνιά· Γαβάθες· Σκεύη μαγειρικής χρήσης· Στίφτες για χυμούς φρούτων· Εργαλεία πολτοποίησης τροφίμων· Σουρωτήρια· Δίσκοι φαγητού· Πλάκες κοπής· Γυαλικά είδη για ποτά· Κύπελλα και κούπες· Πιατέλες· Καλάθια για το ψωμί, για οικιακή χρήση· Δίσκοι για μαχαιροπίρουνα· Σχάρες για το στέγνωμα των πιάτων· Καλάθια για μαχαιροπήρουνα· Λεκάνες πλυσίματος ρούχων· Κάδοι· Κάλαθοι απορριμμάτων χαρτιού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Dust bins; plastic bins (dust bins); drinks containers; food storage containers; pet drinking bowls; watering cans; coffee scoops; jars; funnels; bowl (basines); kitchen utensils; reamers for fruit juice; food mashers; strainers; meal trays; carving boards; drinking glasses; cups and mugs; table plates; bread baskets; cutlery trays; dish drying racks; cutlery baskets; washtubs; buckets; waste paper baskets.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Cubos de basura; Cubos de plástico [cubos de basura]; Recipientes para bebidas; Recipientes para almacenar alimentos; Cuencos de beber para animales domésticos; Regaderas; Cucharas medidoras de café; Botes (tarros); Embudos; Tazones (cuencos); Utensilios de cocina; Exprimidores para zumo de fruta; Pasapurés; Coladores; Bandejas para la comida; Tablas para trinchar; Cristalería para bebidas; Tazas y tazones; Platos; Cestas para el pan de uso doméstico; Bandejas de cubertería; Secadores de vajilla [escurreplatos]; Cestos para cuchillería; Tinas para lavar la ropa; Cubos; Papeleras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Prügikastid; Plastist prügikorvid; Joogimahutid, joogianumad; Anumad toidu hoidmiseks; Lemmikloomade joogikausid; Kastekannud; Kohvimõõdulusikad; Purgid; Lehtrid; Kausid, vaagnad; Köögitarbed; Käsimahlapressid; Toidupudrustajad; Kurnad; Toidukandikud; Lõikelauad; Joogiklaasid; Tassid ja kruusid; Taldrikud; Leivakorvid [majatarbed]; Söögiriistakarbid; Nõudekuivatusrestid; Söögiriistakorvid; Pesupalid; Panged, ämbrid; Paberikorvid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Roska-astiat; Muoviroskakorit [jätesäiliöt]; Juomasäiliöt; Elintarvikkeiden säilytysastiat; Lemmikkien juomakupit; Kastelukannut; Kahvimitat; Purkit; Suppilot; Vadit [astiat]; Keittokattilasarjat; Hedelmämehupusertimet; Elintarvikkeiden soseuttajat; Siivilät; Ateriatarjottimet; Leikkuulaudat; Lasiset juoma-astiat; Kupit ja mukit; Lautaset; Leipäkorit kotitalouskäyttöön; Ruokailuvälinelokerikot; Astiankuivaustelineet; Ruokailuvälinekorit; Pesupaljut; Sangot; Paperikorit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Poubelles; Poubelles en matières plastiques; Récipients pour boissons; Récipients pour la conservation d'aliments; Écuelles pour la boisson pour animaux domestiques; Arrosoirs; Cuillers à café; Pots [bocaux]; Entonnoirs; Bols; Ustensiles de cuisine; Presse-fruits pour jus de fruits; Pilons à légumes; Passoires; Plateaux-repas (vaisselle); Planches à découper; Verrerie pour boissons; Tasses et chopes; Assiettes; Corbeilles à pain à usage ménager; Range-couverts; Égouttoirs à vaisselle; Paniers à couverts; Cuves de lavage; Seaux; Corbeilles à papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kante za smeće; Plastične kante za otpatke [kante za smeće]; Posude za piće; Spremnici za hranu; Posude za pojenje kućnih ljubimaca; Kante za zalijevanje; Mjerne žličice za kavu; Tegle; Lijevci; Plitice [zdjelice]; Kuhinjski pribor; Cjedila za agrume; Gnječilice; Cjedila; Poslužavnici za jelo; Daske za rezanje; Stakleno posuđe za pića; Male i velike šalice; Tanjuri; Košare za kruh [za kućanstvo]; Držači pribora za jelo za ladice; Stalci za sušenje posuđa; Košare za pribor za jelo; Lužnice [posude za pranje rublja]; Vedra [drvene posude]; Koševi za otpadni papir.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szemeteskukák; Műanyag szemetesek; Italtartók; Tartók, dobozok élelmiszerek tárolásához; Ivótálak kedvtelésből tartott háziállatoknak; Locsolókannák, öntözőkannák; Kávéadagoló kanalak; Lekváros üvegek, befőttes üvegek; Tölcsérek; Mosdótálak, lavórok; Konyhai eszközök, kis méretű; Gyümölcsfacsarók gyümölcslé készítéséhez; Ételtörők; Szűrők [passzírozók]; Étkező tálcák; Vágódeszkák; Üvegáru italokhoz; Csészék és bögrék; Tányérok; Kenyérkosarak, háztartási célokra; Evőeszköztartók; Edényszárító állványok; Evőeszköz-tároló kosarak; Dézsák; Vödrök; Papírkosarak.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pattumiere; Bidoni in plastica [bidoni della spazzatura]; Contenitori per bibite; Contenitori per la conservazione degli alimenti; Ciotole per bere per animali domestici; Innaffiatoi; Cucchiaini da caffè; Caraffe; Imbuti; Bacinelle; Utensili da cucina; Spremifrutta per fare succhi di frutta; Utensili per schiacciare alimenti; Colini; Vassoi; Taglieri; Vetreria [bicchieri]; Bicchieri e tazze; Piatti; Cestini per il pane per uso domestico; Portaposate; Cestelli per asciugare i piatti; Cestini per coltelleria; Tinozze per il bucato; Secchi; Cestini per rifiuti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Atliekų dėžės; Plastikinės dėžės [šiukšlių dėžės]; Gėrimų tara; Talpyklos maistui laikyti; Kambarinių gyvūnėlių geriamieji dubenėliai; Laistytuvai; Kavos samteliai; Indai plačiu kakleliu; Piltuvėliai; Katiliukai; Virtuviniai indai; Vaisių sulčių spaustuvai; Maisto grūstukai; Koštuvai; Valgių padėklai; Pjaustymo lentos; Stiklinės; Puodeliai ir bokalai; Lėkštės; Duonos krepšeliai (buities reikmėms); Valgomųjų įrankių laikymo dėklai; Indų džiovinimo grotelės; Pintinės stalo įrankiams; Skalbimo dubenys; Kibirai; Šiukšliadėžės popieriui.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Atkritumu tvertnes; Plastmasas tvertnes [atkritumu tvertnes]; Trauki dzērieniem; Pārtikas uzglabāšanas tvertnes; Bļodiņas mājdzīvnieku dzirdināšanai; Lejkannas; Kafijas karotes; Burkas; Piltuves; Bļodas [tvertnes]; Virtuves trauki; Augļu sulas spiedes; Pārtikas stampas; Caurduri; Ēdienu paplātes; Griežamie dēlīši; Dzērienu glāzes; Tases un krūzes; Šķīvji; Maizes groziņi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Galda piederumu kastes; Trauku žāvēšanas plaukti; Grozi ar vāku; Veļas toveri; Spaiņi; Papīrgrozi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Landi taż-żibel; Kontenituri tal-plastik [laned taż-żibel]; Kontenituri għax-xorb; Kontenituri għall-ħażna tal-ikel; Skutelli tax-xorb għall-annimali domestiċi; Laned għat-tisqija; Sassli tal-kafè; Vażetti; Lenbut; Friskaturi [skutelli]; Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir; Għodda biex tagħsar il-meraq tal-frott; Għaffieġa tal-ikel; Passaturi; Trejs tal-ikel; Uċuħ biex tqatta' fuqhom; Tazzi tal-ħġieġ; Kikkri u maggijiet; Platti li fihom jisserva l-ikel; Basktijiet tal-ħobż għal skopijiet domestiċi; Gabarrejiet għall-pożati; Xtillieri għat-tnixxif tad-dixxijiet; Basktijiet għall-pożati; Banjijiet jew friskaturi tal-ħasil; Bramel; Laned għall-karti għar-rimi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Vuilnisbakken; Plastic bakken [afvalbakken]; Houders voor dranken; Houders voor de opslag van voedingsmiddelen; Drinkschalen voor huisdieren; Gieters; Koffiemaatschepjes; Bokalen; Trechters; Kommen; Keukengerei; Vruchtenpersen voor vruchtensap; Voedselstampers; Vergieten; Dienbladen voor maaltijden; Snijplanken; Drinkglazen; Kopjes en bekers; Borden; Broodmanden voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Bestekbakken; Vaatdroogrekken; Bestekmanden; Waskuipen; Kuipjes; Papiermanden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kosze na śmieci; Kosze z tworzyw sztucznych [kosze na śmieci]; Pojemniki do napojów; Pojemniki do przechowywania żywności; Miski do picia dla zwierząt domowych; Konewki; Miarki do kawy; Słoiki; Lejki; Miseczki; Przybory kuchenne; Wyciskarki do soku z owoców; Tłuczki kuchenne; Cedzaki; Tace na posiłki; Deski do krojenia; Naczynia szklane do napojów; Filiżanki i kubki; Talerze; Kosze na chleb do użytku domowego; Pojemniki z przegrodami do przechowywania sztućców; Suszarki-ociekacze do naczyń; Koszyki na sztućce; Balie; Kubły; Kosze na papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Caixotes do lixo; Baldes de plástico [baldes do lixo]; Recipientes para bebidas; Recipientes para o armazenamento de alimentos; Tigelas para beber para animais de estimação; Regadores; Medidores de café; Potes; Funis; Bacias [pias]; Utensílios para cozinha; Espremedores para sumos de fruta; Esmagadores de alimentos; Coadores; Bandejas para refeições; Tábuas para trinchar; Copos para bebidas; Taças e canecas; Louça; Cestos para pão, para uso doméstico; Tabuleiros para serviço de talheres; Suportes de secar louça; Cestos para cutelaria; Tanques para lavar roupa; Baldes; Cestos para papeis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Lăzi de gunoi; Coşuri de gunoi din plastic [cutii pentru gunoi]; Recipiente pentru băuturi; Recipiente pentru depozitarea alimentelor; Boluri pentru băut pentru animale de companie; Stropitori; Linguri de cafea; Borcane; Pâlnii; Chiuvete; Ustensile de bucătărie; Storcătoare pentru sucuri de fructe; Ustensile de zdrobit alimentele; Strecurători; Tăvi pentru servit masă; Tocătoare; Articole din sticlă pentru băuturi; Ceşti şi căni; Farfurii; Coşuri de pâine de uz casnic; Tăvi de tacâmuri; Suporturi pentru uscarea vaselor; Coșuri pentru tacâmuri; Căzi; Doniţe; Coşuri de hârtii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Smetné nádoby; Plastické smetníky [smetné koše]; Nádoby na nápoje; Skladovacie nádoby na jedlo; Misky na pitie pre domáce zvieratká; Polievacie kanvy; Naberačky na kávu; Poháre; Lieviky; Misy; Kuchynský riad; Ručné odšťavovače na citrusy; Mliaždiče na jedlo; Cedidlá; Podnosy na jedlo; Dosky na krájanie; Sklené poháre; Šálky a hrnčeky; Taniere; Košíky na chlieb pre domácnosť; Priehradky na zorganizovanie príborov; Stojany na odkvapkávanie riadu; Koše na prestieranie; Vane na pranie; Kade, putne; Odpadkové koše na papier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Smetnjaki; Plastični koši [koši za smeti]; Posode za pijačo; Posode za shranjevanje hrane; Posode za pitje za hišne ljubljenčke; Kangle za zalivanje; Zajemalke za kavo; Kozarci za shranjevanje (vlaganje); Lijaki za natakanje; Umivalniki (sklede); Kuharski pripomočki; Stiskalniki za sadni sok; Tlačilke za hrano; Cedila; Kovinski pladnji; Deske za rezanje; Kozarci za pijačo; Kozarci in skodelice; Krožniki; Košarice za kruh za gospodinjske namene; Pladnji za pribor; Stojala za sušenje posode; Košarice za pribor; Kadi za pranje perila; Vedra; Koši za odpadni papir.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Soptunnor; plasttunnor (soptunnor); behållare för drycker; behållare för förvaring av livsmedel; vattenskålar för husdjur; vattenkannor; kaffemått; burkar; trattar; bunkar (skålar); köksredskap; pressar för fruktsaft; pressredskap för livsmedel: durkslag; brickor; skärbrädor; dricksglas; koppar och muggar; tallrikar; brödkorgar; besticklådor; diskställ; bestickkorgar; tvättbaljor; hinkar; papperskorgar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/112</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/184</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-09-25</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079049</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>12268</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
