<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-07-29T09:52:43</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018224152</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018224152</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-09</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-24</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-09</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-29</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Aoyubo</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Кръгчета за дъвкане при поникване на зъби; Помпи за изцеждане на кърма; Стерилни чаршафи [хирургия]; Надуваеми подложки за медицински цели; Слухови апарати; Приспособления за обработване на езика; Пособия за масаж на венците на бебета; Биберони за шишета за хранене; Капачки за биберони; Бебешки биберони-залъгалки; Бебешки шишета; Щипки за залъгалки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kousací kroužky; Odsávačky mateřského mléka; Chirurgická sterilní prostěradla; Nafukovací podušky pro lékařské účely; Naslouchátka; Škrabky jazyka; Pomůcky na masírování dásní pro batolata; Dudlíky na kojenecké lahve; Uzávěry kojeneckých lahví; Dudlíky; Dětské láhve; Klipy na dudlíky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Bideringe; Brystpumper; Sterile lagner, kirurgiske; Lufthynder til medicinsk brug; Hjælpemidler for hørelsen; Tungeskrabere; Gummemassageartikler til spædbørn; Sutter til sutteflasker; Ventiler til sutteflasker; Sutter; Sutteflasker; Klips til narresutter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Beißringe zum Erleichtern des Zahnens; Milchpumpen; Sterile Tücher für Operationen; Luftkissen für medizinische Zwecke; Hörgeräte; Zungenreinigungsgeräte; Hilfsmittel für die Gaumenmassage bei Babys; Flaschensauger; Saugflaschenverschlüsse; Schnuller für Säuglinge; Saugflaschen; Clips für Schnuller.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Δακτύλιοι για την ανακούφιση ή τη διευκόλυνση της οδοντοφυίας· Θήλαστρα· Αποστειρωμένα σεντόνια, χειρουργικά· Αέρα (Μαξιλάρια -) για ιατρική χρήση· Βοηθήματα ακοής· Γλυφίδες γλώσσας· Διατάξεις μάλαξης ούλων για βρέφη· Θηλές για μπιμπερό· Βαλβίδες κλεισίματος για μπιμπερό· Πιπίλες (θηλές) για βρέφη· Υποδοχείς για θήλαστρα· Λαβίδες (κλιπ) για πιπίλες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Teething rings; Breast pumps; Sterile sheets, surgical; Air cushions for medical purposes; Hearing aids; Tongue scrapers; Gum massagers for babies; Baby bottle nipples; Feeding bottle valves; Teats; Feeding bottles; Clips for dummies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Anillos de dentición [mordedores]; Sacaleches; Campos quirúrgicos [sábanas estériles]; Cojines de aire para uso médico; Audífonos de corrección auditiva; Limpiadores linguales [raspadores de lengua]; Masajeadores de encía para bebés; Tetinas de biberones; Cierres de biberones; Chupetes [tetinas]; Biberones; Clips para chupetes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hammastumisrõngad, närimisrõngad; Rinnapumbad; Kirurgias kasutatavad steriilsed linad; Meditsiinilised õhkpadjad; Kuuldeaparaadid; Keeleraspaatorid, keeleküretid; Imikute igememassaaživahendid; Pudelilutid; Lutipudeliklapid; Beebilutid, lutid; Lutipudelid; Lutiklambrid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Pururenkaat; Rintapumput; Steriloidut lakanat [kirurgiset]; Ilmatyynyt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Kuulolaitteet; Kielenraaputtimet; Ikeniä hierovat purulelut vauvoille; Tuttipullojen tutit; Sulkimet tuttipulloja varten; Tutit; Tuttipullot; Klipsit tutteja varten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Anneaux pour calmer ou faciliter la dentition; Tire-lait; Champs opératoires [draps stériles]; Coussins à air à usage médical; Appareils auditifs; Cure-langue; Doigtiers de dentition pour bébés; Tétines de biberons; Fermetures de biberons; Sucettes [tétines]; Biberons; Attache-sucettes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Prsteni za ublažavanje ili olakšavanje dobivanja zubi [denticije]; Pumpice za izdajanje mlijeka; Sterilne plahte, kirurške; Zračni jastuci za medicinske potrebe; Slušna pomagala; Strugači jezika; Masažeri za desni dojenčadi; Dude za bočice; Ventili za dječje bočice; Dude za dojenčad; Spremnici dječjih bočica; Kvačice za dude varalice.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Fogzást elősegítő vagy könnyítő gyűrűk; Mellszívók; Steril sebészeti lepedők; Levegővel töltött párnák gyógyászati célokra; Hallókészülékek; Nyelvkaparók; Fogínymasszírozók csecsemők számára; Cumik cumisüvegekhez; Cumisüveg szelepek; Cumik; Cumisüvegtartók; Csíptetők cumikhoz.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Anelli per calmare o facilitare la dentizione; Tira latte; Lenzuola sterili per uso nel campo operatorio; Cuscini ad aria per uso medico; Sussidi per l'udito; Raschiatoi per la lingua; Dispositivi per massaggiare le gengive nei neonati; Tettarelle per poppatoi; Chiusure di poppatoi; Succhiotti per bebè; Poppatoi; Pinze per ciuccio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Dantų žiedai; Motinos pieno siurbtuvai; Steriliosios paklodės [chirurgija]; Pripučiamos pagalvėlės (medicinos reikmėms); Klausos aparatai; Liežuvio grandikliai; Dantenų masažuokliai kūdikiams; Buteliukų žindukai; Žindymo buteliukų vožtuvėliai; Kūdikių čiulptukai; Žindymo buteliukai; Čiulptukų segtukai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Riņķi zīdaiņu zobu šķilšanās atvieglošanai; Krūts piena sūknīši; Sterili palagi ķirurģiskiem nolūkiem; Piepūšamie spilveni medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Dzirdes aparāti; Rīki mēles tīrīšanai; Gumijas rīki zīdaiņu smaganu masēšanai; Barošanas pudelīšu knupīši; Barošanas pudelīšu vāciņi; Māneklīši (knupji); Barošanas pudelītes; Knupīšu klipši.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ċrieki għat-trabi biex igiddmu fihom huma u jaqsmu s-snien; Pompi tas-sider; Lożor sterilizzati (kirurġiċi); Kuxxini tal-arja għal skopijiet mediċi; Mezzi għall-għajnuna fis-smigħ; Barraxa tal-ilsien; Massaġġaturi tal-ħanek għat-trabi; Gażażi tal-fliexken tal-ħalib; Valvoli tal-fliexken tal-ħalib; Gażażi; Reċipjenti bħala fliexken għat-tmigħ tat-trabi; Klipep għall-gażażi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Bijtringen; Borstpompen; Operatielakens, steriel; Luchtkussens voor medisch gebruik; Hoorapparaten; Tongschrapers; Middelen voor het masseren van tandvlees bij baby's; Spenen voor zuigflessen; Sluitingen voor zuigflessen; Spenen; Zuigflessen; Clips voor spenen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Gryzaki pierścienie dla ząbkujących dzieci; Urządzenia do odciągania mleka z piersi; Prześcieradła sterylne chirurgiczne; Dmuchane poduszki do celów medycznych; Aparaty słuchowe; Szczoteczki do czyszczenia języka; Masażery do dziąseł dla niemowląt; Smoczki do butelek do karmienia; Zamknięcia do butelek do karmienia; Smoczki; Pojemniki na butelki do karmienia; Zawieszki do smoczków.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Anéis estimuladores da dentição; Bombas tira-leite; Lençóis esterilizados para cirurgia; Almofadas de ar para uso médico; Auxiliares auditivos; Limpadores de línguas; Massajadores de gengiva para bebés; Tetinas de biberão para alimentação; Tampas de biberão; Chupetas; Biberons [biberões]; Correntes para chupetas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Inele pentru erupția dentară; Pompe de sân; Câmpuri operatorii sterile, chirurgicale; Perne cu aer pentru uz medical; Dispozitive auditive; Dispozitive pentru curățarea limbii; Dispozitive pentru masaj gingival pentru bebeluși; Tetine de biberon; Dispozive de închidere pentru biberoane; Tetine; Recipiente pentru biberoane; Cleme pentru suzete.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Krúžky na prerezávanie zubov; Dýchacie prístroje; Chirurgické, sterilné plachty; Nafukovacie podušky na lekárske použitie; Načúvacie pomôcky; Škrabky na čistenie jazyka; Pomôcky na masírovanie ďasien pre bábätká; Cumle na detské fľaše; Uzávery na detské fľaše; Cumle pre dojčatá; Detské fľaše; Klipy na cumlíky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Obročki za grizenje za ublažitev bolečin pri rasti zob; Prsne črpalke; Kirurške sterilizirane rjuhe; Zračne blazine za medicinske namene; Slušni pripomočki; Strgala za jezik; Pripomočki za masažo dlesni za dojenčke; Cuclji za stekleničke za hranjenje dojenčkov; Ventili za stekleničke za hranjenje; Cuclji za dojenčke; Posodice za stekleničke za hranjenje; Priponke za dude.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bitringar; Bröstpumpar; Sterila lakan (kirurgiska); Luftdynor för medicinska ändamål; Hörselhjälpmedel; Tungskrapor; Tandköttsmasserare för spädbarn; Nappar för nappflaskor; Tillslutningsringar för nappflaskor; Nappar för spädbarn; Nappflaskor; Clips för nappar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Хартия; Покрити с мастило листове за копирни машини; Хартия за копиране; Хартия Ксуан [за китайски рисунки и калиграфии]; Картон; Каталози; Пликове [канцеларски принадлежности]; Плакати; Сребърна хартия; Хартиени торби за употреба при стерилизиране на медицински инструменти; Кламери за офиси; Книговезки преси [неелектрически телбод]; Острилки за моливи [електрически или неелектрически]; Шнурове за подвързване на книги; Училищни пособия [канцеларски принадлежности]; Калъфи за паспорти; Ролетки за държачи за баджове за имена [офисни принадлежности]; Пломбиращи щемпели; Прибори за откъсване на парчета лепенки [за офиси]; Линии за чертежи; Пломбиращи уреди за офиси.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Papír; Barvicí plátna do rozmnožovacích strojů; Průklepový papír; Papír Xuan pro čínskou malbu a kaligrafii; Lepenka; Katalogy; Obálky [papírnické zboží]; Plakáty; Stříbrný papír; Papírové sáčky k použití při sterilizaci lékařských nástrojů; Spony do sešívaček; Neelektrické sešívačky; Ořezávátka na tužky, elektrická i neelektrická; Provázky a nitě pro knižní vazby; Školní potřeby [papírnické zboží]; Pouzdra na cestovní pasy; Navíjecí šňůrky pro držáky na jmenovky [kancelářské potřeby]; Razítka; Dávkovače lepicích pásek [kancelářské potřeby]; Rýsovací pravítka; Zatavovací kancelářské stroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Papir; Sværteark til duplikatorer; Kopipapir [kontorartikler]; Papir til malerkunst og kaligrafi; Pap; Kataloger; Konvolutter; Plakater; Sølvpapir; Papirposer til brug ved sterilisering af medicinske instrumenter; Hæfteklammer til kontorbrug; Hæftemaskiner (ikke-elektriske hæftemaskiner); Blyantspidsere, elektriske og ikke-elektriske; Tråd til bogbinding; Skolerekvisitter [papirvarer]; Etuier til pas; Spoler med tilbagetrækningsfunktion til navneskilteholdere [kontorartikler]; Segl [mærker]; Holdere til klæbebånd [kontorrekvisitter]; Tegnelinealer; Forseglingsmaskiner til kontorbrug.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Papier; Drucktücher für Vervielfältigungsgeräte; Kopierpapier [Schreibwaren]; Papier für Malerei und Kalligrafie; Pappe; Kataloge; Hüllen [Papier- und Schreibwaren]; Plakate; Silberpapier; Papierbeutel zur Verwendung bei der Sterilisation von medizinischen Instrumenten; Büroklammern; Hefter [nicht elektrische Hefter]; Elektrische oder nicht elektrische Bleistiftspitzer; Buchbindegarn; Schülerbedarf [Papier- und Schreibwaren]; Reisepasshüllen; Clips mit Aufrollmechanismus für Halter von Namensschildern [Büroartikel]; Siegelstempel; Klebstreifenspender [Papier- und Schreibwaren]; Zeichenlineale; Siegelmaschinen für Bürozwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Χαρτί· Φύλλα μελάνης πολυγράφων· Αντιγραφικό χαρτί· Χαρτί Xuan για χρήση στην κινεζική ζωγραφική και καλλιγραφία· Χαρτόνι· Κατάλογοι· Φάκελοι [είδη χαρτοπωλείου]· Αφίσες· Ασημόχαρτο· Χάρτινες σακούλες για χρήση στην αποστείρωση ιατρικών εργαλείων· Συνδετήρες γραφείου· Συρραπτικά (μη ηλεκτρικές συρραπτικές μηχανές)· Ξύστρες, ηλεκτρικές ή μη· Σύρματα για βιβλιοδεσίες· Είδη σχολικά· Θήκες διαβατηρίων· Αναδιπλούμενοι κύλινδροι για υποδοχές διακριτικών σημάτων ονομάτων [είδη γραφείου]· Σφραγίδες για σήμανση· Διανεμητές (αυτοκόλλητης ταινίας -)[είδη χαρτοποιίας]· Χάρακες σχεδίου· Σφράγισης (Μηχανές -) γραφείου.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Paper; Inking sheets for duplicators; Copying paper [stationery]; Papers for painting and calligraphy; Cardboard; Catalogues; Envelopes [stationery]; Posters; Silver paper; Paper bags for use in the sterilization of medical instruments; Clips for offices; Stapling presses [non-electric staplers]; Pencil sharpeners, electric or non-electric; Bookbinding cords; School supplies [stationery]; Passport holders; Retractable reels for name badge holders [office requisites]; Stamps [seals]; Dispensers (Adhesive tape -) [office requisites]; Adhesive tape dispensers [office requisites]; Drawing rulers; Sealing machines for offices.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Papel; Telas entintadas para duplicadores [multicopistas]; Papel de copia [artículos de papelería]; Papel de pintura y caligrafía; Cartón; Catálogos; Sobres [artículos de papelería]; Carteles; Papel de plata; Bolsas de papel para la esterilización de instrumentos médicos; Grapas de oficina; Grapadoras [no eléctricas]; Sacapuntas eléctricos o no; Hilos de encuadernación; Material escolar; Fundas para pasaportes; Carretes con cordón extensible para soportes de tarjetas de identificación; Sellos de estampar; Distribuidores de cinta adhesiva [artículos de papelería]; Reglas de dibujo; Máquinas de sellado para oficinas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Paber; Paljundusaparaadi värviplaadid; Paljunduspaber; Paber maali ja kalligraafia jaoks; Papp, kartong; Kataloogid; Ümbrikud [kirjatarbed]; Plakatid, müürilehed; Hõbepaber; Meditsiiniinstrumentide steriliseerimise paberkotid; Kirjaklambrid; Kiirköitjad [v.a elektrilised]; Elektrilised või mitteelektrilised pliiatsiteritid; Raamatuköitmisnöörid; Koolitarbed [kirjatarbed]; Passikaaned; Sissetõmmatava kaabliga nimekaardihoidikud [kontoritarbed]; Templid, pitsatid; Teibi-, kleepribahoidikud [kantseleitarbed]; Joonlauad; Pitseerimismasinad, pitseermasinad [kantseleitarbed].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Paperi; Värikankaat monistuslaitteisiin; Kopiopaperi; Maalaus- ja kalligrafiapaperit; Pahvi; Luettelot; Kirjekuoret; Julisteet; Hopeapaperi; Paperipussit käytettäväksi lääketieteellisten välineiden steriloinnissa; Paperiniitit toimistotarvikkeina; Nitojakoneet (muut kuin sähkökäyttöiset nitojat); Kynänteroittimet [sähkö- tai käsikäyttöiset]; Kirjansidontapunokset; Koulutarvikkeet [paperikauppatavaroina]; Passikotelot; Nimikortinpidikkeiden sisäänkelausmekanismit [toimistotarvikkeet]; Lyijykkeet; Jakelulaitteet teipeille [toimistotarvikkeina]; Luonnosviivaimet; Sinetöintilaitteet toimistotarkoituksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Papier; Toiles d'encrage pour duplicateurs; Papier à copier [articles de papeterie]; Papiers pour la peinture et la calligraphie; Carton; Catalogues; Enveloppes [papeterie]; Affiches; Papier d'argent; Sacs en papier pour la stérilisation d'instruments médicaux; Agrafes de bureau; Agrafeuses non électriques; Taille-crayons, électriques ou non électriques; Fils pour reliures; Fournitures scolaires; Pochettes pour passeports; Enrouleurs pour porte-badges d'identification [articles de bureau]; Timbres [cachets]; Distributeurs de ruban adhésif [articles de papeterie]; Règles à dessiner; Machines à cacheter de bureau.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Papir; Platno namočeno bojom za uređaje za umnožavanje; Kopirni papir; Papir Xuan [za kineski krasopis i slikarstvo]; Ljepenka [karton]; Katalozi; Omotnice [papirnati proizvodi]; Posteri; Srebrni papir; Papirnate vrećice za sterilizaciju medicinskih instrumenata; Uredske spajalice; Preše za spajanje [neelektrične klamerice]; Strojevi za oštrenje olovaka; Kanap za uvezivanje knjiga; Školska oprema; Džepići za putovnice; Koluti za namatanje za kartice s imenom [uredski pribor]; Pečati [žigovi]; Držači ljepljivih traka [uredski pribor]; Ravnala za nacrte; Uredski strojevi za pečaćenje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Papír; Festéklapok másológépekhez; Fénymásolópapír, nyomtatópapír; Xuan papír [kínai festményekhez és kalligráfiákhoz]; Karton; Katalógusok; Borítékok [papíráruk]; Poszterek; Ezüstpapír; Papírzacskók gyógyászati eszközök sterilizálásához történő használatra; Irodai kapcsok, iratkapcsok; Tűzőgépek [nem elektromos tűzőgépek]; Ceruzahegyezők [elektromos vagy nem elektromos]; Könyvkötő fonalak; Iskolaszerek [papíráruk]; Útlevéltartók; Visszahúzódó zsinórok névtábla-tartókhoz [irodai felszerelések]; Pecsétbélyegek; Ragasztószalag-adagolók [irodai cikkek]; Vonalzók műszaki rajzokhoz; Irodai bélyegzőgépek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Carta; Tele d'inchiostratura per duplicatori; Carta copiativa [cancelleria]; Carta per pittura e calligrafia; Cartone; Cataloghi; Buste [cartoleria]; Cartelloni; Carta d'argento; Sacchetti di carta per l'uso nella sterilizzazione di strumenti medici; Fermagli da ufficio; Cucitrici [cucitrici non elettriche]; Tempera-matite elettrici o non elettrici; Fili per rilegature; Forniture scolastiche; Portapassaporti; Bobine retattili per porta badge [articoli per ufficio]; Timbri; Distributori di nastro adesivo [articoli di cartoleria]; Righe da disegno; Macchine per sigillare da ufficio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Popierius; Dauginimo aparatų dažų plokštelės; Kopijavimo popierius [raštinės reikmenys]; Ksuano popierius [kinų tapybai ir kaligrafijai]; Kartonas; Katalogai; Vokai [raštinės reikmenys]; Afišos; Sidabrinis popierius; Popieriniai medicinos instrumentų sterilizavimo maišeliai; Sankabėlės (raštinės reikmėms); Sankabėlių segikliai [ne elektriniai]; Elektriniai ar ne elektriniai pieštukų drožtukai; Knygų įrišimo siūlai, virvutės; Mokykliniai raštinės reikmenys; Pasų laikikliai; Vardinių kortelių laikiklių įtraukiamosios ritės [raštinės reikmenys]; Spaudai [antspaudai]; Lipniųjų juostų laikikliai [raštinės reikmenys]; Braižymo liniuotės; Antspaudavimo mašinos (raštinės reikmėms).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Papīrs; Tintes loksnes kopējamajām mašīnām; Papīrs kopēšanai (kancelejas preces); Papīrs ķīniešu stila glezniecībai un kaligrāfijai (xuan); Kartons; Katalogi; Aploksnes [rakstāmpiederumi]; Plakāti; Sudraba papīrs; Papīra maisi medicīnas instrumentu sterilizēšanai; Skavas (biroja preces); Skavotāji [neelektriskie skavotāji]; Elektriski un neelektriski zīmuļu asināmie; Auklas grāmatu iesiešanai; Skolas piederumi (kancelejas preces); Pasu apvāki; Spoles personas vārda plāksnīšu turētājiem (biroja piederumi); Zīmoglakas spiedogi; Līmlenšu turētāji [kancelejas piederumi]; Lineāli (rasēšanai); Zīmogošanas (frankēšanas) mašīnas biroja darbiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Karti; Folji bil-linka għad-duplikaturi; Karti tad-duplikazzjoni; Karta Xuan għal pittura u kaligrafija Ċiniża; Kartunċin; Katalogi; Envelops [kartoleriji]; Kartelluni; Fojl irqiq tal-aluminju, jew ta' materjal ieħor ta' lewn il-fidda; Boroż tal-karti għall-użu fl-isterilizzazzoni ta' strumenti mediċi; Stejpils għal uffiċċji; Stejplers [mhux elettriċi]; Temprini tal-lapsijiet, tal-elettriku jew mhux tal-elettriku; Spag għal-legatura tal-kotba; Forniment għall-iskejjel [kartolerija]; Kavers għall-passaporti; Irkieket retrattabbli għal ħowlders tal-beġis tal-isem [oġġetti neċessarji għall-uffiċċju]; Timbri li jissiġillaw; Distributuri tat-tejp li jwaħħal (rekwiżiti tal-uffiċċju); Rigi wżati għat-tpinġija; Magni li jissiġillaw għal uffiċċji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Papier; Inktdoek voor duplicators; Kopieerpapier; Xuan papier [voor het chinees verven en kalligraferen]; Karton; Catalogi; Enveloppen; Aanplakbiljetten; Zilverpapier; Papieren zakken voor gebruik bij het steriliseren van medische instrumenten; Nietjes voor kantoorgebruik; Nietmachines [niet-elektrische nietmachines]; Potloodslijpers; Draad voor het boekbinden; Schoolbehoeften; Paspoorthoesjes; Intrekbare afrolmechanismen voor houders van naamkaartjes [kantoorbenodigdheden]; Kantoorstempels; Afgifte-inrichtingen voor plakband [kantoorartikelen]; Tekenlinialen; Zegelmachines voor kantoorgebruik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Papier; Płótno nasączone tuszem do powielaczy; Papier przebitkowy; Papier do malarstwa i kaligrafii; Karton; Katalogi; Koperty [artykuły piśmienne]; Afisze, plakaty; Papier srebrny; Torby papierowe do użytku przy sterylizacji narzędzi medycznych; Zszywki biurowe; Zszywacze [nieelektryczne]; Temperówki do ołówków, elektryczne lub nieelektryczne; Sznurek introligatorski; Przybory szkolne [artykuły piśmienne]; Okładki na paszporty; Zwijacze do identyfikatorów [artykuły biurowe]; Stemple do pieczętowania; Dozowniki taśmy przylepnej [artykuły biurowe]; Linijki rysownicze [kreślarskie]; Biurowe maszyny do stemplowania.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Papel; Telas de tinta para duplicadores; Papel para cópias [artigos de papelaria]; Papeis para pintura e caligrafia; Cartão; Catálogos; Envelopes [papelaria]; Cartazes; Papel de prata; Sacos em papel para uso na esterilização de instrumentos médicos; Agrafos para escritório; Agrafadores [não elétricos]; Apara-lápis elétricos ou não elétricos; Fios para encadernações; Material escolar [artigos de papelaria]; Bolsas para passaportes; Enroladores retrácteis para suportes para crachás [artigos de escritório]; Carimbos de escritório [selos]; Distribuidores de fita adesiva [artigos de papelaria]; Réguas para desenhar; Máquinas de selar para escritórios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Hârtie; Benzi impregnate cu cerneală pentru aparate de multiplicat; Hârtie de copiat [articole de papetărie]; Hârtie Xuan pentru pictură și caligrafie chineză; Carton; Cataloage; Plicuri [papetărie]; Afișe; Hârtie metalizată argintie; Pungi de hârtie destinate utilizării în sterilizarea instrumentelor medicale; Capse de birou; Capsatoare [neelectrice]; Creioane (ascuțitori de -, electrice sau neelectrice); Sfoară de legătorie; Rechizite școlare; Etuiuri pentru pașapoarte; Clipsuri retractabile pentru suporturi pentru ecusoane cu nume [articole de birou]; Sigilii; Bandă adezivă (distribuitoare de -) [articole de papetărie]; Rigle pentru desen tehnic; Sigilat (mașini de - de birou).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Papier; Farbiace plátna do rozmnožovacích strojov; Kopírovací papier (papiernický tovar); Papier xuan (na čínsku kaligrafiu a čínske maľby); Kartón, lepenka; Katalógy; Obálky (papiernický tovar); Plagáty; Strieborný papier; Papierové vrecká na použitie pri sterilizácii lekárskych nástrojov; Kancelárske štipce; Neelektrické zošívačky; Strúhadlá na ceruzky (elektrické aj neelektrické); Knihárske nite; Školské potreby (papiernický tovar); Puzdrá na pasy; Navíjacie rolosystémy pre držiaky na menovky [kancelárske potreby]; Pečate; Dávkovače lepiacej pásky (kancelárske potreby); Rysovacie pravítka; Kancelárske pečatné stroje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Papir; Indigo papir; Kopirni papir [pisarniška potrebščina]; Xuan papir (za kitajsko slikanje in kaligrafijo); Lepenka; Katalogi; Ovoji [pisalne potrebščine]; Plakati (posterji); Srebrni papir; Papirnate vrečke za uporabo pri sterilizaciji medicinskih instrumentov; Sponke (pisarniški pripomočki); Neelektrični spenjači; Šilčki za svinčnike (električni ali neelektrični); Vrvice za vezavo knjig; Šolske potrebščine [pisalne potrebščine]; Ovitki (etuiji) za potne liste; Izvlečne vrvice za držala za imenske priponke [pisarniški pripomočki]; Štampiljke [žigi]; Stojala za lepilni trak (pisarniški pripomočki); Ravnila za skiciranje; Pečatni stroji za pisarne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Papper; Färgdukar för dupliceringsapparater; Kopieringspapper; Papper för målning och kalligrafi; Kartong; Kataloger; Kuvert; Affischer; Silverpapper; Papperspåsar för användning vid sterilisering av medicinska instrument; Gem; Icke-elektriska häftapparater; Pennvässare (elektriska eller icke-elektriska); Bokbinderigarn; Skolmaterial [pappersvaror]; Passfodral; Indragningsmekanismer för namnbrickshållare [kontorsförnödenheter]; Stämplar [sigill]; Tejphållare [kontorsförnödenheter]; Skisslinjaler; Förseglingsmaskiner för kontor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>20</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Бебешки кошарки; Лавици за бутилки; Стойки за кърпи [мебели]; Рафтове за складове; Табла за обяви; Неметални закачалки с куки за палта; Обиколници за бебешки креватчета, различни от спално бельо; Дюшеци за къмпинг; Опорни стойки [мебели]; Калъфи за дрехи; Паравани [мебелировки]; Сандъци за играчки; Постелки за преобличане на бебета; Скоби за пердета; Поставки за шапки [мебели].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Dětské ohrádky; Stojany na lahve; Stojany na ručníky [nábytek]; Policové skříně; Nástěnky (vývěsky); Nekovové háčky na kabáty; Mantinely do dětských postýlek, jiné než ložní prádlo; Kempinkové matrace; Stojany (nábytek); Obaly na oděvy; Volně stojící příčky [nábytek]; Bedny na hračky; Přebalovací podložky; Stuhy a spony na uchycení závěsů; Stojany a poličky na klobouky (nábytek).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kravlegårde til småbørn; Flaskestativer; Håndklædestativer [møbler]; Hyldemoduler; Plakattavler; Frakkeknager (ikke af metal); Sengerande til barnesenge, undtagen sengelinned; Madrasser til campingbrug; Støttestativer [møbler]; Poser til opbevaring af tøj; Fritstående skillevægge [møbler]; Kister til legetøj; Puslepuder til babyer; Gardinsnore; Stativer til hatte [møbler].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Laufställe für Kleinkinder; Flaschenkästen; Handtuchständer [Möbel]; Regaleinheiten; Anschlagtafeln; Mantelhaken, nicht aus Metall; Stoßleisten für Kinderbettchen, ausgenommen Bettzeug; Campingmatratzen; Stützgestelle [Möbel]; Schutzhüllen für Bekleidung; Freistehende Raumteiler [Möbel]; Spielzeugkisten; Wickelauflagen; Raffrosetten für Gardinen; Hutregale [Möbel].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Βρεφικά πάρκα· Φιάλες (Ράφια για -)· Κρεμάστρες για πετσέτες [έπιπλα]· Ράφια για αποθήκευση· Πίνακες αγγελιών· Μη μεταλλικά άγκιστρα για κρέμασμα παλτών· Προστατευτικά πρόσκρουσης για βρεφικά κρεβατάκια, εκτός από λευκά είδη κρεβατοκάμαρας· Στρώματα κατασκήνωσης· Βάσεις στήριξης [έπιπλα]· Καλύμματα από ύφασμα· Χωρίσματα χώρου [έπιπλα]· Κιβώτια παιχνιδιών· Αλλαξιέρα· Κουρτινόξυλα· Ράφια για καπέλα [έπιπλα].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Playpens for babies; Bottle racks; Towel stands [furniture]; Shelving units; Display boards; Non-metallic coat hooks; Bumper guards for cots, other than bed linen; Camping mattresses; Support stands [furniture]; Clothes covers; Freestanding partitions [furniture]; Toy boxes [chests]; Baby changing mats; Curtain tie-backs; Hat racks [furniture].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Parques de bebés; Botelleros [muebles]; Toalleros [muebles]; Estanterías; Tablones de anuncios; Ganchos de percha no metálicos; Protectores de barrotes para cunas de bebé que no sean ropa de cama; Colchones de camping; Soportes [mobiliario (piezas de -)]; Fundas para ropa; Tabiques autoportantes [muebles]; Baúles para juguetes; Cambiadores para bebés [colchonetas]; Alzapaños de cortinas; Percheros para sombreros [muebles].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Väikelaste mänguaiad; Pudelihoidikud [riiulid]; Rätikuvarnad [mööbel]; Laoriiulid; Kuulutustahvlid; Mittemetallist mantlivarnad; Beebivoodite pehmendused, v.a voodipesu; Matkamadratsid; Tugialused [mööbel]; Rõivakatted; Kergvaheseinad [mööbel]; Kastid mänguasjadele, mänguasjakastid; Mähkimismatid; Kardinasidumispaelad; Kübaravarnad [mööbel].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Leikkikehät; Pullotelineet; Pyyhetelineet (kalusteet); Hyllyt (Varastointi -); Esittelytaulut; Muut kuin metalliset takinkoukut; Kehtojen reunapehmusteet, muut kuin vuodevaatteet; Retkeilypatjat; Tukitelineet [huonekalut]; Vaatteiden suojat (vaatepussit); Vapaasti seisovat väliseinät [huonekalut]; Kirstut (Lelu -); Vaipanvaihtoalustat; Verhojen tukiankkurit (pidikkeet); Hattutelineet [huonekalut].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Parcs pour bébés; Casiers à bouteilles; Porte-serviettes [meubles]; Étagères [meubles]; Tableaux d'affichage; Patères pour vêtements, non métalliques; Protège-barreaux pour lits à barreaux pour bébés, autres que linge de lit; Matelas de camping; Supports [meubles]; Housses à vêtements; Cloisons autoportantes [meubles]; Coffres à jouets; Tapis de change pour bébés; Patères de rideaux; Porte-chapeaux [meubles].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Ogradice [vrtići] za igranje male djece [beba]; Police za boce; Stalci za ručnike [namještaj]; Police za skladištenje; Ploče za prikazivanje; Nemetalne kuke za vješanje odjeće; Štitnici za dječje krevetiće, osim posteljine; Madraci za kampiranje; Potporni stalci [namještaj]; Navlake za odjeću; Samostojeće pregrade [namještaj]; Sanduci za igračke; Podloge za prematanje; Kuke za zavjese; Police za šešire [namještaj].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Járókák; Palacktartók; Törölközőállványok [bútor]; Tárolópolcok; Hirdetőtáblák; Nem fém kabátakasztók; Rácsvédők kiságyakhoz, nem ágynemű; Kemping matracok; Támasztó állványok [bútorok]; Ruhazsákok; Szabadon álló válaszfalak [bútor]; Dobozok játékokhoz; Pelenkázó matracok; Függönyelkötők, függönyösszefogók; Kalaptartók [bútorok].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Recinti per bebè; Portabottiglie; Porta-asciugamani [mobili]; Scaffali; Tabelloni per affissione; Ganci non metallici per abiti; Rostri paracolpi per culle, diversi da biancheria da letto; Materassini da campeggio; Supporti [mobili]; Custodie per abiti; Tramezzi autoportanti [mobili]; Casse per giocattoli; Materassini fasciatoio per bebè; Borchie per tende; Attaccapanni a pioli [mobili].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kilnojamieji aptvarėliai (pradedantiems vaikščioti kūdikiams); Butelių dėžės su pertvaromis; Rankšluosčių kabyklos [baldai]; Stelažai; Skelbimų lentos; Ne metaliniai apsiaustų kabliai; Vaikiškų lovelių apsauginiai apmušalai (ne lovos baltiniai); Turistiniai čiužiniai; Atraminiai stovai [baldai]; Drabužių maišai; Pertvaros [baldai]; Žaislų dėžės; Kūdikių vystymo patiesalai; Užuolaidų raiščiai; Skrybėlių stovai [baldai].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Zīdaiņu sētiņas; Pudeļu statņi (plaukti); Dvieļu statīvi; Plauktu sistēmas; Ziņojumu dēļi; Nemetāliski mēteļu āķi; Bērnu gultiņu aizsargapmales, izņemot aizsargapmales, kas ir gultas veļa; Matrači pārgājieniem; Atbalsta statīvi [mēbeles]; Apģērbu pārvalki; Savrupstāvošas starpsienas (mēbeles); Rotaļlietu kastes; Paklājiņi zīdaiņu pārtīšanai; Aizkaru turētāji (atsaites); Cepuru plaukti [mēbeles].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Playpens; Xtillieri għall-fliexken; Stends tax-xugamani [għamara]; Xkafef għall-ħażna; Bords għall-wiri; Ganċijiet tal-kowtijiet mhux tal-metall; Protezzjonijiet tal-bamper għal kots, minbarra l-frix tas-sodda; Saqqijiet għall-kampeġġ; Stends għal appoġġ [għamara]; Għotjien għall-ħwejjeġ; Diviżorji li jżommu weqfin mingħajr ebda lqugħ [għamara]; Gradenzi għall-ġugarelli; Twapet żgħar għat-tibdil għat-trabi; Tagħmir għall-irbit tal-purtieri; Stends tal-kpiepel [Għamara].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Boxen voor baby's; Flessenkratten; Handdoekkasten; Legplanken; Mededelingenborden; Niet-metalen kleerhaken; Stootkussentjes voor kinderbedden, anders dan bedlinnen; Kampeermatrassen; Standaards [meubelen]; Hoezen voor kledingstukken; Losstaande afscheidingen [meubelen]; Speelgoedkisten; Kussens voor het verschonen van baby's; Gordijnknoppen; Hoedenrekken [meubelen].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kojce; Stojaki do butelek; Stojaki na ręczniki [meble]; Półki magazynowe; Tablice ogłoszeniowe; Niemetalowe haczyki na płaszcze; Ochraniacze na szczebelki do łóżeczek dla dzieci, inne niż pościel; Materace kempingowe; Stojaki podporowe [meble]; Pokrowce na ubrania; Wolnostojące przepierzenia [meble]; Skrzynki na zabawki; Maty do przewijania niemowląt; Sznury do podwiązywania zasłon; Wieszaki na kapelusze [meble].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Parques para bebés; Garrafeiras; Toalheiros [mobiliário]; Estantes; Painéis de afixação; Cabides de parede não metálicos para casacos; Proteções [amparos] para berços, não sendo roupa de cama; Colchões para campismo; Suportes de apoio [mobiliário]; Capas para vestuário; Divisórias autónomas [mobiliário]; Caixas para brinquedos; Tapetes [esteiras] para mudar fraldas a bebés; Presilhas para cortinados; Estantes para chapéus [mobiliário].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Țarcuri pentru bebeluși; Sticle (Stelaje de -); Suporturi pentru prosoape [mobilier]; Rafturi pentru depozitare; Afișare (Tablouri de -); Cârlige de cuier nemetalice; Protecții antilovire pentru pătuțuri de copii, altele decât lenjeriile de pat; Saltele pentru camping; Picioare de sprijin [mobilier]; Huse pentru haine; Elemente de separare individuale [mobilă]; Jucării (Cutii pentru -); Mușamale pentru schimbarea bebelușilor; Cordoane pentru perdele draperii; Suport de pălării [mobilier].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ohrádky pre dojčatá; Prepravky na fľaše; Stojany na uteráky (nábytok); Police (nábytok); Zobrazovacie tabule; Nekovové háčiky na vešanie kabátov; Textilné chrániče do detských postieľok; Kempingové matrace; Stojany [nábytok]; Obaly na odevy; Samostatne stojace deliace priečky (nábytok); Skrinky na hračky; Prebaľovacie podložky; Záclonové šnúry; Stojany na klobúky [nábytok].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Stajice; Police za steklenice; Stojala za brisače [pohištvo]; Police za shranjevanje; Oglasni panoji; Nekovinske kljuke za plašče; Ščitniki za otroške posteljice, razen posteljnine; Blazine za kampiranje; Podporna stojala [pohištvo]; Zaščitna pokrivala za oblačila; Samostoječe pregrade [pohištvo]; Skrinje za igrače; Previjalne podloge; Trakovi za zavezovanje zaves; Police za klobuke [pohištvo].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Lekhagar för barn; Flaskställ; Handduksställ [möbler]; Lagerhyllor; Anslagstavlor; Krokar för rockar, inte av metall; Stötskydd för spjälsängar, med undantag av sängkläder; Campingmadrasser; Stödstativ [möbler]; Malpåsar för kläder; Fristående mellanväggar [möbler]; Leksakslådor; Dynor för blöjbyten; Gardinomtag; Hatthyllor [möbler].</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Поставки за подправки; Комплект шишенца за олио и оцет; Домакински принадлежности; Съдове за домакински или кухненски цели [с изключение на такива от благороден метал]; Сервизи за хранене; Сервизи за хранене, с изключение на вилици, ножове и лъжици; Чаши от хартия или пластмаса; Чинии за еднократна употреба; Кухненски принадлежности, не от благороден метал; Съдове за печене [не играчки]; Комплектовани кошници за пикник; Преси за чесън [кухненски уреди]; Цедки за домакински цели; Лъжици за разбъркване [кухненски прибори]; Бутилки от стъкло; Порцеланови орнаменти; Бутилки за течности при спортуване; Гарафа за вино; Кутии за сапун; Пръскачки за поливане на цветя и растения; Четки; Триещи гъбички за кухненски цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Sady kořenek; Karafy; Kuchyňské potřeby pro domácnost; Dózy, boxy a nádoby pro použití v domácnosti a kuchyni; Jídelní soupravy [nádobí]; Stolní náčiní, s výjimkou vidliček, nožů a lžic; Papírové nebo plastové kelímky; Talíře na jedno použití; Sady hrnců; Nádobí na pečení (nikoliv hračky); Piknikové koše s vybavením; Lisy na česnek [kuchyňské potřeby]; Cedníky pro použití v domácnosti; Vařečky [kuchyňské náčiní]; Skleněné lahve [nádoby]; Dekorační předměty z porcelánu; Lahve na pití pro sportovní účely; Karafy na víno; Krabičky na mýdlo; Rozstřikovače na zalévání květin a rostlin; Kartáče; Abrazivní houbičky pro kuchyňské použití.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Krydderisæt [glas og krukker]; Olie-eddikeflasker til platmenager; Redskaber til husholdningsbrug; Beholdere til husholdnings- eller køkkenbrug; Service [spisestel]; Bordservice, undtagen gafler, knive og skeer; Kopper af pap eller plast; Engangstallerkener; Grydesæt; Bageredskaber [ikke legetøj]; Picnickurve med udstyr; Hvidløgspressere [køkkenredskaber]; Sier til husholdningsbrug; Salatbestik [køkkenredskaber]; Glasflasker [beholdere]; Nipsting af porcelæn; Drikkedunke til brug ved sport; Vinkarafler til dekantering; Sæbeæsker; Håndsprøjter til blomster og planter; Børster; Skuresvampe til køkkenbrug.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gewürzservice; Essig- und Ölkännchen; Haushaltsgeräte; Gefäße für Haushalt oder Küche; Tafelservice [Geschirr]; Tafelgeschirr; Papier- oder Plastikbecher; Wegwerfteller; Kochgeschirr; Backformen [kein Spielzeug]; Ausgestattete Picknickkoffer; Knoblauchpressen [Küchengeräte]; Löchersiebe für den Haushalt; Rührlöffel [Küchengeräte]; Glasflaschen; Chinoiserie aus Porzellan; Trinkflaschen für sportliche Aktivitäten; Dekantierkaraffen; Seifendosen; Blumen- und Pflanzenspritzen; Bürsten; Scheuerkissen für die Küche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Μπαχαρικά (Σετ με -)· Αλατοπιπεριέρες· Σκεύη οικιακής χρήσης· Δοχεία οικιακά ή μαγειρικά· Υπηρεσίες [πιάτα]· Επιτραπέζια σκεύη, εκτός από πιρούνια, μαχαίρια και κουτάλια· Κύπελλα από χαρτί ή πλαστικό· Επιτραπέζια πιάτα μιας χρήσης· Σκεύη μαγειρικής χρήσης· Σκεύη για ψήσιμο [όχι παιχνίδια]· Εξοπλισμένα καλάθια για πικνίκ· Σκόρδου πρέσες [σκεύη κουζίνας]· Φίλτρα οικιακής χρήσης· Κουτάλες ανάμειξης[σκέυη κουζίνας]· Γυάλινες φιάλες· Κινέζικες πορσελάνες (είδη πορσελάνης)· Παγούρια για τον αθλητισμό· Καράφες κρασιού· Σαπουνοθήκες· Πότισμα λουλουδιών και φυτών (Τρόμπες για το -)· Βούρτσες· Σφουγγαράκια στιλβωτικά για την κουζίνα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Spice sets; Cruets; Household utensils; Household or kitchen containers; Services [dishes]; Tableware, except forks, knives and spoons; Cups of paper or plastic; Disposable table plates; Cooking pot sets; Bakeware [not toys]; Fitted picnic baskets; Garlic presses; Strainers for household use; Mixing spoons; Glass bottles; Ornaments made of porcelain; Drinking bottles for sports; Wine decanters; Soap boxes; Sprinklers for watering flowers and plants; Brushes; Abrasive pads for kitchen purposes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios para especias [especieros]; Vinagreras; Utensilios para uso doméstico; Recipientes para uso doméstico o culinario; Servicios de mesa [vajilla]; Vajilla, excepto tenedores, cuchillos y cucharas; Vasos de papel o materias plásticas; Platos desechables; Baterías de cocina; Artículos para cocinar al horno [que no sean juguetes]; Cestas de picnic equipadas; Prensa-ajos [utensilios de cocina]; Filtros para uso doméstico; Cucharas para mezclar [utensilios de cocina]; Botellas de cristal [recipientes]; Adornos de porcelana; Cantimploras; Decantadores de vino; Jaboneras [estuches]; Jeringas para regar flores y plantas; Cepillos; Esponjas abrasivas para la cocina.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Maitseainetooside komplektid; Lauapudelid; Majariistad; Köögi- või majapidamismahutid; Serviisid [lauanõud]; Lauanõud, v.a kahvlid, noad ja lusikad; Paber- või plasttopsid; Ühekorrataldrikud; Poti- ja pannikomplektid; Küpsetusnõud [v.a mänguasjad]; Komplekteeritud piknikukorvid; Küüslaugupressid [köögitarbed]; Majapidamiskurnad; Segamislusikad (köögitarbed); Klaaspudelid [mahutid]; Portselanornamendid; Sportimisel kasutatavad joogipudelid; Veinikarahvinid; Seebikarbid; Lille- ja taimekastmispiserdid, - pritsid; Harjad; Abrasiivpadjakesed köögis kasutamiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Maustetelineet; Mausteikkopullot öljyä ja etikkaa varten; Kotitalousvälineet; Säiliöt koti- tai keittiökäyttöön; Astiastot; Pöytäastiasto, paitsi haarukat, veitset ja lusikat; Mukit (Paperi- tai muovi -); Kertakäyttölautaset; Keittokattilasarjat; Leivontavälineet (ei leikkikalut); Kattauksen sisältävät eväskorit; Valkosipulipuristimet [keittiövälineinä]; Läviköt keittiövälineinä; Sekoituslusikat [keittiövälineinä]; Lasipullot; Posliinikoristeet; Taskumatit; Viinidekantterit; Saippuatelineet; Ruiskut kukkien ja kasvien kasteluun; Harjat; Hiomasienet keittiökäyttöön.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services à épices; Burettes; Ustensiles de ménage; Récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine; Services [vaisselle]; Vaisselle, à l’exception des fourchettes, couteaux et cuillères; Gobelets en papier ou en matières plastiques; Assiettes jetables; Batteries de cuisine; Ustensiles de cuisson autres que jouets; Paniers garnis pour pique-niquer; Presse-ail [ustensiles de cuisine]; Passoires à usage domestique; Cuillers à mélanger [ustensiles de cuisine]; Bouteilles en verre; Ornements en porcelaine; Gourdes; Carafes à décanter pour vin; Boîtes à savon; Seringues pour l'arrosage des fleurs et des plantes; Brosses; Tampons abrasifs pour la cuisine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Setovi za začine; Setovi za ulje i ocat; Kućanski pribor; Posude za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju; Servisi za jelo; Stolni pribor, osim vilica, noževa i žlica; Čaše, papirnate ili plastične; Jednokratni tanjuri; Posuđe (kuhinjsko metalno posuđe); Posude za pečenje [nisu igračke]; Opremljene košare za piknik; Bijeli luk [spravice za cijeđenje bijelog luka]; Filtri za kućanstvo; Kuhače [kuhinjski pribor]; Staklene boce; Ukrasi izrađeni od porculana; Sportske bočice za vodu [bidoni]; Dekanteri za vino; Kutije za sapun; Poljevače za cvijeće i biljke; Četke; Abrazivne krpe za kuhinjsku uporabu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Fűszertartó szettek; Asztali ecet- és olajtartók; Háztartási eszközök, kis méretű; Tárolók, tároló edények háztartási vagy konyhai célokra; Étkészletek; Étkészletek, a villák, kések és kanalak kivételével; Poharak papírból vagy műanyagból; Eldobható tányérok; Konyhai eszközök, kis méretű; Tűzálló edényáru [nem játékok]; Felszerelt piknikkosarak; Fokhagymaprések, fokhagymanyomók [konyhai eszközök]; Háztartási szűrők; Keverőkanalak [konyhai eszközök]; Üvegpalackok; Porcelándíszek; Ivópalackok sportoláshoz; Dekantálók borokhoz; Szappantartók; Öntözők virágok és más növények locsolásához; Kefék; Konyhai dörzsik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi per spezie; Ampolle; Utensili per la casa; Recipienti per la casa o per la cucina; Servizi [vasellame]; Servizi da tavola, eccetto forchette, coltelli e cucchiai; Bicchieri in carta o in materie plastiche; Piatti usa e getta; Batterie di cucina; Teglie e pirofile da forno [non giocattoli]; Cestini da picnic accessoriati; Spremi aglio [utensili da cucina]; Filtri per uso domestico; Cucchiai per mescolare [utensili da cucina]; Bottiglie di vetro [recipienti]; Ornamenti in porcellana; Bidoncini [fiaschette]; Decanter per vino; Scatole per sapone; Spruzzatoi per l'innaffiamento di fiori e di piante; Spazzole; Cuscinetti abrasivi per la cucina.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Prieskonių indelių rinkiniai; Indeliai; Buities reikmenys; Buitinės ar virtuvinės talpyklos; Servizai [valgomieji indai]; Stalo reikmenys, išskyrus peilius, šakutes ir šaukštus; Popieriaus ar plastiko puodeliai; Vienkartinės lėkštės; Virtuvės indų komplektai; Kepimo indai [ne žaislai]; Pritaikytos iškilų pintinės; Česnakų spaustuvai [virtuvės reikmenys]; Buitiniai sieteliai; Maišomieji šaukštai [virtuvės reikmenys]; Stikliniai buteliai; Porcelianiniai kiniški dailės mažmožiai; Sportininkų gertuvės; Vyno grafinai; Muilinės; Gėlių ir augalų švirkštuvai; Šepečiai; Virtuviniai švitriniai šveistukai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Garšvielu trauciņu komplekti; Menāžas; Mājsaimniecības piederumi; Tilpnes mājturības vai virtuves nolūkiem; Servīzes (trauki); Galda piederumi, izņemot dakšiņas, nažus un karotes; Tases no papīra un plastmasas; Vienreizlietojamie šķīvji; Ēdienu gatavošanas trauku komplekti; Cepšanas trauki [nav rotaļlietas]; Pielāgoti piknika grozi; Ķiploku spiedes (virtuves piederumi); Caurduri mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Pavārnīcas; Stikla pudeles; Porcelāna dekori; Kabatas formāta blašķes; Vīna karafes; Ziepju trauki ar vāku; Smidzināšanas ierīces puķu un augu laistīšanai; Sukas; Abrazīvi sūkļi, kas paredzēti izmantošanai virtuvē.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Settijiet tal-ħwawar; Kwies; Utensili domestiċi; Kontenituri għal użu domestiku jew għal użu fil-kċina; Settijiet [dixxijiet]; Tagħmir ta' fuq il-mejda, esklużi frieket, skieken u mgħaref; Tazzi tal-karti jew tal-plastik; Platti tal-mejda, disponibbli; Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir; Oġġetti għall-ħami [mhux ġugarelli]; Basktijiet tal-piknik; Preses tat-tewm [għodda tal-kċina]; Passaturi għal użu domestiku; Mgħaref biex tħawwad (għodod tal-kċina); Fliexken tal-ħġieġ [kontenituri]; Ornamenti magħmula mill-kina; Fliexken tax-xorb għall-isports; Reċipjenti tal-kristall għall-inbid; Kontenituri tas-sapun; Injezzjonijiet għas-saqi ta' fjuri u pjanti; Pniezel; Peds joborxu għal-skopijiet tal-kċina.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Specerijenstellen; Olie-en azijnflesjes, niet van edele metalen; Gerei voor de huishouding; Houders voor de huishouding of de keuken; Tafelserviezen; Tafelgerei, met uitzondering van vorken, messen en lepels; Bekers van papier of plastic; Eetborden, voor eenmalig gebruik; Pannensets; Bakgerei [geen speelgoed]; Volledig uitgeruste picknickmanden; Knoflookpersen [keukengerei]; Filters [zeven] voor huishoudelijk gebruik; Menglepels [keukengerei]; Glazen flessen; Chinese kunstvoorwerpen [porselein]; Veldflessen; Decanteerflessen (Wijn -); Zeepdozen; Plantenspuiten; Borstels; Schuursponsjes voor de keuken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Zestawy do przypraw; Pojemniki na olej, ocet, sól i pieprz; Przybory do użytku w gospodarstwie domowym; Pojemniki do użytku domowego lub kuchennego; Serwisy [zastawy stołowe]; Zastawa stołowa, z wyjątkiem widelców, noży i łyżek; Kubki z papieru lub z tworzyw sztucznych; Talerze jednorazowego użytku; Przybory kuchenne; Przybory do wypieków [nie zabawki]; Koszyki piknikowe z wyposażeniem; Prasy do czosnku [sprzęt kuchenny]; Cedzaki do użytku domowego; Łyżki do mieszania [przybory kuchenne]; Butelki szklane [pojemniki]; Ozdoby z porcelany; Butelki na napoje dla podróżnych; Karafki na wino; Mydelniczki; Zraszacze do podlewania kwiatów i roślin; Szczotki; Zmywaki ścierne do celów kuchennych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Conjuntos para especiarias; Galheteiros; Utensílios para uso doméstico; Recipientes para uso doméstico ou para cozinha; Serviços de loiça; Louça, exceto garfos, facas e colheres; Copos em papel ou em plástico; Pratos descartáveis; Trens de cozinha; Utensílios para cozinhar no forno [que não sejam brinquedos]; Cestos de piquenique guarnecidos; Espremedor de alho [utensílios de cozinha]; Filtros para uso doméstico; Colheres para misturar [utensílios de cozinha]; Garrafas de vidro [recipientes]; Porcelanas chinesas; Cantis para desportos; Decantadores para vinho; Saboneteiras [caixas]; Seringas para regar flores e plantas; Escovas; Esponjas abrasivas para cozinha.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Condimente (Servicii de -); Oliviere; Ustensile de menaj; Recipiente pentru menaj sau bucătărie; Servicii [veselă]; Veselă, altele decât furculițe, cuțite și linguri; Pahare din plastic sau hârtie; Farfurii de unică folosință; Ustensile de bucătărie; Tăvi și forme de copt [nu jucării]; Coșuri de picnic cu accesorii; Prese de usturoi [ustensile de bucătărie]; Filtre pentru menaj; Linguri de amestecat [ustensile de bucătărie]; Sticle din sticlă (recipiente); Bibelouri de porțelan; Sticle pentru băuturi pentru sportivi; Decantoare de vin; Savoniere; Seringi pentru stropit flori și plante; Perii; Bureți abrazivi pentru bucătărie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Koreničky; Kanvičky; Potreby pre domácnosť; Nádoby na použitie v domácnosti alebo v kuchyni; Jedálenské súpravy (riad); Stolovací riad, okrem vidličiek, nožov a lyžíc; Papierové alebo plastové poháre; Jednorazové taniere; Súpravy kuchynského riadu; Plechy a nádoby na pečenie [okrem hračiek]; Piknikové koše s vybavením; Lisy na cesnak (kuchynské náradie); Cedidlá pre domácnosť; Varechy; Sklené fľaše [nádoby]; Čínsky porcelán; Čutory, cestovné fľaše; Dekantačné karafy na víno; Obaly na mydlá; Kropiace ružice na polievanie kvetov; Kefy; Drôtenky na použitie v kuchyni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Garniture za shranjevanje začimb; Stekleničke za kis in olje; Gospodinjski pripomočki; Posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo; Servisi [namizni pribor]; Namizni pribor, razen vilic, nožev in žlic; Kozarci iz papirja ali plastike; Namizni krožniki za enkratno uporabo; Kuharski pripomočki; Posode za peko [ne kot igrače]; Opremljene košare za piknik; Stiskalnice za česen [kuhinjski pripomočki]; Cedila za gospodinjstva; Kuhalnice za mešanje [kuhinjski pripomoček]; Steklenice; Okraski iz porcelana; Plastenka za vodo za šport; Vinske karafe; Posodice za milo; Razpršilniki za vrt; Krtače; Grobe kuhinjske krpice (strgalniki).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kryddställ; Flaskor för bordsställ; Hushållsredskap; Behållare för hushålls- eller köksändamål; Serviser [bordsserviser]; Bordsserviser, förutom gafflar, knivar och skedar; Muggar av papper eller plast; Engångstallrikar; Kastrullset; Bakredskap [inte leksaker]; Utrustade picknickkorgar; Vitlökspressar [köksutrustning]; Silar för hushållsändamål; Skedar för omröring [köksredskap]; Glasflaskor; Porslinsprydnader; Dryckesflaskor för sport; Vinkaraffer; Tvålaskar; Vattenspridare för blommor och plantor; Borstar; Slipkuddar för köksändamål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>24</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Тъкани за тапициране; Тъкани за ботуши, боти и обувки; Копринени тъкани с щамповани шарки; Тензух; Газ [плат]; Коприна [плат]; Тюл; Басма; Кърпи за бърсане на стъкла; Нетъкани текстилни тъкани; Филц, кече, плъст; Текстилни изделия за баня [с изключение на облекло]; Калъфи за матраци; Мрежи за комари; Постелки за преповиване на бебета; Завивки за домашни любимци; Бебешки спални чували с качулка; Покривала за мебели; Текстилни артикули за домакински цели; Одеяла за пикник; Банери от текстил или пластмаса.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Čalounické látky; Látky na obuv; Hedvábné látky pro tištěné vzory; Sýrařské plátno; Gázovina [látka]; Hedvábí [látky]; Tyl; Kartoun; Utěrky na nádobí; Netkané textilie; Plst; Koupelnový textil, s výjimkou oděvů; Potahy na matrace; Sítě proti hmyzu; Látkové podložky na přebalování; Přikrývky pro domácí zvířata; Spací pytle pro kojence; Ochranné povlaky na nábytek; Textilních výrobky do domácnosti; Piknikové deky; Bannery z textilií nebo plastických hmot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Møbelstoffer; Stoffer til fodtøj; Silkestoffer til trykmønstre; Ostelærred; Gaze [florstof]; Silke [vævet stof]; Tyl; Kalico [bomuldsstof]; Viskestykker; Ikke-vævede tekstilstoffer; Filt; Badelinned, undtagen beklædning; Madrasbetræk; Moskitonet; Underlagsklæde til bleskift af småbørn; Tæpper til kæledyr; Køreposer til spædbørn; Møbelovertræk; Husholdningstekstiler; Picnictæpper; Bannere af tekstil eller plastik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Möbelstoffe; Textilien für Schuhwaren; Seidenstoffe für Druckschablonen; Käsetücher; Gaze [Stoff]; Seidenstoffe; Tüll; Kattun; Abtrockentücher; Vliesstoffe [Textilien]; Filz; Badewäsche [ausgenommen Bekleidungsstücke]; Matratzenüberzüge; Moskitonetze; Textile Unterlagen zum Wechseln von Babywindeln; Decken für Haustiere; Schlafsäcke mit Kapuze für Babys; Möbelüberzüge; Haushaltstextilien; Picknickdecken; Banner aus Stoff oder Kunststoff.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Επιπλώσεων υφάσματα· Υφάσματα για υποδήματα· Έντυπα (Μεταξωτά υφάσματα για πατρόν -)· Τυρί (τουλπάνια για πήξιμο -ου)· Γάζα [ύφασμα]· Μετάξι (Υφάσματα από -)· Τούλι· Ινδικό [ύφασμα εμπριμέ]· Υαλοϋφάσματα [πετσέτες]· Mη υφασμένα είδη υφαντουργίας· Πίλημα· Μπάνιου (λευκά είδη -) [εκτός ιματισμού]· Καλύμματα στρωμάτων· Κουνουπιέρες· Πανιά για την αλλαγή βρεφικών πανών· Κουβέρτες για κατοικίδια ζώα· Ολόσωμες φόρμες για μωρά· Καλύμματα για έπιπλα· Υφάσματα οικιακής χρήσης· Κουβέρτες για πικνίκ· Λάβαρα από ύφασμα ή πλαστικό.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Upholstery fabrics; Fabric for footwear; Silk fabric for printing patterns; Cheese cloth; Gauze fabric; Silk cloth; Tulle; Calico; Glass-cloth [towels]; Non-woven textiles; Felt; Bath linen, except clothing; Mattress covers; Mosquito nets; Diaper changing cloths for babies; Blankets for household pets; Baby buntings; Coverings for furniture; Household textiles; Picnic blankets; Banners of textile or plastic.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Telas para tapizar muebles; Tejidos para el calzado; Tejidos de seda para patrones de imprenta; Telas para hacer queso; Gasa [tela]; Tejidos de seda; Tul; Calicó; Paños para secar vasos; Materias textiles no tejidas; Fieltro; Ropa de baño, excepto prendas de vestir; Fundas de colchón; Mosquiteros [colgaduras]; Cambiadores de tela para bebés; Mantas para animales de compañía; Nanas [ropa de cama]; Fundas para muebles; Artículos textiles para el hogar; Esteras de picnic; Banderolas de materias textiles o de materias plásticas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Mööbliriie; Riie jalatsite valmistamiseks, jalatsiriie; Siidriie mustrite trükkimiseks; Marli, kurnariie; Gaasriie; Siidriie; Tüll [riie]; Kalingur; Klaaskiudlapid; Lausriie, -kangas; Vilt; Vannilinad; Madratsikatted; Moskiitovõrgud, sääsevõrgud; Tekstiilist mähkimislinad imikutele; Lemmikloomatekid; Kapuutsiga magamiskotid beebidele; Mööblikatted; Majapidamise tekstiiltooted; Piknikutekid; Tekstiilist või plastikust ribareklaamid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Verhoilukankaat; Kangas jalkineita varten; Silkkikankaat kuviopainantaan; Juustokangas; Harsokangas; Silkkikangas; Tylli; Kalikoo; Lasipyyhkeet [pyyheliina]; Kuitukankaat; Huopa; Kylpypellavakankaat; Patjanpäälliset; Sääskiverkot; Vaipanvaihtokankaat; Peitteet lemmikkieläimille; Vauvojen hupulliset makuupussit; Huonekalujen päälliset; Kotitaloustekstiilit; Huovat eväsretkille; Kankaiset tai muoviset viirit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Étoffe pour meubles; Tissus pour chaussures; Tissus de soie pour patrons d'imprimerie; Toiles à fromage; Gaze [tissu]; Tissus de soie; Tulles; Calicot; Essuie-verres; Non-tissés [textile]; Feutre; Linge de bain à l'exception de l'habillement; Enveloppes de matelas; Moustiquaires; Tissus à langer pour bébés; Couvertures pour animaux d'intérieur; Nids d'ange; Housses de protection pour meubles; Articles textiles de maison; Couvertures de pique-nique; Bannières en matières textiles ou en matières plastiques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Materijali za tkaninu za namještaj; Tkanina za obuću; Svilena tkanina za tiskanje uzoraka; Platno za sir; Gaza [tkanina]; Svilena tkanina; Til [tkanina]; Pamučno platno; Tkanina za brisanje stakla; Netkana tkanina; Pust; Rublje za kupanje [osim odjevnih predmeta]; Omotači za madrace; Mreže za komarce; Krpice za mijenjanje pelena za bebe; Pokrivači za kućne ljubimce; Ukrasne zastavice za bebe; Prekrivači za namještaj; Kućanska tekstilna roba; Pokrivači za piknik; Baneri od tekstila ili od plastike.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Bútorszövetek, kárpitok; Textilanyagok lábbelikhez; Selyemszövetek nyomdai sablonokhoz; Sajtruha, sajtvászon; Géz [fátyolszövet]; Selyemszövet; Tüll; Pamutvászon, karton, kalikó; Pohártörlő ruhák; Nem szőtt textíliák; Nemez, filc; Fürdőszobai vászonneműk, a ruházat kivételével; Matrachuzatok; Szúnyoghálók; Babatörlőkendők; Takarók kisállatok számára; Hálózsákok babáknak; Bútorhuzatok; Háztartási textiláruk; Pikniktakarók; Lobogók textilből vagy műanyagból.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Tessuti per ammobiliamento; Tessuti per calzature; Tessuti di seta per modelli di tipografia; Tele per formaggi; Garza [tessuto]; Tessuti di seta; Tulle; Calicot; Asciuga-vetri; Tessuti non tessuti; Feltro; Biancheria da bagno eccettuati i capi d'abbigliamento; Federe di materassi; Zanzariere; Tessuti di ricambio per bebè; Coperte per animali domestici; Sacchi nanna per bebè; Coperture per mobili; Prodotti tessili per la casa; Coperte da picnic; Stendardi in tessuto o materie plastiche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Baldų gobelenai; Avalynės audiniai; Šilkinis audinys (piešiniams spausdinti); Marlė; Marlė [audinys]; Šilkas; Tiulis; Kartūnas; Stiklinių šluostės; Neaustiniai tekstiliniai audiniai; Veltiniai; Pirties baltiniai [išskyrus drabužius]; Čiužinių užvalkalai; Tinkleliai nuo moskitų; Kūdikių vystyklų keitimo paklotai; Naminių gyvūnėlių antklodės; Kūdikių vokeliai; Baldų apmautai; Tekstilės prekės namų apyvokos reikmėms; Iškylų patiesalai; Tekstilinės ar plastikinės reklamjuostės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tapsēšanas audumi; Apaviem paredzēts audums; Zīda audums apdrukas šabloniem; Audums siera siešanai; Marle (audums); Zīds (audums); Tills; Kalikons; Drānas (dvieļi) stikla slaucīšanai; Neausti tekstilaudumi; Filcs; Vannas veļa, izņemot apģērbu; Matraču pārvalki; Moskītu tīkli; Paladziņi zīdaiņu autiņbiksīšu nomaiņai; Sedziņas mājas (istabas) dzīvniekiem; Guļammaisi konverti zīdaiņiem; Mēbeļu pārvalki; Tekstilizstrādājumi mājsaimniecības nolūkiem; Piknika segas; Reklāmkarogi no tekstilizstrādājumiem un plastmasas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Drapp tat-tapizzerija; Drapp għax-xedd tas-saqajn; Tessut tas-satin għal disinni tal-istampar; Garża; Garża [drapp]; Ħarir [drapp]; Tull; Kalikò; Ċraret għall-imsiħ tal-ħġieġ [xugamani]; Drappijiet tessili mhux minsuġa; Feltru; Bjankerija tal-banju, ħlief ilbies; Għata għas-saqqu; Xibka tan-nemus; Ċraret għall-bdil tal-ħrieqi għat-trabi; Kutri għal annimali domestiċi; Ħwejjeġ għat-trabi [buntings]; Koperti għall-għamara; Oġġetti tat-tessuti għall-użu fid-dar; Kutri tal-pikniks; Strixxuni tat-tessut jew plastik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Meubelstoffen; Weefsels voor schoenen; Weefsels van zijde voor drukpatronen; Kaasdoek; Gaas [weefsel]; Zijdeweefsels; Tule; Calicot; Glazendoeken; Non-woven textielstoffen; Vilt; Badgoed [uitgezonderd kleding]; Matrasbeschermers; Klamboes; Doekjes voor het verschonen van baby's; Dekens voor huisdieren; Trappelzakken; Overtrekken voor meubels; Textielproducten voor de huishouding; Picknickdekens; Banieren [vaandels] van textiel of van plastic.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Materiały do tapicerki; Tkanina do obuwia; Tkaniny jedwabne do szablonów drukarskich; Rzadkie płótno; Gaza [tkanina]; Jedwab [tkanina]; Tiul; Kaliko [perkal]; Ścierki do osuszania szkła [ręczniki]; Materiały tekstylne nietkane; Filc; Bielizna kąpielowa, z wyjątkiem odzieży; Pokrycie na materace; Moskitiery; Płótno do przewijania niemowląt; Koce dla zwierząt domowych; Śpiworki z kapturem dla niemowląt; Pokrowce i narzuty na meble; Artykuły tekstylne do użytku w gospodarstwie domowym; Koce piknikowe; Sztandary z materiałów tekstylnych lub tworzyw sztucznych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Tecidos para revestimento; Tecidos para calçado; Tecidos em seda para moldes de imprensa; Panos para queijos; Gaze [tecido]; Seda [tecidos]; Tule; Calicó; Tecidos para limpeza de loiça; Têxteis, sem ser em tecido; Feltro; Roupa de banho, exceto vestuário; Cobertas para colchões; Redes mosquiteiras; Panos para mudança de fraldas de bebés; Cobertores para animais domésticos; Bolsas [agasalhos] para bebés; Revestimentos para mobiliário; Artigos têxteis para o lar; Mantas para piqueniques; Estandartes [bandeiras] em matérias têxteis ou em plástico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Materiale pentru capitonare; Materiale textile pentru încălțăminte; Imprimat (Țesături din mătase pentru șabloane de -); Sedilă (Pânză pentru scurs brânza); Tifon [țesătură]; Mătase (Țesături de -); Tul; Calico; Prosoape pentru șters sticlă; Articole nețesute (textile); Fetru; Materiale textile pentru baie [cu excepția articolelor de îmbrăcăminte]; Huse pentru saltele; Plase contra țânțarilor; Materiale textile pentru schimbarea scutecelor pentru bebeluși; Pături pentru animale de companie; Săculeți de dormit pentru bebeluși; Huse pentru mobilă; Produse textile de uz casnic; Pături de picnic; Bannere din material textil sau plastic.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Čalúnnické textílie; Textílie na obuv; Hodvábne tkaniny na tlačové vzory; Gázovina, riedke plátno na výrobu syra; Gáza (textílie); Hodvábne textílie; Tyl; Bavlnené plátno; Utierky na riad; Netkané textílie; Plsť; Kúpeľňové textílie (okrem oblečenia); Obliečky na matrace; Ochranné siete proti komárom (moskytiéry); Textilné podložky na prebaľovanie; Deky pre zvieratá chované v domácnosti; Dojčenské zavinovačky; Poťahy a pokrývky na nábytok; Textilné výrobky do domácnosti; Piknikové deky; Textilné alebo plastové banery.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Tkanine za tapetništvo; Tkanine za obutev; Svilene tkanine za tiskanje vzorcev; Platno za sir; Gaza; Svila [blago]; Til; Kaliko; Krpe za brisanje kozarcev (brisačke); Netkane tkanine; Filc; Kopalniško perilo, razen oblačila; Prevleke za žimnice; Mreže proti komarjem; Podloge za previjanje dojenčkov; Odeje za hišne ljubljenčke; Spalne vreče za dojenčke; Zaščitna pregrinjala za pohištvo; Tekstilni izdelki za gospodinjstvo; Odeje za piknik; Prapori iz blaga ali plastike.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Möbeltyger; Tyger för fotbeklädnader; Silkscreen för tryckning; Tunna bomullstyger; Gas [väv]; Siden; Tyll; Kalikåtyger; Glasväv [handdukar]; Non-woven textilväv; Filt; Badlinne (med undantag för kläder); Madrassöverdrag; Myggnät; Dukar för blöjbyten, för spädbarn; Filtar för husdjur; Sovpåsar för spädbarn; Överdrag för möbler; Textilartiklar för hushållsändamål; Picknickfiltar; Standar av textil eller plast.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>28</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Играчки за домашни любимци; Балони; Строителни кубчета [играчки]; Играчки; Кукли марионетки; Плюшени играчки с прикрепено към тях одеяло за комфорт; Пластилин; Инструмент за заглаждане на буци пръст [принадлежности за голф]; Топки за играта пейнтбол [снаряди]; Люлки за йога; Свещници за коледни елхи; Камбанки, звънчета за коледни елхи; Топчета за игра; Облекла за кукли; Уреди за трениране на тялото; Пристягащи колани за кръста за упражнения; Играчки за употреба в плувни басейни; Орнаменти и декорации, всички за коледни дръвчета.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Hračky pro domácí zvířata; Balónky na hraní; Stavebnicové kostky [hračky]; Hračky; Loutky; Plyšové hračky s dečkou; Inteligentní plastelína na hraní; Vypichovátka na upravení stopy po dopadu míčku [příslušenství na golf]; Paintballové projektily; Popruhy na jógu; Držáky svíček na vánoční stromeček; Zvonky na vánoční stromeček; Kuličky (hra); Oblečení pro panenky; Posilovací stroje; Stahovací cvičební pásy; Hračky k použití v plaveckých bazénech; Ozdoby a dekorace na vánoční stromky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Legetøj til kæledyr; Legetøjsballoner; Byggeklodser [legetøj]; Legetøj; Marionetter; Plyslegetøj med påsat sutteklud; Legeslim; Reparationsværktøj til udbedring af græstørv [golfudstyr]; Paintballkugler [projektiler]; Yogagynger; Lysholdere til juletræer; Klokker til juletræer; Marmorkugler til spil; Dukketøj; Apparater til bodybuilding; Træningsbælter til trimning af taljen; Legetøj til brug i svømmebassiner; Dekorationer og pynt til juletræer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Spielzeug für Haustiere; Luftballons [Spielwaren]; Bauklötze [Spielwaren]; Spielzeug; Marionetten; Kuscheltuch [Plüschtiere]; Hüpfknete [Spielzeug]; Divotausbesserungswerkzeuge [Golfzubehör]; Paintball-Munition; Yogaschaukeln; Kerzenhalter für Christbäume; Glöckchen für Christbäume; Kleine Spielkugeln; Puppenkleider; Bodybuilding-Geräte; Trainingsgürtel zur Reduzierung der Taillenweite; Spielzeug zur Verwendung in Schwimmbecken; Christbaumschmuck und -verzierungen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παιχνίδια για κατοικίδια ζώα· Μπαλόνια· Κύβοι κατασκευών [παιχνίδια]· Ατομικά παιχνίδια· Μαριονέτες· Λούτρινα παιχνίδια με προσαρτημένες κουβέρτες αγκαλιάς· Πλαστελίνη για παιχνίδι· Εργαλεία επανατοποθέτησης βώλων γης [εξαρτήματα του γκολφ]· Σφαίρες χρώματος [βλήματα]· Κούνιες για γιόγκα· Κηροπήγια για χριστουγεννιάτικα δέντρα· Καμπανάκια για χριστουγεννιάτικα δέντρα· Μπίλιες· Κούκλες, ρούχα και εξαρτήματα για κούκλες· Αποκατάστασης σώματος συσκευές· Ζώνες άσκησης για την σύσφιξη της μέσης· Παιχνίδια για χρήση σε πισίνες· Διακοσμητικά και στολίδια χριστουγεννιάτικων δέντρων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Pet toys; Toy balloons; Building blocks [toys]; Toys; Puppets; Plush toys with attached comfort blanket; Toy putty; Golf divot repair tools; Paintballs [projectiles]; Yoga swings; Candle holders for Christmas trees; Bells for Christmas trees; Marbles for games; Dolls' clothes; Body-building apparatus; Waist trimmer exercise belts; Toys for use in swimming pools; Decorations and ornaments for Christmas trees.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Juguetes para animales de compañía; Globos de juego; Bloques de construcción [juguetes]; Juguetes; Marionetas; Mantitas de apego [dudús]; Masilla de modelar de juguete; Herramientas arreglapiques [accesorios de golf]; Proyectiles para paintball; Columpios de yoga; Portavelas para árboles de Navidad; Campanitas para árboles de Navidad; Canicas para jugar; Ropa de muñecas; Aparatos de culturismo; Correas de ejercicio para reducir la cintura; Juguetes para su uso en la piscina; Decoraciones y adornos para árboles de Navidad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Lemmikloomade mänguasjad; Õhupallid (mänguasjad); Ehitusklotsid [mänguasjad]; Mänguasjad; Hüpiknukud, marionetid; Plüüsmänguasjad koos kaisutekiga; Voolimimass mängimiseks; Golfikepi löögijälje tasandusriistad [golfitarvikud]; Värvikuulid [laskemoon]; Joogakiiged; Jõulupuu küünlaalused; Jõulupuukellukesed; Nipsukivid; Nukuriided; Füüsilise vormi parandamise/taastamise seadmed; Harjutusvööd piha salendamiseks; Basseinimänguasjad; Jõulupuuehted.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lelut lemmikkieläimille; Ilmapallot; Rakennuspalikat [leluina]; Lelut; Marionetit; Pehmolelut, joihin on kiinnitetty lohturiepu; Leikkimuovailuvaha; Golfinpeluussa käytettävät green-haarukat; Värikuulat [ammukset]; Joogakeinut; Kynttilänpidikkeet joulukuusiin; Kellot joulukuusiin [koristeina]; Marmorikuulat; Nukenvaatteet; Kehonrakennusvälineet; Keskivartalonharjoitusvyöt; Lelut käytettäväksi uima-altaissa; Joulukuusen koristeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Jouets pour animaux de compagnie; Ballons de jeu; Blocs de construction [jouets]; Jouets; Marionnettes; Doudous [peluches]; Mastic de modelage en tant que jouet; Outils de remise en place des mottes de terre [accessoires de golf]; Balles de peinture [projectiles]; Balançoires de yoga; Porte-bougies pour arbres de Noël; Clochettes pour arbres de Noël; Billes pour jeux; Vêtements de poupées; Appareils pour le culturisme; Ceintures d'exercice pour affiner la taille; Jouets de piscine; Décorations et ornements pour sapins de Noël.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Igračke za ljubimce; Baloni; Kocke za slaganje [igračke]; Igračke; Marionete; Plišane igračke s pričvršćenom dekicom za maženje; Plastelin; Golf [naprava za stavljanje na mjesto busena s travom u golfu]; Kuglice s bojom za paintball [projektili]; Ljuljačke za jogu; Držači za svijeće za božićna drvca; Zvonca za božićna drvca; Špekule; Odjeća za lutke; Sprave za body building; Remenje za tjelovježbu za smanjenje obujma struka; Igračke za uporabu u bazenima; Dekoracije i ukrasi za božićna drvca.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Játékok kisállatoknak; Léggömbök; Építőkockák [játékok]; Játékszerek; Marionettek, bábuk; Plüss játékok azokra erősített szundikendővel; Játékgitt; Gyepjavító szerszámok [golffelszerelések]; Paintball lövedékek; Jógahinták; Gyertyatartók karácsonyfákhoz; Harangok karácsonyfákra; Üveggolyók; Babaruhák; Testedző berendezések; Testedző övek a derék karcsúsítására; Medencékben használatos játékok; Dísztárgyak és dekorációk karácsonyfákra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Giocattoli per animali da compagnia; Palloni da gioco; Blocchi per costruzioni [giocattoli]; Giocattoli; Marionette; Peluche con attaccata una copertina; Plastilina; Attrezzi per rispintare il tappeto erboso [accessori da golf]; Pallottole da paintball [proiettili]; Altalene per lo yoga; Portacandele per alberi di natale; Campanelle per alberi di natale; Biglie per giochi; Vestitini per bambole; Apparecchi per il culturismo; Cinture per l'esercizio fisico, per il girovita; Giochi da usare in piscina; Decorazioni e ornamenti per alberi di Natale.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kambarinių gyvūnėlių žaislai; Žaidimų balionai; Konstrukciniai kubeliai [žaislai]; Žaislai; Marionetės (lėlės); Pliušiniai žaislai su audeklo skiautėmis; Žaislinis plastilinas; Velėnos taisymo įrankiai [golfo reikmenys]; Dažų kamuoliukai [šoviniai, sviediniai]; Jogos sūpynės; Kalėdų eglučių žvakidėlės; Kalėdų eglučių skambalėliai; Stiklo rutuliukai (vaikų žaidimui); Lėlių drabužiai; Fizinių pratimų prietaisai [kūnui treniruoti]; Liekninantys juosmens pratimų diržai; Žaislai, naudojami plaukimo baseinuose; Kalėdų eglučių papuošalai ir dekoracijos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Mājas (istabas) dzīvnieku rotaļlietas; Rotaļu baloni; Rotaļu klucīši [konstruktori]; Rotaļlietas; Marionetes; Plīša rotaļlietas ar piestiprinātu sedziņu; Veidošanas mastika bērnu rotaļām; Golfa piederumi, kas paredzēti nelielu zāliena bojājumu likvidēšanai; Peintbola bumbiņas [šāviņi]; Jogas šūpoles; Ziemassvētku eglīšu svečturi; Ziemassvētku eglīšu zvaniņi; Mazas stikla spēļu bumbiņas; Leļļu apģērbi; Atlētiskās vingrošanas ierīces; Vidukļa apmēra samazināšanai paredzētas treniņu jostas; Rotaļlietas izmantošanai peldbaseinos; Ziemassvētku eglīšu ornamenti un rotājumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ġugarelli għal annimali domestiċi; Bżieżaq; Blokki għal bini ta' kostruzzjonijiet [ġugarelli]; Ġugarelli; Marjunetti; Ġugarelli tal-filpa b'kutra ta' kumdità mwaħħla magħhom; Stokk tal-logħob; Għodod għat-tiswija tal-ħaxix mill-marki tal-ballun (aċċessorji tal-golf); Blalen taż-żebgħa [projettili]; Bandli tal-joga; Kandilabri għas-siġra tal-Milied; Qniepen għal mas-siġar tal-Milied; Boċċi żgħar tal-ħġieġ; Ilbies tal-pupi; Apparat għat-taħriġ tal-muskoli; Ċinturini tal-eżerċizzji għat-tnaqqis tal-wisa' tal-qadd; Ġugarelli għall-użu fil-pixxini; Ornamenti u dekorazzjonijiet tas-siġra tal-Milied.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Speelgoed voor huisdieren; Ballen om te spelen; Bouwblokken [speelgoed]; Speelgoed; Marionetten; Pluche speelgoederen voorzien van comfortdekentjes; Kneedpasta (speelgoed); Gereedschap voor het terugplaatsen van graszoden [golfaccessoires]; Paintballs [projectielen]; Yogaschommels; Kaarshouders voor kerstbomen; Klokjes voor kerstbomen; Knikkers [speelgoed]; Poppenkleertjes; Fitnesstoestellen; Trainingsgordels voor de taille om af te slanken; Speelgoed voor gebruik in zwembaden; Decoraties en versierselen voor kerstbomen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Zabawki dla zwierząt domowych; Balony; Klocki do zabawy [konstrukcyjne]; Zabawki; Marionetki; Pluszowe zabawki z przymocowanym kocykiem; Plastelina do zabawy; Przyrządy do naprawy darni na polu golfowym [akcesoria golfowe]; Kulki wypełnione farbą do gry w paintball [pociski]; Chusty do jogi; Uchwyty na świeczki choinkowe; Dzwonki na choinkę; Gra w kulki; Ubranka dla lalek; Przyrządy stosowane do ćwiczeń fizycznych; Pasy na talię, do ćwiczeń; Zabawki do użytku w basenach; Dekoracje i ozdoby choinkowe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Brinquedos para animais de estimação; Balões de brinquedo; Blocos de construção [brinquedos]; Brinquedos; Marionetas; Brinquedos de peluche ligados a pequenas mantinhas; Plasticina de brincar; Utensílios para reparar terreno [acessório de golfe]; Bolas de tinta [projéteis]; Baloiços para ioga; Suportes de velas para árvores de natal; Sinos para árvores de natal; Berlindes [jogos]; Vestuário de bonecas; Aparelhos para o culturismo; Cintas adelgaçantes para a prática de exercício; Brinquedos para utilizar em piscinas; Decorações e ornamentos para árvores de Natal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Jucării pentru animale de companie; Baloane; Blocuri de construcție [jucării]; Jucării; Marionete; Jucării de pluș cu păturică de consolare; Plastilină de jucărie; Unelte de refacere a gazonului [accesorii de golf]; Bile de vopsea [proiectile]; Leagăne pentru yoga; Suporturi de lumânări pentru brazi de Crăciun; Clopoței pentru pomul de Crăciun; Bile din sticlă colorată; Îmbrăcăminte de păpuși; Aparate pentru culturism; Curele pentru exerciţii pentru abdomen; Jucării utilizate în piscine; Ornamente pentru pomul de Crăciun.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Hračky pre zvieratá chované v domácnosti; Balóny na hranie; Stavebnicové kocky (hračky); Hračky; Bábky; Detské dečky spojené s plyšovou hračkou; Inteligentná plastelína na hranie; Prostriedky na úpravu golfovej plochy (vybavenie na golf); Paintballové projektily; Popruhy na jogu; Držiaky na sviečky na vianočné stromčeky; Zvončeky na vianočné stromčeky; Guľky na hranie; Odevy pre bábiky; Posilňovacie stroje; Sťahovacie opasky na cvičenie; Hračky na použitie v plaveckých bazénoch; Okrasy a ozdoby na vianočné stromčeky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Igrače za hišne ljubljence; Baloni; Kocke [igrače]; Igrače; Marionete; Plišaste igračke s prišito mehko odejico; Inteligentni plastelin za igranje; Orodje za poravnavanje zemlje [rekvizit pri golfu]; Paintball kroglice [projektili]; Gugalnice za jogo; Svečniki za božična drevesca; Zvončki za božično drevo; Frnikole; Oblačila za punčke; Naprave za telovadbo; Vadbeni pasovi za zmanjšanje obsega pasu; Igrače za uporabo v plavalnih bazenih; Dekoracije in okraski za božična drevesca.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Leksaker för husdjur; Ballonger; Byggklossar [leksaker]; Leksaker; Marionetter; Plyschleksaker med vidhängande tröstfilt; Studslera; Verktyg för att återställa märken/nedslagshål på green [golfutrustning]; Färgkulor (paintball) [projektiler]; Yogagungor; Ljushållare för julgranar; Klockor för julgranar; Spelkulor; Dockkläder; Träningsapparater; Korsetter för midjeträning; Leksaker för användning i simbassänger; Prydnader och pynt för julgranar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/072</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-16</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/141</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1079035</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>61580</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
