<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-11T09:40:14</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018225903</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018225903</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-07</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>es</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-11</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Vgate</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkImageDetails>
<MarkImage>
<MarkImageIdentifier identifierKindCode="EM">000162303875</MarkImageIdentifier>
<MarkImageFileFormat>JPG</MarkImageFileFormat>
<MarkImageURI>file://018/225/018225903/000162303875.JPG</MarkImageURI>
<MarkImageCategory>
         <CategoryCodeDetails>
          <CategoryCode>27.05.01</CategoryCode>
         </CategoryCodeDetails>
        </MarkImageCategory>
</MarkImage>
</MarkImageDetails>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Скенери за изображения; Прецизни измервателни апарати; Черни кутии [устройства за записване на данни]; Електронни апарати и уреди за навигация и позициониране; Електронни контролни панели; Инсталации, предпазващи от кражба, електрически; Защитни устройства за лично ползване за защита при злополуки; Безжични зареждащи устройства; Апарати за глобално позициониращи системи [GPS]; Ръчни 3D скенери.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Skenery (snímače obrazů); Přístroje pro přesná měření; Černé skříňky [zařízení na záznam dat]; Elektronické navigační a polohovací přístroje a nástroje; Elektrické kontrolní panely; Elektrická zabezpečovací zařízení proti krádeži; Osobní ochranné prostředky k prevenci nehod; Bezdrátové nabíječky; Navigační zařízení Globálního polohového systému (GPS); Ruční 3D skenery.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Billedskannere; Præcisionsmåleapparater; Sorte bokse [dataoptagere]; Elektroniske navigations- og positioneringsapparater og -instrumenter; Elektriske kontrolpaneler; Tyverihindrende installationer, elektriske; Beskyttelsesindretninger til personlig brug mod ulykker; Trådløse opladere; Global Positioning System [GPS] apparater; Håndholdte 3D-scannere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Bildscanner; Präzisionsmessgeräte; Blackboxes [Datenrekorder]; Elektronische Navigations- und Ortungsapparate und -instrumente; Elektro-Schalttafeln; Elektrische Diebstahlalarmanlagen; Unfallschutzvorrichtungen für den persönlichen Gebrauch; Kabellose Ladegeräte; GPS-Geräte; Tragbare 3D-Scanner.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Σαρωτές εικόνων· Μέτρηση ακριβείας (Συσκευές -ης -)· Μαύρα κουτιά [συσκευές καταγραφής δεδομένων]· Ηλεκτρονικές συσκευές και όργανα πλοήγησης και προσδιορισμού θέσης· Ηλεκτρικοί πίνακες ελέγχου· Αντικλεπτικές εγκαταστάσεις ηλεκτρικές· Ατυχημάτων (Μηχανισμοί ατομικής προστασίας κατά των -)· Ασύρματοι φορτιστές· Συσκευές παγκόσμιου συστήματος προσδιορισμού θέσης [GPS]· Τρισδιάστατοι σαρωτές χειρός.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Image scanners; Precision measuring apparatus; Black boxes [data recorders]; Electronic navigational and positioning apparatus and instruments; Electric control panels; Theft prevention installations, electric; Protection devices for personal use against accidents; Wireless chargers; GPS navigation devices; Hand-held 3D scanners.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de escáner de imágenes; Aparatos para mediciones de precisión; Cajas negras [registradores de datos]; Aparatos e instrumentos electrónicos de navegación y posicionamiento; Paneles de control de operaciones eléctricos; Instalaciones eléctricas antirrobo; Dispositivos de protección personal contra accidentes; Cargadores inalámbricos; Aparatos para sistemas mundiales de determinación de la posición [GPS]; Escáneres tridimensionales portátiles.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kujutise skannerid; Täppismõõteriistad, täppismõõdikud; Mustad kastid [andmesalvestid]; Elektroonilised navigatsiooni- ja positsioneerimisseadmed ja -vahendid; Elektrilised juhtpaneelid; Elektrilised vargust ennetavad seadmed; Individuaalkaitsevahendid; Juhtmeta laadurid; Globaalse positsioneerimise seadmed, GPS-seadmed; Käeshoitavad 3D-skannerid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Skannerit; Täsmämittauslaitteet; Mustat laatikot [tiedontallentimet]; Elektroniset navigointi- ja paikannuslaitteet ja -välineet; Käytönvalvontataulut [sähköiset]; Varkaudenestolaitteet, sähkökäyttöiset; Suojalaitteet onnettomuuksien varalta, henkilökohtaiset; Langattomat laturit; GPS-laitteet; Kädessä pidettävät 3D-skannerit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Scanneurs d'image; Appareils de mesure de précision; Boîtes noires [enregistreurs de données]; Appareils et instruments électroniques de navigation et de localisation; Tableaux de commande électriques; Installations électriques pour préserver du vol; Dispositifs de protection personnelle contre les accidents; Chargeurs sans fil; Appareils pour GPS [systèmes de repérage universel]; Scanners 3D portables.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Skeneri za slike; Aparati za precizno mjerenje; Crne kutije [zapisivači podataka]; Elektronički uređaj i instrumenti za navigaciju i pozicioniranje; Električne upravljačke ploče; Električne instalacije protiv krađe; Nesreće na radu (uređaji za osobnu zaštitu na radu); Bežični punjači; Uređaji za globalno pozicioniranje [GPS]; Ručni 3D skeneri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Képszkennerek; Precíziós mérőműszerek; Fekete dobozok [adatrögzítők]; Elektronikus navigációs és pozicionáló [helymeghatározó] készülékek és műszerek; Elektromos vezérlőpanelek; Lopásgátló berendezések, elektromos; Védőeszközök személyek balesetvédelmére; Vezeték nélküli töltők; GPS készülékek; Kézi működtetésű háromdimenziós szkennerek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Scanner di immagini; Apparecchi di misura di precisione; Scatole nere [registratori di dati]; Apparecchi e strumenti elettronici di navigazione e di posizionamento; Pannelli di controllo elettrici; Impianti di allarme antifurto elettrici; Dispositivi di protezione personale contro gli infortuni; Caricatori senza filo; Apparecchi GPS [Sistema di Posizionamento Globale]; Scanner 3D portatili.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vaizdo skeneriai; Tikslieji matavimo prietaisai; Juodosios dėžės [duomenų įrašymo įrenginiai]; Elektroniniai navigacijos ir padėties nustatymo aparatai bei prietaisai; Valdymo pultai (elektriniai); Elektriniai įrenginiai nuo vagystės; Asmeninės apsaugos priemonės nuo nelaimingų atsitikimų; Belaidžiai įkrovikliai; Globalinės padėties nustatymo sistemos [GPS] aparatai; Rankiniai 3D skeneriai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Attēlu skeneri; Augstas precizitātes mēraparāti; Melnās kastes (datu reģistratori); Elektroniskie navigācijas un pozicionēšanas aparāti un instrumenti; Elektriski kontroles paneļi; Elektriskās iekārtas zādzību novēršanai; Ierīces individuālai aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem; Bezvadu uzlādes ierīces; Globālās pozicionēšanas sistēmas (GPS) iekārtas; Rokas 3D skeneri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Magna li tiskannja l-immaġini; Apparat għall-kejl bi preċiżjoni; Kaxex suwed [reġistraturi tad-dejta]; Strumenti u apparat elettroniċi għan-navigazzjoni u l-pożizzjonament; Pannelli elettriċi għall-kontroll; Installazzjonijiet li jipprevjenu s-serq, tal-elettriku; Tagħmir ta' protezzjoni għall-użu personali kontra l-inċidenti; Ċarġers mingħajr fili; Apparat ta' Sistema ta' Pożizzjonar Globali [GPS]; Skaners 3D li jinżammu fl-idejn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Beeldscanners; Precisiemeetapparaten; Zwarte dozen [data recorders]; Elektronische navigatie- en positioneringstoestellen en -instrumenten; Bedieningspanelen [elektrisch]; Elektrische installaties voor diefstalpreventie; Inrichtingen voor de bescherming van personen tegen ongevallen; Draadloze opladers; GPS-systemen; Draagbare 3D-scanners.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Skanery obrazu; Urządzenia do pomiarów precyzyjnych; Czarne skrzynki [rejestratory danych]; Elektroniczne urządzenia i przyrządy do nawigacji i ustalania położenia; Elektryczne pulpity sterownicze; Elektryczne instalacje przeciwwłamaniowe; Urządzenia do ochrony osobistej przed wypadkami; Ładowarki bezprzewodowe; Urządzenia systemu GPS; Podręczne skanery 3D.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Scanners de imagem; Aparelhos de medição de precisão; Caixas negras [dispositivos de registo de dados]; Aparelhos e instrumentos eletrónicos de posicionamento e navegação; Painéis elétricos de comando; Instalações elétricas antirroubo; Dispositivos de proteção pessoal contra os acidentes; Carregadores sem fios; Dispositivos para sistemas GPS; Scanners 3D portáteis.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Scanere de imagini; Aparate de măsură de precizie; Cutii negre [dispozitive de înregistrare de date]; Instrumente și aparate electronice de navigație și localizare; Tablouri de operare și comandă [electrice]; Instalații electrice antifurt; Dispozitive de protecție, de uz personal, împotriva accidentelor; Încărcătoare fără fir; Aparate de sistem de poziționare globală [GPS]; Scanere 3D portabile.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Skenery; Presné meracie prístroje; Čierne skrinky (záznamníky údajov); Elektronické navigačné a polohové prístroje a nástroje; Elektrické kontrolné panely; Elektrické zariadenia proti krádežiam; Osobné ochranné prostriedky proti nehodám; Bezdrôtové nabíjačky; Zariadenia globálneho polohového systému (GPS); Ručné 3D skenery.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Skenerji; Aparati za natančno merjenje; Črne skrinjice [zapisovalniki podatkov]; Elektronski navigacijski in pozicijski aparati in instrumenti; Električne kontrolne plošče; Protivlomne napeljave, električne; Zaščitne naprave proti poškodbam, za osebno uporabo; Brezžični polnilniki; GPS aparati [Sistemi za globalno pozicioniranje]; Ročni 3D skenerji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bildskannrar; Precisionsmätapparater; Svarta lådor [dataregistrering]; Elektroniska apparater och instrument för navigering och positionering; Elektriska kontrollpaneler; Elektriska stöldförhindrande installationer; Skyddsanordningar mot olyckor för personligt bruk; Trådlösa laddare; Satellitnavigationssystemapparater [GPS]; Handhållna 3D-skannrar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Агенции за внос и износ; Предоставяне на бизнес информация чрез уебсайт; Осигуряване на онлайн пазар за покупко-продажби на стоки и услуги; Услуги, свързани с преместване на предприятия; Оптимизиране на търсещи системи с цел насърчаване на продажбите; Индексиране на съдържанието на уебсайтове за търговски и рекламни цели; Онлайн реклама в компютърна мрежа; Проучване на пазара; Организиране на търговски изложения; Насърчаване на продажбите [за трети лица].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Zprostředkování dovozu a vývozu; Poskytování obchodních informací prostřednictvím webových stránek; Provozování online trhu pro kupující a prodejce výrobků a služeb; Služby podnikům při jejich přesídlení; Optimalizace vyhledávačů pro účely podpory prodeje; Indexace webových stránek pro obchodní nebo reklamní účely; Online inzerce v počítačové síti; Průzkum trhu; Pořádání veletrhů; Podpora prodeje jiných osob.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Import- og eksportagenturer; Stillen forretningsinformation til rådighed via et websted; Tilvejebringelse af en onlinemarkedsplads til købere og sælgere af varer og tjenesteydelser; Administrativ omlægning af forretningsvirksomhed; Optimering af søgemaskiner til markedsføring; Webindeksering med kommercielle eller reklamemæssige formål; Online-annoncering på et computernetværk; Markedsforskning; Arrangering af handelsmesser; Salgsfremmende foranstaltninger for andre.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Dienstleistungen einer Im- und Exportagentur; Bereitstellung von Geschäftsinformationen über eine Website; Bereitstellen eines Online-Marktplatzes für Käufer und Verkäufer von Waren und Dienstleistungen; Verwaltungsdienstleistungen für Unternehmensverlagerungen; Optimierung von Suchmaschinen zur Verkaufsförderung; Indexierung von Webseiten für Geschäfts- und Werbezwecke; Online-Werbung in einem Computernetzwerk; Marktforschung; Organisation von Handelsmessen; Verkaufsförderung [Sales promotion] für Dritte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Πρακτορεία εισαγωγών-εξαγωγών· Παροχή επιχειρηματικών πληροφοριών μέσω δικτυακού τόπου· Παροχή χώρων αγορών επί γραμμής για αγοραστές και πωλητές προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών· Υπηρεσίες μετεγκατάστασης για επιχειρήσεις· Βελτιστοποίηση μηχανών αναζήτησης για προώθηση πωλήσεων· Διαδικτυακή ευρετηρίαση για εμπορικούς ή διαφημιστικούς σκοπούς· Διαφήμιση on line σε δίκτυο πληροφορικής· Έρευνα αγοράς· Οργάνωση εκθεσιακών σαλονιών· Προώθηση πωλήσεων [για τρίτους].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Import-export agency services; Providing business information via a web site; Provision of an online marketplace for buyers and sellers of goods and services; Administrative services for the relocation of businesses; Search engine optimization for sales promotion; Search engine optimisation for sales promotion; Web indexing for commercial or advertising purposes; Online advertising on a computer network; Marketing research; Organization of trade fairs; Sales promotion for others.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de agencias de importación-exportación; Suministro de información comercial por sitios web; Suministro de espacios de venta en línea para vendedores y compradores de productos y servicios; Servicios de reubicación para empresas; Optimización de motores de búsqueda con fines de promoción de venta; Indexación de páginas web con fines comerciales o publicitarios; Publicidad en línea por una red informática; Servicios de investigación de mercados; Organización de ferias de comercio; Promoción de ventas para terceros.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ekspordi- ja impordiagentuuride teenused; Äriinfo pakkumine veebilehekülgedel; Veebipõhise müügikeskkonna pakkumine kaupade ja teenuste ostjatele ning müüjatele; Äritegevuse siirdeteenused; Otsingumootorite optimeerimine müügiedendusena; Veebi indekseerimine äri või reklaami eesmärgil; Arvutivõrgureklaam; Turu-uuringud; Messide korraldamine; Müügikampaaniad, -reklaam teenusena.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tuonti- ja vientiagentuuripalvelut; Liiketoimintatietojen tarjoaminen verkkosivuston välityksellä; Online-markkinapaikan tarjoaminen tavaroiden ja palvelujen ostajille ja myyjille; Liikeyritysten uudelleensijoituspalvelut; Hakukoneiden optimointi myynnin edistämiseksi; Verkkoluetteloiden tekeminen kaupan tai mainonnan tarkoituksiin; Online-mainonta tietoverkoissa; Markkinatutkimus; Messujen järjestäminen; Myynninedistäminen [muille].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d'agences d'import-export; Informations commerciales par le biais de sites web; Mise à disposition d'espaces de vente en ligne pour acheteurs et vendeurs de produits et services; Services de relogement pour entreprises; Optimisation de moteurs de recherche à des fins de promotion de vente; Référencement de sites web à but commercial ou publicitaire; Publicité en ligne sur un réseau informatique; Étude de marché; Organisation de foires commerciales; Promotion des ventes pour des tiers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Agencije za uvoz-izvoz; Pružanje poslovnih informacija putem web-stranice; Pružanje internetskog tržišnog prostora za kupce i prodavatelje proizvoda i usluga; Poduzeća (usluge preselenja za poduzeća); Optimizacija pretraživača za promidžbu prodaje; Indeksiranje internetskih stranica za komercijalne ili promidžbene potrebe; Online oglašavanje na računalnim mrežama; Istraživanje tržišta; Organiziranje trgovačkih sajmova; Promicanje prodaje za treće osobe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Import-export ügynökségek; Üzleti információk nyújtása weboldalon keresztül; Online piactér biztosítása áruk és szolgáltatások eladói és vásárlói részére; Költöztető szolgálat vállalkozások számára; Keresőmotor-optimalizálás reklámozás céljából; Webindexelés kereskedelmi vagy reklám célokra; On-line hirdetői tevékenység számítógépes hálózaton; Piackutatás; Kereskedelmi vásárok rendezése; Értékesítési promóciós szolgáltatások.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di agenzie per l'importazione e l'esportazione; Informazioni commerciali diffuse tramite siti web; Fornitura di un mercato online per acquirenti e venditori di beni e servizi; Servizi di rialloggio per imprese; Ottimizzazione di motori di ricerca per promozione di vendita; Indicizzazione di siti web a scopi commerciali o pubblicitari; Pubblicità online su rete informatica; Indagini di mercato; Fiere campionarie (Organizzazione di -); Promozione delle vendite per i terzi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Importo ir eksporto agentūrų paslaugos; Verslo informacijos teikimas visuotinio kompiuterių tinklo svetainėse; Interneto prekyviečių teikimas prekių ir paslaugų pardavėjams bei pirkėjams; Administracinės verslo perkėlimo paslaugos; Paieškos sistemos optimizavimas pardavimo skatinimo reikmėms; Žiniatinklio indeksavimas komercijos ar reklamos reikmėms; Viešasis elektroninis reklamavimas kompiuterių tinkle; Rinkos tyrinėjimas; Komercinių mugių rengimas; Prekių pardavimo skatinimas [kitiems].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Importa-eksporta aģentūru pakalpojumi; Uzņēmējdarbības informācijas sniegšana tīmekļa vietnēs; Tiešsaistes tirgus nodrošināšana preču un pakalpojumu pārdevējiem un pircējiem; Administratīvie pakalpojumi uzņēmējdarbības pārvietošanai; Meklētājprogrammu optimizēšana tirdzniecības veicināšanai; Tīmekļa vietņu satura indeksēšana komerciāliem vai reklāmas nolūkiem; Reklāma tiešsaistē ar datortīklu starpniecību; Tirgus pētījumi; Gadatirgu organizēšana; Preču noieta veicināšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' aġenzija tal-importazzjoni u esportazzjoni; Forniment ta' informazzjoni dwar negozju permezz ta' sit web; Forniment ta' suq onlajn għal xerrejja u bejjiegħa ta' prodotti u servizzi; Servizzi ta' rilokazzjoni għan-negozji; Ottimizzazzjoni ta' magna tat-tiftix għall-promozzjoni tal-bejgħ; Indiċjar web għall-finijiet kummerċjali jew ta' reklamar; Reklamar onlajn fuq netwerk tal-kompjuters; Riċerka tas-suq; L-arranġament ta' fieri tal-kummerċ; Il-promozzjoni tal-bejgħ għal oħrajn.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diensten van import- en exportagentschappen; Verschaffen van handelsinformatie via websites; Ter beschikking stellen van online verkoopplaats voor kopers en verkopers van goederen en diensten; Administratieve diensten voor de herhuisvesting voor bedrijven Ni MG; Optimalisatie van zoekmachines voor verkooppromotie; Web indexering voor commerciële of advertentiedoeleinden; Online reclame op een computernetwerk; Marktonderzoek; Organisatie van handelsbeurzen; Verkooppromotie [voor derden].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi agencji importowo-eksportowych; Udostępnianie informacji o działalności gospodarczej za pośrednictwem strony internetowej; Zapewnianie platformy internetowej dla nabywców i sprzedawców towarów i usług; Usługi związane z przenoszeniem przedsiębiorstw; Optymalizacja wyszukiwarek do celów promocji dodatkowej; Indeksowanie stron internetowych w celach handlowych lub reklamowych; Reklama online za pośrednictwem sieci komputerowej; Badania rynkowe; Organizowanie targów handlowych; Promocja sprzedaży dla osób trzecich.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de agências de importação-exportação; Fornecimento de informações comerciais através de um website; Disponibilização de um espaço de mercado online para compradores e vendedores de produtos e serviços; Serviços de sublocação para empresas; Otimização de motores de busca para promoção de vendas; Indexação de websites para fins comerciais ou publicitários; Publicidade online numa rede informática; Estudos de mercado; Organização de feiras de comércio; Promoção de vendas [prestada a terceiros].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Agenții de import-export; Furnizare de informații de afaceri prin intermediul unui site; Furnizarea unei piețe online pentru cumpărătorii și vânzătorii de bunuri și servicii; Afaceri (Servicii de relocare pentru -); Optimizarea motoarelor de căutare pentru promovarea vânzărilor; Indexare web în scop comercial sau publicitar; Publicitate on-line într-o rețea informatizată; Studii de piață; Organizare de târguri comerciale; Promovarea vânzărilor pentru terți.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kancelárie zaoberajúce sa dovozom a vývozom; Poskytovanie obchodných informácií prostredníctvom webových stránok; Online poskytovanie obchodného priestoru pre nákupcov a predajcov tovarov a služieb; Služby poskytované pri premiestňovaní podnikov; Optimalizácia internetových vyhľadávačov na podporu predaja; Indexovanie webových stránok na obchodné alebo reklamné účely; Online reklama na počítačovej komunikačnej sieti; Marketingový prieskum; Usporadúvanie veľtrhov; Podpora predaja (pre tretie osoby).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Uvozno - izvozne agencije; Nudenje poslovnih informacij preko spletne strani; Zagotavljanje spletnega trga za kupce in prodajalce blaga in storitev; Selitvene storitve za podjetja; Optimizacija iskalnikov za pospeševanje prodaje; Spletno indeksiranje za komercialne ali oglaševalske namene; Spletno oglaševanje preko računalniškega omrežja; Tržne raziskave; Prirejanje trgovskih sejmov; Pospeševanje prodaje (za druge).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Import-exportagenturer; Tillhandahållande av affärsinformation via en webbsida; Tillhandahållande av en marknadsplats online för köpare och säljare av varor och tjänster; Administrativa tjänster vid omlokalisering av företag; Sökmotoroptimering som säljfrämjande verksamhet (sales promotion); Webbindexering för kommersiella eller reklamändamål; Annonsering online via datanätverk; Marknadsundersökningar; Anordnande av branschmässor; Sales promotiontjänster.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Провеждане на технически проектни проучвания; Изследвания в областта на механиката; Проучване и разработване на нови продукти за трети лица; Проектиране на интегрални схеми; Тестване на функционалността на апарати и инструменти; Изпитване на продукти; Дизайн на опаковки; Софтуер като услуги; Създаване и разработка на уебсайтове за трети лица; Предоставяне на търсачки за интернет.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Provádění studií technických projektů; Výzkum ve strojírenství; Výzkum a vývoj nových výrobků pro jiné osoby; Návrhářské služby vztahující se k integrovaným obvodům; Testování funkčnosti přístrojů a nástrojů; Testování výrobků; Navrhování obalů; Software jako služba [SaaS]; Tvorba a navrhování webových stránek pro třetí osoby; Provozování internetových vyhledávačů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Gennemførelse af tekniske projektstudier; Forskning vedrørende mekanik; Forskning i og udvikling af nye produkter for andre; Design af integrerede kredsløb; Afprøvning af apparaters og instrumenters funktionalitet; Produktafprøvning; Design af emballage; Software as a service [saas]; Udarbejdelse og design af websider for andre; Stillen søgemaskiner til rådighed på internettet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Durchführung von technischen Projektplanungen; Forschungen auf dem Gebiet des Maschinenbaus; Forschungs- und Entwicklungsdienste bezüglich neuer Produkte für Dritte; Entwurfsdienstleistungen in Bezug auf integrierte Schaltkreise; Prüfung der Funktionalität von Apparaten und Instrumenten; Produktprüfung; Dienstleistungen eines Verpackungsdesigners; Software as a Service [SaaS]; Gestaltung und Konzeption von Webseiten für Dritte; Bereitstellung von Suchmaschinen für das Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διεξαγωγή μελετών τεχνικών έργων· Μηχανολογικής (Έρευνες -)· Ερευνα και ανάπτυξη νέων προϊόντων για άλλους· Σχεδιασμός ολοκληρωμένων κυκλωμάτων· Δοκιμή λειτουργικότητας συσκευών και οργάνων· Δοκιμή προϊόντων· Σχεδιαστών συσκευασίας (Υπηρεσίες -)· Λογισμικό σαν υπηρεσία· Δημιουργία και σχεδιασμός ιστοσελίδων για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Λειτουργία μηχανής αναζήτησης για το Διαδίκτυο.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Conducting technical project studies; Mechanical research; Research and development of new products for others; Design of integrated circuits; Testing the functionality of apparatus and instruments; Product testing; Packaging design; Software as a service [SaaS]; Creating and designing web pages for others; Providing search engines for the internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Realización de estudios de proyectos técnicos; Investigación en mecánica; Investigación y desarrollo de nuevos productos para terceros; Servicios de diseño relacionados con circuitos integrados; Comprobar la funcionalidad de aparatos e instrumentos; Prueba de productos; Servicios de diseñadores de embalajes; Software como servicio [SaaS]; Creación y diseño de páginas web para terceros; Provisión de motores de búsqueda para Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tehniliste projektiuuringute läbiviimine; Mehaanikauuringud; Uute toodete uuringud ja arendamine teenusena; Integraallülituste projekteerimine; Seadmete ja riistade funktsioonide katsetamine; Toodete testimine; Pakendidisain, -kujundus; Pilveteenused [SaaS]; Veebisaitide loomine ja kujundamine, teistele isikutele; Interneti otsimootorite loomine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Teknisten projektitutkimusten suorittaminen; Mekaniikkaan liittyvä tutkimus; Tutkimus- ja kehitystyö muille; Mikropiirien suunnittelu; Laitteiden ja välineiden toimivuuden testaus; Tuotetestaus; Pakkausten muotoilu; Verkkosovelluspalvelut [SaaS]; WWW-sivustojen laadinta ja suunnittelu kolmansille osapuolille; Internetin hakukonepalveluiden tarjoaminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Conduite d'études de projets techniques; Recherches en mécanique; Recherche et développement de nouveaux produits pour des tiers; Services de conception de circuits intégrés; Test de la fonctionnalité d'appareils et d'instruments; Services d'essais de produits; Services de dessinateurs pour emballages; Logiciel-service [SaaS]; Création et conception de sites Web pour le compte de tiers; Fourniture de moteurs de recherche pour l'internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Provedba studija tehničkih projekata; Istraživanja u mehanici; Istraživanje i razvoj za druge; Usluge projektiranja u svezi s integriranim krugovima; Testiranje funkcionalnosti aparata i instrumenata; Testiranje proizvoda; Ambalaža (usluge crtača ambalaže); Softver kao usluga [SaaS]; Izrada i dizajn Web stranica za druge; Ponuda pretraživača za Internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Műszaki tervtanulmányok készítése; Mechanikai kutatás; Kutatási és fejlesztési szolgáltatások; Integrált áramkörökhöz kapcsolódó tervezési szolgáltatások; Berendezések és műszerek működésének ellenőrzése; Termékek tesztelése; Csomagolástervezés; Szoftver mint szolgáltatás [SaaS]; Weboldalak készítése és tervezése; Internetes keresőmotorok biztosítása.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Conduzione di studi di progetti tecnici; Ricerche in meccanica; Ricerca e sviluppo di nuovi prodotti per i terzi; Progettazione di circuiti integrati; Esame della funzionalità di apparecchi e strumenti; Test di prodotti; Servizi di disegnatori per imballaggi; Servizi di software [SaaS]; Creazione e progettazione di pagine web per terzi; Fornitura di motori di ricerca per internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Techninių projektų tyrimų vedimas; Mechanikos tyrimai; Naujų produktų tyrimas ir kūrimas (paslaugos kitiems); Projektavimo paslaugos, susijusios su integriniais grandynais; Aparatų ir instrumentų funkcionalumo testavimas; Produktų bandymai; Taros ir pakuočių dizainas; Programinė įranga kaip paslauga [SaaS]; Tinklalapių kūrimas ir projektavimas kitiems; Internetinių paieškos sistemų parūpinimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tehnisko projektu vadība; Izpēte mehānikas jomā; Jaunu produktu izpēte un izstrāde trešajām personām; Projektēšanas pakalpojumi saistībā ar integrētajām shēmām; Aparātu un instrumentu funkcionalitātes testēšana; Produktu testēšana; Iepakojuma dizaina pakalpojumi; Programmatūra kā pakalpojums (SaaS); Tīmekļa vietņu izveide un dizains citiem; Meklētājprogrammu nodrošināšana Internetā.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Twettiq ta' studji ta' proġetti tekniċi; Riċerka fil-mekkanika; Riċerka u żvilupp ta' prodotti ġodda għal oħrajn; Servizzi ta' disinn dwar ċirkwiti integrati; L-ittestjar tal-funzjonalità tal-apparat u l-istrumenti; L-ittestjar ta' prodott; Disinn tal-ippakkjar; Softwer bħala servizz [SaaS]; Ħolqien u disinn ta' paġni ta' siti elettroniċi għal oħrajn; Provvista ta' faċilitajiet ta' tiftix għall-internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Technische projectstudies; Onderzoek op het gebied van de mechanica; Onderzoek en ontwikkeling van nieuwe producten voor derden; Ontwerp met betrekking tot geïntegreerde schakelingen; Het testen van de functionaliteit van apparaten en instrumenten; Het testen van de goederen; Ontwerpen van verpakkingen; Ter beschikking stellen van software [SaaS]; Ontwikkelen en ontwerpen van websites voor anderen; Ter beschikking stellen van zoekmachines voor het internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Opracowywanie projektów technicznych; Badania w dziedzinie mechaniki; Prace badawczo-rozwojowe nad nowymi produktami dla osób trzecich; Usługi projektowania związane z układami scalonymi; Testowanie funkcjonalności sprzętu i instrumentów; Testowanie produktów; Projektowanie opakowań; Oprogramowanie jako usługa [SaaS]; Tworzenie i projektowanie stron internetowych dla osób trzecich; Udostępnienie wyszukiwarek internetowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Realização de estudos de projetos técnicos; Investigação mecânica; Pesquisa e desenvolvimento de novos produtos para terceiros; Serviços de design relacionados com circuitos integrados; Teste da funcionalidade de aparelhos e instrumentos; Testes de produtos; Design de embalagens; Software como serviço [SaaS]; Criação e design de sítios web para terceiros; Serviços de motores de busca para a internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Efectuare de studii de proiecte tehnice; Studii în domeniul mecanicii; Cercetare și dezvoltare de produse noi pentru terți; Proiectare de circuite integrate; Testarea funcționalității aparatelor și instrumentelor; Testarea produselor; Design de ambalaje; Software ca serviciu [SaaS]; Crearea și proiectarea de pagini web pentru terți; Furnizare de motoare de căutăre în internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Štúdie technických projektov; Strojársky výskum; Výskum a vývoj nových výrobkov (pre zákazníkov); Navrhovanie integrovaných obvodov; Testovanie funkčnosti prístrojov a nástrojov; Testovanie výrobkov; Navrhovanie obalov, obalové dizajnérstvo; Poskytovanie softvéru prostredníctvom internetu (SaaS); Vytváranie a navrhovanie webových stránok pre tretie osoby; Poskytovanie internetových vyhľadávačov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Izvajanje študij tehničnih projektov; Raziskave na področju strojništva; Raziskave in razvoj za druge; Storitve oblikovanja v zvezi z integriranimi vezji; Preskušanje funkcionalnosti aparatov in instrumentov; Testiranje izdelkov; Oblikovanje embalaže; Programska oprema kot storitev [SaaS]; Izdelava in oblikovanje spletnih strani za druge; Nudenje internetnih iskalnikov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Genomförande av tekniska projektstudier; Forskning avseende mekanik; Forskning och utveckling av nya produkter för andra; Utformningstjänster avseende integrerade kretsar; Testning av funktionen hos apparater och instrument; Produktprovning; Formgivning av emballage; Molntjänster [SaaS]; Utformning och design av webbsidor åt andra; Upplåtande av sökmotorer för internet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/080</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-29</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/151</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-11</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080291</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>71602</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017739528</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Replacement of representative</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>71602</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-04-20</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>017832109</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Representative - Change of name and professional address</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>71602</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-05-14</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
