<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-07T08:34:39</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018225902</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018225902</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-05</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>fr</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-07</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>LELET NY</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>14</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Бижута с изкуствени скъпоценни камъни; Висулки [бижутерийни изделия]; Медальони с капаче [бижутерия]; Верижки [бижутерия]; Гривни [бижутерийни изделия]; Бижута с изкуствени скъпоценни камъни; Кутии за излагане на бижута; Кутии за бижута [ковчежета]; Бижута, изработени от злато; Бижута, изработени от пластмаса; Дамски бижута; Дребни украшения за гривни; Ахат под формата на бижута; Украшения [бижутерийни изделия]; Амулети [бижутерия]; Огърлици [бижутерия]; Пръстени [бижутерийни изделия]; Пръстени [бижутерийни изделия]; Перли [бижутерийни изделия]; Брошки [бижутерия]; Игли [бижутерия]; Бижутерия; Kутии за бижута и кутии за часовници; Скъпоценни камъни, перли и благородни метали и техни имитации.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Skleněná bižutérie (imitace drahokamů); Přívěšky na krk jako klenoty; Medailónky [šperky]; Řetízky [šperky]; Náramky [šperky]; Skleněná bižutérie (imitace drahokamů); Kazety na šperky; Šperkovnice; Zlaté klenoty; Šperky vyrobené z plastu; Dámské šperky; Přívěsky na náramky; Achát jako klenot; Ozdoby (šperky); Amulety [šperky]; Náhrdelníky [šperky]; Prsteny [šperky]; Prsteny [šperky]; Perly [šperky]; Brože [šperky]; Jehlice [šperky]; Šperky; Pouzdra na šperky a pouzdra na hodiny a hodinky; Drahé kameny, perly a drahé kovy, jakož i jejich imitace.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Simili; Smykkevedhæng; Medaljoner (smykker); Kæder [smykker]; Armbånd (smykker); Simili; Præsentationsæsker til smykker; Smykkeskrin; Guldsmykker; Smykker fremstillet af plastik; Smykker til kvinder; Charms (smykkevedhæng) til armbånd; Agat som smykker; Smykker [guldsmedevarer]; Amuletter (smykker); Halskæder [smykker]; Ringe (smykker); Ringe (smykker); Perler [smykker]; Brocher [smykker]; Smykkenåle; Juvelerarbejder; Smykkekasser og urkasser; Smykkesten, perler og ædle metaller og imitationer deraf.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Strass [Edelsteinimitation]; Schmuckanhänger; Medaillons [Schmuck]; Ketten [Schmuckwaren]; Armbänder [Schmuck]; Strass [Edelsteinimitation]; Präsentationsschatullen für Schmuck; Schmucketuis; Goldschmuck; Schmuckstücke aus Kunststoff; Schmuckwaren für Frauen; Armbandanhänger; Achate als Schmuckwaren; Schmuckwaren; Amulette [Schmuckwaren]; Halsketten [Schmuck]; Ringe [Schmuck]; Ringe [Schmuck]; Perlen [Schmuck]; Broschen [Schmuck]; Anstecknadeln [Schmuckwaren]; Juwelierwaren, Schmuckwaren; Schmuck- und Uhrenbehältnisse; Edelsteine, Perlen und Edelmetalle sowie Imitationen hiervon.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Στρας κοσμηματοποιίας· Κρεμαστά κοσμήματα· Μενταγιόν [κοσμήματα]· Αλυσίδες [κοσμήματα]· Βραχιόλια [κοσμήματα]· Στρας κοσμηματοποιίας· Κουτιά παρουσίασης για κοσμήματα· Κοσμηματοθήκες· Χρυσά κοσμήματα· Κοσμήματα από πλαστικό· Γυναικεία κοσμήματα· Διακοσμητικά υλικά για βραχιόλια· Αχάτης ως κόσμημα· Στολίδια [κοσμήματα]· Φυλακτά [κοσμήματα]· Περιδέραια· Δακτυλίδια [κοσμήματα]· Δακτυλίδια [κοσμήματα]· Μαργαριτάρια [κοσμήματα]· Καρφίτσες [κοσμήματα]· Καρφίτσες [κοσμηματοποιία]· Κοσμήματα· Κοσμηματοθήκες και κουτιά ρολογιών· Πολύτιμοι λίθοι, μαργαριτάρια και πολύτιμα μέταλλα, και απομιμήσεις αυτών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Paste jewellery [costume jewelry (Am.)]; Jewel pendants; Lockets [jewellery]; Chains [jewelry]; Bracelets [jewellery, jewelry (Am.)]; Paste jewellery [costume jewelry (Am.)]; Presentation boxes for jewelry; Jewelry boxes; Gold jewellery; Jewellery made of plastics; Women's jewelry; Bracelet charms; Agate as jewellery; Ornaments [jewellery, jewelry (Am.)]; Amulets [jewellery, jewelry (Am.)]; Necklaces [jewellery]; Rings [jewellery, jewelry (Am.)]; Rings [jewellery, jewelry (Am.)]; Pearls [jewellery]; Brooches [jewellery]; Pins being jewelry; Jewelry; Jewellery boxes and watch boxes; Gemstones, pearls and precious metals, and imitations thereof.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Estrás; Colgantes [joyas]; Medallones [joyería]; Cadenas [joyería]; Pulseras [joyería]; Estrás; Cajas de presentación para joyas; Joyeros; Joyería de oro; Joyería de plástico; Joyería de señora; Colgantes de pulsera; Ágatas como joyería; Adornos [artículos de joyería]; Amuletos [joyería]; Collares [joyería]; Anillos [joyería]; Anillos [joyería]; Perlas [artículos de joyería]; Broches [joyería]; Alfileres [joyería]; Artículos de joyería; Joyeros y estuches para relojes; Piedras preciosas, perlas y metales preciosos y sus imitaciones.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Strassist juveeltooted; Ripatsid [juveeltooted]; Medaljonid [juveeltooted]; Ketid [juveeltooted]; Käevõrud [juveeltooted]; Strassist juveeltooted; Juveeltoodete esitluskarbid; Ehtekarbid; Kuldehted; Plastist ehted; Naiste juveeltooted; Käevõruripatsid; Ahhaat juveelina; Ehted [juveeltooted]; Amuletid [juveeltooted]; Kaelakeed; Sõrmused [juveeltooted]; Sõrmused [juveeltooted]; Pärlid [juveeltooted]; Prossid [juveeltooted]; Ehisnõelad [juveeltooted]; Juveeltooted; Juveeltoodete karbid ja kellakarbid; Vääriskivid, pärlid ja väärismetallid ning nende imitatsioonid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Strassikorut; Koruriipukset; Medaljongit [koruina]; Ketjut [korut]; Rannerenkaat [korut]; Strassikorut; Korujen esittelylaatikot; Korurasiat; Kultakorut; Muovista tehdyt korut; Naisten korut; Riipukset rannekoruihin; Agaatit koruina; Koristeet (Korut); Amuletit [korut]; Kaulakorut [korut]; Sormukset [korut]; Sormukset [korut]; Helmet [koruina]; Rintaneulat [korut]; Koristeneulat [korut]; Korut; Korurasiat ja kellokotelot; Jalokivet, helmet ja jalometallit ja niiden jäljitelmät.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Bijoux fantaisie; Pendentifs [bijoux]; Médaillons [bijouterie]; Chaînes [bijouterie]; Bracelets [bijouterie]; Bijouterie fantaisie; Écrins à bijoux; Boîtes à bijoux; Bijoux en or; Bijoux en plastique; Bijoux pour femmes [bijouterie-joaillerie]; Breloques (bijouterie); Agate [bijouterie]; Parures [bijouterie]; Amulettes [bijouterie]; Colliers [bijouterie]; Anneaux [bijouterie]; Bagues [bijouterie]; Perles [bijouterie]; Broches [bijouterie]; Épingles [bijouterie]; Articles de bijouterie-joaillerie; Coffrets à bijoux et coffrets à montres; Pierres précieuses, perles et métaux précieux, et leurs imitations.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Bižuterija; Privjesci za lančiće [nakit]; Medaljoni [nakit]; Lančići [nakit]; Narukvice [nakit]; Bižuterija; Kutije za izlaganje nakita; Kutijice za nakit; Zlatni nakit; Nakit napravljen od plastike; Ženski nakit; Privjesci za narukvice; Ahat kao nakit; Ukrasi [dragulji]; Amuleti [nakit]; Ogrlice [nakit]; Prstenje [nakit]; Prstenje [nakit]; Biseri [nakit]; Broševi [nakit]; Broš igle [nakit]; Nakit; Kutije za nakit i kutije za satove; Drago kamenje, biseri i plemeniti metali te njihove imitacije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Strassz [drágakő utánzat]; Ékszer függők; Medálok [ékszerek]; Láncok [ékszerek]; Karkötők [ékszerek]; Strassz [drágakő utánzat]; Ékszerbemutató dobozok; Ékszerdobozok; Arany ékszerek; Műanyagból készült ékszerek; Női ékszerek; Karkötőre fűzhető díszek; Achát ékszer; Díszek [ékszerek]; Amulettek [ékszerek]; Nyakláncok [ékszerek]; Gyűrűk [ékszerek]; Gyűrűk [ékszerek]; Gyöngyök [ékszerek]; Brossok [ékszerek]; Dísztűk [ékszerek]; Ékszerek; Ékszerdobozok és óradobozok; Drágakövek, gyöngyök és nemesfémek, beleértve utánzataikat is.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Bigiotteria; Pendenti [gioielleria]; Medaglioni [gioielleria]; Catene [gioielleria]; Braccialetti [gioielleria]; Bigiotteria; Astucci di presentazione di gioielli; Scatole per gioielli; Gioielleria in oro; Articoli di gioielleria in plastica; Gioielleria da donna; Ciondoli per braccialetti; Agata, ovvero gioielli; Ornamenti [gioielleria]; Amuleti [gioielleria]; Collane [gioielleria]; Anelli [gioielleria]; Anelli [gioielleria]; Perle [gioielleria]; Spillette [gioielleria]; Spille [gioielleria]; Oreficeria; Porta gioie e porta orologi; Gemme, perle e metalli prezioni e loro imitazioni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Strazai; Pakabukai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Medalionai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Grandinėlės [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Apyrankės [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Strazai; Juvelyrinių dirbinių dovanų dėžutės; Brangenybių dėžutės; Auksiniai juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Plastikiniai juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Moteriški juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Apyrankių karuliai; Agatas (juvelyriniai dirbiniai); Papuošalai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Amuletai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Karoliai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Žiedai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Žiedai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Perlai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Sagės [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Smeigtukai [juvelyriniai dirbiniai]; Juvelyriniai dirbiniai; Juvelyrinių dirbinių dėžutės ir laikrodžių dėžutės; Brangakmeniai, perlai ir brangieji metalai, ir jų pakaitalai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Strass [stikla juvelierizstrādājumi]; Dārgakmeņu karekļi; Medaljoni [juvelierizstrādājumi]; Ķēdītes [juvelierizstrādājumi]; Rokassprādzes (juvelierizstrādājumi); Strass [stikla juvelierizstrādājumi]; Juvelierizstrādājumu prezentācijas kastītes; Dārglietu kārbiņas; Zelta juvelierizstrādājumi; Plastmasas dārglietas; Sieviešu juvelierizstrādājumi; Aproču piekariņi; Ahāts [juvelierizstrādājumi]; Rotājumi (juvelierizstrādājumi); Amuleti (juvelierizstrādājumi); Kaklarotas [juvelierizstrādājumi]; Gredzeni (juvelierizstrādājumi); Gredzeni (juvelierizstrādājumi); Pērles (juvelierizstrādājumi); Brošas [juvelierizstrādājumi]; Dekoratīvas piespraudes [juvelierizstrādājumi]; Juvelierizstrādājumi; Kastītes juvelierizstrādājumiem un pulksteņiem; Dārgakmeņi, pērles un cēlmetāli, un to imitācijas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Ġojjellerija falza; Pendenti tal-ġojjelli; Lokits [ġojjellerija]; Ktajjen [ġojjellerija]; Brazzuletti [ġojjellerija]; Ġojjellerija falza; Kaxxi għall-preżentazzjoni tal-ġojjelli; Kaxxi għall-ġojjelli; Ġojjellerija tad-deheb; Ġojjellerija magħmula mill-plastik; Ġojjelli tan-nisa; Oġġetti żgħar li jiddendlu mal-brazzuletti; Agata bħala ġojjellerija; Ornamenti [ġojjellerija]; Amuleti [ġojjellerija]; Kullani [ġojjellerija]; Ċrieket [ġojjellerija]; Ċrieket [ġojjellerija]; Perli [ġojjellerija]; Labar ornamentali [ġojjellerija]; Labar [ġojjellerija]; Ġojjelli; Kaxex għall-ġojjelli u kaxex għall-arloġġi; Ħaġar prezzjuż, perli u metalli prezzjużi, u l-imitazzjonijiet tagħhom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Namaakjuwelen; Juwelen hangertjes; Medaillons [juwelierswaren]; Kettingen [juwelierswaren]; Armbanden [juwelierswaren]; Namaakjuwelen; Presentatiedoosjes voor sieraden; Juwelenkistjes; Juwelierswaren vervaardigd uit goud; Juwelierswaren vervaardigd uit plastic; Damesjuwelen; Bedeltjes voor armbanden; Agaat als sieraad; Sieraden [juwelierswaren]; Amuletten [juwelierswaren]; Halskettingen [juwelierswaren]; Ringen [juwelierswaren]; Ringen [juwelierswaren]; Parels [juwelierswaren]; Broches [juwelierswaren]; Spelden [bijouterieën]; Juwelen; Juwelendoosjes en horlogedoosjes; Edelstenen, parels en edele metalen, alsmede imitaties daarvan.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Biżuteria ze szkła sztrasowego; Wisiorki [klejnoty]; Medaliony [biżuteria]; Łańcuszki [biżuteria]; Bransoletki [biżuteria]; Biżuteria ze szkła sztrasowego; Kasety do prezentacji wyrobów jubilerskich; Kasetki na biżuterię [szkatułki]; Biżuteria ze złota; Wyroby jubilerskie wykonane z tworzyw sztucznych; Biżuteria damska; Zawieszki do bransoletek; Agat stosowany w biżuterii; Ozdoby [biżuteria]; Amulety [biżuteria]; Naszyjniki [biżuteria]; Pierścionki [biżuteria]; Pierścionki [biżuteria]; Perły [biżuteria]; Broszki [biżuteria]; Szpilki [biżuteria]; Biżuteria i wyroby jubilerskie; Pudełka na biżuterię i pudełka na zegarki; Kamienie szlachetne, perły, metale szlachetne i ich imitacje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Strass [bijuteria]; Pendentes de joalharia; Medalhões [joalharia]; Correntes [joalharia]; Pulseiras [bijutaria]; Strass [bijuteria]; Caixas de apresentação para joalharia; Caixas para joias; Joalharia de ouro; Joalharia em matérias plásticas; Joalharia de senhora; Amuletos para pulseiras; Ágata em joalharia; Adereços [bijutaria]; Amuletos [joalharia]; Colares [joalharia]; Anéis [joalharia]; Anéis [joalharia]; Pérolas [bijutaria]; Broches [joalharia]; Alfinetes [joalharia]; Jóias; Caixas de joias e caixas de relógios; Pedras preciosas, pérolas e metais preciosos, e suas imitações.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ştrasuri; Bijuterii-pandantive; Medalioane [bijuterii]; Lanţuri [bijuterii]; Brăţări [bijuterii]; Ştrasuri; Cutii de prezentare pentru bijuterii; Casete de bijuterii; Bijuterii din aur; Bijuterii confecţionate din plastic; Bijuterii de damă; Talismane pentru brăţări; Agat ca bijuterie; Podoabe [bijuterie]; Amulete; Coliere [bijuterii]; Inele [bijuterii]; Inele [bijuterii]; Perle [bijuterii]; Broşe [bijuterii]; Broşe [bijuterii]; Bijuterii; Casete pentru bijuterii şi cutii pentru ceasuri; Pietre preţioase, perle şi metale preţioase şi imitaţii ale acestora.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Štras (brúsené olovnaté sklo); Prívesky na krk [šperky]; Medailóny (klenotnícke výrobky); Retiazky (klenotnícke výrobky); Náramky (klenotnícke výrobky); Štras (brúsené olovnaté sklo); Krabičky na šperky; Šperkovnice; Zlaté šperky; Šperky z plastov; Dámske šperky; Prívesky na náramky; Achát ako šperky; Ozdoby [šperky]; Amulety (klenotnícke výrobky); Náhrdelníky (klenotnícke výrobky); Prstene (klenotnícke výrobky); Prstene (klenotnícke výrobky); Korálky (klenotnícke výrobky); Brošne (klenotnícke výrobky); Ihlice (klenotnícke výrobky); Šperky; Šperkovnice a kazety na hodinky; Drahokamy, perly, drahé kovy a ich napodobeniny.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Bižuterija (ceneni modni nakit); Obeski z dragulji; Medaljoni [nakit]; Verižice [nakit]; Zapestnice [nakit]; Bižuterija (ceneni modni nakit); Skrinjice za razstavljanje nakita; Škatle za nakit; Nakit iz zlata; Nakit iz umetnih materialov; Ženski nakit; Obeski za zapestnice; Ahat kot nakit; Okraski [nakit]; Amuleti [nakit]; Ogrlice [nakit]; Prstani [nakit]; Prstani [nakit]; Biseri [nakit]; Broške [nakit]; Okrasne igle [nakit]; Nakit; Šatulje za nakit in šatulje za ure; Dragulji, biseri in žlahtne kovine ter imitacije naštetega.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Bijouterier; Hängsmycken [juveler]; Medaljonger [smycken]; Kedjor [smycken]; Armband [smycken]; Bijouterier; Presentationsaskar för smycken; Smyckeskrin; Smycken tillverkade av guld; Smycken tillverkade av plast; Damsmycken; Armbandsberlocker; Agat som smycke; Prydnader (juvelerarvaror); Amuletter [smycken]; Halsband [smycken]; Ringar (juvelerarvaror); Ringar (juvelerarvaror); Pärlor [smycken]; Broscher [smycken]; Prydnadsnålar [smycken]; Juvelerarvaror; Smyckeskrin och klockaskar; Ädelstenar, pärlor och ädla metaller samt imitationer därav.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/079</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/148</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-06</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
