<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-09-07T16:44:28</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018225915</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018225915</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>fr</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-07-27</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Vitaxium</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Витаминни добавки; Витаминни и минерални добавки; Диетични добавки, състоящи се от витамини; Витаминни препарати под формата на хранителни добавки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vitaminové doplňky; Vitaminové a minerální doplňky; Potravinové doplňky obsahující vitaminy; Vitaminové přípravky jako doplňky stravy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Vitamintilskud; Vitamin- og mineraltilskud; Kosttilskud bestående af vitaminer; Vitaminpræparater i form af kosttilskud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Vitaminzusätze; Vitamin- und Mineralstoffzusätze; Nahrungsergänzungsmittel aus Vitaminen; Vitaminpräparate in Form von Nahrungsergänzungsstoffen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συμπληρώματα βιταμινών· Συμπληρώματα βιταμινών και μεταλλικών στοιχείων· Βιταμινούχα συμπληρώματα διατροφής· Βιταμινούχα παρασκευάσματα με τη μορφή συμπληρωμάτων διατροφής.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Vitamin supplements; Vitamin and mineral supplements; Dietary supplements consisting of vitamins; Vitamin preparations in the nature of food supplements.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Suplementos vitamínicos; Suplementos vitamínicos y minerales; Complementos dietéticos de vitaminas; Preparados de vitaminas como complementos alimenticios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Vitamiinilisandid; Vitamiini- ja mineraallisandid; Vitamiinidest koosnevad toidulisandid; Vitamiinipreparaadid toidulisanditena.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vitamiinilisät; Vitamiini- ja kivennäislisäaineet; Dieettien täydennysaineet, jotka sisältävät vitamiineja; Vitamiinivalmisteet elintarvikelisinä.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Compléments vitaminés; Compléments vitaminés et minéraux; Compléments alimentaires composés de vitamines; Produits vitaminés sous forme de compléments alimentaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Vitaminski dodaci; Vitaminski i mineralni dodaci hrani; Dodaci prehrani koji sadrže vitamine; Vitaminski pripravci u obliku prehrambenih dodataka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vitamin kiegészítők; Vitamin és ásványi anyag kiegészítők; Vitaminokat tartalmazó étrend-kiegészítők; Vitaminkészítmények ételkiegészítők formájában.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Integratori vitaminici; Integratori vitaminici e minerali; Integratori alimentari di vitamine; Preparati vitaminici in forma di integratori alimentari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vitaminų papildai; Vitamininiai ir mineraliniai papildai; Dietiniai papildai iš vitaminų; Vitamininiai maisto papildai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vitamīnu piedevas; Vitamīni un diētiskas minerālvielu piedevas; Uztura piedevas, kas sastāv no vitamīniem; Kā uztura bagātinātāji lietojami vitamīnu preparāti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Supplimenti ta' vitamini; Supplimenti tal-vitamini u tal-minerali; Supplimenti dijetetiċi li jikkonsistu minn vitamini; Preparazzjonijiet tal-vitamini f'għamla ta' supplimenti tal-ikel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Vitaminesupplementen; Vitamine- en mineralensupplementen; Voedingssupplementen bestaande uit vitaminen; Vitaminepreparaten in de vorm van voedingssupplementen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Dodatki witaminowe; Dodatki witaminowe i mineralne; Suplementy diety składające się z witamin; Preparaty witaminowe w postaci suplementów diety.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Suplementos vitamínicos; Suplementos vitamínicos e minerais; Suplementos dietéticos de vitaminas; Preparações vitamínicas sob a forma de suplementos alimentares.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Suplimente pe bază de vitamine; Suplimente vitaminice și minerale; Suplimente dietetice care conțin vitamine; Preparate pe bază de vitamine sub formă de suplimente alimentare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vitamínové doplnky; Vitamíny a minerálne doplnky; Dietetické doplnky obsahujúce vitamíny; Vitamínové prípravky v podobe potravinových doplnkov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Vitaminski dodatki; Vitaminski in mineralni dodatki; Prehranski dodatki, sestavljeni iz vitaminov; Vitaminski pripravki v obliki prehranskih dopolnil.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Vitamintillskott; Vitamin- och mineraltillskott; Kosttillskott bestående av vitaminer; Vitaminpreparat i form av livsmedelstillskott.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/079</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-28</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>482682</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003126819</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-07-27</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>fr</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>FR</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>3991710</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2013-03-20</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>3991710</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2013-07-26</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>VIT-ALLIUM</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>176634</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>11412</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
