<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-21T09:52:57</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018225941</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018225941</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-06-23</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-10-20</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-06-23</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-21</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>LIBAI</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Чанти за медицински инструменти; Апарати за измерване на кръвно налягане; Апарати за изкуствено дишане; Термометри за медицински цели; Стоматологично оборудване; Ръкавици за медицински цели; Хирургически костюми; Подложки за медицински цели; Маски за медицински персонал; Бебешки шишета; Помпи за изцеждане на кърма; Секс играчки; Презервативи; Изкуствени крайници; Столове-подлоги; Хирургически маски; Маски за медицински персонал; Високофилтърни хирургични маски.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Speciální kufříky na lékařské nástroje; Přístroje na měření krevního tlaku; Přístroje pro umělé dýchání; Teploměry pro lékařské účely; Zařízení pro zubní lékařství; Rukavice pro lékařské účely; Operační pláště; Podušky pro lékařské účely; Roušky pro lékařský personál; Dětské láhve; Odsávačky mateřského mléka; Erotické hračky; Kondomy; Umělé končetiny; Židle s nočníkem; Chirurgické masky; Roušky pro lékařský personál; Chirurgické masky vysokofiltrační.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Tasker specielt fremstillet til medicinske instrumenter; Blodtryksmålere; Apparater til kunstigt åndedræt; Termometre til medicinsk brug; Tandlægeapparater og -instrumenter; Handsker til medicinske formål; Operationskitler; Puder til medicinske formål; Masker til brug for medicinsk personel; Sutteflasker; Brystpumper; Sexlegetøj; Kondomer; Kunstige lemmer; Klosetstoler; Operationsmasker; Masker til brug for medicinsk personel; Højfiltrerende masker til kirurgiske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Spezialkoffer für medizinische Instrumente; Blutdruckmessgeräte; Apparate für die künstliche Beatmung; Thermometer für medizinische Zwecke; Zahnärztliche Apparate und Instrumente; Handschuhe für medizinische Zwecke; Operationskittel; Kissen für medizinische Zwecke; Masken für medizinisches Personal; Saugflaschen; Milchpumpen; Sexspielzeug; Präservative [Kondome]; Prothesen; Nachtstühle, Leibstühle; Chirurgischer Mundschutz; Masken für medizinisches Personal; Chirurgische Masken mit hoher Filterwirkung.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Βαλίτσες ειδικές για ιατρικά εργαλεία· Πιεσόμετρα· Αναπνευστήρες· Θερμόμετρα ιατρικά· Οδοντιατρικός εξοπλισμός· Γάντια ιατρικής χρήσης· Χειρουργικές ποδιές· Μαξιλάρια για χρήση ιατρική· Μάσκες για το ιατρικό προσωπικό· Υποδοχείς για θήλαστρα· Θήλαστρα· Σεξουαλικά παιχνίδια· Προφυλακτικά· Μέλη τεχνητά· Καθίσματα με άνοιγμα για τοποθέτηση ουροδοχείου· Χειρουργικές μάσκες· Μάσκες για το ιατρικό προσωπικό· Χειρουργικές μάσκες υψηλής διήθησης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">cases fitted for medical instruments; Sphygmomanometers; apparatus for artificial respiration; thermometers for medical purposes; Dental apparatus; gloves for medical purposes; surgical gowns; Cushions for medical purposes; masks for use by medical personnel; feeding bottles; breast pumps; sex toys; Condoms; artificial limbs; commode chairs; Surgical masks; Medical masks; high filter surgical masks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Maletines especiales para instrumental médico; Esfigmomanómetros; Aparatos para la respiración artificial; Termómetros para uso médico; Aparatos e instrumentos odontológicos; Guantes para uso médico; Batas para uso quirúrgico; Cojines para uso médico; Mascarillas para personal médico; Biberones; Sacaleches; Juguetes sexuales; Preservativos; Prótesis; Sillas orinal; Mascarillas quirúrgicas; Mascarillas para personal médico; Mascarillas quirúrgicas de alta filtración.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arstiriistade jaoks kohandatud kohvrid; Arteriaalvererõhumõõturid, sfügmomanomeetrid; Kunstliku hingamise aparaadid; Meditsiinilised termomeetrid; Hambaraviseadmed ja -riistad; Meditsiinilised kindad; Kirurgias kasutatavad kitlid; Meditsiinilised padjad; Maskid meditsiinipersonalile; Lutipudelid; Rinnapumbad; Sekslelud; Kondoomid, preservatiivid; Kunstjäsemed, tehisjäsemed, jäsemeproteesid; Potitoolid; Kirurgimaskid; Maskid meditsiinipersonalile; Peenfiltreerivad kirurgimaskid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kotelot lääketieteellisiä laitteita varten; Verenpainemittarit; Tekohengityslaitteet; Kuumemittarit lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Hammaslääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Käsineet lääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Leikkaussalivaatteet kirurgiseen käyttöön; Tyynyt lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Suojanaamarit lääkintähenkilökuntaa varten; Tuttipullot; Rintapumput; Seksilelut; Kondomit; Tekojäsenet; Yöastiatuolit; Kirurgin naamarit; Suojanaamarit lääkintähenkilökuntaa varten; Vaimennussuodattimet kirurgisiin kasvosuojuksiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Mallettes spéciales pour instruments médicaux; Sphygmotensiomètres; Appareils pour la respiration artificielle; Thermomètres à usage médical; Appareils et instruments dentaires; Gants à usage médical; Blouses chirurgicales; Coussins à usage médical; Masques utilisés par le personnel médical; Biberons; Tire-lait; Jouets sexuels; Préservatifs; Prothèses; Chaises percées; Masques chirurgicaux; Masques utilisés par le personnel médical; Masques chirurgicaux avec filtres à grand débit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kovčežići posebno namijenjeni za medicinske instrumente; Sfigmomanometri; Uređaji za umjetno disanje; Toplomjeri za medicinske potrebe; Stomatološka oprema; Rukavice za medicinsku uporabu; Kirurški ogrtači; Jastuci za medicinske potrebe; Maske za medicinsko osoblje; Spremnici dječjih bočica; Pumpice za izdajanje mlijeka; Seksualne igračke; Kondomi; Proteze [umjetni udovi]; Stolice s otvorom za noćne posude; Kirurške maske; Maske za medicinsko osoblje; Kirurške maske visoke filtracije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Speciális táskák/tartók, orvosi eszközöknek; Vérnyomásmérő készülékek; Mesterséges lélegeztető készülékek; Hőmérők gyógyászati célokra; Fogászati berendezések; Kesztyűk gyógyászati használatra; Köpenyek sebészeti használatra; Párnák gyógyászati használatra; Maszkok egészségügyi személyzet általi használatra; Cumisüvegtartók; Mellszívók; Szexuális játékszerek; Óvszerek; Művégtagok; Toalett székek; Sebészeti maszkok; Maszkok egészségügyi személyzet általi használatra; Nagy hatékonyságú sebészeti szűrőmaszkok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Valigette speciali per strumenti medici; Apparecchi per la misurazione della pressione arteriosa; Apparecchi per la respirazione artificiale; Termometri per uso medico; Apparecchi e strumenti dentari; Guanti per uso medico; Camici da chirurgo; Cuscini per uso medico; Maschere utilizzate dal personale medico; Poppatoi; Tira latte; Giocattoli del sesso [sex toys]; Preservativi; Arti artificiali; Seggette; Mascherine chirurgiche; Maschere ad alta filtrazione per uso chirurgico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Dėklai (pritaikyti medicinos instrumentams); Sfigmotenzimetrai; Dirbtinio kvėpavimo aparatai; Medicininiai termometrai; Odontologijos aparatūra ir instrumentai; Pirštinės (medicinos reikmėms); Chalatai chirurgijos reikmėms; Medicininės pagalvėlės; Kaukės medicinos personalui; Žindymo buteliukai; Motinos pieno siurbtuvai; Sekso žaislai; Prezervatyvai; Kojų ir rankų protezai; Kėdės su naktipuodžiais; Chirurginės kaukės; Kaukės medicinos personalui; Aukštos filtracijos chirurginės kaukės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pielāgotas medicīnas instrumentu somas; Asinsspiediena mērierīces; Mākslīgās elpināšanas ierīces; Medicīniskie termometri; Zobārstniecības ierīces un instrumenti; Cimdi medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Halāti ķirurģiskiem nolūkiem; Medicīniskie spilveni; Medicīnas personālam paredzētās maskas; Barošanas pudelītes; Krūts piena sūknīši; Seksa rotaļlietas; Prezervatīvi; Locekļu protēzes; Tualetes krēsli; Ķirurģiskās maskas; Medicīnas personālam paredzētās maskas; Ķirurģiskās maskas ar stipru filtru.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Bagalji speċjali għal strumenti mediċi; Sfigmomanometri; Apparat għar-respirazzjoni artifiċjali; Termometri għal skopijiet mediċi; Tagħmir dentali; Ingwanti għal skopijiet mediċi; Ġagagi għall-użu kirurġiku; Kuxxini għal skopijiet mediċi; Maskri għal personal mediku; Reċipjenti bħala fliexken għat-tmigħ tat-trabi; Pompi tas-sider; Ġugarelli tas-sess; Kondoms; Dirgħajn artifiċjali; Siġġijiet b'awrinar; Maskri kirurġiċi; Maskri għal personal mediku; Maskri kirurġiċi b'filtru qawwi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Koffertjes, speciaal aangepast voor medische instrumenten; Bloeddrukmeetapparaten; Apparaten voor kunstmatige ademhaling; Thermometers voor medisch gebruik; Tandheelkundige apparaten en instrumenten; Handschoenen voor medisch gebruik; Operatieschorten; Kussens voor medisch gebruik; Maskers te gebruiken door medisch personeel; Zuigflessen; Borstpompen; Seksspeeltjes; Condooms; Kunstledematen; Kamerstoelen; Maskers voor chirurgisch gebruik; Maskers te gebruiken door medisch personeel; Chirurgische maskers met hoge filtercapaciteiten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Futerały na instrumenty medyczne; Aparaty do pomiaru ciśnienia tętniczego krwi; Urządzenia do sztucznego oddychania; Termometry do celów medycznych; Przyrządy i przybory dentystyczne; Rękawice do celów medycznych; Fartuchy do użytku chirurgicznego; Poduszki do celów medycznych; Maski stosowane przez personel medyczny; Pojemniki na butelki do karmienia; Urządzenia do odciągania mleka z piersi; Zabawki erotyczne; Prezerwatywy; Protezy kończyn; Krzesła sedesowe; Maski chirurgiczne; Maski stosowane przez personel medyczny; Maski chirurgiczne z wysokim współczynnikiem filtracji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Maletas especiais para instrumentos médicos; Esfigmo-tensiómetros [medidores de tensão arterial]; Aparelhos para a respiração artificial; Termómetros para uso médico; Aparelhos e instrumentos dentários; Luvas para uso médico; Batas para uso cirúrgico; Almofadas para uso medicinal; Máscaras para pessoal médico; Biberons [biberões]; Bombas tira-leite; Brinquedos sexuais; Preservativos; Membros artificiais [próteses]; Cadeiras retretes; Máscaras cirúrgicas; Máscaras para pessoal médico; Máscaras cirúrgicas de elevada filtração.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Truse cu instrumentar medical; Sfigmomanometre; Respirație artificială (Aparate pentru -); Termometre de uz medical; Echipament stomatologic; Mănuși de uz medical; Halate de uz chirurgical; Perne de uz medical; Măști utilizate de personalul medical; Recipiente pentru biberoane; Pompe de sân; Jucării erotice; Prezervative; Membre artificiale; Scaune pentru necesități; Măști chirurgicale; Măști utilizate de personalul medical; Măști chirurgicale cu filtru de înaltă protecție.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Nádoby, kazety na lekárske nástroje; Krvné tlakomery; Prístroje na umelé dýchanie; Lekárske teplomery; Zubárske prístroje a nástroje; Rukavice na lekárske použitie; Chirurgické odevy; Podušky na lekárske použitie; Rúška (pre nemocničný personál); Detské fľaše; Dýchacie prístroje; Erotické pomôcky; Kondómy, prezervatívy; Protézy (umelé končatiny); Stoličky s otvorom; Chirurgické masky; Rúška (pre nemocničný personál); Chirurgické masky s vysokoúčinným filtrom.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kovčki, prirejeni za medicinske inštrumente; Aparati za merjenje krvnega pritiska; Aparati za umetno dihanje; Termometri za medicinske namene; Zobozdravstveni aparati in instrumenti; Rokavice za medicinske namene; Halje za kirurško uporabo; Blazine za medicinske namene; Maske za medicinsko osebje; Posodice za stekleničke za hranjenje; Prsne črpalke; Spolni pripomočki; Kondomi; Proteze (umetni udje); Stoli z odprtino za nočne posode; Kirurške maske; Maske za medicinsko osebje; Kirurške maske z močnimi filtri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Etuier för medicinska instrument; Blodtrycksmätare; Apparater för konstgjord andning; Termometrar för medicinska ändamål; Dentala apparater och instrument; Handskar för medicinska ändamål; Rockar för kirurgiskt bruk; Kuddar för medicinska ändamål; Munskydd för medicinsk personal; Nappflaskor; Bröstpumpar; Sexleksaker; Kondomer; Konstgjorda lemmar; Duschstolar (handikapphjälpmedel); Operationsmasker; Munskydd för medicinsk personal; Starka filter för kirurgiska masker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Кранове [канелки]; Фитинги за дренаж за вода; Електрически вентилатори за лично ползване; Електрическо фенерче; Апарати за санитарни цели; Душове; Лампи; Сешоари за коса; Водни пречиствателни инсталации; Фитинги за баня; Радиатори, електрически; Тоалетни седалки; Тоалетни [клозети]; Сушилни апарати за ръце за умивални; Уреди за печене; Мивки; Вани; Умивалници [части на санитарни инсталации].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kohouty a kohoutky; Armatury pro vodní drenáže; Elektrické ventilátory pro osobní potřebu; Vyhledávací světlomety; Sanitární přístroje a zařízení; Sprchy; Svítidla; Vysoušeče vlasů; Zařízení na čištění vody; Koupelnové armatury; Elektrické radiátory; Záchodová sedátka; Splachovací záchody; Vysoušeče rukou do umýváren; Grily [kuchyňské spotřebiče]; Dřezy; Koupací vany; Umyvadla [součásti hygienických zařízení].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Vandhaner; Rørstykker til vandafløbsrør; Elektriske vifter til personlig brug; Lyskastere; Sanitære apparater og installationer; Brusere; Lamper; Hårtørrere; Vandrenseinstallationer; Armaturer til badeinstallationer; Radiatorer, elektriske; Toiletsæder; WC'er; Håndtørreapparater til toiletrum; Grillapparater til madlavning; Køkkenvaske; Badekar; Håndvaske [dele af sanitetsinstallationer].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Hähne; Armaturen für den Wasserabfluss; Elektrische Lüfter für den persönlichen Gebrauch; Suchscheinwerfer; Sanitäre Apparate und Anlagen; Duschen; Beleuchtungslampen; Haartrockner; Wasserreinigungsanlagen; Badeapparate; Elektrische Radiatoren; Toilettensitze [WC]; Toiletten [WCs]; Handtrockner für Waschräume; Grillgeräte [Küchengeräte]; Abwaschbecken, Spülen; Badewannen; Waschbecken [Teile von Sanitäreinrichtungen].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Στρόφιγγες· Εξαρτήματα για την αποχέτευση νερού· Ανεμιστήρες ηλεκτρικοί για προσωπική χρήση· Προβολείς εντοπισμού· Υγιεινής (Συσκευές και εγκαταστάσεις -)· Ντους· Φωτισμός (λαμπτήρες -ού)· Στεγνωτήρες μαλλιών· Ύδωρ (εγκαταστάσεις καθαρισμού του -ος)· Παρελκόμενα για λουτρά· Ηλεκτρικά θερμαντικά σώματα· Λεκάνες τουαλέτας, καθίσματα τουαλέτας· Αποχωρητήρια· Τουαλέτες (Συσκευές για το στέγνωμα των χεριών για -)· Σχάρες [μαγειρικές συσκευές]· Νεροχύτες· Καμπίνες για ντους· Νιπτήρες [τμήματα εγκαταστάσεων υγιεινής].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Faucets; Fittings for the draining of water; Electric fans for personal use; Searchlights; Sanitary apparatus and installations; Showers; Lamps; Hair driers; Water purification installations; Bath fittings; Radiators, electric; Toilet seats; Water closets; Hand drying apparatus for washrooms; Roasting apparatus; Sinks; bath tubs; wash-hand basins [parts of sanitary installations].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Grifos; Piezas para drenar agua; Ventiladores eléctricos para uso personal; Proyectores de luz; Aparatos e instalaciones sanitarias; Duchas; Lámparas [aparatos de iluminación]; Secadores de pelo; Instalaciones de depuración de agua; Aparatos para baños; Radiadores eléctricos; Asientos de inodoro; Inodoros; Secamanos para lavabos; Parrillas [utensilios de cocción]; Fregaderos; Bañeras; Lavabos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kraanid; Veeäravoolutarvikud; Elektriventilaatorid isiklikuks tarbeks; Taskulambid [valgustusseadmed], helgiheitjad, prožektorid; Sanitaarseadmed; Dušid; Lambid [valgustid]; Juuksekuivatid; Veepuhastusseadmed; Vannitarvikud; Elektriradiaatorid; Klosetiistmed; Veeklosetid; Pesuruumide kätekuivatusaparaadid, kätekuivatid; Röstimisseadmed; Valamud; Vannid; Kätepesukausid [sanitaarseadmete osad].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Vesihanat; Tarvikkeet veden valuttamiseen; Tuulettimet (Sähkö -), henkilökohtaiseen käyttöön; Soihdut valaistukseen; Saniteettilaitteet; Suihkut; Lamput; Hiustenkuivaimet; Vedenpuhdistuslaitteet; Kylpyhuoneiden kiintovarusteet; Lämpöpatterit, sähkökäyttöiset; WC-istuimet; Vesiklosetit; Käsienkuivauslaitteet pesuhuoneisiin; Grillit; Pesualtaat; Kylpyammeet; Käsienpesualtaat [saniteettitilojen osina].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Robinets; Chasse d'eau; Ventilateurs électriques à usage personnel; Projecteurs d'éclairage; Appareils et installations sanitaires; Douches; Lampes d'éclairage; Sèche-cheveux; Installations pour la purification de l'eau; Appareils pour bains; Radiateurs électriques; Sièges de toilettes [W.-C.]; Toilettes [W.-C.]; Appareils à sécher les mains pour lavabos; Grils [appareils de cuisson]; Éviers; Baignoires; Lavabos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Pipe [slavine]; Oprema za drenažu vode; Električni ventilatori za osobnu uporabu; Džepne svjetiljke za rasvjetu; Uređaji za sanitarne potrebe; Tuševi; Rasvjetne svjetiljke; Sušila za kosu; Uređaj za pročišćavanje vode; Oprema za kupaonicu; Radijatori, električni; Zahodske daske; Zahodi; Umivaonici (sušila ruku za umivaonike); Gril [aparat za pečenje]; Sudoperi; Kade; Umivaonici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Csapok; Szerelvények vízelvezetéshez; Elektromos ventilátorok személyes használatra; Keresőlámpák, zseblámpák; Egészségügyi készülékek és berendezések; Zuhanyok; Lámpák; Hajszárítók; Víztisztító berendezések; Fürdőszoba szerelvények; Radiátorok, elektromos; Vécéülőkék; Toalettek [WC-k]; Kézszárító készülékek mosdókba; Rostok, grillsütők; Mosogatók, mosdók; Fürdőkádak; Mosdókagylók [szaniter berendezések részei].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Rubinetti; Impianti per lo scarico dell'acqua; Ventilatori elettrici per uso personale; Proiettori; Apparecchi ed impianti sanitari; Docce; Lampade per illuminazione; Asciugacapelli; Impianti per la depurazione dell'acqua; Apparecchi per bagni; Radiatori elettrici; Sedili di gabinetti [WC]; Gabinetti [w.-c.]; Apparecchi per asciugare le mani, per lavandini; Griglie [apparecchi di cottura]; Lavandini; Vasche da bagno; Lavabi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Čiaupai; Vandens nutekėjimo sistemų priedai; Elektriniai asmeniniai ventiliatoriai; Prožektoriai; Sanitariniai aparatai ir įrenginiai; Dušai; Lempos; Plaukų džiovintuvai; Vandens valymo įrenginiai; Vonių įrengimo reikmenys; Elektriniai radiatoriai; Klozetų sėdynės; Tualetai [vandens klozetai]; Prausyklų rankų džiovintuvai; Kepimo aparatai; Plautuvės [virtuvinės]; Vonios; Rankų prausyklės [sanitarinių įrenginių dalys].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ūdens krāni; Armatūra ūdens novadīšanas iekārtām; Elektriskie ventilatori personiskai lietošanai; Prožektori; Sanitārtehniskās ierīces, iekārtas un aparāti; Dušas; Lampas; Matu žāvēšanas ierīces; Ūdens attīrīšanas iekārtas; Vannu armatūra; Elektriskie radiatori; Tualetes podu sēdriņķi; Klozetpodi; Roku žāvēšanas ierīces tualetes telpām; Cepšanas ierīces; Izlietnes; Vannas; Izlietnes (sanitārtehniskā aprīkojuma daļas).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Viti [għal bittiji]; Tagħmir għat-tbattil tal-ilma; Fannijiet tal-elettriku għal użu personali; Torċ għad-dawl; Apparat għal skopijiet sanitarji; Doċoċ; Lampi; Nixxiefa tax-xagħar; Sistemi għat-tisfija tal-ilma; Tagħmir tal-banjijiet; Radjaturi, tal-elettriku; Sedili tat-tojlit; Loki; Nixxiefa tal-idejn għal kmamar tal-ħasil; Tagħmir tax-xiwi; Sinkijiet; Banjijiet; Sinkijiet għall-ħasil tal-idejn [partijiet ta' installazzjonijiet sanitarji].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kranen; Hulpstukken voor de afvoer van water; Elektrische ventilatoren voor persoonlijk gebruik; Toortsen voor verlichting; Sanitaire apparaten en installaties; Douches; Lampen voor verlichting; Haardrogers; Waterzuiveringsinstallaties; Apparaten voor baden; Elektrische radiatoren; Toiletbrillen; Toiletten; Handdroogapparaten voor wasgelegenheden; Grills [kookapparaten]; Gootstenen; Badkuipen; Wastafels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Krany; Osprzęt do odprowadzania wody; Wentylatory elektryczne do użytku osobistego; Latarki; Urządzenia do celów sanitarnych; Natryski, prysznice; Lampy oświetleniowe; Suszarki do włosów; Instalacje do uzdatniania wody; Akcesoria łazienkowe; Kaloryfery elektryczne; Deski sedesowe; Muszle klozetowe [WC]; Urządzenia do suszenia rąk do toalet; Urządzenia do opiekania i pieczenia; Zlewozmywaki; Wanny; Umywalki [części instalacji sanitarnych].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Torneiras; Acessórios para a drenagem de água; Ventiladores elétricos para uso pessoal; Tochas [archotes] para a iluminação; Aparelhos e instalações sanitários; Chuveiros; Lâmpadas; Secador de cabelo; Instalações para a purificação da água; Aparelhos para banhos; Radiadores elétricos; Assentos de sanitas; Sanitas com autoclismo; Aparelhos para secar as mãos para lavabos; Aparelhos para grelhar; Lava - loiças; Banheiras; Lavabos [lavatórios].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Robinete; Fitinguri pentru drenarea apei; Ventilatoare electrice de uz personal; Lanterne pentru iluminat; Aparate de uz sanitar; Dușuri; Lămpi de iluminat; Uscătoare de păr; Instalații pentru purificarea apei; Accesorii pentru baie; Radiatoare electrice; Scaune de toaletă; Toalete [w.c.]; Aparate pentru uscat mâinile pentru toalete publice; Grătare [aparate de gătit]; Chiuvete; Cabine pentru duș; Lavabouri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kohútiky; Armatúry na odtok vody; Elektrické ventilátory (stolové); Baterky (svietidlá); Sanitárne (toaletné) prístroje a zariadenia; Sprchy; Lampy; Sušiče na vlasy; Zariadenia na úpravu vody; Inštalačný materiál na vane; Elektrické radiátory; Záchodové sedadlá; Toalety (WC); Sušiče na ruky do umyvární; Grily (prístroje na pečenie); Drezy; Vane; Umývadlá.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pipe; Oprema za odtok vode; Električni ventilatorji za osebno uporabo; Žepne svetilke za razsvetljavo; Aparati za sanitarne namene; Tuši; Svetilke; Sušilniki za lase; Čistilne naprave za vodo; Kopalniška oprema; Električni radiatorji; Straniščne deske; Stranišča; Sušilniki za roke za umivalnice; Naprave za pečenje; Kuhinjska korita; Banje; Umivalniki [deli sanitarne opreme].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Vattenkranar; Armaturer för vattenavrinning; Elektriska fläktar för personligt bruk; Handlyktor; Sanitära apparater och installationer; Duschar; Lampor; Hårtorkar; Vattenreningsinstallationer; Badarmaturer; Elektriska element; Toalettsitsar; Vattenklosetter; Handtorkningsapparater för tvättrum; Köksgrillar; Vaskar; Badkar; Handfat [delar av sanitära installationer].</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Тоалетни принадлежности; Кофи за боклук; Закачалки и халки за кърпи и хавлии; Поставки за тоалетна хартия; Кухненски прибори, не от благороден метал; Стойки за дрехи [за изсушаване]; Порцеланови изделия; Козметични принадлежности; Гребени; Съдове за пиене; Инструменти за чистене [ръчни]; Съдове за домакински или кухненски цели [с изключение на такива от благороден метал]; Сервизи за хранене; Дозатори на кърпи; Кутии за сапун; Поставки за душ гелове; Четки за тоалетни.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Toaletní potřeby; Nádoby na odpad; Tyčové a kruhové držáky na ručníky; Držáky na toaletní papír; Kuchyňské potřeby, s výjimkou potřeb z drahých kovů; Prádelní sušáky; Výrobky z porcelánu; Kosmetické pomůcky; Hřebeny; Nádoby na pití; Ruční nástroje na čištění; Dózy, boxy a nádoby pro použití v domácnosti a kuchyni; Jídelní soupravy [nádobí]; Dávkovače na papírové ručníky; Držáky na mýdlo; Stojany na sprchové gely; Štětky na čištění záchodů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Toiletredskaber; Skraldebøtter; Stænger og ringe til håndklæder; Toiletpapirholdere; Køkkenredskaber, ikke af ædelmetal; Tørrestativer til tøj; Porcelænsservice; Redskaber til kosmetisk brug; Kamme; Drikkebeholdere; Rengøringsredskaber [håndredskaber]; Beholdere til husholdnings- eller køkkenbrug; Service [spisestel]; Kasser til udlevering af papirhåndklæder; Sæbeholdere; Holdere til brusegeléer; Børster til toiletter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Toilettegeräte [Körperpflege]; Mülleimer; Stangen und Ringe für Handtücher; Toilettenpapierhalter; Küchengeräte [nicht aus Edelmetall]; Ständer zum Lüften von Bekleidungsstücken; Porzellan; Kosmetische Geräte; Kämme; Trinkgefäße; Handbetätigte Putzgeräte; Gefäße für Haushalt oder Küche; Tafelservice [Geschirr]; Papierhandtuchspender; Seifenhalter, -schalen; Duschgelablagen; Toilettenbürsten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Τουαλέτας (Σκεύη -)· Δοχεία απορριμμάτων· Ράβδοι ανάρτησης για πετσέτες και δακτυλίδια· Θήκες χαρτιού τουαλέτας· Εργαλεία κουζίνας από μη πολύτιμα μέταλλα· Απλώστρες ρούχων, για στέγνωμα· Πορσελάνης είδη· Καλλυντικά (Σκεύη -)· Χτένες· Πόσης (Δοχεία -)· Εργαλεία καθαρισμού, χειροκίνητα· Δοχεία οικιακά ή μαγειρικά· Υπηρεσίες [πιάτα]· Διανομείς χάρτινων πετσετών καθαρισμού· Σαπουνοθήκες· Ράφια για ζελέ για το ντους· Βούρτσες τουαλέτας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Toilet utensils; Refuse bins; Towel rails and rings; Toilet paper holders; Kitchen utensils, not of precious metal; Clothes drying racks; Porcelain ware; Cosmetic utensils; Combs; Drinking vessels; Cleaning instruments,hand-operated; Containers for household or kitchen use; Dishware; Boxes for dispensing paper towels; Dishes for soap; Shower gel racks; Toilet brushes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Utensilios de tocador; Cubos de basura; Toalleros de aro y de barra; Portarrollos de papel higiénico; Utensilios de cocina que no sean de metales preciosos; Secadores [tendederos] de ropa; Artículos de porcelana; Utensilios cosméticos; Peines; Recipientes para beber; Instrumentos de limpieza accionados manualmente; Recipientes para uso doméstico o culinario; Servicios de mesa [vajilla]; Cajas distribuidoras de toallitas de papel; Portajabones [jaboneras]; Estantes para geles de ducha; Escobillas de baño.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tualett-tarbed; Prügikastid; Käterätihoidikud; Tualettpaberihoidlid; Mitteväärismetallist köögitarvikud; Pesukuivatusrestid; Portselantooted; Kosmeetikatarbed; Kammid; Jooginõud; Puhastusriistad [käsi-tööriistad]; Köögi- või majapidamismahutid; Serviisid [lauanõud]; Pabersalvrätijaoturid; Seebialused; Dušigeelialused; Tualettharjad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Toalettivälineet; Roska-astiat; Pyyhetangot ja -renkaat; Pidikkeet WC-paperirullille; Keittiövälineet, ei jalometalliset; Vaatteiden kuivaustelineet; Posliinitavarat; Kosmetiikkavälineet; Kammat; Juoma-astiat; Siivousvälineet, käsikäyttöiset; Säiliöt koti- tai keittiökäyttöön; Astiastot; Paperipyyhkeiden annostelijat; Saippuarasiat; Telineet suihkugeeleille; Toalettiharjat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Ustensiles de toilette; Poubelles; Barres et anneaux porte-serviettes; Porte-rouleaux pour papier hygiénique; Ustensiles de cuisine non en métaux précieux; Séchoirs à lessive; Porcelaines; Ustensiles cosmétiques; Peignes; Récipients à boire; Instruments de nettoyage actionnés manuellement; Récipients pour le ménage ou la cuisine; Services [vaisselle]; Boîtes pour la distribution de serviettes en papier; Porte-savon; Étagères pour gels douche; Brosses de toilette.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Toaletni pribor; Kante za smeće; Ravni i prstenasti držači ručnika; Držači higijenskog papira [napravice]; Kuhinjski pribor, nije od plemenitih metala; Stalci za sušenje odjeće; Porculansko posuđe; Kozmetički pribor; Češljevi; Posude za pića; Ručni pribor za čišćenje; Posude za kućanstvo ili za kuhinju; Servisi za jelo; Držači za papirnate ručnike; Kutije za sapun; Stalci za gel za tuširanje; Četke za WC školjke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Toaletteszközök; Szemeteskukák; Törölközőtartók és törölközőtartó gyűrűk; Toalettpapír-tartók; Nem nemesfémből készült konyhai eszközök; Ruhaszárító állványok; Porcelánok; Kozmetikai eszközök; Fésűk; Ivóedények; Tisztítóeszközök, kézi működtetésű; Tárolók, tároló edények háztartási vagy konyhai célokra; Étkészletek; Papírtörölköző adagolók; Szappantartók; Tusfürdő tartó polcok; Toalettkefék, WC-kefék.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Utensili per la toilette; Pattumiere; Anelli e barre porta-asciugamani; Portarotoli per carta igienica; Utensili da cucina, non in metallo prezioso; Stenditoi per bucato; Porcellane; Utensili cosmetici; Pettini; Recipienti per bere; Strumenti per la pulizia azionati manualmente; Recipienti per la casa o per la cucina; Servizi [vasellame]; Scatole per la distribuzione dei tovaglioli di carta; Porta-sapone; Ripiani per gel per doccia; Spazzole per toilette.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Tualetiniai indai; Atliekų dėžės; Rankšluosčių kabyklos ir žiedai; Tualetinio popieriaus laikikliai; Virtuviniai įrankiai, ne brangiųjų metalų; Drabužių džiovyklos; Porceliano dirbiniai; Kosmetikos reikmenys; Šukos; Geriamieji indai; Valymo reikmenys [rankiniai]; Buitinės ar virtuvinės talpyklos; Servizai [valgomieji indai]; Popierinių rankšluosčių dalijimo dėžutės; Muilo padėklai; Lentynėlės dušo geliams; Prausiamieji šepečiai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Tualetes piederumi; Atkritumu tvertnes; Dvieļu pakaramie stieņi un gredzeni; Tualetes papīra turētāji; Virtuves piederumi, kas nav izgatavoti no dārgmetāla; Drēbju žāvēšanas statīvi; Porcelāna trauki; Kosmētikas piederumi; Ķemmes; Dzērienu trauki; Ar roku darbināmas tīrīšanas ierīces; Tilpnes mājturības vai virtuves nolūkiem; Servīzes (trauki); Papīra dvieļu automāti; Ziepju trauki ar vāku; Dušas gēlu plaukti; Tualetes birstes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Utensili għat-tojlit; Landi taż-żibel; Vireg u ħoloq li magħhom jiddendlu x-xugamani; Distributuri tat-toilet paper; Tagħmir tal-kċina, mhux tal-metall prezzjuż; Xtillieri għall-ħwejjeġ, għat-tnixxif; Oġġetti tal-porċellana; Utensili kożmetiċi; Pettnejiet; Reċipjenti għax-xorb; Strumenti tat-tindif, li jinħadmu bl-idejn; Kontenituri għal użu domestiku jew għal użu fil-kċina; Settijiet [dixxijiet]; Dispensers għas-srievet tal-karti; Kontenituri tas-sapun; Xkafef għall-ġellijiet tad-doċċa; Xkupilji tat-tojlit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Toiletgerei; Afvalbakken; Handdoekstangen en -ringen; Toiletrolhouders; Keukengerei, niet van edele metalen; Rekken voor het luchten van kleding [droogrekken]; Porseleinwerk; Cosmetisch gerei; Kammen; Drinkgerei; Reinigingsinstrumenten, handbediend; Houders voor de huishouding of de keuken; Tafelserviezen; Dozen van metaal, voor de afgifte van papieren servetten of handdoeken; Zeephouders; Rekjes voor douchegels; Toiletborstels.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Przybory toaletowe; Kosze na śmieci; Wieszaki na ręczniki [pręty i koła]; Dozowniki papieru toaletowego; Kuchenne przybory nie z metali szlachetnych; Suszarki do ubrań; Porcelana; Przybory kosmetyczne; Grzebienie; Naczynia na napoje; Narzędzia do czyszczenia, ręczne; Pojemniki do użytku domowego lub kuchennego; Serwisy [zastawy stołowe]; Dozowniki do ręczników papierowych; Mydelniczki; Półki na żel pod prysznic; Szczotki do misek klozetowych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Utensílios para casa de banho; Caixotes do lixo; Toalheiros [de barra e de aro]; Suportes para papel higiénico; Utensílios de cozinha, não em metais preciosos; Estendais para a roupa; Loiça de porcelana; Utensílios cosméticos; Pentes; Recipientes para bebidas; Instrumentos para limpeza, manuais; Recipientes para uso doméstico ou para cozinha; Serviços de loiça; Caixas dispensadoras de toalhetes em papel; Saboneteiras [suportes]; Estantes para gel de duche; Piaçabas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Toaletă (Ustensile de -); Lăzi de gunoi; Inele și bare pentru suportul prosoapelor; Suporturi pentru role de hârtie igienică; Utensile de bucătărie, nu din metale prețioase; Suporturi de uscat haine; Porțelanuri; Cosmetice (Ustensile -); Piepteni; Recipiente de băut; Curățat (instrumente pentru -, acționate manual); Recipiente pentru menaj sau bucătărie; Servicii [veselă]; Distribuitoare de prosoape de hârtie; Savoniere; Rafturi pentru geluri de duș; Toaletă (Perii de -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Toaletné pomôcky; Smetné nádoby; Prstencové a tyčové vešiaky na uteráky; Zásobníky na kotúčový toaletný papier; Kuchynské náradie, s výnimkou náradia z drahých kovov; Sušiaky na sušenie oblečenia; Porcelán; Kozmetické pomôcky; Hrebene; Poháre, šálky, hrnčeky na pitie; Nástroje na čistenie na ručný pohon; Nádoby na použitie v domácnosti alebo v kuchyni; Jedálenské súpravy (riad); Zásobníky na papierové utierky; Držiaky na mydlo; Držiaky na sprchovacie gély; Záchodové kefy.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Toaletne potrebščine; Smetnjaki; Nosilci za brisače v obliki prečk in obročev; Nosilci za WC papir; Kuhinjske potrebščine, ne iz plemenitih kovin; Stojala za sušenje oblačil; Posoda iz porcelana; Kozmetični pripomočki; Glavniki; Posode za pitje; Čistilne priprave, ročne; Posode za gospodinjstvo ali kuhinjo; Servisi [namizni pribor]; Podajalniki papirnatih brisačk; Posodice za milo; Stojala za gele za prhanje; Krtače za telesno nego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Toalettutensilier; Soptunnor; Stänger och ringar för handdukar; Hållare för toalettpapper; Köksgeråd, inte av ädelmetall; Torkställningar för kläder; Porslinsvaror; Kosmetikutensilier; Kammar; Dryckeskärl; Rengöringsredskap (handdrivna); Behållare för hushålls- eller köksändamål; Serviser [bordsserviser]; Automater för pappershanddukar; Tvålhållare; Ställ för duschgel; Toalettborstar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/129</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-07-10</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/201</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-21</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1080357</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>15066</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
