<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-10-16T15:16:28</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018225939</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018225939</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-09-30</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>de</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-10-02</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>CentoSwab</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>1</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Химически продукти за индустрията; Химикали използвани в областта на науката; Комплекти за тестване; Тестови комплекти за доказване на микроорганизми, бактерии, вируси или гъбички; Комплекти за вземане и съхранение на проби.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Průmyslové chemické látky; Chemické výrobky určené pro vědu; Zkušební soupravy; Testovací sady pro dokazování mikroorganizmů, bakterií, virů nebo kvasinek; Sady pro odběr a ukládání vzorků.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kemiske produkter til industrielle formål; Kemikalier til brug i videnskaben; Testsæt; Testsæt til påvisning af mikroorganismer, bakterier, vira eller svampe; Sæt til udtagning og opbevaring af prøver.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Chemische Erzeugnisse für gewerbliche Zwecke; chemische Erzeugnisse für wissenschaftliche Zwecke; Testkits; Testkits zum Nachweis von Mikroorganismen, Bakterien, Viren oder Pilzen; Kits zum Nehmen und Aufbewahren von Proben.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Χημικά για τη βιομηχανία· Χημικά προϊόντα για χρήση στις επιστήμες· Κιτ εξετάσεων· Κιτ δοκιμών για την ανίχνευση μικροοργανισμών, βακτηρίων, ιών ή μυκήτων· Κιτ για τη λήψη και φύλαξη δειγμάτων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Chemicals used in industry; Chemicals used in science; Test kits; Testing kits for the detection of microorganisms, bacteria, viruses or fungi; Kits for taking and storing samples.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Productos químicos utilizados en la industria; Productos químicos utilizados en la ciencia; Kits para pruebas; Kits de prueba para el análisis de microorganismos, bacterias, virus u hongos; Kits para recoger y almacenar muestras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tööstuskemikaalid; Teaduses kasutatavad kemikaalid; Katsekomplektid; Testimiskomplektid mikroorganismide, bakterite, viiruste või seente tuvastamiseks; Komplektid proovide võtmiseks ja säilitamiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Teollisuuskemikaalit; Kemikaalit tieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Testaussarjat; Testisarjat mikro-organismien, bakteerien, virusten tai sienten osoittamiseen; Tuotesarjat näytteiden ottamiseen ja säilyttämiseen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits chimiques destinés à l'industrie; Produits chimiques à usage scientifique; Kits de test; Kits de test pour détecter des microorganismes, bactéries, virus ou champignons; Kits pour prélever et conserver des échantillons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kemijska sredstva za uporabu u industriji; Kemijski proizvodi koji se upotrebljavaju u znanosti; Testni kompleti; Setovi za testiranje namijenjeni dokazivanju prisutnosti mikroorganizama, bakterija, virusa ili gljiva; Setovi za uzimanje i pohranu uzoraka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vegyszerek ipari használatra; Tudományos célra használt vegyszerek; Vizsgálati készletek; Tesztkészletek mikroorganizmusok, baktériumok, vírusok vagy gombák kimutatására; Készletek minták vételéhez és tárolásához.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Prodotti chimici per l'industria; Prodotti chimici per uso scientifico; Insiemi per test; Kit di test per l'identificazione di microrganismi, batteri, virus o funghi; Kit per il prelievo e la conservazione di campioni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Cheminės medžiagos (pramonės reikmėms); Cheminės medžiagos mokslo reikmėms; Bandinių rinkiniai; Testų rinkiniai mikroorganizmų, bakterijų, virusų ar grybelių tyrimų reikmėms; Mėginių ėmimo ir laikymo priemonių rinkiniai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Ķimikālijas rūpnieciskiem nolūkiem; Ķīmiskie preparāti zinātnes nolūkiem; Pārbaudes piederumi; Testu komplekti, lai noteiktu mikroorganismus, baktērijas, vīrusus vai sēnītes; Komplekti paraugu ņemšanai un uzglabāšanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Sustanzi kimiċi użati fl-industrija; Kimiċi għall-użu fix-xjenza; Kitts għall-ittestjar; Kits tat-test għall-identifikazzjoni ta' mikro-organiżmi, batterji, virus jew fungi; Kits għat-teħid u l-ħżin ta' kampjuni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Chemische producten voor industrieel gebruik; Chemische producten voor wetenschappelijk gebruik; Testsets; Testsets voor detectie van micro-organismen, bacteriën, virussen of schimmels; Sets voor het afnemen en bewaren van monsters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Środki chemiczne dla przemysłu; Środki chemiczne do celów naukowych; Zestawy testowe; Zestawy testów do wykazywania obecności mikroorganizmów, bakterii, wirusów lub grzybów; Zestawy do pobierania i przechowywania próbek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Produtos químicos destinados à indústria; Produtos químicos utilizados na ciência; Kits de ensaio; Kits de ensaio para a deteção de micro-organismos, bactérias, vírus ou fungos; Kits para recolha e armazenamento de amostras.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Produse chimice folosite în industrie; Produse chimice utilizate în domeniul ştiinţific; Kituri de analiză; Seturi de testare pentru identificarea microorganismelor, bacteriilor, virușilor sau ciupercilor; Seturi pentru prelevarea și păstrarea de probe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Priemyselné chemikálie; Chemikálie používané vo vede; Testovacie súpravy; Testovacie sady k preukázaniu mikroorganizmov, baktérií, vírusov alebo plesní; Sady na odoberanie a uschovávanie vzoriek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kemikalije, ki se uporabljajo v industriji; Kemikalije, ki se uporabljajo v znanosti; Testni kompleti; Kompleti za testiranje za odkrivanje mikroorganizmov, bakterij, virusov ali gliv; Kompleti za zbiranje in shranjevanje vzorcev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Industrikemikalier; Kemikalier för vetenskapliga ändamål; Testsatser; Testsatser för analys av mikroorganismer, bakterier, virus eller svampar; Satser för att ta och förvara prover.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>5</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Препарати и материали за диагностициране; Диагностични реактиви за медицинска и ветеринарна употреба; Диагностични препарати за медицински или ветеринарни цели; Тестови комплекти за диагностициране на заболявания; Тестови комплекти за диагностициране на инфекциозни заболявания.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Diagnostické přípravky a materiály; Diagnostická činidla pro léčebné a veterinární účely; Diagnostické přípravky pro lékařské a veterinární účely; Testovací sady pro diagnózu onemocnění; Testovací sady pro diagnózu infekčních onemocnění.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Diagnostiske præparater og materialer; Diagnostiske reagenser til medicinske og veterinærmedicinske formål; Diagnosepræparater til medicinske eller veterinærmedicinske formål; Testsæt til sygdomsdiagnosticering; Testsæt til diagnosticering af infektionssygdomme.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Diagnostikmittel und -materialien; diagnostische Reagenzien für medizinische oder veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Diagnosepräparate für medizinische oder veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Testkits für Diagnose von Erkrankungen; Testkits für Diagnose von Infektionskrankheiten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Διαγνωστικά παρασκευάσματα και υλικά· Διαγνωστικά αντιδραστήρια για ιατρικές και κτηνιατρικές χρήσεις· Διαγνωστικά παρασκευάσματα για ιατρική ή κτηνιατρική χρήση· Κιτ δοκιμών για τη διάγνωση ασθενειών· Κιτ δοκιμών για τη διάγνωση λοιµωδών νόσων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Diagnostic preparations and materials; diagnostic reagents for medical and veterinary use; Diagnostic preparations for medical or veterinary purposes; Testing kits for disease diagnosis; Testing kits for diagnosing infectious diseases.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Productos y materiales de diagnóstico; Reactivos de diagnóstico de uso médico y veterinario; Preparaciones para diagnóstico de uso médico o veterinario; Kits de prueba para diagnosticar enfermedades; Kits de prueba para diagnosticar enfermedades infecciosas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Diagnostikapreparaadid ja -materjalid; Meditsiinilised ja veterinaarsed diagnostikareaktiivid; Meditsiinilised või veterinaarsed diagnostikapreparaadid; Haiguste diagnoosimise katsekomplektid; Nakkushaiguste diagnoosimise katsekomplektid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Diagnostiset valmisteet ja aineet; Diagnostiset reagenssit lääketieteelliseen ja eläinlääketieteelliseen käyttöön; Diagnostiset valmisteet lääkinnälliseen tai eläinlääkinnälliseen käyttöön; Testisarjat sairauksien diagnosointiin; Testisarjat infektiosairauksien diagnosointiin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Produits et matériaux de diagnostic; Réactifs de diagnostic à usage médical et vétérinaire; Préparations de diagnostic à usage médical ou vétérinaire; Kits de test pour diagnostic de maladies; Kits de test pour diagnostic de maladies infectieuses.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Dijagnostički preparati i materijali; Dijagnostički reagensi za medicinsku i veterinarsku primjenu; Dijagnostički pripravci za medicinske ili veterinarske potrebe; Setovi za testiranje namijenjeni dijagnozi bolesti; Setovi za testiranje namijenjeni dijagnozi zaraznih bolesti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Diagnosztikai készítmények és anyagok; Diagnosztikai reagensek, orvosi és állatorvosi használatra; Diagnosztikai készítmények gyógyászati vagy állatgyógyászati alkalmazásra; Tesztkészletek betegségek diagnosztizálására; Tesztkészletek fertőző betegségek diagnosztizálására.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Preparati e materiali per la diagnostica; Reagenti diagnostici per uso medico e veterinario; Prodotti di diagnostica per uso medico o veterinario; Kit di test per la diagnosi di malattie; Kit di test per la diagnosi di malattie infettive.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Diagnostiniai preparatai ir medžiagos; Diagnostikos reagentai, išskyrus medicinos ar veterinarijos reikmėms; Diagnostiniai preparatai medicinos arba veterinarijos reikmėms; Testų rinkiniai ligoms diagnozuoti; Testų rinkiniai infekcinėms ligoms diagnozuoti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Diagnostikas preparāti un materiāli; Diagnostikas reaģenti lietošanai medicīnā un veterinārijā; Diagnostikas preparāti medicīniskai un veterinārai lietošanai; Testu komplekti slimību diagnostikai; Testu komplekti infekciju slimību diagnostikai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Preparazzjonijiet u materjali dijanjostiċi; Reaġenti dijanjostiċi għall-użu mediku u veterinarju; Preparazzjonijiet dijanjostiċi għal skopijiet mediċi u veterinarji; Kits tat-test għad-dijanjosi ta' mard; Kits tat-test għad-dijanjosi ta' mard infettiv.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diagnostische preparaten en materialen; Diagnostische reagentia voor medisch en diergeneeskundig gebruik; Diagnostische preparaten voor medische of diergeneeskundige doeleinden; Testsets voor het diagnosticeren van ziektes; Testsets voor het diagnosticeren van infectieziekten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Preparaty i materiały diagnostyczne; Odczynniki diagnostyczne do użytku medycznego i weterynaryjnego; Preparaty diagnostyczne do celów medycznych lub weterynaryjnych; Zestawy testów do diagnozowania chorób; Zestawy testów do diagnozowania chorób zakaźnych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Preparações e materiais de diagnóstico; Reagentes de diagnóstico para uso medicinal e veterinário; Preparações de diagnóstico para uso médico ou veterinário; Kits de ensaio para diagnóstico de doenças; Kits de ensaio para diagnóstico de doenças infeciosas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Preparate şi materiale de diagnostic; Reactivi de diagnostic pentru uz medical şi veterinar; Preparate de diagnosticare de uz medical sau veterinar; Seturi de testare pentru diagnosticarea de afecțiuni; Seturi de testare pentru diagnosticarea de boli infecțioase.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Diagnostické prípravky a materiály; Diagnostické činidlá na lekárske a zverolekárske účely; Diagnostické prípravky na lekárske alebo zverolekárske účely; Testovacie sady pre diagnostiku ochorení; Testovacie sady pre diagnostiku infekčných chorôb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Diagnostični pripravki in materiali; Diagnostični reagenti za medicinsko ali veterinarsko uporabo; Diagnostični pripravki za medicinske ali veterinarske namene; Kompleti za testiranje za diagnozo bolezni; Kompleti za testiranje za diagnozo nalezljivih bolezni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Diagnostiska preparat och material; Diagnostiska reagenser medicinskt eller veterinärt bruk; Diagnostiska preparat för medicinska och veterinära ändamål; Testsatser för sjukdomsdiagnostik; Testsatser för diagnos av infektionssjukdomar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Научни, изследователски, измервателни, контролни и детекционни апарати и уреди; Апарати за научни изследвания и лаборатории.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vědecké, výzkumné, měřicí, monitorovací a detekční přístroje a nástroje; Přístroje pro vědecký výzkum a laboratoře.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Videnskabelige, forsknings-, målings-, overvågnings- og detekteringsrelaterede apparater og instrumenter; Apparater til videnskabelig forskning og til laboratoriebrug.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wissenschaftliche, Forschungs-, Mess-, Überwachungs- und Detektionsapparate und -instrumente; Apparate für wissenschaftliche Forschung und Labor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές και όργανα επιστημονικά, έρευνας, μέτρησης, παρακολούθησης και ανίχνευσης· Συσκευές για την επιστημονική έρευνα και για εργαστηριακή χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Scientific, research, measuring, monitoring and detection apparatus and instruments; Apparatus for scientific research and laboratories.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos e instrumentos científicos, de investigación, de medición, de supervisión y de detección; Aparatos para la investigación científica y laboratorios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Teadusotstarbelised, uurimis-, kalibreerimine, seire ja tuvastusaparaadid ja -vahendid; Teadus- ja laboriseadmed.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tieteelliset, tutkimus-, mittaus-, valvonta- ja ilmaisinlaitteet ja -kojeet; Laitteet tieteelliseen tutkimukseen ja laboratoriokäyttöön.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils et instruments scientifiques, de recherche, mesure, surveillance et détection; Appareils pour la recherche scientifique et en laboratoire.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Znanstveni aparati i instrumenti, aparati i instrumenti za istraživanje, mjerenje, nadzor i detekciju; Aparati za znanstvena istraživanja i laboratorij.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tudományos, kutatási, mérési, megfigyelési és észlelési készülékek és eszközök; Készülékek tudományos kutatáshoz és laborba.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi e strumenti scientifici, di ricerca, di misura, di sorveglianza e di rilevamento; Apparecchi per la ricerca scientifica e da laboratorio.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Moksliniai, mokslinių tyrimų, matavimo, stebėjimo ir aptikimo aparatai ir instrumentai; Mokslinių tyrimų ir laboratorijų aparatai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Zinātniski, pētniecības, mērīšanas, uzraudzības un detektēšanas aparāti un instrumenti; Aparāti zinātniskajai izpētei un laboratorijām.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat u strumenti xjentifiċi, tar-riċerka, tal-kejl, tal-monitoraġġ u tal-identifikazzjoni; Apparat għar-riċerka xjentifika u laboratorji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Wetenschappelijke, onderzoeks-, meet-, controle- en detectietoestellen en -instrumenten; Toestellen voor wetenschappelijk onderzoek en laboratoria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia i przyrządy naukowe, badawcze, pomiarowe, monitorujące i wykrywające; Przyrządy do badań naukowych i do laboratoriów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos e instrumentos científicos, de investigação, medição, monitorização e deteção; Aparelhos para investigação científica e para laboratórios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate și instrumente științifice, de cercetare, de măsurare, de supraveghere și de detectare; Aparate pentru cercetare ştiinţifică şi laboratoare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vedecké, výskumné, meracie, monitorovacie a detekčné zariadenia a nástroje; Aparáty na vedecký výskum a laboratórium.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Znanstveni, raziskovalni, merilni aparati in instrumenti in aparati in instrumenti za spremljanje in odkrivanje; Aparati za znanstvene raziskave in laboratorije.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Vetenskapliga, forsknings-, mät-, övervaknings- och detektionsapparater och -instrument; Apparater för vetenskaplig forskning och laboratorier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Медицински и ветеринарни апарати и уреди; Медицински и ветеринарни шпатули; Медицински и ветеринарни тръбички за вземане на проби; Комплекти за вземане и съхранение на медицински и ветеринарни проби.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Lékařské a veterinární nástroje a přístroje; Lékařské a veterinářské špachtle; Lékařské a veterinářské trubičky na odběr vzorků; Sady pro odběr a ukládání lékařských a veterinárních vzorků.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Medicinske og veterinærmedicinske apparater og instrumenter; Medicinske og veterinærmedicinske spatler; Medicinske og veterinærmedicinske prøveudtagelsesrør; Sæt til udtagning og opbevaring af medicinske og veterinærmedicinske prøver.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Ärztliche und tierärztliche Instrumente und Apparate; medizinische und veterinärmedizinische Spatel; medizinische und veterinärmedizinische Probennahmeröhrchen; Kits zum Nehmen und Aufbewahren von medizinischen und veterinärmedizinischen Proben.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές και εργαλεία ιατρικά και κτηνιατρικά· Ιατρικές και κτηνιατρικές σπάτουλες· Ιατρικοί και κτηνιατρικοί σωληνίσκοι δειγματοληψίας· Κιτ για τη λήψη και φύλαξη ιατρικών και κτηνιατρικών δειγμάτων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Medical and veterinary apparatus and instrumentation; Medical and veterinary spatulas; Medical and veterinary sampling tubes; Kits for taking and storing medical and veterinary samples.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos e instrumentos médicos y veterinarios; Espátulas médicas y veterinarias; Tubos pequeños para recoger muestras médicas y veterinarias; Kits para recoger y almacenar muestras médicas y veterinarias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arstide ja loomaarstide instrumendid ja aparaadid; Meditsiinilised ja veterinaarsed spaatlid; Meditsiinilised ja veterinaarsed proovivõtutorud; Meditsiiniliste ja veterinaarsete proovide võtmise ja säilitamise komplektid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Lääketieteelliset ja eläinlääketieteelliset laitteet ja välineet; Lääketieteelliset ja eläinlääketieteelliset spaattelit; Lääketieteelliset ja eläinlääketieteelliset näytteenottoputket; Tuotesarjat lääketieteellisten ja eläinlääketieteellisten näytteiden ottamiseen ja säilyttämiseen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils et instruments médicaux et vétérinaires; Spatules médicales et vétérinaires; Tubes de prélèvement d'échantillons médicaux et vétérinaires; Kits pour prélever et conserver des échantillons médicaux et vétérinaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Liječnički i veterinarski instrumenti i aparati; Medicinske i veterinarske lopatice; Medicinske i veterinarske cjevčice za uzimanje uzoraka; Setovi za uzimanje i pohranu medicinskih i veterinarskih uzoraka.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Orvosi és állatorvosi műszerek és készülékek; Orvosi és állatorvosi spatula; Orvosi és állatorvosi mintavételi csövek; Készletek orvosi és állatorvosi minták vételére és tárolására.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi e strumenti medici e veterinari; Spatole per uso medico e veterinario; Tubi capillari per il prelievo di campioni per uso medico e veterinario; Kit per il prelievo e la conservazione di campioni per uso medico e veterinario.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Medicinos ir veterinarijos instrumentai ir aparatai; Medicinos ir veterinarijos mentelės; Medicinos ir veterinarijos mėginių ėmimo vamzdeliai; Medicinos ir veterinarijos mėginių ėmimo ir laikymo priemonių rinkiniai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Medicīniskie un veterinārmedicīniskie instrumenti un aparāti; Medicīniskas un veterinārmedicīniskas lāpstiņas; Medicīniskas un veterinārmedicīniskas paraugu ņemšanas caurulītes; Komplekti medicīnisku un veterinārmedicīnisku paraugu ņemšanai un uzglabāšanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Strumenti u apparat tat-tobba u tal-veterinarji; Spatuli mediċi u tal-mediċina veterinarja; Tubi għat-teħid tal-kampjuni mediċi u tal-mediċina veterinarja; Kits għat-teħid u l-ħżin ta' kampjuni mediċi u tal-mediċina veterinarja.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Medische en diergeneeskundige toestellen en instrumenten; Medische en diergeneeskundige spatels; Medische en diergeneeskundige pipetten voor bemonstering; Sets voor het nemen en bewaren van medische en diergeneeskundige monsters.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia i instrumenty medyczne i weterynaryjne; Łopatki medyczne i weterynaryjne; Medyczne i weterynaryjne probówki do pobierania próbek; Zestawy do pobierania i przechowywania próbek medycznych i weterynaryjnych.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos e instrumentos médicos e veterinários; Espátulas médicas e veterinárias; Tubos de amostragem médica e veterinária; Kits para recolha e armazenamento de amostras médicas e veterinárias.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate si instrumente medicale si veterinare; Spatule medicale și veterinare; Tuburi capilare medicale și veterinare pentru prelevarea de probe; Seturi pentru prelevarea și păstrarea de probe medicale și veterinare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Lekárske a zverolekárske nástroje a prístroje; Lekárske a veterinárne špachtle; Lekárske a veterinárne rúrky na odoberanie vzoriek; Sady na odoberanie a uschovávanie lekárskych a veterinárnych vzoriek.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zdravniški in veterinarski instrumenti in aparati; Medicinske in veterinarske lopatice; Medicinske in veterinarske epruvete za vzorce; Kompleti za odvzem in shranjevanje medicinskih in veterinarskih vzorcev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Medicinska och veterinära apparater och instrument; Medicinska och veterinära spatlar; Medicinska och veterinära provtagningsrör; Satser för att ta och förvara medicinska och veterinära prover.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Научни и технологични услуги; Промишлени анализи и проучвания; Услуги за медицински и/или фармакологични проучвания; Провеждане на клиничи тестове; Консултации в областта на промишлените изследвания; Предоставяне на информация относно услуги за промишлени анализи и проучвания; Услуги за научно проектиране; Разработване, програмиране и внедряване на компютърен софтуер; Проектиране на софтуер за компютърна база данни; Проектиране и разработване на компютърен хардуер; Хостинг услуги и софтуер като услуга и отдаване под наем на софтуер.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vědecké a technologické služby; Analytické a výzkumné služby v průmyslu; Lékařský a/nebo farmakologický výzkum; Klinický výzkum; Poradenství v oblasti průmyslového výzkumu; Poskytování informací o průmyslové analýze a výzkumu; Vědecké projektování; Vývoj softwaru, programování a implementace softwaru; Navrhování softwaru počítačové databáze; Navrhování a vývoj počítačového hardwaru; Webhostingové služby a software jako služba a pronájem softwaru.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Videnskabelige og teknologiske tjenesteydelser; Industriel analyse og forskning; Medicinsk og/eller farmakologisk forskning; Klinisk forskning; Konsulentbistand inden for industriforskning; Formidling af information om industrielle analyser og industriel forskning; Videnskabelige tjenesteydelser inden for design; Udvikling af software, programmering og implementering; Design af computerdatabasesoftware; Design og udvikling af computerhardware; Hostingtjenesteydelser og software as a service og udlejning af software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wissenschaftliche und technologische Dienstleistungen; industrielle Analyse- und Forschungsdienstleistungen; medizinische und pharmakologische Forschungsdienstleistungen; Durchführung klinischer Studien; Beratung auf dem Gebiet der industriellen Forschung; Bereitstellung von Informationen über industrielle Analyse und Forschung; wissenschaftliche Designdienstleistungen; Entwicklung, Programmierung und Implementierung von Software; Entwurf von Computer-Datenbanksoftware; Entwurf und Entwicklung von Computerhardware; Hosting-Dienste, Software as a Service [SaaS] und Vermietung von Software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Επιστημονικές και τεχνολογικές υπηρεσίες· Υπηρεσίες βιομηχανικής ανάλυσης και έρευνας· Υπηρεσίες ιατρικής και/ή φαρμακολογικής έρευνας· Κλινική έρευνα· Παροχή συμβουλών στον κλάδο της βιομηχανικής έρευνας· Παροχή πληροφοριών σχετικά με υπηρεσίες βιομηχανικής ανάλυσης και έρευνας· Υπηρεσίες επιστημονικού σχεδιασμού· Ανάπτυξη, προγραμματισμός και εφαρμογή λογισμικού· Σχεδιασμός λογισμικού για βάσεις δεδομένων υπολογιστή· Σχεδιασμός και ανάπτυξη υλικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Υπηρεσίες φιλοξενίας και λογισμικό ως μία υπηρεσία και ενοικίαση λογισμικού.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Science and technology services; Industrial analysis and research services; Medical and/or pharmaceutical research; Clinical research; Consultancy in the field of industrial research; Providing information about industrial analysis and research services; Scientific design services; Software development, programming and implementation; Design of computer database software; Design and development of computer hardware; Hosting services and software as a service and rental of software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios científicos y tecnológicos; Servicios de análisis e investigaciones industriales; Servicios de investigaciones médicas o farmacológicas; Estudios clínicos; Consultoría en investigación industrial; Suministro de información sobre servicios de análisis e investigación industriales; Servicios de diseño científico; Desarrollo, programación e implementación de software; Diseño de software de bases de datos; Desarrollo y diseño de hardware; Servicios de alojamientos de sitios web y alquiler de software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Teadus- ja tehnoloogiateenused; Tööstuslikud analüüsid ja uuringud teenusena; Meditsiini- ja farmakoloogiauuringud; Kliiniliste uuringute läbiviimine; Tööstusuuringute alased konsultatsioonid; Tööstusanalüüsi- ja -uuringuteenuste teabe pakkumine; Teadusprojekteerimise teenused; Arvutitarkvaraarendus ja -teostus, programmeerimine; Arvutiandmebaasitarkvara projekteerimine; Arvutiriistvara projekteerimine ja arendamine; Hostimine ja pilveteenused (SaaS) ning tarkvara rent.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tieteelliset ja teknologiset palvelut; Teolliset analyysi- ja tutkimuspalvelut; Lääketieteelliset ja/tai farmakologiset tutkimuspalvelut; Tieteelliset kliiniset tutkimustyöt; Teolliseen tutkimukseen liittyvä neuvonta; Teollisuuden analyysi- ja tutkimuspalveluja koskevien tietojen tarjoaminen; Tieteelliset suunnittelupalvelut; Tietokoneohjelmistojen kehittäminen, ohjelmointi ja toteutus; Tietokantaohjelmistojen suunnittelu; Tietokoneiden suunnittelu ja kehittäminen; Verkkoisännöintipalvelut ja verkkosovelluspalvelut (SaaS) sekä ohjelmistojen vuokraus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services scientifiques et technologiques; Services d'analyses et de recherches industrielles; Services de recherches médicales et/ou pharmacologiques; Recherche clinique; Consultation dans le domaine de la recherche industrielle; Mise à disposition d'informations concernant des services d'analyse et de recherche industrielles; Services de conception scientifique; Développement, programmation et implémentation de logiciels; Conception de logiciels de bases de données informatiques; Conception et développement de matériel informatique; Services d'hébergement et logiciel en tant que service, et location de logiciel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge znanosti i tehnologije; Usluge industrijskih analiza i istraživanja; Usluge medicinskih i/ili farmakoloških istraživanja; Kliničko istraživanje; Savjetovanje u području industrijskog istraživanja; Pružanje informacija o uslugama industrijske analize i istraživanja; Znanstvene usluge projektiranja; Razvoj, programiranje i implementacija softvera; Dizajn softvera za računalne baze podataka; Projektiranje i razvoj računalnih hardvera; Usluge hostinga i softver kao usluga te iznajmljivanje softvera.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Tudományos és technológiai szolgáltatások; Ipari elemző és kutató szolgáltatások; Orvosi és/vagy farmakológiai kutatási szolgáltatások; Klinikai kutatási szolgáltatások; Ipari kutatásokkal kapcsolatos konzultáció; Tájékoztatás ipari elemzési és kutatási szolgáltatásokról; Tudományos tervezési szolgáltatások; Szoftverfejlesztés, programozás és kivitelezés; Számítógépes adatbázis-kezelő szoftverek tervezése; Számítógépes hardverek tervezése és fejlesztése; Webtárhely és szoftver szolgáltatások, szoftver bérlés.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di scienza e tecnologia; Servizi di analisi e di ricerche industriali; Servizi di ricerca medici e/o farmacologici; Conduzione di studi clinici; Consulenza nel campo della ricerca industriale; Fornitura di informazioni relative a servizi di analisi e ricerca industriale; Servizi di progettazione scientifica; Sviluppo, programmazione ed implementazione di software; Progettazione di software per banche dati informatiche; Elaborazione e sviluppo di hardware; Servizi di hosting e software come servizio e noleggio di software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Mokslo ir technologijų paslaugos; Pramoninės analizės ir tyrimų paslaugos; Medicinos ir (arba) farmakologijos tyrimai; Klinikiniai tyrimai; Pramonės tyrimų konsultacijos; Informacijos apie pramoninės analizės ir tyrimų paslaugas teikimas; Mokslinio projektavimo paslaugos; Programinės įrangos tobulinimas, programavimas ir įdiegimas; Kompiuterių duomenų bazių programinės įrangos projektavimas; Kompiuterių aparatinės įrangos projektavimas ir tobulinimas; Prieglobos (talpinimo) paslaugos ir programinė įranga kaip paslauga bei programinės įrangos nuoma.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Zinātniskie un tehnoloģiskie pakalpojumi; Rūpnieciskā izpēte un izstrādnes; Medicīniskās un/vai farmakoloģiskās pētniecības pakalpojumi; Klīniskā izpēte; Konsultācijas rūpnieciskās pētniecības jomā; Informācijas nodrošināšana par rūpnieciskās analīzes un izpētes pakalpojumiem; Zinātniskās projektēšanas pakalpojumi; Programmatūras izstrāde, programmēšana un ieviešana; Datoru datubāzu programmatūras projektēšana; Datoraparatūras dizains un izstrāde; Datņu izvietošanas un uzturēšanas pakalpojumi, arī programmatūras izvietošana un uzturēšana mākonī un programmatūras iznomāšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi xjentifiċi u teknoloġiċi; Analiżi industrijali u servizzi ta' riċerka; Servizzi ta' riċerki mediċi u/jew farmakoloġiċi; Riċerka klinika; Konsulenza fil-qasam tar-riċerka industrijali; Provvista ta' informazzjoni dwar servizzi ta' analiżi u riċerka industrijali; Servizzi ta' disinn xjentifiku; Żvilupp tas-softwer, programmar u implimentazzjoni; Disinn ta' softwer ta' bażi tad-data kompjuterizzat; Disinn u żvilupp ta' ħardwer tal-kompjuter; Servizzi ta' hosting u softwer bħala servizz u kiri ta' softwer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Wetenschappelijke en technologische diensten; Dienstverlening op het gebied van industriële analyse en industrieel onderzoek; Medisch en/of farmacologisch onderzoek; Het uitvoeren van klinische tests; Advisering op het gebied van industrieel onderzoek; Informatieverstrekking over industriële analyse- en onderzoeksdiensten; Wetenschappelijke ontwerpdiensten; Ontwikkeling, programmering en implementatie van software; Ontwerp van computerdatabasesoftware; Computerhardware (Ontwerp en ontwikkeling van -); Hostingdiensten en ter beschikking stellen van software (Saas) en verhuur van software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi naukowe i technologiczne; Przemysłowe analizy i usługi badawcze; Usługi w zakresie badań medycznych i farmakologicznych; Badania kliniczne; Doradztwo w zakresie badań przemysłowych; Udzielanie informacji na temat usług analiz i badań przemysłowych; Usługi w zakresie projektowania naukowego; Rozwój, programowanie i wdrażanie oprogramowania komputerowego; Projektowanie oprogramowania komputerowych baz danych; Projektowanie i rozwój sprzętu komputerowego; Hosting, oprogramowanie jako usługa oraz wypożyczanie oprogramowania komputerowego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de ciência e tecnologia; Serviços de análises e de pesquisas industriais; Serviços de pesquisas médicas e/ou farmacológicas; Investigação clínica; Consultoria na área da investigação industrial; Disponibilização de informação sobre serviços de análises e pesquisas industriais; Serviços de design científico; Desenvolvimento, programação e implementação de software; Design de software de bases de dados informáticas; Conceção e desenvolvimento de hardware informático; Serviços de alojamento de sites de Internet e software como serviço e aluguer de software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii în domeniul ştiinţei şi tehnologiei; Servicii de analiză şi cercetare industrială; Servicii de cercetări medicale şi/sau farmacologice; Cercetare clinică; Consultanţă în domeniul cercetării industriale; Furnizare de informaţii despre servicii de analize şi cercetare industrială; Servicii de proiectare științifică; Dezvoltare software, programare şi implementare; Proiectare de software pentru baze de date informatice; Proiectare şi dezvoltare de hardware de calculator; Servicii de găzduire, software ca şi serviciu şi închiriere de software.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vedecké a technologické služby; Priemyselné analýzy a priemyselný výskum; Služby v oblasti lekárskeho a/alebo farmakologického výskumu; Klinický výskum; Poradenstvo v oblasti priemyselného výskumu; Poskytovanie informácií v oblasti priemyselných analytických a výskumných služieb; Vedecké projektovanie; Vývoj softvéru, programovanie a zavádzanie programov; Dizajn počítačového databázového softvéru; Navrhovanie a vývoj počítačového hardvéru; Hosťovanie na internetových stránkach, softvérové služby, prenájom softvéru.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Znanstvene in tehnološke storitve; Industrijske analize in raziskave; Storitve medicinskih in/ali farmakoloških raziskav; Izvajanje kliničnih poskusov; Svetovanje na področju industrijskih raziskav; Nudenje informacij o industrijskih analitičnih in raziskovalnih storitvah; Storitve znanstvenega načrtovanja; Razvoj programske opreme, programiranje in uvajanje programske opreme; Oblikovanje programske opreme za računalniške podatkovne zbirke; Oblikovanje in razvoj računalniške strojne opreme; Storitve gostovanja in nudenje programske opreme preko spleta ter dajanje programske opreme v najem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Vetenskapliga och tekniska tjänster; Industriella analyser och forskningstjänster; Tjänster med avseende på medicinsk och/eller farmakologisk forskning; Genomförande av kliniska försök; Konsultationer inom området industriell forskning; Tillhandahållande av information om tjänster för industriell analys och forskning; Vetenskapliga designtjänster; Mjukvaruutveckling, -programmering och –implementering; Design av databasprogram för datorer; Design och utveckling av datorhårdvaror; Hostingtjänster, molntjänster (SaaS) och uthyrning av mjukvara.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>44</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Здравни грижи за хора и животни; Медицински и ветеринарни услуги, По-специално медицински анализи във връзка с лечението на отделни лица; Медицински услуги за тестване, свързани с диагностициране и лечение на заболявания; Медицинска информация; Услуги на здравен център; Медицински клиники; Терапевтични услуги; Диагностични услуги; Услуги за вземане на проби за медицински и ветеринарни цели; Услуги за вземане на проби за диагностициране и лечение на болести.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Péče o hygienu osob nebo zvířat; Lékařské a veterinární služby, Zejména lékařské analýzy v souvislosti s léčbou jednotlivců; Lékařské testovací služby týkající se diagnostikování a léčení nemocí; Lékařské informace; Služby zdravotních center; Zdravotnická střediska; Terapeutické služby; Diagnostické služby; Odběr vzorků k lékařským a veterinárním účelům; Služby pro odběr vzorků pro diagnostikování a ošetření nemocí.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Sundhedspleje til mennesker og dyr; Medicinske ydelser og veterinære medicinske ydelser, Især medicinsk analyse i forbindelse med behandling af enkeltpersoner; Tjenester vedrørende medicinsk afprøvning inden for diagnosticering og behandling af sygdomme; Information om lægebehandlingsvirksomhed; Sundhedscentre; Tjenester ydet af medicinske klinikker; Terapivirksomhed; Diagnostik; Prøveudtagning til medicinske og veterinærmedicinske formål; Prøveudtagning med henblik på diagnosticering og behandling af sygdomme.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Gesundheitspflege für Menschen oder Tiere; medizinische oder veterinärmedizinische Dienstleistungen, insbesondere medizinische Analysen im Zusammenhang mit der Behandlung von Einzelnen; Durchführung von medizinischen Tests im Zusammenhang mit der Diagnose und Behandlung von Krankheiten; medizinische Auskünfte; Leistungen von Gesundheitszentren; Dienstleistungen von Kliniken (Ambulanzen); Therapiedienste; Diagnosedienste; Probennahmedienste für medizinische und veterinärmedizinische Zwecke; Probennahmedienste für Diagnose und Behandlung von Krankheiten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Φροντίδες υγιεινής παρεχόμενες σε ανθρώπους και ζώα· Ιατρικές και κτηνιατρικές υπηρεσίες, Ειδικότερα ιατρικές αναλύσεις σε σχέση με τη θεραπεία μεμονωμένων ατόμων· Υπηρεσίες ιατρικών εξετάσεων σε σχέση με τη διάγνωση και θεραπεία ασθενειών· Ιατρική πληροφόρηση και ενημέρωση· Υπηρεσίες κέντρων υγείας· Υπηρεσίες ιατρικής κλινικής· Θεραπευτικές υπηρεσίες· Διαγνωστικές υπηρεσίες· Υπηρεσίες δειγματοληψίας για ιατρικούς και κτηνιατρικούς σκοπούς· Υπηρεσίες δειγματοληψίας για τη διάγνωση και τη θεραπεία ασθενειών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Hygienic care for human beings or animals; Medical and veterinary medical services, In particular medical analysis in connection with the treatment of individuals; Medical testing services relating to the diagnosis and treatment of disease; Medical information; Health clubs; Medical clinic services; Therapy services; Diagnostic services; Sampling for medical and veterinary purposes; Sampling for the diagnosis and treatment of diseases.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de higiene para personas o animales; Servicios médicos y veterinarios, En particular análisis médicos relacionados con el tratamiento de personas individuales; Pruebas médicas relacionadas con el diagnóstico y tratamiento de enfermedades; Información médica; Servicios de centros sanitarios; Servicios de clínicas médicas; Servicios terapéuticos; Servicios de diagnóstico; Servicios para recoger muestras para uso médico y veterinario; Servicios para recoger muestras para el diagnóstico y tratamiento de enfermedades.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Inimeste ja loomade tervishoid; Meditsiinilised ja veterinaarmeditsiinilised teenused, Eelkõige meditsiinilised analüüsid seoses üksikisikute ravimisega; Haiguste diagnostika ja raviga seotud meditsiinikatsete teenused; Meditsiiniteave, -info; Tervisekeskuste teenused; Kliinikute, kliiniliste haiglate meditsiiniteenused; Teraapiateenused; Diagnostika; Proovide võtmise teenused meditsiini ja veterinaaria tarbeks; Proovide võtmise teenused haiguste diagnoosimiseks ja ravimiseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ihmisten tai eläinten hygieniapalvelut; Lääketieteelliset ja eläinlääketieteelliset palvelut, Erityisesti lääketieteelliset analyysit yksittäisten henkilöiden hoidon yhteydessä; Sairauksien diagnosointiin ja hoitoon liittyvät lääketieteelliset testauspalvelut; Lääketieteellinen tiedotus; Terveyskeskusten palvelut; Lääkintäklinikoiden palvelut; Terapiapalvelut; Diagnostiset palvelut; Näytteenottopalvelut lääketieteellisiin ja eläinlääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Näytteenottopalvelut sairauksien diagnosointia ja hoitamista varten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d' hygiène pour les personnes ou les animaux; Services médicaux et vétérinaires, En particulier analyses médicales en rapport avec le traitement d'individus; Services d'examens médicaux en matière de diagnostic et de traitement de maladies; Informations médicales; Services de centres de santé; Services de clinique médicale; Services thérapeutiques; Services de diagnostic; Services de prélèvement d'échantillons à usage médical et vétérinaire; Services de prélèvement d'échantillons pour le diagnostic et traitement de maladies.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Njega zdravlja ljudi i životinja; Medicinske i veterinarske usluge, Osobito medicinske analize povezane s liječenjem pojedine osobe; Usluge medicinskog testiranja u vezi s dijagnozom i liječenjem bolesti; Medicinske informacije; Usluge zdravstvenih centara; Medicinske kliničke usluge; Terapeutske usluge; Dijagnostičke usluge; Usluge uzimanja uzoraka za medicinske i veterinarske potrebe; Usluge uzimanja uzoraka za dijagnozu i liječenje bolesti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Egészségápolás emberek és állatok részére; Orvosi és állatgyógyászati szolgáltatások, Különösen gyógyászati elemzések az egyes személyek kezelésével kapcsolatban; Gyógyászati vizsgálati szolgáltatások betegségek diagnosztizálásával és kezelésével kapcsolatban; Egészségügyi ellátással kapcsolatos információs szolgáltatások; Egészségügyi központok által nyújtott szolgáltatások; Klinikák, orvos rendelők szolgáltatásai; Terápiás szolgáltatások; Diagnosztikai szolgáltatások; Mintavételi szolgáltatások orvosi és állatorvosi célokra; Mintavételi szolgáltatások a betegségek diagnosztizálásához és kezeléséhez.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Cura della salute delle persone e degli animali; Servizi medici e veterinari, In particolare analisi mediche legate al trattamento di singoli individui; Servizi di esami medici in tema di diagnosi e trattamento delle patologie; Informazioni mediche; Servizi di centri sanitari; Cliniche (mediche); Servizi terapeutici; Servizi di diagnostica; Prelievo di campioni per uso medico e veterinario; Prelievo di campioni per la diagnosi e la cura di malattie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Žmonių ir gyvūnų sveikatos priežiūra; Medicinos ir veterinarijos paslaugos, Ypač medicinos analizės, susijusios su atskirų asmenų gydymu; Medicinos tyrimų paslaugos, susijusios su ligos diagnostika ir gydymu; Informacija apie mediciną; Sveikatos priežiūros centrų paslaugos; Medicinos klinikų paslaugos; Gydymo paslaugos; Diagnostikos paslaugos; Mėginių ėmimo paslaugos medicinos ir veterinarijos srityse; Mėginių ėmimo paslaugos ligoms diagnozuoti ir gydyti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Cilvēku un dzīvnieku veselības kopšana; Medicīniskie un veterinārmedicīniskie pakalpojumi, Jo īpaši medicīniskas analīzes saistībā ar atsevišķu personu aprūpi; Medicīnisko pārbaužu pakalpojumi saistībā ar slimību diagnosticēšanu un ārstēšanu; Medicīniskās informācijas nodrošināšana; Veselības centru pakalpojumi; Medicīnisko klīniku pakalpojumi; Terapijas pakalpojumi; Diagnostikas pakalpojumi; Paraugu ņemšanas pakalpojumi medicīniskiem un veterinārmedicīniskiem nolūkiem; Paraugu ņemšanas pakalpojumi diagnostikai un slimību ārstēšanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kura tas-saħħa għall-bniedem u l-annimali; Servizzi mediċi u mediċi veterinarji, Speċjalment analiżi mediċi relatati mat-trattament ta' individwi; Servizzi ta' testijiet mediċi relatati mad-dijanjosi u t-trattament ta' mard; Informazzjoni medika; Servizzi ta' ċentri tas-saħħa; Servizzi ta' klinika medika; Servizzi ta' terapija; Servizzi dijanjostiċi; Servizzi ta' teħid ta' kampjuni għal skopijiet mediċi u tal-mediċina veterinarja; Servizzi ta' teħid ta' kampjuni għad-dijanjosi u t-trattament ta' mard.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Dienstverlening op het gebied van hygiëne voor mensen of dieren; Medische en diergeneeskundige diensten, Met name medische analyses in verband met de behandeling van individuen; Medische testen met betrekking tot de diagnostiek en behandeling van ziektes; Medische informatie; Diensten van gezondheidscentra; Diensten van medische klinieken; Therapeutische diensten; Diensten op het gebied van diagnostiek; Bemonsteringsdiensten voor medisch en diergeneeskundig gebruik; Bemonsteringsdiensten voor het diagnosticeren en behandelen van ziekten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi w zakresie higieny dla ludzi i zwierząt; Usługi medycyny i medycyny weterynaryjnej, W szczególności analizy medyczne w związku z leczeniem jednostek; Usługi badań medycznych związane z diagnozowaniem i leczeniem chorób; Informacja medyczna; Usługi świadczone przez ośrodki zdrowia; Usługi klinik medycznych; Usługi terapeutyczne; Usługi diagnostyczne; Usługi pobierania próbek do celów medycznych i weterynaryjnych; Usługi pobierania próbek do diagnozowania i leczenia chorób.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Cuidados de saúde no âmbito da medicina humana e animais; Serviços médicos e de medicina veterinária, Em especial análises médicas no contexto do tratamento de indivíduos; Serviços de exames médicos para o diagnóstico e tratamento de doenças; Informações médicas; Serviços prestados por centros de saúde; Serviços de clínicas médicas; Serviços de terapia; Serviços de diagnóstico; Serviços de amostragem para fins médicos e veterinários; Serviços de amostragem para diagnóstico e tratamento de doenças.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Prestare de servicii in domeniul igienei pentru oameni sau animale; Servicii medicale şi servicii veterinare, În special analize medicale în legătură cu tratamentul persoanelor individuale; Servicii de teste medicale pentru diagnosticul şi tratamentul bolilor; Servicii de furnizare de informaţii medicale; Servicii ale centrelor de sănătate; Servicii ale clinicilor medicale; Servicii de terapie; Servicii de diagnosticare; Servicii de prelevare de probe de uz medical și veterinar; Servicii de prelevare de probe pentru diagnosticarea și tratarea bolilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zdravotná starostlivosť pre ľudí a zvieratá; Lekárske a zverolekárske služby, Predovšetkým medicínske analýzy v súvislosti s liečbou jednotlivých pacientov; Lekárske testovacie služby v oblasti diagnostiky a liečenia ochorení; Informácie v oblasti medicíny; Starostlivosť o hygienu a krásu ľudí alebo zvierat; Zdravotné strediská (služby); Terapeutické služby; Diagnostické služby; Služby odoberania vzoriek na lekárske alebo zverolekárske účely; Služby odoberania vzoriek pre diagnostiku a liečbu chorôb.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zdravstvena nega za ljudi in živali; Medicinske in veterinarske storitve, Zlasti medicinske analize v povezavi z zdravljenjem posameznih oseb; Storitve medicinskega testiranja v zvezi z diagnostiko in zdravljenjem bolezni; Medicinske informacije; Storitve zdravstvenih centrov; Storitve zdravstvenih klinik; Terapevtske storitve; Diagnostične storitve; Storitve vzorčenja za medicinske in veterinarske namene; Storitve vzorčenja za diagnozo in zdravljenje bolezni.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Hälsovård för människor och djur; Medicinska och veterinärmedicinska tjänster, Speciellt medicinsk analys i samband med behandling av enskilda; Medicinska provtagningstjänster avseende diagnosticering och behandling av sjukdomar; Medicinsk information; Tjänster tillhandahållna av vårdcentraler; Medicinska kliniktjänster; Terapitjänster; Diagnostik; Provtagningstjänster för medicinska och veterinära ändamål; Provtagningstjänster för diagnos och behandling av sjukdomar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/117</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-06-23</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/189</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.2</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-10-02</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>1105188</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>19519</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<MarkRecordDetails>
<MarkRecord>
<BasicRecord>
<RecordIdentifier>018291537</RecordIdentifier>
<BasicRecordKind>Proprietor - Change of name and address</BasicRecordKind>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>19519</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<RecordCurrentStatusCode>Not to be published</RecordCurrentStatusCode>
<RecordCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-10</RecordCurrentStatusDate>
</BasicRecord>
</MarkRecord>
</MarkRecordDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
