<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-05T16:31:37</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018225927</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018225927</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-31</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>it</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Gebulin</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>25</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Костюми за Хелоуин; Детско облекло; Цилиндри [шапки]; Малки шапки; Бикини; Наметки за баня; Дрехи за театрална употреба; Кожени шапки; Кожени дрехи; Костюми; Хартиени шапки [облекло]; Шапки за парти [дрехи]; Костюми за употреба при ролеви игри; Шалове за плаж; Трикотажно и плетено облекло; Рокли; Спортни обувки; Физкултурни униформи; Залепящи се сутиени; Кръгли памучни шапки; Наметала; Тренировъчни обувки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Kostýmy na Halloween; Dětské oděvy; Cylindry; Malé klobouky; Bikiny; Tuniky přes dámské plavky; Oděvní zboží pro použití v divadle; Kožešinové klobouky; Kožené oděvy; Pánské obleky; Papírové klobouky [oděvy]; Klobouky na společenské akce (oděvy); Kostýmy používané k hraní rolí; Plážová parea; Pletené oděvní výrobky; Dámské šaty; Sportovní vyšší obuv; Atletické úbory; Samodržící podprsenky; Kloboučky; Tunika; Obuv na trénování sportů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Halloweenkostumer; Børnetøj; Høje hatte; Små hatte; Bikinier; Beklædningsgenstande til at tage ud over badetøj; Beklædningsgenstande til teaterforestillinger; Pelshatte; Lædertøj; Spadseredragter; Papirhatte [beklædningsgenstande]; Festhatte [beklædningsgenstande]; Kostumer til brug i forbindelse med rollespil; Saronger til brug på stranden; Strikkede beklædningsgenstande; Kjoler; Sportsstøvler; Atletikdragter; Selvsiddende bh'er; Bøllehatte; Lette beklædningsgenstande til brug over badetøj; Træningssko.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Halloween-Kostüme; Bekleidung für Kinder; Zylinderhüte; Kleine Hüte; Bikinis; Longshirts für den Strand; Bekleidungsstücke für den Theatergebrauch; Pelzmützen; Lederbekleidung; Anzüge; Papierhüte [Bekleidung]; Partyhüte [Bekleidungsstücke]; Kostüme zur Verwendung bei Rollenspielen; Pareos; Strickwaren [Bekleidung]; Damenkleider; Sportschuhe; Mannschaftssportbekleidung; Selbsthaftende BHs; Fischerhüte; Coverups [leichte Damenbekleidungsstücke zum Tragen über Badebekleidung]; Trainingsschuhe.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αποκριάτικα κοστούμια· Παιδικά ενδύματα· Καπέλα ημίψηλα· Μικρά καπέλα· Μαγιό μπικίνι· Ενδύματα που φοριούνται πάνω από το μαγιό· Είδη ένδυσης για χρήση στο θέατρο· Γούνινα καπέλα· Ενδύματα από δέρμα· Κοστούμια (επίσημα ενδύματα)· Καπέλα (χάρτινα -) [ενδύματα]· Καπέλα για πάρτι [ενδύματα]· Κοστούμια προοριζόμενα για χρήση σε παιχνίδια υπόδυσης ρόλων· Ενδύματα παραλίας· Πλεκτά [ενδύματα]· Βραδινές τουαλέτες· Αθλητικά υποδήματα· Τύποι ένδυσης διαφόρων αθλημάτων· Αυτοκόλλητοι στηθόδεσμοι· Καπέλα από μαλακό ύφασμα που θυμίζουν το καπέλο του ψαρά· Ενδύματα κάλυψης· Αθλητικά παπούτσια προπόνησης.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Halloween costumes; clothing for children; top hats; small hats; bikinis; beach cover-ups; articles of clothing for theatrical use; fur hats; articles of clothing made of hides; dress suits; paper hats [clothing]; party hats [clothing]; costumes for use in role-playing games; pareus; knitwear [clothing]; dresses; boots for sports; athletic uniforms; adhesive bras; bucket caps; Coverups; Training shoes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Disfraces para Halloween (víspera de Todos los Santos); Prendas de vestir para niños; Sombreros de copa; Sombreros pequeños; Biquinis; Prendas para cubrir trajes de baño; Vestuario teatral; Sombreros de piel; Ropa de cuero; Trajes; Sombreros de papel [prendas de vestir]; Gorros para fiestas [prendas de vestir]; Trajes para usar en juegos de rol; Pareos; Prendas de punto; Vestidos; Calzado de deporte; Uniformes de deporte; Sostenes adhesivos; Gorros tipo pescador; Camisetas largas; Zapatillas de deporte.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Halloween'i kostüümid; Lasterõivad; Silindrid (peakatted); Väikesed kübarad; Bikiinid; Ujumistrikoode pealisrõivad; Lavakunstis kasutatavad rõivad; Karusnahksed mütsid; Nahkrõivad; Ülikonnad, kostüümid; Paberist peakatted [rõivad]; Peomütsid [rõivad]; Kostüümid rollimängude mängimiseks; Rannasallid, -rätid; Kudumid (rõivad); Kleidid; Spordisaapad; Spordirõivad; Liimuvad rinnahoidjad; Suvemütsid; Õhukesed pealisrõivad; Spordisaapad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Halloween-asut; Lastenvaatteet; Silinterit; Pienet hatut; Bikinit; Uimapuvun päällä pidettävät vaatekappaleet; Vaatteet teatterikäyttöön; Turkislakit; Nahkavaatteet; Puvut; Hatut (paperi -) [vaatetukseen]; Juhlahatut [vaatteet]; Roolipeliasut; Uimarannalla käytettävät kietaisuasusteet; Neulevaatteet; Kaavut; Lenkkitossut; Urheiluasut; Itsekiinnittyvät rintaliivit; Kalastajanlakit; Kylpytunikat; Lenkkitossut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Costumes pour la fête d'Halloween; Vêtements pour enfants; Hauts-de-forme; Petits chapeaux; Bikinis; Cache-maillots; Articles vestimentaires pour représentations théâtrales; Chapeaux en fourrure; Vêtements en cuir; Costumes; Chapeaux en papier [habillement]; Chapeaux de fête [vêtements]; Costumes pour jeux de rôles; Paréos; Tricots [vêtements]; Robes; Chaussures de sport; Tenues d'athlétisme; Soutiens-gorge adhésifs; Bobs [chapeau rond]; Combinaisons; Chaussures de training.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Kostimi za Noć vještica; Dječja odjeća; Cilindri [šeširi za glavu]; Mali šeširi; Bikini kupaći kostimi; Odjeća koja se nosi na kupaći kostim; Odjevni predmeti za kazalište; Krzneni šeširi; Kožna odjeća; Nošnje; Šeširi od papira [odjeća]; Šeširi za zabave [odjeća]; Kostimi za igre s ulogama; Parei; Pletena odjeća [odjevni predmeti]; Dugačke haljine; Sportska obuća; Sportske uniforme; Samoljepljivi grudnjaci; Ribarska kapa; Ogrtači; Tenisice za trening.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Halloween-jelmezek; Gyermekruházat; Cilinderek, kürtőkalapok; Kisméretű kalapok; Bikinik; Strandruhák; Ruházati cikkek színházi használatra; Szőrmesapkák; Bőrruházat; Öltönyök; Papírkalapok [ruházat]; Parti kalapok [ruházat]; Kosztümök szerepjátékokhoz; Strandkendők; Kötöttáruk [ruházat]; Talárok; Sportcipők; Sportruhák és -mezek; Öntapadós melltartók; Horgászsapkák; Leplek; Edzőcipők.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Costumi da Halloween; Articoli di abbigliamento per bambini; Cappelli a cilindro; Cappelli di piccole dimensioni; Bikini; Parei per costumi da bagno; Articoli di abbigliamento per il teatro; Cappelli di pelliccia; Abbigliamento in pelle; Abiti [completi]; Cappelli di carta [abbigliamento]; Cappelli per feste [abbigliamento]; Costumi per giochi di ruolo; Parei; Indumenti lavorati a maglia; Abiti; Calzature per lo sport; Vestiti da atletica; Reggiseni adesivi; Cappelli stile pescatore; Parei; Calzature per lo sport.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Helovino kostiumai; Vaikų drabužiai; Cilindrai [skrybėlės]; Mažos skrybėlaitės; Bikiniai; Drabužiai, skirti vilkėti ant maudymosi kostiumėlių; Drabužiai, skirti teatro reikmėms; Kailinės kepurės; Odiniai drabužiai; Kostiumai; Popierinės kepurės [apranga]; Šventinės kepuraitės [drabužiai]; Vaidmenų žaidimų kostiumai; Paplūdimio skraistės; Megzti drabužiai; Suknelės; Sportinė avalynė; Lengvaatlečių uniformos; Klijuojamosios liemenėlės; Skrybėlaitės formos kepurės; Lengvi moteriški viršutiniai drabužiai; Gimnastikos bateliai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Helovīna kostīmi; Bērnu apģērbi; Cilindri (cepures); Mazas cepurītes; Bikini; Apģērbi peldkostīma apsegšanai; Apģērbs teātrim; Kažokādas cepures; Ādas apģērbi; Uzvalki; Papīra cepures (apģērbi); Viesību cepures (apģērbs); Kostīmi, kas paredzēti lomu spēlēm; Pludmales kleitas; Adījumi (apģērbi); Kleitas; Zābaki sportam; Sporta uniformas; Pielīmējami krūšturi; Auduma vasaras mīkstās cepures ar malām; Aizsegi (viegls sieviešu apģērbs, ko valkāt virs peldkostīma); Krosa kurpes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Kostumi ta' halloween; Ilbies tat-tfal; Kpiepel nofs tomna; Kpiepel żgħar; Bikinis; Lbies ta' fuq il-malji tal-għawm; Ħwejjeġ għall-użu f'teatru; Kpiepel tal-fer; Ħwejjeġ tal-ġilda; Libsa intiera; Karta (Kpiepel tal- -) [ilbies]; Kpiepel tal-festin [ilbies]; Kostumi għal attivitajiet fejn wieħed jaħdem parti; Ħwejjeġ biex titgeżwer fihom għal ħdejn il-baħar; Xogħol tal-malja [lbies]; Ilbiesi twal tan-nisa; Żraben tal-isports; Uniformijiet tal-atletika; Riċipetti li jeħlu; Brieret fondi; Biċċiet tad-drapp biex jgħattu xi partijiet mill-ġisem; Żraben tat-taħriġ.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Halloweenkostuums; Kinderkleding; Hoge hoeden; Kleine hoeden; Bikini's; Omslagdoeken voor badpakken; Kledingstukken voor gebruik in het theater; Hoeden van bont; Kledingstukken van leder; Kostuums; Hoeden van papier [kleding]; Feesthoedjes [kledingstukken]; Kostuums voor rollenspellen; Omslagdoeken voor het strand; Gebreide kleding; Japonnen; Sportschoeisel; Atletiekpakken; Zelfklevende beha's; Vishoedjes; Mantels; Trainingsschoenen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Kostiumy na Halloween; Odzież dziecięca; Cylindry [kapelusze]; Małe kapelusze; Bikini; Okrycia zakładane na kostiumy kąpielowe; Artykuły odzieżowe do użytku teatralnego; Czapki futrzane; Odzież ze skóry; Garnitury; Kapelusze papierowe [odzież]; Czapeczki na przyjęcia [odzież]; Kostiumy do użytku w grach fabularnych; Chusty plażowe; Dzianina [odzież]; Długie luźne stroje; Buty sportowe; Stroje sportowe; Biustonosze samonośne; Kapelusze wędkarskie typu bucket hat; Tuniki; Buty treningowe [obuwie sportowe].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Fatos para o Dia das Bruxas; Vestuário para criança; Chapéus-altos; Chapéus pequenos; Biquínis; Túnicas para usar por cima do fato de banho; Artigos de vestuário para uso em teatro; Chapéus de pele; Vestuário em couro; Fatos; Chapéus em papel [vestuário]; Chapéus para festas [vestuário]; Fatos de fantasia para jogos de interpretação de personagens; Páreos de praia [tecido que se enrola à volta do corpo]; Malhas [vestuário]; Vestidos; Botas para desporto; Uniformes desportivos; Soutiens adesivos; Chapéu de tecido; Vestidos de praia; Sapatos de treino.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Costume de Halloween; Haine pentru copii; Jobene; Pălării mici; Bikini; Rochii și cămăși de damă pentru plajă; Articole de îmbrăcăminte pentru teatru; Pălării din blană; Articole de îmbrăcăminte din piele; Costume bărbătești și taioare; Pălării de hârtie [îmbrăcăminte]; Pălării pentru petreceri [articole de îmbrăcăminte]; Costume utilizate în jocurile cu interpretare de roluri; Saronguri pentru plajă; Tricoturi [îmbrăcăminte]; Rochii lungi de seară; Încălțăminte de sport; Echipament sportiv; Sutiene aderente; Pălărioare de soare; Saronguri; Încălțăminte pentru antrenament.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Kostýmy na Halloween; Detské oblečenie; Cylindre (klobúky); Malé klobúky; Bikini; Tuniky na plavky; Odevné výrobky na divadelné účely; Kožušinové klobúky; Kožené odevy; Kostýmy, obleky; Papierové klobúky (oblečenie); Klobúky na spoločenské podujatia (odevy); Kostýmy používané pri hraní rolí; Plážové zavinovacie šatky; Pleteniny (oblečenie); Šaty; Športová obuv; Športový úbor; Samolepiace podprsenky; Rybárske klobúky; Pracovné overaly; Obuv na trénovanie športov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kostumi za noč čarovnic; Otroška oblačila; Cilindri; Majhni klobuki; Bikini kopalke; Ogrinjala za kopalke; Oblačila za gledališko uporabo; Krznene kape; Oblačila iz usnja; Obleke; Papirnati klobuki [oblačila]; Klobuki za zabave [oblačila]; Kostumi za igre igranja vlog; Ogrinjala za plažo; Pletenine [oblačila]; Halje; Športni čevlji; Oblačila za šport; Lepljivi modrčki; Športni okrogli klobučki; Ogrinjala; Telovadni čevlji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Halloweendräkter; Barnkläder; Cylinderhattar; Små hattar; Bikini; Överdragskläder för baddräkter; Kläder för teateranvändning; Pälshattar; Kläder av läder; Kostymer; Pappershattar [kläder]; Kalashattar [kläder]; Kostymer för användning vid spelande av rollspel; Strandkjolar; Trikåvaror [kläder]; Klänningar; Boots för sport; Sportdräkter; Självhäftande bh:ar; Fiskehattar; Coverups (strandkläder); Träningsskor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/146</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>85806</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
