<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-11-11T00:54:10</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018225679</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018225679</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="22" status="5">Application opposed</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-06-18</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>CARRERA</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>10</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Предпазни респираторни маски (с или без клапа), за медицинска употреба, Маски за лице за медицинска употреба, Защитни маски за устата и носа, за медицинска употреба, пластмасови предпазни прегради за медицински цели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Ochranné dýchací masky (s ventilací a bez ní) k lékařským účelům, Roušky k lékařskému použití, Ochranné ústní a nosní masky k lékařským účelům, plastové obličejové štíty k lékařským účelům.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Beskyttende åndedrætsmasker (med og uden ventil) til medicinske formål, Ansigtsmasker til medicinske formål, Beskyttende mund- og næsemasker til medicinske formål, ansigtsskærme af plastic til medicinske formål.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Atemschutzmasken (mit und ohne Ventil) für medizinische Zwecke, Gesichtsmasken für medizinische Zwecke, Mund- und Nasenschutzmasken für medizinische Zwecke, Gesichtsschutzschirme aus Kunststoff für medizinische Zwecke.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Προστατευτικές διατάξεις αναπνοής (με και χωρίς βαλβίδα) όχι για ιατρική χρήση, Μάσκες προσώπου για ιατρική χρήση, Μάσκες προστασίας του στόματος και της μύτης για ιατρική χρήση, πλαστικές ασπίδες προσώπου για ιατρική χρήση.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Respiratory protection masks (valved and non-valved) for medical use, face masks for medical use, mouth and nose protection masks for medical use, plastic face shields for medical use.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Máscaras de protección respiratoria (con y sin válvula) para uso médico, Máscaras faciales para uso médico, Mascarillas de protección de boca y nariz para uso médico, protecciones faciales de plástico para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Hingamisteede kaitsemaskid (ventiiliga ja ilma) meditsiinikasutuseks, Meditsiinilised näomaskid, Suu ja nina kaitsemaskid meditsiinikasutuseks, plastist näokatted meditsiinikasutuseks.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kasvonaamarit hengityselinten suojaamiseen (venttiileillä tai venttiilittömät) lääketieteelliseen käyttöön, Kasvonaamarit lääketieteelliseen käyttöön, Suojaavat suu- ja nenänaamarit lääketieteelliseen käyttöön, muoviset kasvosuojat lääketieteelliseen käyttöön.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Masques respiratoires de protection (avec et sans valve) à usage médical, Masques pour le visage à usage médical, Masques de protection pour la bouche et le nez à usage médical, écrans faciaux en matières plastiques à usage médical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Maske za zaštitu dišnog sustava (s ventilom i bez ventila) za medicinsku upotrebu, Maske za lice za medicinsku uporabu, Maske za zaštitu usta i nosa za medicinsku upotrebu, plastični štitnici za lice za medicinsku upotrebu.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Légzésvédő maszkok (szelepes és nem szelepek) orvosi használatra, Arcmaszkok gyógyászati használatra, Száj- és orrvédő maszkok orvosi használatra, műanyag arcvédők orvosi használatra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Maschere per la protezione respiratoria con e senza valvola per uso medico, Maschere per il viso per uso medico, Maschere di protezione per bocca e naso per uso medico, schermi facciali di plastica per uso medico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kvėpavimo organų apsaugos kaukės (su vožtuvais ir be vožtuvų), skirtos naudoti medicinoje, Veido kaukės medicinos reikmėms, Burnos ir nosies apsaugos kaukės medicinos reikmėms, plastikiniai veido skydai medicinos reikmėms.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elpceļu aizsardzības maskas [ar ventili vai bez] izmantošanai medicīnā, Sejas maskas medicīniskām vajadzībām, Mutes un deguna aizsargmaskas medicīniskai lietošanai, plastmasas sejas aizsargi medicīniskiem nolūkiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Maskri għall-protezzjoni respiratorja (bil-valv u mingħajr valv) għall-użu mediku, Maskri tal-wiċċ għall-użu mediku, Maskri għall-protezzjoni tal-ħalq u tal-imnieħer għall-użu mediku, protezzjoni tal-plastik għall-wiċċ għall-użu mediku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Beschermende ademhalingsmaskers, al dan niet met klep, voor medisch gebruik, Gezichtsmaskers voor medisch gebruik, Maskers voor mond- en neusbescherming voor medisch gebruik, plastic gezichtsschermen voor medisch gebruik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Maseczki ochronne do oddychania (z zaworami lub bez nich) do użytku medycznego, Maski na twarz do użytku medycznego, Maski ochronne na usta i na nos do użytku medycznego, osłony na twarz z tworzyw sztucznych do użytku medycznego.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Máscaras de proteção respiratória (com e sem válvula) destinadas a uso médico, Máscaras faciais para uso médico, Máscaras de proteção para a boca e o nariz para uso médico, viseiras de plástico para uso médico.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Măști de respirat de protecție (cu supapă și fără supapă) pentru uz medical, Măști medicale, Măști de protecție pentru gură și nas, de uz medical, protecții din plastic pentru față, de uz medical.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Ochranné dýchacie masky (s ventilom a bez bentilu) na lekárske použitie, Masky na tvár na lekárske účely, Masky na ochranu úst a nosa, určené na lekárske použitie, plastové štíty na tvár, určené na lekárske použitie.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zaščitne dihalne naprave (z ventili in brez) za medicinsko uporabo, Obrazne maske za medicinsko uporabo, Maske za zaščito ust in nosu za medicinsko uporabo, plastični ščitniki za obraz za medicinsko uporabo.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Skyddande andningsmasker (med ventiler eller ej) för medicinskt bruk, Ansiktsmasker för medicinskt bruk, Skyddande masker för mun och näsa för medicinskt bruk, ansiktsskydd av plast för medicinskt bruk.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/082</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>539392</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>10776</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
<OppositionDetails>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003124401</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-06-18</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>de</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>011755337</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2013-04-19</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>011755337</RegistrationNumber>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>Carrera</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>DE</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>3020090192731</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2009-03-28</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>302009019273</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2013-06-17</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>CARRERA</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>12842</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003125523</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-07-03</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Likelihood of confusion</OppositionGroundText>
<EarlierMarkDetails>
<EarlierMark>
<EarlierMarkCountryCode>EM</EarlierMarkCountryCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018012045</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2019-01-21</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationNumber>018012045</RegistrationNumber>
<RegistrationDate>2019-07-16</RegistrationDate>
<MarkFeature>Figurative</MarkFeature>
<WordMarkSpecification>
           <MarkVerbalElementText>CARRERAS by Fusté Carreras</MarkVerbalElementText>
          </WordMarkSpecification>
</EarlierMark>
</EarlierMarkDetails>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>978419</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>22326</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
<Opposition>
<OppositionIdentifier>003126949</OppositionIdentifier>
<OppositionDate>2020-07-29</OppositionDate>
<ProceedingLanguageCode>en</ProceedingLanguageCode>
<OppositionGroundText>
Art. 8(4)</OppositionGroundText>
<OpponentDetails>
<OpponentKey>
<Identifier>20481</Identifier>
</OpponentKey>
</OpponentDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>46574</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</Opposition>
</OppositionDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
