<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-05T16:31:39</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018225918</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018225918</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-31</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>it</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>en</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>ACB</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Електронни публикации записани на компютърен носител; Ежеседмични публикации с възможност за записване в електронна форма от интернет; Бази данни (електронни); Електронни публикации, които могат да бъдат прехвърляни върху друг носител; Компютърни софтуерни приложения, за сваляне; Електронни публикации под формата на списания, с възможност за изтегляне от интернет.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Elektronické publikace nahrané na počítačových médiích; Týdenní publikace stahovatelné z internetu v elektronické podobě; Databáze (elektronické); Stahovatelné elektronické publikace; Stahovatelné počítačové aplikace; Elektronické publikace ke stažení v podobě časopisů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Elektroniske publikationer optaget på computermedier; Ugentlige publikationer downloadet i elektronisk format fra internettet; Elektroniske databaser; Elektroniske publikationer, downloadable; Softwareapplikationer til computere, downloadable; Elektroniske tidsskrifter, der kan downloades.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Auf Computermedien gespeicherte elektronische Veröffentlichungen; Wöchentliche Veröffentlichungen, die in elektronischer Form aus dem Internet heruntergeladen werden; Elektronische Datenbanken; Herunterladbare elektronische Publikationen; Herunterladbare Software-Anwendungen für Computer; Herunterladbare elektronische Publikationen in Form von Magazinen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Ηλεκτρονικές εκδόσεις εγγεγραμμένες σε μέσα ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Εβδομαδιαίες εκδόσεις που μεταφορτώνονται σε ηλεκτρονική μορφή από το Διαδίκτυο· Βάσεις δεδομένων (ηλεκτρονικές)· Ηλεκτρονικές εκδόσεις, με δυνατότητα μεταφόρτωσης· Εφαρμογές λογισμικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών, μεταφορτώσιμες· Τηλεφορτώσιμες ηλεκτρονικές εκδόσεις με τη μορφή περιοδικών.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Electronic publications recorded on computer media; Weekly publications downloaded in electronic form from the internet; Databases (electronic); Electronic publications, downloadable; Computer software applications, downloadable; Downloadable electronic publications in the nature of magazines.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Publicaciones electrónicas grabadas en soportes informáticos; Publicaciones semanales descargadas en formato electrónico desde Internet; Bases de datos electrónicas; Publicaciones electrónicas descargables; Aplicaciones informáticas descargables; Publicaciones electrónicas descargables [revistas].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arvutimeediumidele salvestatud elektroonilised publikatsioonid; Elektroonilises vormis internetist allalaaditavad kord nädalas ilmuvad publikatsioonid; Elektroonilised andmebaasid; Elektroonilised allalaaditavad publikatsioonid; Allalaaditavad arvutitarkvararakendused; Allalaaditavad digiajakirjad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tietokonevälineille tallennetut elektroniset julkaisut; Internetistä ladattavat viikoittaiset julkaisut elektronisessa muodossa; Tietokannat (sähköiset); Elektroniset julkaisut [järjestelmästä toiseen poimittavat]; Ladattavat tietokoneohjelmistosovellukset; Ladattavat elektroniset julkaisut aikakauslehtien muodossa.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Publications électroniques enregistrées sur support informatique; Publications hebdomadaires téléchargées sous forme électronique à partir d'Internet; Bases de données (électroniques); Publications électroniques téléchargeables; Applications logicielles informatiques téléchargeables; Publications électroniques téléchargeables sous forme de revues.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Elektroničke publikacije snimljene na računalnom mediju; Tjedne publikacije preuzete u elektroničkom obliku s Interneta; Baze podataka (elektroničke); Elektronske publikacije koje se mogu preuzeti s Interneta; Aplikacije za računalne programe koje se mogu preuzeti s Interneta; Elektronske publikacije u obliku časopisa koje se mogu preuzimati.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Számítógépes hordozókon rögzített elektronikus kiadványok; Internetről elektronikus formában letöltött heti kiadványok, publikációk; Elektronikus adatbázisok; Letölthető elektronikus kiadványok, publikációk; Számítógépes szoftveralkalmazások, letölthető; Letölthető elektronikus kiadványok magazinok formájában.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">pubblicazioni elettroniche memorizzate su supporti informatici; Pubblicazioni settimanali scaricabili in forma elettronica da Internet; banche dati (elettroniche); Pubblicazioni elettroniche [scaricabili]; applicazioni per computer software, scaricabili.; pubblicazioni elettroniche scaricabili sotto forma di riviste.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Elektroniniai leidiniai, įrašyti į kompiuterių laikmenas; Elektroniniai savaitraščiai, parsisiunčiami iš interneto; Elektroninės duomenų bazės; Elektroniniai leidiniai [parsisiunčiamieji]; Parsisiunčiamoji kompiuterių programinė įranga; Parsisiunčiamieji žurnalų pobūdžio elektroniniai leidiniai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Elektroniskas publikācijas, saglabātas virtuālā veidā; Elektroniskā formā ar Interneta starpniecību lejupielādējamas iknedēļas publikācijas; Elektroniskās datubāzes; Lejupielādējamas elektroniskās publikācijas; Lejupielādējamas datorprogrammu lietotnes; Lejupielādējamas elektroniskās publikācijas periodisku izdevumu veidā.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi rreġistrati fuq mezzi tal-kompjuter; Pubblikazzjonijiet ta' kull ġimgħa li jitniżżlu f'forma elettronika mill-internet; Bażi tad-dejta (elettroniċi); Pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi, li jistgħu jitniżżlu; Applikazzjonijiet ta' softwer tal-kompjuter, li jitniżżlu; Pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi li jistgħu jitniżżlu fl-għamla ta' rivisti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Elektronische uitgaven vastgelegd op computermedia; Wekelijkse uitgaven in elektronische vorm te downloaden vanaf internet; Databases (elektronische-); Elektronische publicaties [te downloaden]; Downloadbare computersoftware-applicaties; Downloadbare elektronische publicaties in de vorm van tijdschriften.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Publikacje elektroniczne zarejestrowane na nośnikach komputerowych; Tygodniowe publikacje w formie elektronicznej do pobrania z Internetu; Elektroniczne bazy danych; Publikacje elektroniczne, do pobrania; Aplikacje komputerowe do pobrania; Publikacje elektroniczne do pobrania w postaci magazynów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Publicações eletrónicas gravadas em suportes informáticos; Publicações semanais descarregadas em formato eletrónico da Internet; Bases de dados eletrónicas; Publicações eletrónicas descarregáveis; Aplicações de software informático descarregáveis; Publicações eletrónicas para download sob a forma de revistas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Publicații electronice înregistrate pe suport computerizat; Publicații săptămânale ce pot fi descărcate în format electronic de pe internet; Baze de date (electronice); Publicații electronice descărcabile; Aplicații software de calculator, descărcabile; Publicații electronice descărcabile sub formă de reviste.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Elektronické publikácie zaznamenané na počítačových médiách; Týždenné publikácie sťahované v elektronickej podobe z internetu; Elektronické databázy; Elektronické publikácie (sťahovateľné); Počítačové softvérové aplikácie (sťahovateľné); Stiahnuteľné elektronické publikácie v podobe časopisov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Elektronske publikacije, posnete na računalniške medije; Tedenske publikacije, naložene v elektronski obliki iz interneta; Elektronske zbirke podatkov; Naložljive elektronske publikacije; Računalniška programska oprema, naložljiva preko računalniške mreže; Naložljive elektronske publikacije v obliki revij.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Elektroniska publikationer registrerade på datormedier; Veckopublikationer nedladdningsbara i elektronisk form från Internet; Databaser (elektroniska); Tidskrifter (elektroniska), nedladdningsbara; Softwareapplikationer för datorer, nedladdningsbara; Nedladdningsbara elektroniska publikationer i form av tidskrifter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>16</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Вестници; Наръчници [справочници]; Печатни публикации; Книжки; Папки с печатна информация; Списания [периодични]; Книги; Книжки; Календари; Листовки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Noviny; Manuály [návody]; Tištěné publikace; Brožury; Tištěné informační letáky; Časopisy [periodika]; Knihy; Brožuřky; Kalendáře; Letáky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Aviser; Håndbøger [lærebøger]; Trykte publikationer; Pjecer [tryksager]; Trykte informationsfoldere; Magasiner [tidsskrifter]; Bøger; Brochurer; Kalendere; Løbesedler.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Zeitungen; Handbücher; Schriften [Veröffentlichungen]; Broschüren; Gedruckte Informationsprospekte; Zeitschriften [Magazine]; Bücher; Booklets; Kalender; Flyer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Εφημερίδες· Βοηθήματα[εγχειρίδια]· Έντυπες εκδόσεις· Φυλλάδια· Έντυπα ενημερωτικά ντοσιέ· Περιοδικές εκδόσεις· Βιβλία· Φυλλάδια· Ημεροδείκτες· Φέιγ-βολάν.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Newspapers; Manuals [handbooks]; Printed publications; Pamphlets; Printed informational folders; Magazines [periodicals]; Books; Booklets; Calendars; Flyers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Diarios; Manuales; Publicaciones impresas; Folletos; Carpetas informativas impresas; Revistas [publicaciones periódicas]; Libros; Cartillas [cuadernillos]; Calendarios; Volantes [folletos].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ajalehed; Käsiraamatud; Trükiväljaanded; Pisitrükised, brošüürid; Trükitud infovoldikud; Ajakirjad; Raamatud; Brošüürid; Kalendrid; Lendlehed (flaierid).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Sanomalehdet; Käsikirjat [manuaalit]; Julkaisut (painetut); Kirjaset; Painetut tiedotuskansiot; Aikakauslehdet; Kirjat; Kirjaset; Kalenterit; Lentolehtiset.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Journaux; Manuels; Publications imprimées; Brochures; Dossiers d'informations imprimés; Revues [périodiques]; Livres; Livrets; Calendriers; Flyers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Novine; Priručnici; Publikacije; Brošure; Tiskane informativne mape; Periodični časopisi; Knjige; Brošure; Kalendari; Letci.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Újságok; Kézikönyvek [útmutatók]; Nyomtatott publikációk; Könyvecskék, brosúrák; Nyomtatott információs mappák; Magazinok, revük [időszaki lapok]; Könyvek; Könyvecskék, brosúrák; Naptárak; Szórólapok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">giornali; manuali; pubblicazioni; opuscoli; brochure informative stampate; riviste [periodici]; libri; libretti; Calendari; volantini..</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Laikraščiai; Vadovėliai; Spausdintiniai leidiniai; Brošiūros; Spausdinti informacijos aplankai; Žurnalai [periodiniai leidiniai]; Knygos; Bukletai; Kalendoriai; Skrajutės.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Avīzes; Rokasgrāmatas/mācību grāmatas; Iespiestas publikācijas; Brošūras (pamfleti); Drukāti informatīvu bukletu vāki; Žurnāli (periodiskie izdevumi); Grāmatas; Bukleti; Kalendāri; Reklāmlapas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Gazzetti; Manwali; Pubblikazzjonijiet stampati; Kotba żgħar; Fowlders tal-informazzjoni stampati; Magazins [perjodiċi]; Kotba; Kotba żgħar; Kalendarji; Flyers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Kranten; Handboeken; Gedrukte publicaties; Brochures; Gedrukte informatiefolders; Tijdschriften; Boeken; Boekjes; Kalenders; Flyers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Gazety; Podręczniki [książki]; Publikacje drukowane; Broszury; Drukowane foldery informacyjne; Czasopisma [periodyki]; Książki; Broszury; Kalendarze; Ulotki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Jornais; Manuais; Publicações impressas; Panfletos [brochuras]; Pastas informativas impressas; Revistas [periódicas]; Livros; Brochuras; Calendários; Panfletos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Ziare; Manuale; Publicații imprimate; Broșuri; Pliante informative tipărite; Reviste [publicații periodice]; Cărți; Broșuri; Calendare; Fluturași publicitari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Noviny; Príručky; Tlačené publikácie; Brožúry; Tlačené informačné fascikle; Časopisy (periodiká); Knihy; Brožované knihy; Kalendáre; Letáky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Časopisi; Priročniki; Tiskane publikacije; Knjižice; Tiskane informacijske mape; Revije [periodične]; Knjige; Knjižice; Koledarji; Letaki.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Tidningar; Handböcker [manualer]; Tryckta publikationer; Pamfletter; Tryckta broschyrer; Magasin [periodiska]; Böcker; Mindre böcker; Kalendrar; Annonsblad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>35</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Консултиране относно бизнес оценяване; Проучване с търговска цел; Търговски посреднически услуги; Експертни оценки и доклади, свързани с бизнес въпроси; Пазарни проучвания; Подпомагане при управлението на търговски дейности; Предоставяне на търговска и фирмена информация за контакт; Експертни услуги по бизнес експедитивност; Предоставяне на съдействие при управлението на промишлени или търговски предприятия; Търговски оценки; Бизнес изследвания; Търговско управление при лицензиране на стоки и услуги за трети лица; Систематизиране на информация в компютърни бази данни; Услуги, свързани с водене на преговори и сключване на търговски сделки за сметка на трети лица; Попълване на данъчни декларации; Търговски справки; Предоставяне на търговска информация и съвети за клиенти [център за потребителски съвети]; Консултация по бизнес управление; Провеждане на бизнес проучвания; Консултантски услуги в областта на човешките ресурси; Преглед на печата; Проучване на пазара; Административно управление на компании от подизпълнител; Информация в областта на бизнеса; Маркетингови услуги; Събиране на статистически данни; Услуги за оценяване в сферата на бизнеса; Бизнес одит; Услуги, свързани с бизнес консултации; Икономическо прогнозиране; Компютъризирани информационни услуги за оценки на бизнес възможности; Компютъризирано облагане с данък (подготовка) [счетоводни услуги]; Консултации в областта на търговското ръководство и организация; Набиране на спонсори; Управление на компютърни файлове; Услуги за подаване на данъчни декларации; Услуги в областта на връзките с обществеността; Агенции за търговска информация; Услуги, свързани с пазарна оценка; Услуги по бизнес компетентност; Бизнес одит.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Poradenství v oblasti obchodních odhadů; Obchodní průzkum; Zprostředkování obchodů; Znalecká odhady a zprávy vztahující se k obchodním záležitostem; Průzkum trhu; Pomoc při řízení obchodní činnosti; Poskytování informací o obchodních kontaktech; Služby odborníka na výkonnost podniku; Poskytování pomoci v oblasti řízení průmyslových nebo obchodních podniků; Oceňování podniků; Obchodní průzkumy; Obchodní správa licencí k výrobkům a službám jiných osob; Systematizace údajů do počítačových databází; Sjednávání a uzavírání obchodních transakcí pro třetí strany; Příprava daňových přiznání; Poptávky; Obchodní informace a rady pro spotřebitele [poradna pro spotřebitele]; Poradenství v oblasti řízení obchodní činnosti; Provádění obchodních průzkumů; Poradenství v oblasti řízení lidských zdrojů; Výstřižková služba; Průzkum trhu; Externí správa společností; Obchodní informace; Marketing; Sestavování statistiky; Obchodní odhady a hodnocení obchodních záležitostí; Účetnictví; Profesionální obchodní poradenství; Vyhotovování hospodářských prognóz; Elektronické informační služby v oblasti hodnocení obchodních příležitostí; Zpracování daňových výměrů pomocí počítače (účetnictví); Poradenství v oblasti řízení a organizace podniku; Vyhledávání sponzorů; Vedení počítačové evidence; Služby spojené s podáváním daňových přiznání; Styk s veřejností; Zprostředkování obchodních informací; Služby v oblasti hodnocení trhu; Služby v oblasti obchodních expertíz; Provádění podnikových auditů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Konsulentbistand i forbindelse med vurdering af virksomheder; Forretningsresearch; Kommerciel formidling; Ekspertevalueringer og -rapporter vedrørende forretningsanliggender; Markedsundersøgelser; Bistand ved forretningsledelse; Stillen kommercielle og forretningsmæssige kontaktoplysninger til rådighed; Tjenesteydelser udbudt af rationaliseringseksperter indenfor forretningsvirksomhed; Stille assistance til rådighed inden for ledelse af industri- eller handelsvirksomheder; Vurdering i forretningsanliggender; Undersøgelser om forretningsvirksomhed; Kommerciel administration ved licensering af andres varer og tjenesteydelser; Sortering og redigering af informationer computerdatabaser; Forhandling og afslutning af kommercielle transaktioner for tredjemand; Udfærdigelse af selvangivelser; Indhentning af forretningsoplysninger; Kommerciel information og rådgivning til forbrugere [forbrugerrådgivning]; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsledelse; Gennemførelse af forretningsundersøgelser; Rådgivning vedrørende personaleledelse; Nyhedsudklipsbureau; Markedsforskning; Udlicitering af virksomhedsadministration; Stillen information til rådighed vedrørende forretningsvirksomhed; Marketing; Kompilering af statistikker; Virksomhedsvurderinger og -evalueringer i forretningsanliggender; Regnskabsførelse; Professionel rådgivning vedrørende forretningsvirksomhed; Økonomiske prognoser; Computerstyret informationsvirksomhed til brug ved vurdering af forretningsmuligheder; Udarbejdelse af computerstyrede skattevurderinger [regnskabsførelse]; Rådgivning vedrørende forretningsledelse og organisation; Søgning efter sponsorater; Administration af datastyrede arkiver; Tjenesteydelser ved indsendelse af selvangivelse; PR-virksomhed; Forretningsmæssig oplysningsagenturvirksomhed; Rådgivning vedrørende markedsvurderinger; Ydelser inden for forretningsekspertise; Auditering af virksomheder.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Beratung in Bezug auf Unternehmensbewertungen; Betriebswirtschaftliche Recherche; Vermittlungsdienste in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Erstellen von Sachverständigengutachten in Bezug auf Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Marktstudien; Planungen [Hilfe] bei der Geschäftsführung; Bereitstellung von Kontaktinformationen in Handels- und Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Erstellung von Geschäftsgutachten; Hilfe bei der Führung von Industrie- oder Handelsbetrieben; Unternehmensbewertungen; Durchführung von Konjunkturumfragen; Kommerzielle Verwaltung der Lizenzierung von Waren und Dienstleistungen für Dritte; Systematisierung von Daten in Computerdatenbanken; Vermittlung und Abschluss von Handelsgeschäften für Dritte; Erstellung von Steuererklärungen; Auskünfte in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Erteilung von Auskünften [Information] und Beratung für Verbraucher in Handels- und Geschäftsangelegenheiten [Verbraucherberatung]; Beratung in Fragen der Geschäftsführung; Ausforschung in geschäftlichen Angelegenheiten; Beratung in Fragen des Personalwesens; Sammeln und Zusammenstellen von themenbezogenen Presseartikeln; Marktforschung; Outgesourcte Verwaltungsdienstleistungen für Unternehmen; Bereitstellung von Informationen in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Marketing; Erstellen von Statistiken; Unternehmensbewertungen und -beurteilungen in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Buchführung; Betriebswirtschaftliche Beratung; Erstellung von Wirtschaftsprognosen; Computergestützte Auskünfte über die Bewertung von geschäftlichen Optionen; Computergestützte Steuererklärung [Buchführung]; Beratung bei der Organisation und Führung von Unternehmen; Sponsorensuche; Dateienverwaltung mittels Computer; Einreichung von Steuererklärungen für Dritte; Öffentlichkeitsarbeit; Erteilung von Auskünften in Handels- und Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Beurteilung von Märkten; Erstellen von Gutachten in Geschäftsangelegenheiten; Prüfen von Geschäftsabläufen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Παροχή συμβουλών σε θέματα εκτίμησης επιχειρήσεων· Επιχειρηματική έρευνα· Υπηρεσίες εμπορικής διαμεσολάβησης· Αξιολογήσεις και εκθέσεις εμπειρογνωμόνων σε σχέση με επιχειρηματικά θέματα· Μελέτες αγοράς· Υποστήριξη στον τομέα της διαχείρισης επιχειρηματικών δραστηριοτήτων· Παροχή εμπορικών πληροφοριών και στοιχείων επικοινωνίας επιχειρήσεων· Υπηρεσίες ειδικού στην αποδοτικότητα των επιχειρήσεων· Παροχή υποστήριξης στη διαχείριση βιομηχανικών ή εμπορικών επιχειρήσεων· Εκτιμήσεις επιχειρηματικές· Συλλογή στοιχείων σε σχέση με επιχειρήσεις· Εμπορική διοίκηση αδειών εκμετάλλευσης προϊόντων και υπηρεσιών για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Συστηματοποίηση δεδομένων σε βάσεις δεδομένων· Διαπραγμάτευση και διακανονισμός εμπορικών συναλλαγών για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Δηλώσεων φορολογικών (Σύνταξη -)· Επιχειρηματικές έρευνες· Παροχή εμπορικών πληροφοριών και παροχή συμβουλών σε καταναλωτές [καταστήματα παροχής συμβουλών σε καταναλωτές]· Παροχή επιχειρηματικών συμβουλών· Διεξαγωγή ερευνών επιχειρήσεων· Συμβουλευτική για θέματα διοίκησης προσωπικού· Υπηρεσίες συγκέντρωσης αποκομμάτων ειδήσεων· Έρευνα αγοράς· Υπεργολαβική διοικητική διαχείριση επιχειρήσεων· Πληροφόρηση για επιχειρήσεις· Υπηρεσίες μάρκετινγκ· Σύνταξη στατιστικών· Επιχειρηματικές εκτιμήσεις και αξιολογήσεις σε επιχειρηματικά θέματα· Λογιστικός έλεγχος επιχειρήσεων· Υπηρεσίες συμβουλευτικής επιχειρήσεων· Προβλέψεις οικονομικές· Υπηρεσίες παροχής πληροφοριών μέσω υπολογιστή σε σχέση με εκτιμήσεις επιχειρηματικών ευκαιριών· Μηχανογραφημένες φορολογικές εκτιμήσεσις (προετοιμασία) λογιστική· Επιχειρήσεων (Συμβουλές για οργάνωση και διεύθυνση -)· Αναζήτηση χορηγίας· Διαχείρηση αρχείων πληροφορικής· Υπηρεσίες συμπλήρωσης φορολογικών δηλώσεων· Υπηρεσίες δημοσίων σχέσεων· Πρακτορεία εμπορικών πληροφοριών· Υπηρεσίες αξιολόγησης αγοράς· Υπηρεσίες πραγματογνωμοσύνης επιχειρήσεων· Λογιστικός έλεγχος επιχειρήσεων.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Business appraisal consultancy; Business research; Commercial intermediation services; Expert evaluations and reports relating to business matters; Market studies; Business management assistance; Provision of commercial and business contact information; Business efficiency expert services; Providing assistance in the management of industrial or commercial enterprises; Business appraisals; Business surveys; Commercial administration of the licensing of the goods and services of others; Systemization of information into computer databases; Negotiation and conclusion of commercial transactions for third parties; Tax preparation; Business inquiries; Commercial information and advice for consumers [consumer advice shop]; Business management consultancy; Conducting of business research; Personnel management consultancy; News clipping services; Market research; Outsourced administrative management for companies; Business information; Marketing; Compilation of statistics; Business appraisals and evaluations in business matters; Book-keeping; Professional business consultancy; Economic forecasting; Computerised information services to business opportunities appraisals; Computerised tax assessments (preparation of -) [accounting]; Business management and organization consultancy; Sponsorship search; Computerized file management; Tax filing services; Public relations services; Commercial information agency services; Market assessment services; Business expertise services; Business auditing.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Consultas sobre tasación de negocios; Búsquedas de negocios; Servicios de intermediación comercial [conserjería]; Evaluaciones e informes expertos relacionados con asuntos de negocios; Estudios de mercado; Asistencia en la dirección de negocios; Suministro de información comercial sobre contactos de negocios; Servicios de expertos en eficiencia empresarial; Prestación de asistencia en la gestión de empresas industriales o comerciales; Valoración de negocios comerciales; Peritajes para negocios; Gestión comercial de licencias de productos y servicios de terceros; Sistematización de información en bases de datos informáticas; Negociación y conclusión de transacciones comerciales para terceros; Elaboración de declaraciones tributarias; Indagaciones sobre negocios; Información y asesoramiento comerciales al consumidor; Consultoría sobre dirección de negocios; Realización de investigaciones sobre negocios; Consultoría sobre gestión de personal; Servicios de comunicados de prensa; Servicios de investigación de mercados; Gestión administrativa externalizada para empresas; Información sobre negocios; Marketing; Recopilación de estadísticas; Valoraciones en negocios comerciales y evaluaciones en asuntos de negocios; Contabilidad; Consultoría profesional sobre negocios comerciales; Previsiones económicas; Servicios de información informatizados para valorar oportunidades de negocio; Preparación de liquidaciones de impuestos computarizada (contabilidad); Consultoría sobre organización y dirección de negocios; Búsqueda de patrocinadores; Servicios de gestión informática de archivos; Servicio de cumplimentación y presentación de declaraciones fiscales; Servicios de relaciones públicas; Servicios de agencias de información comercial; Servicios de evaluación de mercados; Servicios de expertos en negocios; Auditoría empresarial.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ettevõtte hindamise konsultatsioonid; Äriuuringud; Kaubandusvahendusteenused; Ärialased eksperthinnangud ja aruanded; Turu-uuringud; Ärijuhtimisabi; Kaubandus- ja ärikontaktiinfo pakkumine; Äri efektiivsuse ekspertiisid; Tööstus- või kaubandusettevõtete juhtimisabi; Äritegevuse hindamine; Äriuuringud; Teiste omanike kaupade ja teenuste litsentsimise korraldamine äri eesmärgil; Info süstematiseerimine arvuti andmebaasides; Läbirääkimised ja äritehingute sõlmimine kolmandate poolte jaoks; Maksudokumentatsiooni koostamine; Ärialased päringud, küsitlused; Äriteave ja klientide äriline nõustamine [klientide nõustamise keskus]; Äritegevuse juhtimise konsultatsioonid; Äriuuringute läbiviimine; Personalijuhtimisalased konsultatsioonid; Pressiülevaateteenused; Turu-uuringud; Ettevõtete administratiivhaldus alltöövõtuna; Äriinfo, -teave; Turundus; Statistika koostamine; Äritegevuse hindamine ja ärialased hinnangud; Arvepidamine, raamatupidamine; Ärialased konsultatsiooniteenused; Majandusprognoosid; Ärivõimaluste hindamise info arvuti kaudu; Arvutipõhine maksudokumentatsiooni koostamine [arvepidamine]; Äritegevuse juhtimise ja korraldamise konsultatsioonid; Sponsorite otsimine; Arvutipõhine dokumendihaldus; Maksudeklaratsiooni esitamise teenused; Suhtekorraldusteenused; Kaubandusteabeagentuuride teenused; Turuhindamisteenused; Äriekspertiisid; Äri auditeerimine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Liiketoiminnan arviointiin liittyvä konsultointi; Liikkeenhoitoa koskeva tutkimus; Kaupalliset välityspalvelut; Liikeasioihin liittyvät asiantuntija-arvioinnit ja -raportit; Markkinatutkimukset; Avustaminen liiketoiminnan johtamisessa; Kaupallisten ja liiketoiminnallisten yhteystietojen tarjoaminen; Yritystehokkuutta koskevat asiantuntijapalvelut; Teollisten tai kaupallisten yritysten johtamiseen liittyvä avustaminen; Liiketoiminnan arviointi; Yritystutkimukset; Kaupallinen hallinnointi koskien toisten tavaroiden ja palveluiden lisensointia; Tietokantatietojen systematisointi; Kolmansille osapuolille suoritettavat neuvottelu- ja sopimusliiketoimet; Verotuksen valmistelupalvelut; Liikkeenhoitoa koskevat kyselyt; Kaupallinen tiedotus ja kuluttajaneuvonta; Liikkeenhoidon konsultointi; Yritystutkimuksen tekeminen; Henkilöstöhallintakonsultointi; Lehtileikepalvelut; Markkinatutkimus; Yrityshallintoon liittyvien tehtävien hoitaminen alihankintatyönä; Informaatio (Liiketoiminta -); Markkinointipalvelut; Tilastotietojen kerääminen; Yritysten arviointi ja evaluointi liikeasioissa; Yritysten tilintarkastus; Liiketoiminnan konsultointipalvelut; Talousennusteiden tekeminen; Liiketoimintamahdollisuuksien arviointeihin liittyvät tietokoneavusteiset tiedotuspalvelut; Tietokoneistettujen verotusarviointien valmistelu [laskentatoimi]; Liikkeenhoitoon ja organisaatioon liittyvä konsultointi; Sponsoroinnin etsintäpalvelut; Tietokonetiedostojen hallinta; Veroilmoitusten täyttäminen; Suhdetoimintapalvelut; Tietotoimistot, kaupalliset; Markkina-arviointipalvelut; Liiketoimintaa koskevat asiantuntijapalvelut; Yritysten tilintarkastus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Conseil en estimations commerciales; Recherches pour affaires; Services d'intermédiation commerciale [conciergerie]; Expertises et rapports d'experts liés à des questions commerciales; Études de marché; Aide à la direction des affaires; Informations en matière de contacts d'affaires et commerciaux; Services d'expertise en productivité d'entreprise; Fourniture d’assistance à la direction d’entreprises commerciales ou industrielles; Estimation en affaires commerciales; Enquêtes de conjoncture; Administration commerciale de licences de produits et de services de tiers; Systématisation d'informations dans des bases de données informatiques; Négociation et conclusion de transactions commerciales pour des tiers; Établissement de déclarations fiscales; Renseignements d'affaires; Informations et conseils commerciaux aux consommateurs; Consultation pour la direction des affaires; Réalisation de recherches commerciales; Services de conseils en gestion de personnel; Services de revues de presse; Étude de marché; Gestion administrative externalisée d'entreprises; Informations d'affaires; Marketing; Établissement de statistiques; Estimations et évaluations en matière commerciale; Comptabilité; Consultation professionnelle d'affaires; Prévisions économiques; Services d'informations informatisés pour évaluations d'opportunités d'affaires; Préparation de cotisations fiscales informatisée [comptabilité]; Conseils en organisation et direction des affaires; Recherche de parraineurs; Services de gestion informatisée de fichiers; Services de dépôt de déclaration fiscale; Services de relations publiques; Services d'agences d'informations commerciales; Services d'évaluation du marché; Services d'expertises en affaires commerciales; Audits d'entreprises [analyses commerciales].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Savjetovanje u vezi s poslovnim procjenama; Istraživanje za poslove; Usluge posredovanja u trgovini; Stručne procjene i izvještaji u svezi poslovnih pitanja; Istraživanja tržišta; Pomoć u vođenju poslova; Pružanje komercijalnih i poslovnih kontaktnih podataka; Usluge stručnjaka za poslovnu učinkovitost; Pružanje pomoći u području upravljanja poslovnim industrijskim ili komercijalnim pothvatima; Procjene komercijalnih poslova; Poslovna istraživanja; Komercijalno upravljanje u svezi licenci proizvoda i usluga trećih osoba; Sistematiziranje podataka za središnju kartoteku; Pregovaranje i zaključenje komercijalnih transakcija za treće osobe; Izračun poreza; Poslovi (obavještenja o poslovima); Potrošači [pružanje komercijalni savjeta i informacija potrošačima]; Konzultacije u svezi vođenje poslova; Vođenje poslovnog istraživanja; Savjetovanje o osoblju; Tisak (praćenje tiska); Istraživanje tržišta; Vanjsko administrativno upravljanje za tvrtke; Poslovne obavijesti; Marketing; Izrada statističkih podataka; Poslovne procjene i valorizacije u vezi poslovnih aktivnosti; Vođenje knjiga; Stručne poslovne konzultacije; Predviđanje gospodarske situacije; Računalne informativne usluge za procjene poslovnih prilika; Računalni izračun poreza (priprema za -) [računovodstvo]; Savjeti o organizaciji i vođenju poslova; Traženje sponzorstva; Vođenje informatičkih kartoteka; Usluge prijave poreza; Usluge odnosa s javnošću; Agencije za komercijalne obavijesti; Usluge procjene tržišta; Usluge poslovne ekspertize; Vođenje knjiga.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Vállalati értékbecslési konzultáció; Kutatások ügyletekkel kapcsolatban; Kereskedelmi közvetítői szolgáltatások; Üzleti ügyekkel kapcsolatos szakértői értékelések és beszámolók; Piaci tanulmányok; Segítségnyújtás üzleti tevékenységek menedzsmentjében; Kereskedelmi és üzleti kapcsolattartási adatok biztosítása; Üzleti hatékonysági szakértő szolgáltatásai; Segítségnyújtás ipari vagy kereskedelmi vállalatok menedzsmentjéhez; Üzleti értékelések; Üzleti felmérések; Áruk és szolgáltatások engedélyezésének kereskedelmi ügyintézése; Információk számítógépes adatbázisokba való rendezése; Kereskedelmi tranzakciók tárgyalása és megállapodások kötése harmadik fél számára; Adóbevallások elkészítése; Üzleti tájékoztatás, információnyújtás; Kereskedelmi információ és tanácsadás fogyasztóknak [fogyasztói tanácsadás]; Üzletvezetési konzultáció; Üzleti kutatás lebonyolítása; Konzultáció személyzeti kérdésekben; Sajtófigyelés; Piackutatás; Kiszervezett vállalatirányítás; Üzleti információk; Marketing szolgáltatások; Statisztikák összeállítása; Üzleti becslések és értékelések üzleti ügyekben; Üzleti könyvvizsgálat; Üzleti konzultációs szolgáltatások; Gazdasági előrejelzések; Számítógépesített információs szolgáltatások üzleti lehetőségek értékeléséhez; Számítógépesített adóalap megállapítás [számvitel]; Üzletszervezési és üzletvezetési tanácsadás; Szponzorok felkutatása; Számítógépes fájlkezelés, adatkezelés; Adóbevallás-benyújtási szolgáltatások; Közönségszolgálati szolgáltatások; Kereskedelmi információs ügynökségek; Piacértékelési szolgáltatások; Üzleti szakértői szolgáltatások; Üzleti könyvvizsgálat.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">consulenza in materia di valutazioni commerciali; ricerche per affari; servizi di intermediazione commerciale; valutazioni e relazioni di esperti in materia di questioni aziendali.; ricerche di mercato; assistenza nella gestione degli affari; fornitura di informazioni in materia di contatti d'affari e commerciali; perizie in materia di affari; assistenza nella gestione di imprese industriali o commerciali; Valutazioni (Affari -); indagini (Commerciali -); Amministrazione commerciale di licenze di prodotti e di servizi di terzi; sistemazione di informazioni in banche dati informatiche; negoziazione e conclusione di transazioni commerciali per conto di terzi; stesura di dichiarazioni fiscali; ragguagli d'affari; informazioni e consulenza commerciale ai consumatori; consulenza per la gestione degli affari; conduzione di ricerche commerciali; servizi di consulenza in materia di gestione del personale; servizi di rassegne stampa; ricerche di marketing; gestione amministrativa esternalizzata delle imprese; informazioni di affari; marketing; elaborazione di statistiche; valutazioni aziendali e valutazioni in questioni aziendali; contabilità; consultazione professionale di affari; previsioni economiche; Servizi computerizzati di informazione per la valutazione di opportunità commerciali; valutazioni di imposta computerizzate (preparazione di -) [contabilità]; servizi di consulenza per l'organizzazione e la gestione degli affari; ricerca di sponsor; gestione di archivi informatici; servizi di assistenza per la dichiarazione dei redditi; valutazioni in affari commerciali; relazioni pubbliche; servizi di agenzie di informazioni commerciali; consulenza in materia di valutazioni di mercato; servizi di perizie aziendali; verifica di conti; servizi di valutazioni di mercato.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Verslo vertinimo konsultacijos; Verslo tyrimai; Komercinio tarpininkavimo paslaugos; Ekspertų vertinimai ir ataskaitos verslo klausimais; Rinkos nagrinėjimas; Verslo vadybos pagalba; Komercinės ir verslo kontaktų informacijos teikimas; Verslo efektyvumo (veiksmingumo) specialistų paslaugos; Pagalbos teikimas pramonės arba prekybos įmonių vadybos srityje; Verslo operacijų įvertinimas; Verslo apklausos; Trečiųjų asmenų prekių ir paslaugų licencijavimo komercinis administravimas; Informacijos sisteminimas kompiuterinėse duomenų bazėse; Prekybos sandorių derybos ir susitarimai (tretiesiems asmenims); Mokesčių apskaičiavimas; Verslo patikrinimai; Komercinė informacija ir patarimai vartotojams [konsultacijų teikimas]; Verslo vadybos konsultacijos; Verslo tyrimų vykdymas; Personalo vadybos konsultacijos; Naujienų apžvalgų paslaugos; Rinkos tyrinėjimas; Užsakomosios administracinio valdymo paslaugos įmonėms; Verslo informacija; Rinkodara; Statistinių duomenų rinkimas; Verslo operacijų įvertinimas ir vertinimai verslo srityje; Buhalterinė apskaita; Verslo specialistų konsultacijos; Ekonominis prognozavimas; Kompiuterizuotos verslo galimybių vertinimo informavimo paslaugos; Kompiuterizuoto mokesčių apskaičiavimo įvertinimo paruošimas [apskaita]; Verslo vadybos ir organizavimo konsultacijos; Rėmėjų paieška; Kompiuterizuotas rinkmenų (bylų) tvarkymas; Mokesčių deklaracijų pildymas; Viešųjų ryšių paslaugos; Komercinės informacijos agentūrų paslaugos; Rinkos vertinimo paslaugos; Verslo specialistų paslaugos; Verslo auditas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Uzņēmējdarbības novērtēšanas konsultācijas; Pētījumi darījumu jomā; Komercstarpniecības pakalpojumi; Ekspertu novērtējumi un ziņojumi par uzņēmējdarbības jautājumiem; Tirgus izpēte; Atbalsta sniegšana uzņēmējdarbības vadībā; Komerciālās informācijas un uzņēmumu kontaktinformācijas sniegšana; Ekspertu pakalpojumi uzņēmējdarbības efektivitātes novērtēšanā; Palīdzības sniegšana rūpniecības vai tirdzniecības uzņēmumu vadības jomā; Uzņēmumu novērtēšana; Uzņēmējdarbības apskats; Preču un pakalpojumu licencēšanas komerciālā vadība; Informācijas sistematizēšana datoru datubāzēs; Sarunu vešana un komercdarījumu kārtošana trešo personu interesēs; Nodokļu aprēķināšanas pakalpojumi; Uzņēmējdarbības uzziņu sniegšana; Komerciālas informācijas un padomu sniegšana patērētājiem par preču un pakalpojumu izvēli; Konsultāciju sniegšana uzņēmējdarbības vadībā; Uzņēmējdarbības pētījumu veikšana; Konsultāciju sniegšana personālvadībā; Ziņu apkopošanas pakalpojumi; Tirgus pētījumi; Ārpakalpojumu nodrošināšana uzņēmumu administratīvās vadības jomā; Darījumu informācijas sniegšana; Mārketinga pakalpojumi; Statistikas apkopošana; Uzņēmējdarbības novērtēšana un uzņēmējdarbības jautājumu izvērtēšana; Grāmatvedības pakalpojumi; Profesionālo konsultāciju sniegšana darījumu jomā; Ekonomiskā prognozēšana; Datorizēti informācijas pakalpojumi saistībā ar uzņēmējdarbības iespēju novērtēšanu; Datorizēta nodokļu deklarāciju sagatavošana [grāmatvedība]; Konsultāciju sniegšana darījumu vadīšanā un organizēšanā; Sponsoru meklēšana; Datorizēta failu pārvaldība; Nodokļu deklarēšanas pakalpojumi; Sabiedrisko attiecību pakalpojumi; Komercinformācijas aģentūru pakalpojumi; Tirgus vērtējuma pakalpojumi; Uzņēmējdarbības ekspertīžu pakalpojumi; Uzņēmējdarbības audita pakalpojumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Konsultazzjoni dwar stima tan-negozju; Riċerka dwar negozju; Servizzi ta' intermedjazzjoni kummerċjali; Evalwazzjonijiet esperti u rapporti dwar affarijiet ta' negozju; Studji tas-suq; Assistenza fil-ġestjoni ta' attivitajiet tan-negozju; Forniment ta' informazzjoni ta' kuntatt kummerċjali u tan-negozju; Servizzi esperti dwar l-effiċjenza tan-negozju; Għoti ta’ assistenza fil-ġestjoni ta’ intrapriżi industrijali jew kummerċjali; Stimi ta' negozji; Stħarriġ dwar in-negozju; Servizzi ta' amministrazzjoni kummerċjali ta' ħaddieħor, għal-liċenzjar ta' oġġetti u servizzi; Is-sistematizzazzjoni ta' informazzjoni f'dejtabejżis tal-kompjuter; Negozjar u soluzzjoni ta' transazzjonijiet kummerċjali għal terzi persuni; Servizzi ta' preparazzjoni tat-taxxa; Inkjesti dwar negozju; Konsumaturi (Tagħrif kummerċjali u pariri għal -) [ċentru ta' pariri lill-konsumatur]; Konsulenza fil-ġestjoni ta' negozju; It-tmexxija tar-riċerka ta' negozji; Konsulenza dwar il-ġestjoni tal-personàl; Servizzi ta' qtugħ ta' siltiet ta' aħbarijiet; Riċerka tas-suq; Ġestjoni amministrattiva esternalizzata għall-kumpaniji; Informazzjoni dwar negozju; Servizzi ta' kummerċjalizzazzjoni; Il-kumpilazzjoni ta' statistika; Stimi tan-negozji u evalwazzjonijiet f'affarijiet tan-negozji; Il-verifika tan-negozju; Servizzi ta' konsulenza dwar in-negozju; Tbassir ekonomiku; Servizzi ta' informazzjoni kompjuterizzati għal valutazzjonijiet ta' opportunitajiet tan-negozju; Evalwazzjonijiet kompjuterizzati tat-taxxa (Preparazzjoni tal- -) [kontabilità]; Konsulenza dwar il-ġestjoni u l-organizzazzjoni ta' negozju; Tiftix għal sponsorizzazzjoni; Il-ġestjoni kompjuterizzata ta' fajls; Servizzi ta' ffajljar tat-taxxa; Servizzi tar-relazzjonijiet pubbliċi; Aġenziji ta' informazzjoni kummerċjali; Servizzi tal-valutazzjoni tas-suq; Servizzi ta' esperti tan-negozju; Il-verifika tan-negozju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Evaluatie op zakelijk gebied; Zakelijk onderzoek; Zakelijke bemiddeling; Evaluaties (Deskundige -) en rapporten met betrekking tot zaken; Marktonderzoek; Hulp bij de leiding van zaken; Verschaffen van informatie op het gebied van zakelijke en handelscontacten; Expertises in bedrijfsefficiëntie; Ondersteuning bij het beheer van industriële of commerciële ondernemingen; Evaluaties op zakelijk gebied; Zakelijke bedrijfsinspecties; Zakelijke administratie van licenties op producten en diensten van derden; Systematisering in een centraal bestand van gegevens; Onderhandeling en afsluiting van commerciële transacties voor derden; Het invullen van belastingformulieren; Inlichtingen over zaken; Handelsinformatie en -adviezen voor consumenten; Advisering inzake bedrijfsvoering; Verrichten van commercieel-zakelijk onderzoek; Advisering met betrekking tot personeel; Knipseldiensten; Marktonderzoek; Outsourcing van administratief beheer voor ondernemingen; Verschaffen van informatie over commerciële zaken; Marketing; Opstellen van statistieken; Evaluaties (Zakelijke -) en evaluaties inzake zakelijke aangelegenheden; Boekhouding; Professionele consultatie op het gebied van zaken; Economische prognoses; Geautomatiseerde informatie met betrekking tot inschatting van zakelijke mogelijkheden; Geautomatiseerde belastingaanslagen (voorbereiding van -) [boekhouden]; Bedrijfsorganisatorische en -bestuurlijke advisering; Sponsorwerving; Beheer van gegevensbestanden; Invullen van belastingformulieren; Public relationsdiensten; Diensten van agentschappen voor handelsinlichtingen; Marktevaluati; Commerciële bedrijfsexpertise; Zakelijke analyse van bedrijven [auditing].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Konsultacje w dziedzinie wycen biznesowych; Badania w zakresie biznesu; Usługi pośrednictwa w handlu; Specjalistyczne wyceny i raporty w zakresie spraw dotyczących działalności gospodarczej; Badania rynkowe; Pomoc w zarządzaniu działalnością gospodarczą; Dostarczanie informacji dotyczących kontaktów handlowych i biznesowych; Usługi ekspertów w zakresie efektywności biznesowej; Wsparcie w dziedzinie zarządzania przedsiębiorstwami przemysłowymi lub handlowymi; Wyceny handlowe; Badania statystyczne przedsiębiorstw; Zarządzanie handlowe w zakresie koncesjonowania dóbr i usług na rzecz osób trzecich; Systematyzacja danych w komputerowych bazach danych; Negocjowanie i rozliczanie transakcji handlowych dla osób trzecich; Przygotowywanie zeznań podatkowych; Badania dotyczące działalności gospodarczej; Handlowe informacje i porady udzielane konsumentom [punkty informacji konsumenckiej]; Doradztwo w zakresie zarządzania biznesem; Przeprowadzanie badań w zakresie działalności gospodarczej; Doradztwo w zakresie zarządzania personelem; Usługi przeglądu prasy; Badania rynkowe; Obsługa administracyjna firm na zlecenie; Informacja o działalności gospodarczej; Usługi marketingowe; Statystyczne zestawienia; Biznesowe oceny i wyceny w sprawach handlowych; Audyt działalności gospodarczej; Usługi doradztwa w zakresie działalności gospodarczej; Ekonomiczne prognozy; Skomputeryzowane usługi informacyjne w zakresie ocen możliwości biznesowych; Skomputeryzowane ustalanie wysokości podatku [rachunkowość]; Doradztwo w zakresie organizowania i prowadzenia działalności gospodarczej; Poszukiwania w zakresie patronatu; Komputerowe zarządzanie plikami; Usługi wypełniania zeznań podatkowych; Usługi public relations; Agencje informacji handlowej; Usługi oceny rynku; Usługi w zakresie ekspertyzy dotyczącej działalności gospodarczej; Audyt działalności gospodarczej.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Consultoria relativa a avaliações comerciais; Pesquisas comerciais; Serviços de intermediação comercial; Avaliações e relatórios de peritos relacionados com assuntos empresariais; Estudos de mercado; Assistência na direção de negócios comerciais; Fornecimento de informações em matéria de contatos comerciais; Serviços de peritagens em negócios comerciais; Prestação de assistência na gestão de empresas industriais ou comerciais; Avaliações em negócios comerciais; Inquéritos comerciais; Administração comercial do licenciamento de produtos e serviços para terceiros [serviços de]; Sistematização de informação numa base de dados informática; Negociação e conclusão de transações comerciais para terceiros; Elaboração de declarações fiscais; Inquéritos de negócios comerciais; Serviços de aconselhamento e informação comercial aos consumidores [loja do consumidor]; Consultadoria para direção de negócios comerciais; Realização de pesquisas de negócios; Consultadoria em gestão de pessoal; Serviços de revistas de imprensa; Estudos de mercado; Gestão administrativa por outsourcing para empresas; Informações comerciais; Marketing; Compilação de estatísticas; Estimativas e avaliações comerciais em matéria de negócios comerciais; Contabilidade; Consultadoria profissional em negócios comerciais; Previsões económicas; Serviços de informação computorizada relacionada com avaliações de oportunidades de negócios; Preparação de declarações de impostos informatizadas [contabilidade]; Consultadoria em organização e direção de negócios comerciais; Angariação de patrocínios; Gestão de ficheiros informáticos; Serviços de declarações fiscais; Serviços de relações públicas; Serviços de agências de informações comerciais; Serviços de avaliação de mercados; Serviços de peritos em negócios comerciais; Auditorias de empresas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Consultanță cu privire la evaluări ale afacerilor; Cercetări pentru afaceri; Servicii de intermediere comercială; Evaluări și rapoarte efectuate de experți, referitoare la afaceri; Studii de piață; Asistență în conducerea afacerilor; Furnizare de informații de contact comerciale și de afaceri; Servicii de expertiză în materie de eficiența afacerilor; Asistență în domeniul administrării întreprinderilor industriale sau comerciale; Estimare în afaceri comerciale; Anchete de conjunctură; Administrarea comercială a licențelor produselor și a serviciilor pentru terți; Sistematizarea informațiilor în fișiere electronice; Negociere și încheiere de tranzacții comerciale pentru terți; Declarații fiscale (Întocmire de -); Date referitoare la afaceri; Informații și asistență comerciale pentru consumatori; Consultanță pentru conducerea afacerilor; Efectuare de cercetări de afaceri; Consultanță pentru probleme legate de personal; Servicii de revista presei; Studii de piață; Gestiune administrativă externalizată pentru companii; Informații pentru afaceri; Servicii de marketing; Compilații statistice; Estimări și evaluări de afaceri în materie de aspecte comerciale; Contabilitate; Consultanță în afaceri; Previziuni economice; Servicii de informații computerizate cu privire la evaluarea oportunităților de afaceri; Pregătirea evaluării computerizate în vedera impozitării [contabilitate]; Consultanță în managementul și organizarea afacerilor; Căutare de sponsorizare; Gestionare de fișiere informatice; Servicii de depunere a declarațiilor fiscale; Servicii de relații cu publicul; Agenții de informații comerciale; Servicii în domeniul evaluării de piață; Servicii de expertiză în afaceri; Contabilitate.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Konzultácie v oblasti oceňovania podnikov; Obchodný alebo podnikateľský výskum; Obchodné sprostredkovateľské služby; Odborné hodnotenia a správy v obchodných záležitostiach; Prieskum trhu; Pomoc pri riadení obchodnej činnosti; Poskytovanie obchodných alebo podnikateľských kontaktných informácií; Odborné posudky efektívnosti podnikov; Poskytovanie pomoci pri riadení priemyselných alebo obchodných podnikov; Obchodné odhady; Obchodné alebo podnikateľské prieskumy; Obchodná správa licencií výrobkov a služieb (pre tretie osoby); Zoraďovanie údajov v počítačových databázach; Vyjednávanie a uzatváranie obchodných transakcií pre tretie osoby; Vypracovávanie daňových priznaní; Poskytovanie obchodných alebo podnikateľských informácií; Obchodné informácie a rady spotrebiteľom pri výbere tovarov a služieb; Poradenstvo pri riadení podnikov; Vedenie obchodných prieskumov; Personálne poradenstvo; Prehľad tlače (výstrižkové služby); Marketingový prieskum; Externé administratívne riadenie podnikov; Obchodné alebo podnikateľské informácie; Marketing; Zostavovanie štatistík; Obchodné odhady a hodnotenia v obchodných záležitostiach; Účtovníctvo; Odborné obchodné alebo podnikateľské poradenstvo; Hospodárske (ekonomické) predpovede; Informačné služby vykonávané pomocou počítača v oblasti hodnotenia obchodných príležitostí; Vypracovanie daňových výmerov pomocou počítača [účtovníctvo]; Poradenstvo pri organizovaní a riadení obchodnej činnosti; Vyhľadávanie sponzorov; Správa počítačových súborov; Podávanie daňových priznaní; Vzťahy s verejnosťou (public relations); Komerčné informačné kancelárie; Služby v oblasti hodnotenia trhu; Služby v oblasti obchodnej expertízy; Obchodné alebo podnikové audity (revízia účtov).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Svetovanje v zvezi s poslovnim vrednotenjem; Raziskave na področju poslovanja; Storitve poslovnega posredovanja; Strokovne ocene in poročila v zvezi s poslovnimi zadevami; Tržne študije; Pomoč pri upravljanju poslovnih dejavnosti; Nudenje komercialnih in poslovnih kontaktnih informacij; Strokovne storitve na področju poslovne učinkovitosti; Pomoč pri vodenju industrijskih ali komercialnih podjetij; Poslovne cenitve; Poslovne raziskave; Poslovna administracija licenciranja blaga in storitev drugih; Sistematizacija informacij v računalniške baze podatkov; Pogajanje in poravnave komercialnih transakcij za tretje osebe; Davčne napovedi; Poslovne poizvedbe; Komercialne informacije in svetovanje za potrošnike (poslovalnica za svetovanje potrošnikom); Poslovodno svetovanje; Izvajanje poslovnih raziskav; Svetovanje pri upravljanju s človeškimi viri; Raziskovanje in zbiranje podatkov iz medijev; Tržne raziskave; Oddajanje upravnega poslovodenja za podjetja v izvajanje zunanjim izvajalcem; Poslovne informacije; Storitve trženja; Sestavljanje statistik; Poslovne cenitve in ocenjevanje poslovnih zadev; Poslovno revidiranje; Storitve na področju poslovnega svetovanja; Ekonomske prognoze; Računalniške informacijske storitve za ocene poslovnih priložnosti; Priprava za računalniško ocenitev davka (računovodstvo); Poslovodno in organizacijsko svetovanje; Iskanje sponzorstva; Vodenje podatkovnih baz; Storitve davčnih napovedi; Storitve na področju odnosov z javnostmi; Agencije za poslovne informacije; Storitve tržnega ocenjevanja; Storitve poslovnih strokovnjakov; Poslovno revidiranje.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Konsultation rörande företagsvärdering; Företagsundersökningar; Kommersiella förmedlingstjänster; Expertutvärderingar och -rapporter avseende företagsfrågor; Marknadsstudier; Assistans vid förvaltning av affärsverksamheter; Upplåtande av kommersiella och affärsmässiga kontaktuppgifter; Experttjänster i företagseffektivitet; Tillhandahållande av stöd vid ledning av industri- eller handelsföretag; Affärsvärderingar; Undersökningar avseende företag; Kommersiell administration av licensiering av varor och tjänster för andra; Systematisering av information i databaser; Förhandlingar och överenskommelser om kommersiella transaktioner för tredje part; Deklarationsbyråer; Undersökningar avseende företags- eller affärsverksamhet; Rådgivning för konsumenter (kommersiell information och -) [konsumentrådgivningsbutik]; Konsulttjänster avseende management; Genomförande av företagsundersökningar; Konsultationer avseende personaladministration; Nyhetsklippningstjänster; Marknadsundersökningar; Administrativa tjänster för företag (outsourcing); Företagsinformation; Marketing; Sammanställande av statistik; Affärsvärderingar och utvärderingar i affärsfrågor; Bokföring; Professionella företagskonsultationer; Ekonomisk prognostisering; Datoriserade informationstjänster i samband med värdering av affärsmöjligheter; Förberedande av datoriserad skattetaxering [bokföring]; Konsultationer avseende företagsledning och -organisation; Sökande av sponsring; Datoriserad registerhantering; Skatteadministreringstjänster; Public relationstjänster; Byråer för kommersiell information; Marknadsbedömningstjänster; Företagsexpertistjänster; Företagsrevision.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>36</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Посредничество при отпусане кредити; Услуги за оценка на риска при инвестиране; Финансова информация; Уреждане на финансиране за строителни проекти; Финансови консултации; Борсови котировки; Управление на капитали; Управление на недвижимо имущество; Организиране на кампании за набиране на средства за благотворителни цели; Застрахователно посредничество; Данъчни оценки; Предоставяне на финансова информация чрез уебсайт; Управление на активи; Оценяване на риска на финансови и застрахователни проекти; Оценяване на произведения на изкуството; Банково дело; Услуги за оценяване на интелектуална собственост; Оценка на движимо имущество; Брокерски услуги; Финансови оценки; Оценяване на недвижимо имущество; Агенции за недвижимо имущество; Финансови оценки; Финансово оценяване и анализ; Попечителство; Услуги за финансово оценяване; Ликвидация на предприятия [финансови сделки]; Информация в областта на застраховането; Оценяване на антики; Агенции за възстановяване на задължения; Посреднически услуги при сделки с недвижимо имущество; Оценки (Финансови -) [застраховане, банково дело, недвижимо имущество]; Борсово посредничество; Управление на жилищни и административни сгради; Набиране на дарения с благотворителна цел; Услуги на борсови посредници; Консултантски услуги по дългове; Застрахователни консултации; Събиране на наеми; Финансово управление на плащания за възстановяване на средства за трети лица; Финансови брокерски услуги пред митници; Финансови анализи; Оценяване на бижута.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Služby úvěrové kanceláře; Hodnocení investičního rizika (služby); Finanční informace; Zajištění financování stavebních projektů; Finanční poradenství; Burzovní kotace; Finanční řízení; Správa nemovitostí; Pořádání dobročinných sbírek; Zprostředkování pojištění; Daňové odhady; Poskytování finančních informací prostřednictvím webových stránek; Správa aktiv; Pojistně-matematické služby; Oceňování uměleckých děl; Bankovnictví; Oceňování duševního vlastnictví; Oceňování movitého majetku; Makléřství, jednatelství; Finanční oceňování; Oceňování nemovitostí; Služby realitní kanceláře; Finanční odhady; Finanční oceňování a analýzy; Správa majetku; Služby finančního hodnocení; Finanční služby v oblasti likvidace podniků; Informace o pojištění; Oceňování starožitností; Služby agentury vymáhající pohledávky; Zprostředkování v oblasti nemovitostí; Finanční hodnocení [pojištění, bankovnictví, nemovitosti]; Obchodování s cennými papíry; Správa bytového domu; Pořádání sbírek; Makléřské služby; Dluhové poradenství; Poradenství v oblasti pojištění; Inkasování nájemného; Finanční řízení výplat náhrad pro jiné osoby; Finanční služby ve formě zprostředkování celního odbavení; Finanční analýza; Oceňování šperků.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Kreditgivning; Vurdering af investeringsrisiko; Finansiel information; Arrangering af finansiering til anlægsprojekter; Finansiel rådgivning; Fondsbørsnoteringer; Finansiel styring; Forvaltning af fast ejendom; Indsamlinger til velgørenhed; Forsikringsmæglervirksomhed; Vurderinger af skatteforhold; Stillen finansiel information til rådighed via et websted; Forvaltning af aktiver; Aktuarvirksomhed; Værdifastsættelse af kunst; Bankvirksomhed; Værdiansættelse af intellektuel ejendom; Vurdering af løsøregenstande; Finansiel mæglervirksomhed; Finansiel vurdering; Vurdering af fast ejendom; Ejendomsmæglerbureauvirksomhed; Tjenesteydelser vedrørende finansiel vurdering; Finansiel vurdering og analyse; Forvaltning af båndlagt kapital; Finansielle vurderinger; Finansiel bistand ved afvikling af virksomheder; Information om forsikringer; Antikvitetsvurdering; Inkassovirksomhed; Ejendomsmæglervirksomhed; Finansielle vurderinger [forsikring, bankvirksomhed, fast ejendom]; Fondsbørsmæglervirksomhed; Forvaltning af lejlighedskomplekser; Organisering af pengeindsamlinger; Børsmæglervirksomhed; Rådgivning om gæld; Rådgivning vedrørende forsikringsforhold; Lejeopkrævning [husleje]; Finansiel styring af refusionsprogrammer for andre; Finansielle toldklareringstjenester; Finansielle analyser; Vurdering af smykker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Dienstleistungen von Kreditauskunfteien; Anlage-Risikobewertung; Erteilung von Finanzauskünften; Organisation von Finanzierungen für Bauprojekte; Finanzielle Beratung; Börsenkursnotierung; Vermögensverwaltung; Immobilienverwaltung; Sammeln von Spenden für Wohltätigkeitszwecke; Vermittlung von Versicherungen; Erstellung von Steuergutachten und -schätzungen; Bereitstellung von finanziellen Informationen über eine Website; Anlagenverwaltung; Dienstleistungen eines Aktuars; Schätzung von Kunstgegenständen; Bankgeschäfte; Finanzielle Bewertung von geistigen Eigentumsrechten; Bewertung von beweglichem Vermögen; Dienstleistungen eines Maklers; Finanzielle Bewertung; Schätzung von Immobilien; Dienstleistungen von Immobilienbüros; Finanzielle Begutachtungsdienste; Erstellen von Finanzgutachten und -analysen; Vermögensverwaltung durch Treuhänder; Monetäre Schätzungen; Geschäftsliquidationen [Finanzdienstleistungen]; Erteilung von Auskünften in Versicherungsangelegenheiten; Schätzung von Antiquitäten; Dienstleistungen von Inkassobüros; Dienstleistungen eines Immobilienmaklers; Finanzielle Schätzung [Versicherungs-, Bank-, Grundstücksangelegenheiten]; Dienstleistungen eines Wertpapiermaklers; Wohngebäudeverwaltung; Organisation von Geldspendenaktionen; Dienstleistungen eines Börsenmaklers; Schuldnerberatung; Versicherungsberatung; Einziehen von Miet- und Pachterträgen; Finanzielle Verwaltung von Kostenerstattungszahlungen für Dritte; Finanzdienstleistungen bei der Zollabfertigung für Dritte; Finanzanalysen; Schätzen von Schmuck.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες πρακτορείων πίστωσης· Υπηρεσίες εκτίμησης επενδυτικών κινδύνων· Πληροφόρηση χρηματοοικονομική· Οργάνωση χρηματοδότησης για κατασκευαστικά έργα· Συμβουλευτική χρηματοοικονομική· Χρηματιστηρίου (Δημοσίευση τιμών -)· Χρηματοοικονομική διαχείριση· Διαχείριση ακινήτων· Φιλανθρωπικοί έρανοι· Μεσιτεία ασφαλιστική· Εκτιμήσεις φορολογικές· Παροχή χρηματοοικονομικών πληροφοριών μέσω δικτυακού τόπου· Διαχείριση στοιχείων ενεργητικού· Αναλογιστική· Εκτίμηση έργων τέχνης· Τραπεζιτικές υπηρεσίες· Υπηρεσίες εκτίμησης πνευματικής ιδιοκτησίας· Εκτίμηση κινητών περιουσιακών στοιχείων· Μεσιτεία· Χρηματοοικονομική αξιολόγηση· Υπηρεσίες αποτίμησης ακίνητης περιουσίας· Κτηματομεσιτικά γραφεία· Υπηρεσίες οικονομικών/χρηματοπιστωτικών εκτιμήσεων· Χρηματοοικονομική αξιολόγηση και ανάλυση· Καταπιστευτικές υπηρεσίες· Χρηματο/οικονομικές αποτιμήσεις· Υπηρεσίες εκκαθάρισης επιχειρήσεων, χρηματοπιστωτικές· Πληροφόρηση για ασφάλειες· Εκτίμηση αντικών· Πρακτορεία είσπραξης οφειλών· Μεσιτεία ακινήτων· Εκτιμήσεις χρηματοοικονομικές [ασφάλειες, τράπεζες,ακίνητα]· Χρηματιστηρίου (Μεσιτεία -)· Διαχείριση πολυκατοικιών· Έρανοι· Μεσιτεία χρηματιστηρίου· Συμβουλετική για χρέος· Συμβουλευτική για ασφάλειες· Είσπραξη ενοικίων· Χρηματοοικονομική διαχείριση εξόφλησης πληρωμών για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Οικονομικές υπηρεσίες τελωνειακής μεσιτείας· Ανάλυση χρηματοοικονομική· Κοσμημάτων (Εκτίμηση -).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Credit bureau services; Investment risk assessment services; Financial information; Arranging finance for construction projects; Financial consultancy; Stock exchange quotations; Financial management; Real estate management; Charitable fund raising; Insurance brokerage; Fiscal valuation; Providing financial information via a web site; Asset management; Actuarial services; Art appraisal; Banking; Intellectual property valuation services; Evaluation of chattels; Brokerage; Financial evaluation; Real estate appraisal; Real estate agency services; Valuation services; Financial evaluation and analysis; Trusteeship; Financial valuation services; Business liquidation services, financial; Insurance information; Antique appraisal; Debt collection agency services; Real estate brokerage; Financial evaluation [insurance, banking, real estate]; Securities brokerage; Apartment house management; Organization of monetary collections; Stock brokerage services; Debt advisory services; Insurance consultancy; Rent collection; Financial management of reimbursement payments for others; Financial customs brokerage services; Financial analysis; Jewellery appraisal.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de agencias de crédito; Evaluación de riesgos para inversiones; Información financiera; Organización de la financiación de proyectos de construcción; Consultoría financiera; Cotizaciones en bolsa; Gestión financiera; Administración de bienes inmuebles; Recaudación de fondos de beneficencia; Corretaje de seguros; Servicios de estimaciones fiscales; Suministro de información financiera por sitios web; Gestión de activos; Servicios actuariales; Tasación de obras de arte; Servicios bancarios; Servicios de tasación de la propiedad intelectual; Valoración de bienes muebles; Corretaje; Estimaciones financieras; Tasación de bienes inmuebles; Servicios de agencias inmobiliarias; Servicios de valoración; Valoraciones y análisis financieros; Servicios fiduciarios; Valoraciones financieras; Servicios de liquidación de empresas [finanzas]; Información en materia de seguros; Tasación de antigüedades; Servicios de agencias de cobro de deudas; Corretaje de bienes inmuebles; Evaluación financiera [seguros, bancos, bienes inmuebles]; Corretaje de valores; Administración de edificios de viviendas; Organización de colectas financieras; Corretaje de valores bursátiles; Asesoramiento sobre deudas; Consultoría sobre seguros; Cobro de alquileres; Gestión financiera de pagos de reembolso para terceros; Servicios financieros de correduría aduanera; Análisis financiero; Tasación de joyas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Krediidikontoriteenused, krediidibürooteenused; Investeerimisriski hindamise teenused; Finantsteave, -info, rahandusteave, -info; Ehitusprojektide rahastamise korraldamine; Finantskonsultatsioonid; Väärtpaberite koteerimine, fondibörsikoteeringud; Finantsjuhtimine; Kinnisvara haldamine, juhtimine; Heategevusfondide korjandused, heategevuskorjandused; Kindlustusvahendus; Fiskaalhinnangud, rahandushinnangud; Veebilehe kaudu finantsinfo pakkumine; Varahaldus; Kindlustusstatistilised teenused; Kunstiteoste, taieste hindamine; Pangandus; Intellektuaalomandi hindamise teenused; Vallasvara hindamise teenused; Maaklerlus, vahendus, vahendamine; Finantsilised hinnangud; Kinnisvara hindamine; Kinnisvaraagentuuriteenused; Finantsilise hindamise teenused; Finantshindamine ja -analüüs; Fidutsiaarteenused, usaldusisikuteenused, usaldusteenused; Finantshindamised; Ettevõtete finantsilised likvideerimisteenused; Kindlustusteave, -info; Antiikesemete hindamine; Võlgade sissenõudeagentuuride teenused; Kinnisvaramaaklerlus; Finantstegevuse hinnangud, rahandushinnangud [kindlustus-, pangandus-, kinnisvaratehingud]; Väärtpaberite vahendamine; Kortermajade haldamine; Korjanduste korraldamine, läbiviimine; Aktsiavahendus; Võlanõustamisteenused; Kindlustuskonsultatsioonid; Üürikogumine, rendikogumine; Hüvitismaksete finantshaldusteenus; Finantsilised tollimaaklerlusteenused; Finants-, rahandusanalüüsid; Juveelide hindamine, juveeltoodete, väärisehete hindamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Luottokonttorit; Sijoitusten riskinarviointipalvelut; Rahoitusneuvonta; Rahoituksen järjestäminen rakennushankkeita varten; Rahoituskonsultointi; Pörssinoteeraukset; Varainhoito; Omaisuuden (Kiinteistö-) hoito; Hyväntekeväisyyskeräykset; Vakuutusmeklarointi; Veroarviointi; Taloudellisten tietojen tarjoaminen verkkosivuston kautta; Varainhoito; Aktuaari-, vakuutusmatemaatikkopalvelut; Taide-esineiden arvonmääritys; Pankkitoiminta; Immateriaaliomaisuuden arviointipalvelut; Irtaimiston arviointi; Meklaritoiminta; Rahataloudellinen arviointi; Kiinteistöjen arvonmääritys; Kiinteistönvälitystoimistot; Rahataloudelliset arviointipalvelut; Rahatalouteen liittyvä analysointi ja arviointi; Uskotun miehen tehtävät; Rahallisen arvon määrittäminen; Likvidaatioselvitykset yritystoiminnan lopettamiseksi [raha-asioita koskevat]; Vakuutusneuvonta; Antiikkiesineiden arvonmääritys; Perintätoimistot; Kiinteistönvälitys; Finanssiarviointi [koskien vakuutuksia, pankkeja ja kiinteistöjä]; Pörssi- ja osakemeklarointi; Isännöintipalvelut; Keräysten (Rahan -) järjestäminen; Arvopaperinvälityspalvelut; Velkaneuvontapalvelut; Vakuutuskonsultointi; Vuokranperintä; Korvausmaksujen taloudellinen hallinta muiden lukuun; Taloudellinen tulliselvitys; Rahoitusanalyysit; Jalokivi- ja koruarviointi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d'agences de crédit; Services d'évaluation des risques d'investissement; Informations financières; Organisation du financement de projets de construction; Consultation en matière financière; Cote en Bourse; Gestion financière; Gérance de biens immobiliers; Services de collecte de bienfaisance; Courtage en assurances; Services d'estimation fiscale; Informations financières par le biais de sites web; Gestion d'actifs; Services actuariels; Estimation d'objets d'art; Services bancaires; Services d'évaluation financière de la propriété intellectuelle; Évaluation de biens meubles; Courtage; Évaluation financière; Estimations immobilières; Services d'agences immobilières; Services d'évaluation financière; Analyses et évaluations financières; Services fiduciaires; Services d'estimations financières; Services de liquidation d'entreprises [affaires financières]; Informations en matière d'assurances; Estimation d'antiquités; Services d'agences de recouvrement de créances; Courtage en biens immobiliers; Estimations financières [assurances, banques, immobilier]; Courtage de valeurs mobilières; Gérance d'immeubles d'habitation; Organisation de collectes financières; Courtage de valeurs boursières; Conseils en matière d'endettement; Consultation en matière d'assurances; Recouvrement de loyers; Gestion financière de paiements de remboursements pour des tiers; Services financiers de courtage en douane; Analyse financière; Estimation de bijoux.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Krediti; Usluge procjene investicijskog rizika; Financijske obavijesti; Osiguravanje financijskih sredstava za građevinske projekte; Savjetovanje o financijskim pitanjima; Kotacije cijena na burzi; Financijsko upravljanje; Upravljanje imovinom [nekretninama]; Prikupljanje za dobrotvorne svrhe; Posredovanje u osiguranju; Fiskalne procjene; Pružanje informacija o financijama putem web-stranice; Upravljanje aktivom; Aktuarske usluge; Procjena umjetnina; Bankarstvo; Usluge vrednovanja intelektualnog vlasništva; Procjena pokretne imovine; Posredovanje [mešetarenje]; Financijsko vrednovanje; Procjene nekretnina; Agencija za nekretnine; Usluge financijske procjene; Usluge financijskog ocjenjivanja i analize; Skrbništva; Usluge financijskog vrednovanja; Usluge likvidacije poduzeća [financijske usluge]; Osiguravateljske informacije; Procjena antikviteta; Agencije za utjerivanje potraživanja; Posredovanje u prometu nekretninama; Financijske procjene [osiguranje, banke, nekretnine]; Posredovanje na burzi; Upravljanje građevinskim objetima; Skupljanje priloga; Usluge posredovanja u prometu dionica na burzi; Savjetodavne usluge u svezi s dugovima; Savjetovanje o osiguranju; Ubiranje najamnine; Financijsko upravljanje isplatama naknada troškova za druge; Carinske usluge financijskog posredovanja; Financijska analiza; Procjena nakita.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Hitelügynökségek, hitelirodák; Befektetési kockázatbecslési szolgáltatások; Pénzügyi információs szolgáltatások; Pénzügyek intézése építőipari projektekhez; Pénzügyi tanácsadás; Tőzsdei árfolyamjegyzés; Pénzügyi menedzsment; Ingatlantulajdon-kezelés; Jótékonysági célú gyűjtések; Biztosításközvetítés; Adóbecslések; Pénzügyi információk nyújtása weboldalon keresztül; Vagyonkezelési szolgáltatások; Biztosítási statisztikai szolgáltatások; Műtárgyak értékbecslése; Bankügyletek lebonyolítása; Szellemi tulajdonnal kapcsolatos értékelési szolgáltatások; Ingóság felbecslése; Alkuszi/ügynöki tevékenység; Pénzügyi értékelés; Ingatlanok értékbecslése; Ingatlanügynökség; Pénzügyi becslési szolgáltatások; Pénzügyi értékelés és elemzés; Vagyonkezelés; Pénzügyi értékelési szolgáltatások; Felszámolási szolgáltatások, pénzügyi; Biztosítási információs szolgáltatás; Régiségek értékbecslése; Követelésbehajtási ügynökségek; Ingatlanközvetítés; Pénzügyi értékbecslés [biztosítás, bankügyletek, ingatlan]; Tőzsdeügynöki tevékenység; Bérházak kezelése; Gyűjtések szervezése; Tőzsdeügynöki szolgáltatások; Adósságrendezési szolgáltatások; Biztosítási tanácsadás; Lakbér beszedés; Visszatérítések pénzügyi kezelése harmadik felek számára; Vámügynöki pénzügyi szolgáltatások; Pénzügyi elemzések; Ékszerek értékbecslése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">servizi di agenzie di credito; valutazione del rischio in materia d'investimenti.; informazioni finanziarie; progettazione di finanziamenti per progetti di costruzione; consulenza in materia finanziaria; quotazione di borsa; amministrazione di patrimoni; Amministrazione di beni immobiliari; servizi di collette di beneficenza; mediazione in assicurazioni; perizie fiscali; informazioni finanziarie diffuse tramite siti web; gestione di beni; servizi attuari; stima di oggetti d'arte; servizi bancari; servizi di valutazione in materia di proprietà intellettuale; stima di beni mobili; brokeraggio; stime finanziarie; stima di beni immobili; servizi di agenzie immobiliari; servizi di stime finanziarie; analisi e valutazioni finanziarie; servizi fiduciari; servizi di valutazione finanziaria; servizi di liquidazione di imprese [affari finanziari]; informazioni in materia di assicurazioni; stima di oggetti di antiquariato; servizi di agenzie di recupero di crediti; mediazione in beni immobiliari; stime finanziarie [assicurazioni, banche, immobili]; brokeraggio di valori mobiliari; amministrazione di immobili; organizzazione di raccolte di denaro; servizi di mediazione in borsa [brokeraggio]; servizi di consulenza sull'indebitamento; consulenza in materia di assicurazioni; stima di beni immobiliari; riscossione di pigioni; servizi di mediazione; gestione finanziaria di programmi di rimborso per conto di terzi; servizi finanziari di brokeraggio doganale; analisi finanziaria; stima di gioielli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kredito agentūrų paslaugos; Investavimo rizikos vertinimo paslaugos; Finansinė informacija; Statybos projektų finansų tvarkymas; Finansinės konsultacijos; Biržos kursų kitimo informacija; Finansinės veiklos vadyba; Nekilnojamojo turto valdymas; Labdaros fondų lėšų rinkimas; Draudimo tarpininkavimas (draudimo makleriai); Finansinis įvertinimas; Finansinės informacijos teikimas visuotinio kompiuterių tinklo svetainėse; Turto valdymas; Draudimo rizikos vertintojų [aktuarų] paslaugos; Meno kūrinių įvertinimas; Banko operacijos; Intelektinės nuosavybės vertinimo paslaugos; Kilnojamojo turto įvertinimas; Tarpininkavimas [maklerių veikla]; Finansinis vertinimas; Nekilnojamojo turto įvertinimas; Nekilnojamojo turto agentūrų paslaugos; Finansinio įvertinimo paslaugos; Finansinis vertinimas ir analizė; Turto patikėtinių veikla; Finansinis vertinimas; Verslo likvidavimo paslaugos (finansinės); Draudimo informacija; Antikvarinių daiktų įvertinimas; Skolų inkasavimo agentūrų paslaugos; Nekilnojamojo turto tarpininkavimas; Finansinis įvertinimas [draudimo, banko operacijų, nekilnojamojo turto]; Vertybinių popierių supirkimo ir pardavimo tarpininkavimas [vertybinių popierių makleriai]; Daugiabučių namų valdymas; Pinigų rinkliavų rengimas; Biržos maklerių paslaugos; Skolinimosi patarėjų paslaugos; Draudimo konsultacijos; Nuompinigių rinkimas; Kompensacinių mokėjimų finansinė vadyba (kitiems); Finansinės muitinės tarpininkų paslaugos; Finansų analizė; Juvelyrinių dirbinių įvertinimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Kredītu aģentūru pakalpojumi; Investīciju riska novērtēšanas pakalpojumi; Finanšu informācijas sniegšana; Finansējuma nodrošināšana būvniecības projektiem; Konsultāciju sniegšana finanšu jomā; Akciju kotācija biržā; Finanšu pārvaldība; Nekustamā īpašuma pārvaldība; Ziedojumu vākšana labdarībai; Starpniecības pakalpojumi apdrošināšanas jomā; Fiskālā novērtēšana; Finanšu informācijas sniegšana tīmekļa vietnēs; Aktīvu pārvaldes pakalpojumi; Aktuāru pakalpojumi; Mākslas darbu novērtēšana; Banku pakalpojumi; Intelektuālā īpašuma novērtēšanas pakalpojumi; Kustamās mantas novērtēšana; Starpniecības pakalpojumi finanšu jomā; Finanšu novērtēšana; Nekustamā īpašuma finansiāla novērtēšana; Nekustamā īpašuma aģentūru pakalpojumi; Finansiālā stāvokļa novērtēšanas pakalpojumi; Finanšu novērtēšana un analīze; Fiduciāru darījumu nodrošināšana; Finansiālās novērtēšanas pakalpojumi; Finanšu pakalpojumi uzņēmumu likvidācijas gadījumos; Informācijas sniegšana par apdrošināšanu; Senlietu novērtēšana; Parādu piedziņas aģentūru pakalpojumi; Starpniecības pakalpojumi nekustamā īpašuma jomā; Finanšu novērtēšana apdrošināšanas, banku darbības un nekustamā īpašuma jomās; Starpniecības pakalpojumi darījumos ar vērtspapīriem; Daudzdzīvokļu māju pārvaldība; Naudas vākšanas organizēšana; Starpniecības pakalpojumi biržas darījumos; Konsultāciju sniegšana parādu jautājumos; Konsultāciju sniegšana apdrošināšanas jomā; Nomas un īres maksas iekasēšana; Atmaksas maksājumu finansiālā pārvaldība trešajām personām; Finanšu starpniecības pakalpojumi muitai; Finanšu analīzes nodrošināšana; Juvelierizstrādājumu novērtēšana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Aġenzija tal-kreditu; Servizzi ta' valutazzjoni tar-riskju tal-investiment; Informazzjoni finanzjarja; Arranġament ta' finanzi għal proġetti ta' kostruzzjoni; Konsulenza finanzjarja; Kwotazzjonijiet tal-borża (post fejn jinbiegħu u jinxtraw titoli u ishma); Ġestjoni tal-finanzi; Ġestjoni ta' proprjetà (proprjetà immobbli); Ġbir ta' fondi għall-karità; Sensarija ta' assigurazzjoni; Stimi fiskali; Forniment ta' informazzjoni finanzjarja permezz ta' sit web; Il-ġestjoni ta' assi; Servizzi attwarjali; Stima tal-valur tal-arti; Servizzi bankarji; Servizzi ta' evalwazzjoni ta' proprjetà intellettwali; Stima ta' proprjetà mobbli; Sensarija; Stima finanzjarja; Stimi ta' proprjetà immobbli; Aġenziji tal-proprjeta; Servizzi ta' stima finanzjarja; Evalwazzjoni u analiżi finanzjarja; Kuraziji; Servizzi ta' valutazzjoni finanzjarja; Servizzi ta' likwidazzjoni ta' negozji, finanzjarji; Informazzjoni dwar l-assigurazzjoni; Stima ta' oġġetti antiki; Aġenziji tal-ġbir tad-dejn; Senserija tal-proprjetà immobbli; Evalwazzjoni finanzjarja [assigurazzjoni, operazzjonijiet bankarji, proprjetà immobbli]; Sensarija ta' stokks u bonds; Ġestjoni ta' appartamenti djar; Organizzazzjoni ta' kollezzjonijiet; Servizzi ta' senserija ta' stokks; Servizzi ta' pariri fuq id-dejn; Konsulenza dwar l-assigurazzjoni; Il-ġbir tal-kera; Ġestjoni finanzjarja ta' ħlasijiet ta' rimborż għal oħrajn; Senserija doganali finanzjarja; Analiżi (Finanzjarja); Stima ta' ġojjellerija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Diensten van kredietinstellingen; Risicobeoordeling met betrekking tot investeringen; Verschaffen van financiële informatie; Verzorgen van financiering voor bouwprojecten; Advisering op financieel gebied; Beursnoteringen; Financieel beheer; Beheer van onroerende goederen; Liefdadigheidscollectes; Makelaardij in verzekeringen; Fiscale begroting; Verschaffen van financiële informatie via websites; Vermogensbeheer; Actuariaat; Taxatie van kunstwerken; Bankdiensten; Taxatiediensten van intellectuele eigendommen; Evaluatie van roerende goederen; Courtagediensten; Financiële evaluatie; Taxatie van onroerende goederen; Diensten van agentschappen in onroerend goed; Diensten op het gebied van financiële taxaties; Financiële evaluatie en analyse; Fiduciaire diensten; Financiële taxaties; Liquidatie van ondernemingen [financiële zaken]; Informatie op het gebied van verzekeringen; Taxatie van antiquiteiten; Diensten van incassobureaus; Makelaardij in onroerende goederen; Financiële taxaties [verzekeringen, banken, onroerend goed]; Beursmakelaardij; Beheer van gebouwen; Organiseren van geldcollectes; Makelaardij in Beurswaarden; Advisering met betrekking tot schuldenlasten; Advisering op het gebied van verzekeringen; Incasso van huurgelden; Financieel beheer van betalingen in het kader van geldterugacties voor derden; Financiële diensten van douaneagentschappen; Financiële analyse; Taxatie van juwelen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Agencje kredytowe; Usługi oceny ryzyka inwestycyjnego; Informacje finansowe; Organizowanie finansowania projektów budowlanych; Doradztwo w sprawach finansowych; Notowania giełdowe; Zarządzanie finansami; Zarządzanie nieruchomością; Zbiórki funduszy na cele dobroczynne; Pośrednictwo ubezpieczeniowe; Wyceny fiskalne; Udostępnianie informacji finansowych za pośrednictwem strony internetowej; Zarządzanie aktywami; Usługi aktuarialne; Wycena dzieł sztuki; Transakcje finansowe; Usługi w zakresie wyceny własności intelektualnej; Wycena majątku ruchomego; Maklerstwo; Ewaluacja finansowa; Wycena nieruchomości; Agencje nieruchomości; Usługi w zakresie wycen; Wyceny i analizy finansowe; Powiernictwo; Wyceny finansowe; Usługi likwidacji przedsiębiorstw, finansowe; Informacja o ubezpieczeniach; Wycena antyków; Agencje ściągania wierzytelności; Pośrednictwo w obrocie nieruchomościami; Wycena finansowa [ubezpieczenia, bankowość, nieruchomości]; Pośrednictwo giełdowe [akcje i obligacje]; Administrowanie domami czynszowymi; Organizacja zbiórek; Usługi dotyczące maklerstwa giełdowego; Doradztwo w zakresie długów; Doradztwo w sprawach ubezpieczeniowych; Pobieranie czynszu; Zarządzanie finansowe płatnościami z tytułu refundacji w imieniu osób trzecich; Usługi pośrednictwa finansowego w zakresie ceł; Analizy finansowe; Wycena biżuterii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de agências de crédito; Serviços de avaliação de risco de investimento; Informações financeiras; Organização de financiamento para projetos de construção; Consultadoria financeira; Serviços de cotações em Bolsa; Administração financeira; Gestão de imóveis; Coletas de beneficência; Agências de seguros; Avaliação fiscal; Fornecimento de informações financeiras através de um website; Gestão de ativos; Serviços atuariais; Avaliação de objetos de arte; Serviços bancários; Serviços de avaliação de propriedade intelectual; Avaliação de bens móveis; Corretagem; Avaliação relacionada com finanças; Estimativas imobiliárias [avaliações]; Serviços de agências imobiliárias; Serviços de avaliações financeiras; Avaliação e análise financeira; Serviços fiduciários; Serviços de avaliação financeira; Serviços de liquidação de negócios [assuntos financeiros]; Informações em seguros; Avaliação de antiguidades; Serviços de agências de cobrança de dívidas; Serviços de corretores imobiliários; Avaliações financeiras [seguros, bancos, imobiliário]; Corretagem de valores mobiliários; Administração de imóveis; Organização de coletas; Serviços de corretagem de ações da bolsa de valores; Aconselhamento em matéria de endividamento; Consultadoria em seguros; Cobrança de rendas; Gestão financeira de pagamentos de reembolso para terceiros; Serviços financeiros de corretagem aduaneira; Análise financeira; Avaliação de joalharia.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Agenții de credit; Servicii de evaluare a riscurilor de investiții; Informații financiare; Asigurarea finanțării pentru proiecte de construcții; Consultații în domeniul financiar; Cotații de bursă; Management financiar; Gestionarea proprietăților (imobiliare); Colectare de fonduri de binefacere; Curtaj în asigurări; Estimări fiscale; Furnizare de informații financiare prin intermediul unui site; Gestionare a activelor; Servicii actuariale; Evaluări de obiecte de artă; Servicii bancare; Servicii de evaluare a proprietății intelectuale; Evaluare de bunuri mobile; Curtaj; Evaluare financiară; Evaluări de proprietăți imobiliare; Agenții imobiliare; Servicii de evaluare; Evaluare și analiză financiară; Servicii fiduciare; Servicii de evaluări financiare; Servicii pentru lichidarea unei întreprinderi [financiare]; Informații în domeniul asigurărilor; Expertizare de antichități; Agenții de încasare a creanțelor; Brokeraj imobiliar; Estimări financiare [asigurări, bănci, proprietăți imobiliare]; Curtaj în bursă; Administrare de clădiri cu locuințe; Organizare de colecte; Servicii de brokeraj; Servicii de consiliere privind datoriile; Consultanță în domeniul asigurărilor; Colectarea chiriilor; Managementul financiar al plăților de rambursare pentru alte persoane; Servicii financiare de curtaj vamal; Analiză financiară; Estimări de bijuterii.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Úverové agentúry; Posudzovanie investičného rizika; Finančné informácie; Organizovanie financovania stavebných projektov; Finančné poradenstvo; Kurzové záznamy na burze; Finančné riadenie; Správa nehnuteľností; Organizovanie dobročinných zbierok; Sprostredkovanie poistenia; Daňové odhady (služby); Poskytovanie finančných informácií prostredníctvom webových stránok; Manažment aktív; Aktuárske služby (poistno-matematické); Oceňovanie umeleckých diel; Bankovníctvo; Oceňovanie duševného vlastníctva; Ocenenie hnuteľného majetku; Sprostredkovanie (maklérstvo); Finančné oceňovanie; Oceňovanie nehnuteľností; Realitné kancelárie; Finančné odhadovanie; Finančné oceňovanie a analýza; Správcovstvo majetku (pre tretie osoby); Finančné oceňovacie služby; Likvidácia podnikov (finančné služby); Informácie o poistení; Oceňovanie starožitností; Kancelárie zaoberajúce sa inkasovaním pohľadávok; Sprostredkovanie nehnuteľností; Finančné odhady a oceňovanie (poisťovníctvo, bankovníctvo, nehnuteľnosti); Obchodovanie na burze s cennými papiermi; Správa nájomných domov; Organizovanie zbierok; Sprostredkovanie na burze cenných papierov; Poradenstvo v oblasti splácania dlhov; Konzultačné služby v oblasti poisťovníctva; Vyberanie nájomného; Finančné riadenie refundovaných platieb (pre tretie osoby); Colné deklarácie (finančné služby); Finančné analýzy; Oceňovanie šperkov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Kreditne agencije; Ocenjevanje investicijskega tveganja; Finančno informiranje; Vodenje financ za gradbene projekte; Finančno svetovanje; Borzno notiranje; Finančno upravljanje; Upravljanje lastnine (nepremičnine); Zbiranje dobrodelnih prispevkov; Zavarovalno posredništvo; Fiskalne cenitve; Nudenje finančnih informacij preko spletne strani; Upravljanje premoženja; Aktuarske storitve; Cenitev umetnin; Bančništvo; Vrednotenje intelektualne lastnine; Ocena premičnin; Borzno posredništvo; Finančno vrednotenje; Cenitev nepremičnin; Agencije za posredovanje (nepremičnine); Storitve finančnih cenitev; Finančne ocene in analiza; Fiduciarne storitve; Storitve finančnega vrednotenja; Likvidacije podjetij (finančne storitve); Zavarovalniške informacije; Cenitev starin; Agencije za izterjavo dolgov; Nepremičninsko posredovanje; Finančno vrednotenje [v zavarovalništvu, bančništvu, pri nepremičninah]; Posredovanje v zvezi z vrednostnimi papirji; Upravljanje stanovanjskih zgradb; Organizacija pobiranja in izterjave; Storitve borznega posredovanja; Svetovalne storitve v zvezi z dolgovi; Zavarovalniško svetovanje; Pobiranje najemnin; Finančno upravljanje plačil nadomestil za druge; Storitve posredovanja na finančni carini; Finančna analiza; Cenitev nakita.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kreditinstitut; Bedömning av investeringsrisker; Finansiell information; Anordnande av finansiering för byggprojekt; Finansiella konsultationer; Börsnotering; Finansiell förvaltning; Fastighetsförvaltning [egendom]; Penninginsamlingar för välgörande ändamål; Försäkringsmäkleri; Skatteberäkning; Upplåtande av finansiell information via en hemsida; Förvaltning av tillgångar; Aktuarietjänster; Konstvärdering; Bankrörelse; Värdering av immateriella rättigheter; Utvärdering av lösören; Finansiellt mäkleri; Finansiell värdering; Fastighetsvärderingar; Fastighetsagenturer; Tjänster avseende ekonomiska värderingar; Finansiella analyser och bedömningar; Förvaltarskap; Finansiella värderingstjänster; Affärslikvidering /avvecklingstjänster (finansiella); Information avseende försäkringar; Värdering av antikviteter; Inkassobyråer; Mäkleri avseende fast egendom; Finansiella värderingar [försäkring, bank, fastighet]; Värdepappersmäkleri; Förvaltning av hyreshus; Organisering av penninginsamlingar; Börsmäkleri; Skuldrådgivning; Försäkringskonsultationer; Inkassering av hyror; Finansiella tjänster avseende återbetalningar för andra; Finansiella tullklareringstjänster; Finansiella analyser; Värdering av juveler och smycken.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>41</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Професионално ориентиране; Отдаване под наем на печатни публикации; Публикуване на мултимедиен материал онлайн; Преподавателски услуги; Провеждане на практически семинари [обучение]; Организиране и провеждане на симпозиуми; Организиране на презентации с образователна цел; Организиране и провеждане на обучителни семинари; Публикуване на наръчници; Организиране и провеждане на сказки; Организиране на конференции за образователни цели; Преводачески услуги; Курсове за обучение (предоставяне); Текстове (Публикуване на -), с изключение на рекламни текстове; Заемане на книги и други публикации; Услуги за публикуване на бюлетини с новини; Организиране и провеждане на състезания [обучение и развлечения]; Лизинг на книги; Организиране на обучение; Публикуване на списания и книги в електронен формат; Услуги за дистанционно обучение, предоставяни онлайн; Услуги на частни учители; Провеждане на образователни курсове; Уреждане, провеждане и организиране на работни срещи [обучение]; Мултимедийно издаване на списания, журнали и вестници; Библиотечни услуги; Конферентни услуги; Организиране на конгреси и конференции за културни и образователни цели; Предаване на ноу-хау [обучение]; Уреждане, провеждане и организиране на концерти; Обучение; Организиране и провеждане на конференции, конгреси, симпозиуми; Академии [образование]; Разпространение на образователни материали; Издаване на книги; Доставка на онлайн електронни публикации [без възможност да бъдат прехвърляни върху друг носител]; Обучение за придобиване на професионални умения; Предоставяне на видео онлайн, без възможност за сваляне; Организиране на изложби с културни или развлекателни цели; Културни дейности; Онлайн публикуване на електронни книги и периодични издания; Тийм билдинг (образование); Публикуване на онлайн прегледи в областта на развлечението; Практическо обучение [демонстрация]; Организиране на събирания за културни цели; Семинари.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Poradenství pro volbu povolání [v oblasti vzdělávání nebo školení]; Půjčování tiskovin; Publikování multimediálních materiálů on-line; Školení; Vedení workshopů (školení); Pořádání a vedení symposií; Pořádání prezentací pro vzdělávací účely; Příprava a pořádání vzdělávacích seminářů; Vydávání manuálů; Pořádání a vedení přednášek; Pořádání konferencí pro vzdělávací účely; Překladatelské služby; Vzdělávací kurzy; Vydávání textů, s výjimkou reklamních; Půjčování knih a jiných publikací; Služby vydávání informačních bulletinů; Organizování a vedení soutěží [výchova a zábava]; Půjčování knih; Organizování školení; Vydávání periodik a knih v elektronické formě; Služby dálkového vzdělávání poskytované on-line; Soukromá výuka; Vedení vzdělávacích kurzů; Pořádání, vedení a organizování pracovních setkání [školení]; Multimediální publikování časopisů, žurnálů a novin; Knihovnické služby (půjčovny knih); Konferenční služby; Organizování kongresů a konferencí pro kulturní a vzdělávací účely; Předávání know-how [odborné vzdělávání]; Pořádání, vedení a organizování koncertů; Vyučování, vzdělávání; Organizování a vedení konferencí, kongresů a sympozií; Akademie [vzdělávání]; Šíření vzdělávacích materiálů; Vydávání knih; Poskytování elektronických publikací online bez možnosti stažení; Služby odborného vzdělání; Poskytování videí online bez možnosti stažení; Pořádání výstav ke kulturním nebo vzdělávacím účelům; Kulturní aktivity; Vydávání elektronických knih a časopisů on-line; Budování týmů (vzdělávání); Zveřejňování on-line recenzí v oblasti zábavy; Praktický výcvik [předvádění]; Pořádání kongresů pro kulturní účely; Semináře.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Erhvervsvejledning [vejledning om uddannelse og valg af job]; Udlejning af tryksager; Online-udgivelse af multimediemateriale; Undervisning; Afholdelse af workshops [undervisning]; Arrangering og ledelse af symposier; Arrangering af præsentationer med uddannelsesmæssige formål; Arrangering og afholdelse af undervisningsseminarer; Udgivelse af manualer; Tilrettelæggelse og ledelse af foredrag; Afholdelse af uddannelseskonferencer; Tolkning og oversættelse; Kursusvirksomhed; Udgivelse af tekster, undtagen reklametekster; Udlån af bøger og andre publikationer; Udgivelse af nyhedsbreve; Arrangering og ledelse af konkurrencer [uddannelses- eller underholdningsvirksomhed]; Udlejning af bøger; Organisering af undervisning; Udgivelse af elektroniske tidsskrifter og -bøger; Fjernundervisning leveret online; Tutorundervisning; Afholdelse af undervisningskurser; Arrangering, ledelse og organisering af workshopper [undervisning]; Multimedieudgivelse af blade, tidsskrifter og aviser; Biblioteksvirksomhed; Tjenesteydelser i forbindelse med konferencer; Organisering af kongresser og konferencer med kulturelt og uddannelsesmæssigt sigte; Overførsel af knowhow [undervisningsvirksomhed]; Arrangering, ledelse og organisering af koncerter; Oplæring; Arrangering og ledelse af konferencer, kongresser og symposier; Akademier [undervisning]; Udbredelse af undervisningsmateriale; Udgivelse af bøger; Tilvejebringelse af online elektroniske publikationer, ikke downloadable; Erhvervsuddannelse; Stillen online videoer til rådighed, ikke-downloadable; Organisering af udstillinger med kulturelt eller uddannelsesmæssigt sigte; Kulturelle arrangementer; Online publicering af elektroniske bøger og tidsskrifter; Teambuilding (uddannelse); Udgivelse af onlineanmeldelser inden for underholdning; Praktisk oplæring [undervisning]; Arrangering af kongresser med kulturelle formål; Seminarer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Berufsberatung; Vermietung von Druckerzeugnissen; Veröffentlichung von Multimedia-Materialien online; Erziehung und Unterricht; Durchführung von Workshops [Schulung]; Organisation und Veranstaltung von Symposien; Organisation von Vorstellungen für Schulungszwecke; Veranstaltung und Durchführung von Übungsseminaren; Herausgabe von Handbüchern; Organisation und Durchführung von Vorträgen; Organisation von Bildungskonferenzen; Übersetzung und Dolmetschen; Schulung; Herausgabe von Texten, ausgenommen Werbetexte; Dienstleistungen der Ausleihe von Büchern und anderen Veröffentlichungen; Veröffentlichung von Rundschreiben; Organisation und Durchführung von Wettbewerben [Unterricht oder Unterhaltung]; Buchausleihe; Organisation von Schulungen; Veröffentlichung von Zeitschriften und Büchern in elektronischer Form; Veranstaltung und Durchführung von Online-Fernkursen; Privatunterricht; Veranstaltung von Kursen zu Schulungszwecken; Vorbereitung, Durchführung und Organisation von Workshops [Ausbildung]; Multimediaveröffentlichung von Zeitschriften, Journalen und Zeitungen; Bibliotheksdienstleistungen; Dienstleistungen der Veranstaltung von Konferenzen; Organisation von Kongressen und Konferenzen für kulturelle und Bildungszwecke; Know-how-Transfer [Ausbildung]; Veranstaltung, Durchführung und Organisation von Konzerten; Bereitstellung von Ausbildung; Organisation und Durchführung von Konferenzen, Kongressen und Symposien; Erziehung auf Akademien; Veröffentlichung von Ausbildungsmaterialien; Veröffentlichung von Büchern; Online-Bereitstellung von nicht herunterladbaren elektronischen Publikationen; Ausbildung in Bezug auf berufliche Fähigkeiten; Bereitstellung von nicht herunterladbaren Online-Videos; Veranstaltung von Ausstellungen für kulturelle oder Unterrichtszwecke; Kulturelle Aktivitäten; Online-Publikation von elektronischen Büchern und Zeitschriften; Unterricht zu Teambildungszwecken; Veröffentlichung von Online-Rezensionen im Unterhaltungsbereich; Demonstrationsunterricht in praktischen Übungen; Organisation von Tagungen zu kulturellen Zwecken; Veranstaltung von Seminaren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Προσανατολισμός ενδιαφερόντων (κλίσης)· Εκμίσθωση εντύπων εκδόσεων· Ηλεκτρονική δημοσίευση πολυμεσικού υλικού· Παροχή κατάρτισης· Διεξαγωγή εργαστηρίων [κατάρτιση]· Οργάνωση και διεξαγωγή συμποσίων· Οργάνωση παρουσιάσεων για εκπαιδευτικούς σκοπούς· Οργάνωση και διεξαγωγή επιμορφωτικών σεμιναρίων· Έκδοση εγχειριδίων· Οργάνωση και διεξαγωγή διαλέξεων· Διοργάνωση συνεδρίων για εκπαιδευτικούς σκοπούς· Μετάφραση και ερμηνεία· Παροχή επιμορφωτικών μαθημάτων· Δημοσίευση κειμένων [εκτός από κείμενα διαφημιστικά]· Δανεισμός βιβλίων και άλλων δημοσιεύσεων· Έκδοση ενημερωτικών δελτίων· Οργάνωση και διεξαγωγή διαγωνισμών [εκπαίδευση και ψυχαγωγία]· Ενοικίαση βιβλίων· Οργάνωση επιμόρφωσης· Έκδοση περιοδικών και βιβλίων σε ηλεκτρονική μορφή· Υπηρεσίες εξ αποστάσεως μάθησης παρεχόμενες διαδικτυακά· Ατομική εκπαίδευση· Διεξαγωγή εκπαιδευτικών μαθημάτων· Συντονισμός, διοργάνωση και διεξαγωγή εργαστηρίων [επιμόρφωσης]· Πολυμεσική έκδοση περιοδικών και εφημερίδων· Υπηρεσίες Βιβλιοθήκης· Υπηρεσίες συνεδρίων· Οργάνωση συνεδρίων για πολιτιστικούς και εκπαιδευτικούς σκοπούς· Μεταφορά τεχνογνωσίας [επιμόρφωση]· Συντονισμός, διοργάνωση και διεξαγωγή συναυλιών· Παροχή κατάρτισης· Οργάνωση και διεξαγωγή συσκέψεων, συνεδρίων και συμποσίων· Σχολές [εκπαιδευτικά ιδρύματα]· Διανομή εκπαιδευτικού υλικού· Δημοσίευση βιβλίων· Παροχή ηλεκτρονικών εκδόσεων, χωρίς δυνατότητα τηλεφόρτωσης· Υπηρεσίες επιμόρφωσης [επαγγελματικής κατάρτισης] σχετικά με συγκεκριμένο αντικείμενο ή θέση εργασίας· Παροχή διαδικτυακών βίντεο, μη μεταφορτώσιμων· Οργάνωση εκθέσεων για σκοπούς πολιτιστικούς ή μορφωτικούς· Πολιτιστικές δραστηριότητες· Ηλεκτρονική δημοσίευση βιβλίων και περιοδικών· Συγκρότηση ομάδων (εκπαίδευση)· Δημοσίευση ηλεκτρονικών περιοδικών στον τομέα της ψυχαγωγίας· Πρακτική κατάρτιση [επιδείξεις]· Διοργάνωση διασκέψεων για πολιτιστικούς σκοπούς· Σεμινάρια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Vocational guidance [education or training advice]; Rental of printed publications; Publication of multimedia material online; Teaching; Conducting workshops [training]; Arranging and conducting of symposiums; Arranging of presentations for educational purposes; Arranging and conducting of training seminars; Publication of manuals; Arranging and conducting of lectures; Arrangement of conferences for educational purposes; Translation and interpretation; Provision of training courses; Publication of texts, other than publicity texts; Lending of books and other publications; Services for the publication of newsletters; Arranging and conducting of competitions [education or entertainment]; Rental of books; Organisation of training; Publication of periodicals and books in electronic form; Distance learning services provided online; Tutoring; Conducting of educational courses; Arranging, conducting and organisation of workshops; Multimedia publishing of magazines, journals and newspapers; Lending library services; Conference services; Organisation of congresses and conferences for cultural and educational purposes; Know-how transfer [training]; Arranging, conducting and organisation of concerts; Training; Arranging and conducting of conferences, congresses and symposiums; Academies [education]; Dissemination of educational material; Publication of books; Providing online electronic publications, not downloadable; Vocational skills training; Providing online videos, not downloadable; Organization of exhibitions for cultural or educational purposes; Cultural activities; Online publication of electronic books and journals; Team building (education); Publication of online reviews in the field of entertainment; Practical training [demonstration]; Arranging of conventions for cultural purposes; Seminars.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Orientación profesional [asesoramiento sobre educación o formación]; Alquiler de publicaciones impresas; Publicación de material multimedia en línea; Educación; Dirección de talleres [formación]; Organización y dirección de simposios; Organización de presentaciones con fines educativos; Organización y realización de seminarios de formación; Publicación de manuales; Organización y celebración de charlas; Organización de conferencias relacionadas con la educación; Traducción e interpretación; Prestación de cursos de formación; Publicación de textos que no sean publicitarios; Préstamo de libros y otras publicaciones; Edición de boletines informativos; Preparación y gestión de concursos [educativos o recreativos]; Servicios de alquiler de libros; Organización de actividades de formación; Publicación de publicaciones periódicas y libros en formato electrónico; Servicios de formación a distancia en línea; Servicios de tutoría [instrucción]; Dirección de cursos educativos; Preparación, celebración y organización de talleres [formación]; Publicación multimedia de revistas, revistas especializadas y diarios; Servicios de biblioteca; Servicios de conferencias; Organización de congresos y conferencias con fines culturales y educativos; Transferencia de conocimientos especializados [formación]; Preparación, celebración y organización de conciertos; Formación; Organización y celebración de conferencias, congresos y simposios; Academias [educación]; Divulgación de material educativo; Publicación de libros; Suministro de publicaciones electrónicas en línea, que no sean descargables; Formación en el ámbito de la capacitación profesional; Suministro en línea de vídeos no descargables; Organización de exposiciones con fines culturales o educativos; Actividades culturales; Publicación electrónica de libros y periódicos en línea; Formación de equipos (educación); Publicación de reseñas en línea en el ámbito del entretenimiento; Formación práctica [demostración]; Organización de convenciones con fines culturales; Seminarios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kutsenõustamine [haridus- või koolitusnõuanded]; Trükiste rentimine; Multimeediamaterjali avaldamine veebis; Õpetamine; Õpikodade läbiviimine [väljaõpe]; Sümpoosionide korraldamine ja läbiviimine; Õppe eesmärgil esitluste korraldamine; Koolitusseminaride korraldamine ja läbiviimine; Käsiraamatute avaldamine; Loengute korraldamine ja läbiviimine; Hariduskonverentside korraldamine; Tõlkimine; Koolituskursuste pakkumine; Tekstide, v.a reklaamtekstide publitseerimine, avaldamine; Raamatute ja muude väljaannete laenutus; Infolehtede avaldamine; Võistluste organiseerimine ja läbiviimine [haridus- ja meelelahutus]; Raamatute rentimine; Koolituse korraldamine; Ajakirjandusväljaannete ja raamatute väljaandmine elektroonilisel kujul; Kaugõppeteenused veebis; Individuaalne juhendamine [õpetamine]; Koolituskursuste, õppekursuste läbiviimine; Õpikodade korraldamine, läbiviimine ja organiseerimine [koolitus]; Ajakirjade ja ajalehtede avaldamine multimeedias; Raamatukoguteenused; Konverentsiteenused; Kultuuri- ja hariduskongresside ning -konverentside organiseerimine; Oskusteabe edastamine [koolitus]; Kontsertide korraldamine, läbiviimine ja organiseerimine; Koolitusteenused; Konverentside, kongresside ja sümpoosionide organiseerimine ja korraldamine; Akadeemiad [haridus]; Haridusalaste materjalide levitamine; Raamatute kirjastamine, avaldamine; Elektronväljaannete pakkumine arvutivõrgus, v.a allalaaditavad; Ametialaste oskuste õpetamine; On-line-videote (v.a allalaaditavate) pakkumine; Kultuuriliste või hariduslike näituste korraldamine; Kultuuritegevus; Elektronraamatute ja -ajakirjade kirjastamine veebis; Meeskonnaarendus (haridus, koolitus); Veebiarvustuste avaldamine meelelahutuse valdkonnas; Praktiline väljaõpe, treening (demonstratsioonid); Kultuuriliste eesmärkidega kongresside korraldamine; Seminarid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Ammatinvalinnanohjaus; Painotuotteiden vuokraus; Multimediamateriaalin julkaiseminen online-periaatteella; Opetuksen tarjoaminen; Koulutustyöpajojen pitäminen; Symposiumien järjestäminen; Esittelyjen järjestäminen opetustarkoituksiin; Koulutusseminaarien järjestäminen ja toteuttaminen; Käsikirjojen julkaiseminen; Luentojen järjestäminen ja pitäminen; Koulutuskonferenssien järjestäminen; Käännös ja tulkkaus; Koulutuskurssien tarjoaminen; Julkaisu (tekstien) [paitsi mainostekstien]; Kirjojen ja muiden julkaisujen lainaus; Tiedotuslehtien julkaiseminen; Kilpailujen [koulutus tai ajanviete] järjestäminen ja ohjaaminen; Kirjojen vuokraus; Koulutuksen järjestäminen; Aikakauslehtien ja kirjojen julkaisu elektronisessa muodossa; Etäopetuspalvelut tarjottuina online-periaatteella; Tutorointi; Opetuskurssien pitäminen; Työpajojen järjestäminen, pitäminen ja organisoiminen [koulutus]; Aikakauslehtien, lehtien ja sanomalehtien multimediajulkaiseminen; Kirjastopalvelut; Konferenssipalvelut; Kongressien ja konferenssien organisointi kulttuuri- ja koulutustarkoituksiin; Tietotaidon siirtäminen [valmennus]; Konserttien järjestäminen, pitäminen ja organisoiminen; Koulutuspalvelut; Konferenssien, kongressien ja symposiumien organisointi ja järjestäminen; Akatemiat; Koulutusmateriaalin levittäminen; Kirjojen julkaisu; Sähköisten, ei-ladattavien julkaisujen on-line tarjoaminen; Ammatillisten taitojen harjoittaminen; Muiden kuin ladattavien online-videoiden tarjoaminen; Näyttelyiden järjestäminen kulttuuri- tai koulutustarkoituksiin; Kulttuuritoiminnat; Elektronisten kirjojen ja lehtien julkaiseminen online-periaatteella; Tiimien rakentaminen (koulutus); Viihdearvostelujen julkaiseminen verkossa; Työharjoittelu [osana koulutusta]; Kokousten järjestäminen kulttuuritarkoituksessa; Seminaarit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Orientation professionnelle [conseils en matière d'éducation ou de formation]; Location de publications imprimées; Publication de matériel multimédia en ligne; Enseignement; Organisation et suivi d'ateliers de formation; Organisation et conduite de symposiums; Organisation de présentations à des fins éducatives; Organisation et conduite de séminaires de formation; Publication de manuels; Préparation et coordination de cours magistraux; Organisation de conférences sur l'enseignement; Traduction et interprétation; Offre de cours de formation; Publication de textes autres que textes publicitaires; Prêts de livres et d'autres publications; Publication de bulletins d'information [newsletters]; Préparation et coordination de concours [éducation ou divertissement]; Location de livres; Organisation de formations; Publication de périodiques et de livres sous forme électronique; Services d'enseignement à distance fournis en ligne; Tutorat; Coordination de cours d'enseignement; Préparation, coordination et organisation d'ateliers; Édition multimédia de revues, de revues spécialisées et de journaux; Services de bibliothèque; Services de conférence; Organisation de congrès et conférences à des fins culturelles et éducatives; Transmission de savoir-faire [formation]; Préparation, coordination et organisation de concerts; Formation; Préparation et coordination de conférences, de congrès et de symposiums; Académies [éducation]; Provision de matériel éducatif; Publication de livres; Mise à disposition de publications électroniques en ligne non téléchargeables; Formation axée sur les compétences professionnelles; Mise à disposition en ligne de vidéos non téléchargeables; Organisation d'expositions à buts culturels ou éducatifs; Activités culturelles; Édition en ligne de livres et de périodiques; Constitution d'équipe (éducation); Publication de revues en ligne dans le domaine du divertissement; Formation pratique [démonstration]; Organisation de conventions à buts culturels; Organisation et conduite de séminaires.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Profesionalna orijentacija; Iznajmljivanje tiskanih publikacija; Izdavanje multimedijskog materijala na Internetu; Pružanje poduke; Vođenje radionica [osposobljavanje]; Simpoziji (organizacija i vođenje simpozija); Organiziranje prezentacija u obrazovne svrhe; Organizacija i vođenje seminara osposobljavanja; Objavljivanje priručnika; Organizacija i izvođenje predavanja; Organiziranje konferencija u obrazovne svrhe; Prevođenje i tumačenje; Pružanje tečajeva osposobljavanja; Objavljivanje tekstova [osim u reklamne svrhe]; Posudba knjiga i drugih publikacija; Usluge izdavanja novinskih brošura; Organizacija i izvođenje natjecanja [obrazovnih ili zabavnih]; Iznajmljivanje knjiga; Organizacija osposobljavanja; Izdavanje periodičnih publikacija i knjiga u elektroničkom obliku; Usluge učenja na daljinu koje se pružaju na Internetu; Podučavanje; Vođenje obrazovnih tečajeva; Dogovaranje, izvođenje i organizacija radionica [osposobljavanje]; Multimedijsko izdavanje časopisa, žurnala i novina; Usluge knjižnica; Konferencijske usluge; Organizacija kongresa i konferencija za kulturne i obrazovne svrhe; Prijenos stručnih znanja [osposobljavanje]; Dogovaranje, izvođenje i organizacija koncerata; Pružanje usluga osposobljavanja; Organizacija i izvođenje konferencija, kongresa i simpozija; Akademije [obrazovanje]; Širenje obrazovnog materijala; Izdavanje knjiga; Pružanje elektroničkih publikacija koje se ne mogu preuzimati; Usluge strukovnog osposobljavanja; Pružanje on-line video snimaka, koji nisu za preuzimanje; Organiziranje izložaba u kulturne i odgojne svrhe; Kulturne aktivnosti; Mrežno objavljivanje elektroničkih knjiga i časopisa; Jačanje timskog duha (obrazovanje); Objava internetskih recenzija u području zabave; Obrazovne demonstracije; Organiziranje konvencija u kulturne svrhe; Seminari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Pályaválasztási tanácsadás; Nyomtatott kiadványok kölcsönzése; Multimédiás anyagok online kiadása; Oktatás biztosítása; Műhelyek lebonyolítása [képzés]; Szimpóziumok szervezése és lebonyolítása; Oktatási célú bemutatók rendezése; Szemináriumok rendezése és lebonyolítása; Kézikönyvek kiadása; Előadások szervezése és lebonyolítása; Oktatási célú konferenciák szervezése; Fordítás és tolmácsolás; Tanfolyamok, kurzusok biztosítása; Nem reklámcélú szövegek publikálása; Könyvek és más kiadványok kölcsönzése; Hírlevélkiadási szolgáltatások; Versenyek szervezése és lebonyolítása [oktatás vagy szórakoztatás]; Könyvkölcsönzés; Képzés szervezése; Folyóiratok és könyvek megjelentetése elektronikus formában; Online távoktatási szolgáltatások; Mentorálás; Oktatási célú tanfolyamok lebonyolítása; Workshopok [képzés] szervezése, lebonyolítása és rendezése; Magazinok, folyóiratok és újságok multimédiás megjelentetése; Könyvtári szolgáltatások; Konferencia szolgáltatások; Kulturális és oktatási célú kongresszusok és konferenciák szervezése; Know-how átadása (képzés); Koncertek szervezése, lebonyolítása és rendezése; Szakmai képzés, betanítás; Konferenciák, kongresszusok, szimpóziumok szervezése és lebonyolítása; Akadémiák [oktatás]; Oktatási anyagok terjesztése; Könyvkiadás; Online elektronikus kiadványok biztosítása, nem letölthetők; Szakmai készségfejlesztés; Online, nem letölthető videók biztosítása; Kulturális vagy oktatási célú kiállítások szervezése; Kulturális tevékenységek; Elektronikus könyvek és folyóiratok on-line publikálása; Csapatépítés (oktatás); Online kritikák közzététele szórakoztatási célból; Gyakorlati képzés [szemléltetés]; Kulturális célú gyűlések, szakmai konferenciák szervezése; Szemináriumok.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">orientamento professionale; noleggio di pubblicazioni stampate; pubblicazione di materiale multimediale online; educazione; conduzione di  workshop [formazione]; organizzazione e direzione di simposi; organizzazione di presentazioni per formazione; organizzazione e conduzione di seminari di formazione; pubblicazione di manuali; organizzazione e realizzazione di lezioni; conduzione di conferenze  didattiche; servizi di traduzione; fornitura di corsi di formazione; pubblicazione di testi eccetto quelli pubblicitari; prestito di libri e  di altre pubblicazioni; pubblicazione di bollettini di informazione; organizzazione e realizzazione di concorsi [educativi o ricreativi]; noleggio di libri; organizzazione di attività di formazione; pubblicazione di libri e periodici in forma elettronica; servizi di formazione a distanza forniti online; tutoraggio.; conduzione di corsi didattici; fornitura di corsi  di istruzione; organizzazione, preparazione e realizzazione di workshop [formazione]; pubblicazione multimediale  di riviste, riviste specializzate e giornali; corsi di formazione; servizi di biblioteca; servizi per conferenze; organizzazione di congressi e conferenze a fini culturali ed educativi; trasferimento del know-how [insegnamento]; organizzazione, preparazione e realizzazione di concerti; attività di formazione; organizzazione e realizzazione di conferenze, congressi e simposi; Accademie [educazione]; diffusione di materiale  didattico; pubblicazione di libri; fornitura online di pubblicazioni elettroniche non scaricabili; formazione professionale; fornitura di video online, non scaricabili; organizzazione di mostre per scopi culturali ed educativi; attività culturali; pubblicazione in linea di libri e di riviste online; team building (istruzione); pubblicazione di rassegne online nel settore del divertimento; esercitazione pratica [dimostrazione]; organizzazione di convention per scopi culturali; seminari.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Profesijos pasirinkimo konsultacijos; Spausdintų leidinių nuoma; Multimedijos medžiagos publikavimas internete; Mokymas; Praktinių seminarų vedimas [mokymas]; Simpoziumų rengimas ir vedimas; Pasirodymų rengimas švietimo reikmėms; Mokomųjų seminarų rengimas ir vedimas; Žinynų leidyba; Paskaitų rengimas ir vedimas; Konferencijų rengimas švietimo reikmėms; Vertimai; Mokymo kursų rengimas; Tekstų skelbimas [išskyrus reklaminius]; Knygų ir kitų leidinių skolinimas; Informacinių biuletenių leidybos paslaugos; Konkursų [mokomųjų arba pramoginių] organizavimas ir vedimas; Knygų nuoma; Mokymo organizavimas; Elektroninių periodinių leidinių ir knygų leidyba; Nuotolinio mokymosi paslaugos internetu; Mokymas (mažos grupės ar vieno asmens); Mokomųjų kursų vedimas; Praktinių seminarų [mokymo] rengimas, vedimas ir organizavimas; Žurnalų, specializuotų žurnalų ir laikraščių multimedijos leidyba; Bibliotekų paslaugos; Konferencijų paslaugos; Suvažiavimų ir konferencijų organizavimas kultūrinėms ir švietimo reikmėms; Praktinės patirties (know-how) perdavimas [mokymai]; Koncertų rengimas, vedimas ir organizavimas; Instruktavimas; Konferencijų, kongresų, simpoziumų organizavimas ir rengimas; Akademijos [mokymas]; Mokymo medžiagos platinimas; Knygų leidyba; Elektroninių publikacijų tiesioginis pateikimas per kompiuterių tinklą (ne parsisiunčiamųjų); Profesinių įgūdžių lavinimas; Tiesioginis vaizdo įrašų pateikimas per kompiuterių tinklą (ne parsisiunčiamųjų); Kultūros ar mokomųjų parodų rengimas; Kultūrinė veikla; Elektroninių knygų ir žurnalų publikavimas internete; Komandos kūrimas (švietimo paslaugos); Pramoginių internetinių apžvalgų publikavimas; Praktinis mokymas [parodomasis]; Kultūrinių suvažiavimų rengimas; Seminarų organizavimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Audzināšana un apmācība, proti, profesionālās orientācijas pakalpojumi; Drukātu izdevumu iznomāšana; Multivides materiālu, izņemot reklāmas materiālus, publicēšana tiešsaistē; Mācību pakalpojumi; Darbsemināru vadīšana [apmācība]; Simpoziju rīkošana un vadīšana; Prezentāciju rīkošana apmācības nolūkiem; Apmācības semināru sagatavošana un vadība; Rokasgrāmatu izdošana; Lekciju organizēšana un vadīšana; Konferenču rīkošana izglītības jomā; Mutvārdu un rakstveida tulkošanas pakalpojumi; Apmācības kursu pakalpojumi; Tekstu, izņemot reklāmas tekstus, publicēšana; Grāmatu un citu publikāciju aizdošana; Biļetenu izdošanas pakalpojumi; Konkursu organizēšana un vadīšana [izglītība un izklaide]; Grāmatu noma; Apmācību organizēšana; Periodisku izdevumu un grāmatu izdošana elektroniskā veidā; Tālmācības pakalpojumi tiešsaistē; Individuāla apmācība; Izglītojošu kursu vadīšana; Darbsemināru [apmācību] sagatavošana, vadīšana un organizēšana; Periodisko izdevumu, žurnālu un laikrakstu publicēšana multividē; Bibliotēku pakalpojumi; Konferenču pakalpojumi; Kongresu un konferenču organizēšana kultūras un izglītojošiem mērķiem; Zinātības (know-how) nodošana (apmācība); Koncertu sagatavošana, vadīšana un organizēšana; Treniņu mācību nodrošināšana; Konferenču, kongresu, simpoziju organizēšana un rīkošana; Augstāko un vidējo speciālo mācību iestāžu pakalpojumi; Izglītības materiālu izplatīšana; Grāmatu publicēšana; Nelejupielādējamu elektronisku publikāciju nodrošināšana tiešsaistē; Profesionālo iemaņu trenēšana; Nelejupielādējamu videomateriālu nodrošināšana tiešsaistē; Izstāžu organizēšana kultūras un izglītības nolūkiem; Kultūras pasākumi; Elektronisko grāmatu un žurnālu publicēšana tiešsaistē; Komandu veidošana (izglītība); Recenziju publikācija tiešsaistē izklaides jomā; Apmācība praktisko iemaņu apgūšanā ar demonstrēšanas palīdzību; Sanāksmju rīkošana kultūras jomā; Semināri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Gwida vokazzjonali (konsulenza fil-qasam tal-edukazzjoni jew tat-taħriġ); Kiri ta' opuskoli; Pubblikazzjoni ta' materjal multimedjali onlajn; Provvista ta' tagħlim; Tmexxija ta' werkxops [taħriġ]; L-arranġament u t-tmexxija ta' simpożji; Organizzazzjoni ta' preżentazzjonijiet għal skopijiet edukattivi; L-arranġament u t-tmexxija ta' konferenzi edukattivi; Pubblikazzjoni ta' manwali; L-arranġament u t-tmexxija ta' lezzjonijiet; Organizzazzjoni ta' konferenzi għal skopijiet edukattivi; Traduzzjoni u interpretazzjoni; Il-provvista ta' korsijiet tat-taħriġ; Il-pubblikazzjoni ta' testi (minbarra testi pubbliċitarji); Self ta' kotba u pubblikazzjonijiet oħra; Servizzi għall-pubblikazzjoni ta' rapporti informali; L-arranġament u t-tmexxija ta' kompetizzjonijiet [edukazzjoni jew divertiment]; Kiri ta' kotba; Organizzazzjoni ta' taħriġ; Ħruġ ta' pubblikazzjonijiet ta' perjodiċi u kotba fil-forma elettronika; Servizzi ta' tagħlim mill-bogħod provduti onlajn; Servizzi ta' tuturing; Tmexxija ta' korsijiet edukattivi; Arranġament, tmexxija u organizzazzjoni ta' workshops [taħriġ]; Pubblikazzjoni multimedjali ta' magazins, ġurnali u gazzetti; Servizzi ta' librerija; Servizzi ta' konferenzi; Organizzazzjoni ta' kungressi u konferenzi għal skopijiet kulturali u edukattivi; Trasferiment ta' know-how [taħriġ]; Arranġament, tmexxija u organizzazzjoni ta' kunċerti; Taħriġ; L-organizzazzjoni u t-tmexxija ta' konferenzi, kungressi u simposji; Akkademji [edukazzjoni]; It-tixrid ta' materjal edukattiv; Il-pubblikazzjoni ta' kotba; Provvista ta' pubblikazzjonijiet elettroniċi onlajn, li ma jistgħux jitniżżlu; Servizzi ta' taħriġ għal xogħol; Forniment ta' vidjows online, li ma jitniżżlux; L-organizzazzjoni ta' esibizzjonijiet għal skopijiet kulturali u edukattivi; Attivitajiet kulturali; Il-pubblikazzjoni ta' kotba elettroniċi u ġurnali onlajn; Bini ta' tims (edukazzjoni); Pubblikazzjoni ta’ reviżjonijiet online fil-qasam tad-divertiment; Taħriġ prattiku [demostrazzjoni]; Arranġament ta' konvenzjonijiet għal skopijiet kulturali; Seminars.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Beroepsvoorlichting [advisering op het gebied van opvoeding of opleiding]; Verhuur van gedrukte publicaties; Publicatie van multimediamateriaal online; Educatie; Workshops (opleiding) het houden van -; Het organiseren en houden van symposia; Organisatie van presentaties voor opleidingsdoeleinden; Het organiseren en houden van trainingsseminars; Uitgeven van handleidingen; Organiseren en houden van lezingen; Organisatie van conferenties voor educatieve doeleinden; Vertaling en vertolking; Instructiecursussen (Het geven van -); Tekstuitgave, andere dan publicitair; Uitleen van boeken en andere publicaties; Uitgeven van nieuwsbrieven; Organiseren en houden van wedstrijden [onderwijs of ontspanning]; Verhuur van boeken; Organisatie van opleidingen; Publicatie van tijdschriften en boeken in elektronische vorm; Online afstandsonderwijs; Mentoraat; Educatieve cursussen (Het houden van -); Voorbereiding, uitvoering en organisatie van workshops [training]; Multimediale uitgeverij van magazines, tijdschriften en kranten; Bibliotheekdiensten; Conferentiediensten; Organisatie van congressen en conferenties voor culturele en educatieve doeleinden; Overdracht van knowhow [training]; Voorbereiding, uitvoering en organisatie van concerten; Opleiding; Organiseren en houden van conferenties, congressen en symposia; Academies [onderwijs]; Ter beschikking stellen van onderwijsmateriaal; Uitgave van boeken; Ter beschikking stellen van online, niet-downloadbare elektronische publicaties; Beroepsvaardigheidstraining; Ter beschikking stellen van online niet-downloadbare video's; Organisatie van tentoonstellingen voor culturele of educatieve doeleinden; Culturele activiteiten; Online publicatie van elektronische boeken en periodieken; Teambuilding (onderwijs); Publicatie van onlinerecensies op het gebied van entertainment; Praktijkonderwijs [demonstratie]; Organisatie van bijeenkomsten voor culturele doeleinden; Seminars.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Doradztwo zawodowe; Wypożyczanie publikacji drukowanych; Publikowanie materiałów multimedialnych online; Usługi w zakresie oświaty [nauczanie]; Prowadzenie warsztatów [szkolenia]; Organizowanie i prowadzenie sympozjów; Organizowanie prezentacji do celów edukacyjnych; Organizacja i przeprowadzanie seminariów szkoleniowych; Publikacja podręczników użytkownika; Organizowanie i prowadzenie wykładów; Organizowanie konferencji w celach edukacyjnych; Tłumaczenia; Usługi w zakresie zapewniania kursów szkoleniowych; Publikowanie tekstów, innych niż teksty reklamowe; Wypożyczanie książek i innych publikacji; Usługi w zakresie publikacji biuletynów; Organizowanie i prowadzenie konkursów [edukacyjnych lub rozrywkowych]; Wypożyczanie książek; Organizacja szkoleń; Wydawanie czasopism i książek w postaci elektronicznej; Usługi nauki na odległość świadczone online; Nauczanie indywidualne; Prowadzenie kursów edukacyjnych; Przygotowywanie, organizowanie i prowadzenie warsztatów [szkolenia]; Publikowanie multimedialne magazynów, czasopism i gazet; Usługi biblioteczne; Usługi w zakresie konferencji; Organizowanie kongresów i konferencji w celach kulturalnych i edukacyjnych; Przekazywanie know-how [szkolenia]; Przygotowywanie, organizowanie i prowadzenie koncertów; Nauczanie; Organizowanie i prowadzenie konferencji, kongresów i sympozjów; Wyższe uczelnie [edukacja]; Rozpowszechnianie materiałów edukacyjnych; Publikowanie książek; Udostępnianie publikacji elektronicznych [nie do pobrania]; Trening umiejętności zawodowych; Udostępnianie filmów online nie do pobrania; Organizowanie wystaw w celach kulturalnych lub edukacyjnych; Imprezy kulturalne; Publikowanie on-line elektronicznych książek i czasopism; Budowanie zespołu (edukacja); Publikacja recenzji online w dziedzinie rozrywki; Kształcenie praktyczne [pokazy]; Organizowanie zjazdów w celach kulturalnych; Seminaria.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Orientação profissional [consultoria em educação ou formação]; Aluguer de publicações impressas; Publicação online de material multimédia; Educação; Direção de cursos [formação]; Organização e realização de simpósios; Organização de apresentações com fins educativos; Organização e realização de seminários de formação; Publicação de manuais; Organização e realização de palestras; Organização de conferências relacionadas com educação; Tradução e interpretação; Fornecimento de cursos de formação; Publicação de textos, com exceção dos textos publicitários; Empréstimo de livros e outras publicações; Publicação de boletins informativos; Organização e realização de competições [educação ou divertimento]; Serviços de aluguer de livros; Organização de atividades de formação; Publicação de publicações periódicas e livros em formato eletrónico; Serviços de ensino à distância via online; Tutoria; Realização de cursos educativos; Preparação, direção e organização de workshops [formação]; Publicação multimédia de revistas, revistas especializadas e jornais; Serviços bibliotecários; Serviços de conferências; Organização de congressos e conferências com fins culturais e educativos; Transferência de know-how [formação]; Preparação, direção e organização de concertos; Formação; Organização e realização de conferências, congressos e simpósios; Academias [educação]; Divulgação de material educativo; Publicação de livros; Serviços online de publicações eletrónicas, não descarregáveis; Formação em técnicas profissionais; Disponibilização de vídeos online, não descarregáveis; Organização de exposições para fins culturais ou educativos; Atividades culturais; Publicação on-line de livros e jornais eletrónicos; Formação de equipas (educação); Publicação de críticas em linha no domínio do entretenimento; Formação prática [demonstração]; Organização de convenções para fins culturais; Seminários.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Orientare profesională [consiliere în domeniul educației sau formării]; Împrumut de publicații imprimate; Publicarea de materiale multimedia online; Educație; Coordonare de ateliere de pregătire profesională; Organizarea și conducerea de simpozioane; Organizare de prezentări cu scopuri educative; Organizare și coordonare de seminare de formare; Publicare de manuale; Organizare și coordonare de prelegeri; Organizare de conferințe în scopuri educaționale; Traducere și interpretare; Furnizare de cursuri de instruire; Publicare de texte, altele decât textele publicitare; Împrumut de cărți și de alte publicații; Publicare de buletine informative; Organizare și coordonare de competiții [educație sau divertisment]; Închiriere de cărți; Organizare de sesiuni de formare; Publicare de periodice și cărți în format electronic; Servicii de învățământ la distanță oferite online; Îndrumare; Coordonare de cursuri de instruire; Realizare, coordonare și organizare de ateliere de lucru [instruire]; Publicare multimedia de reviste, jurnale și ziare; Servicii de bibliotecă; Servicii de conferințe; Organizare de congrese și de conferințe în scopuri culturale și educative; Transfer de know-how [instruire]; Realizare, coordonare și organizare de concerte; Instruire; Organizare și coordonare de conferințe, congrese și simpozioane; Academii [educație]; Difuzare de materiale educative; Publicare de cărți; Furnizare de publicații electronice online, nedescărcabile; Formare în domeniul aptitudinilor profesionale; Furnizare de materiale video on-line, nedescărcabile; Organizarea de expoziții în scopuri culturale sau educative; Activități culturale; Publicare on-line de cărți și reviste electronice; Formarea echipelor (educație); Publicare de recenzii online în domeniul divertismentului; Formare practică [demonstrație]; Organizarea de congrese în scopuri culturale; Seminare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Poradenstvo pri voľbe povolania (v oblasti výchovy a vzdelávania); Požičiavanie tlačených publikácií; Vydávanie on-line multimediálnych materiálov; Vyučovanie; Vedenie workshopov [ďalšie vzdelávanie]; Organizovanie a vedenie sympózií; Usporadúvanie vzdelávacích prezentácií; Organizovanie a vedenie vzdelávacích konferencií; Vydávanie manuálov a príručiek; Organizovanie a vedenie prednášok; Organizovanie vzdelávacích konferencií; Prekladateľské a tlmočnícke služby; Vzdelávacie kurzy; Vydávanie textov (okrem reklamných); Požičiavanie kníh a iných publikácií; Služby týkajúce sa vydávania informačných bulletinov; Organizovanie a vedenie vzdelávacích alebo zábavných súťaží; Požičiavanie kníh; Organizovanie školenia; Vydávanie periodík a kníh v elektronickej forme; Služby diaľkového štúdia, poskytované on-line; Individuálne vyučovanie; Vedenie vzdelávacích kurzov; Usporiadanie, vedenie a organizovanie workshopov; Multimediálne vydávanie časopisov, denníkov a novín; Služby knižníc; Konferenčné služby; Organizovanie kongresov a konferencií na kultúrne a vzdelávacie účely; Odovzdávanie know-how [odborné školenie]; Usporiadanie, vedenie a organizovanie koncertov; Vzdelávanie; Organizovanie a vedenie konferencií, kongresov a sympózií; Akadémie (vzdelávanie); Rozširovanie učebných materiálov; Vydávanie kníh; Online poskytovanie elektronických publikácií (bez možnosti kopírovania); Služby týkajúce sa odborného školenia; Online poskytovanie videozáznamov (bez možnosti kopírovania); Organizovanie kultúrnych alebo vzdelávacích výstav; Kultúrna činnosť; Elektronické on-line publikovanie kníh a periodík; Vzdelávanie v oblasti teambuildingu; Zverejnenie online prieskumov v oblasti zábavy; Praktický výcvik (ukážky); Usporadúvanie zjazdov na kultúrne účely; Semináre.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Poklicno usmerjanje; Najem tiskovin; Objavljanje večpredstavnostnih materialov na spletu; Poučevanje; Vodenje delavnic [usposabljanje]; Organizacija in vodenje simpozijev; Organizacija predstavitev za izobraževalne namene; Organizacija in izvajanje seminarjev za usposabljanje; Objavljanje priročnikov; Prirejanje in izvajanje predavanj; Organiziranje konferenc za izobraževalne namene; Prevajanje in tolmačenje; Nudenje tečajev usposabljanja; Publikacija besedil, razen reklamnih besedil; Izposoja knjig in drugih publikacij; Storitve za objavljanje okrožnic; Prirejanje in vodenje tekmovanj [izobraževalnih in zabavnih]; Izposoja knjig; Organizacija usposabljanja; Objavljanje periodičnih publikacij in knjig v elektronski obliki; Storitve učenja na daljavo, nudene na spletu; Mentorstvo; Izvajanje izobraževalnih tečajev; Prirejanje, vodenje in organizacija delavnic [usposabljanje]; Multimedijsko objavljanje revij, dnevnikov in časopisov; Storitve knjižnic; Konferenčne storitve; Organizacija kongresov in konferenc za kulturne in izobraževalne namene; Prenos znanja in izkušenj [usposabljanje]; Prirejanje, vodenje in organizacija koncertov; Usposabljanje; Prirejanje in izvajanje konferenc, kongresov in simpozijev; Akademije [izobraževanje]; Širjenje izobraževalnega gradiva; Objavljanje knjig; Nudenje spletnih elektronskih publikacij, nenaložljivih; Usposabljanje na področju poklicnih spretnosti; Nudenje spletnih videoposnetkov, ki se jih ne da naložiti preko računalniške mreže; Organizacija razstav za kulturne ali izobraževalne namene; Kulturne dejavnosti; Spletno objavljanje elektronskih knjig in časopisov; Gradnja ekipe (izobraževanje); Objavljanje spletnih recenzij s področja razvedrila; Praktično usposabljanje [predstavitve]; Prirejanje kongresov za kulturne namene; Seminarji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Yrkesrådgivning [utbildning eller träningsråd]; Uthyrning av tryckta skrifter; Publicering av multimediematerial online; Anordnande av undervisning; Genomförande av workshopar; Arrangerande och hållande av symposier; Anordnande av presentationer för utbildningsändamål; Anordnande och genomförande av utbildningsseminarier; Publicering av handböcker; Arrangerande och genomförande av föreläsningar; Ledning av utbildningskonferenser; Översättning och tolkning; Anordnande av handledning/instruktion och kurser; Publicering av texter, inte reklamtexter; Utlåning av böcker och andra publikationer; Publicering av informationsblad; Anordnande och genomförande av tävlingar [utbildning och underhållning]; Uthyrning av böcker; Organiserande av handledning/instruktion; Utgivning av tidskrifter och böcker i elektronisk form; Distansstudietjänster tillhandahållna online; Handledning; Ledning av utbildningskurser; Arrangerande, genomförande och anordnande av workshopar [utbildning]; Multimediepublicering av tidskrifter, journaler och tidningar; Bibliotekstjänster; Konferenstjänster; Organisation av kongresser och konferenser för kultur- och utbildningsändamål; Överföring av know-how [utbildning]; Anordnande, genomförande och organisation av konserter; Instruktionstjänster; Arrangerande och genomförande av konferenser, kongresser och symposier; Utbildningsakademier; Spridning av utbildningsmaterial; Utgivning av böcker; Upplåtande av elektroniska publikationer online, inte nedladdningsbara; Yrkesrelaterad handledning; Upplåtande av filmer online, inte nedladdningsbara; Anordnande av utställningar för kulturella eller utbildningsändamål; Kulturverksamhet; Publicering av elektroniska böcker och tidskrifter online; Teambuilding (undervisning/utbildning); Publicering av online-recensioner inom området underhållning; Praktisk utbildning [instruktion]; Anordnande av sammankomster för kulturella ändamål; Seminarier.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>45</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Юридически проучвания; Консултиране относно съдебни спорове; Лицензиране на интелектуална собственност и индустриална такава; Арбитраж в областта на индустриалните отношения; Правно администриране на лицензи; Регистрационни услуги (юридически); Арбитраж; Услуги за изготвяне на правни документи; Предоставяне на експертни становища по правни въпроси; Посредничество при юридически процедури; Услуги за извън съдебно уреждане на спорове; Медиация; Консултантски услуги в областта на интелектуалната собственост; Правна помощ при изготвянето на договори; Услуги за онлайн социални мрежи; Процесуално прeдставителство; Услуги за политическо лобиране; Услуги за арбитраж, медиация и решаване на спорове; Лицензиране на компютърен софтуер [юридически услуги]; Правни услуги във връзка с преговори по договори за трети лица; Лицензиране на търговски марки [правни услуги]; Услуги за разкриване на измами в областта на здравното застраховане; Услуги за правна помощ; Правни консултации; Правни съвети и представителство; Услуги на адвокати, имащи право да пледират във висши съдебни инстанции; Управление на авторски права.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Právní průzkum; Konzultace v oblasti vedení sporů; Poskytování licencí k duševnímu vlastnictví; Arbitrážní služby v oblasti pracovních vztahů; Právní správa licencí; Registrační služby (právní); Služby rozhodců; Příprava právních dokumentů; Poskytování odborných právních posudků; Zprostředkování při právních řízeních; Mimosoudní řešení sporů; Mediace (smírné řešení sporů); Poradenství v oblasti duševního vlastnictví; Právní asistence při sestavování smluv; Služby navazování sociálních kontaktů na internetu; Služby pomoci při vedení soudních sporů; Služby v oblasti politického lobování; Arbitrážní, zprostředkovatelské služby a služby v oblasti řešení sporů; Poskytování licencí k počítačovému softwaru [právní služby]; Právní služby v oblasti sjednávání smluv pro jiné osoby; Udělování licencí k ochranným známkám [právní služby]; Služby odhalování podvodů v oblasti zdravotního pojištění; Služby právní pomoci; Právní poradenství; Právní poradenství a zastupování; Advokátní a právní služby; Správa autorských práv.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Juridiske undersøgelser; Konsulenttjenester vedrørende retstvister; Licensering af immaterielle rettigheder; Voldgiftstjenester i forbindelse med arbejdsmarkedsforhold; Juridisk administration af licenser; Registrering (juridisk); Arbitragevirksomhed [voldgift]; Udfærdigelse af juridiske dokumenter; Tilvejebringelse af juridiske ekspertudtalelser; Mægling ved retslige procedurer; Alternativ konfliktmægling; Mediation [mægling]; Rådgivning vedrørende immaterielle rettigheder; Juridisk assistance ved udarbejdelse af kontrakter; On-line sociale netværkstjenester; Støtte ved retstvister; Politisk lobbyvirksomhed; Tjenester vedrørende voldgift, mægling og bilæggelse af tvister; Licensering af computer software [juridisk bistand]; Juridisk bistand i forbindelse med forhandling af kontrakter for tredjepart; Licensgivning i forbindelse med varemærker [juridisk bistand]; Tjenester vedrørende påvisning af svindel med sygeforsikringer; Retshjælpstjenester; Juridiske råd; Juridisk bistand og repræsentation; Tjenesteydelser udbudt af en advokat; Administration af ophavsret.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Rechtsrecherche; Beratungsdienste bei Rechtsstreitigkeiten; Lizenzvergabe von gewerblichen Schutzrechten; Schlichtungsdienstleistungen bezüglich geschäftlichen Beziehungen; Rechtliche Lizenzverwaltung; Juristische Registrierungsdienste; Schlichtungsdienstleistungen; Abfassung juristischer Dokumente für Dritte; Zurverfügungstellen von juristischen Gutachten; Mediation in Rechtsverfahren; Dienstleistungen auf dem Gebiet der nicht-juristischen Streitregelung; Mediation; Beratung in Fragen gewerblicher Schutzrechte; Rechtshilfe bei der Erstellung von Verträgen; Knüpfen von sozialen Kontakten im Internet; Unterstützende Dienstleistungen in Prozessangelegenheiten; Politisches Lobbying; Schlichtungs-, Mediations- und Konfliktlösungsdienstleistungen; Lizenzierung von Computersoftware [juristische Dienstleistungen]; Juristische Dienstleistungen auf dem Gebiet der Vertragsverhandlung für Dritte; Lizenzierung von Marken [juristische Dienstleistungen]; Betrugsaufdeckungsdienstleistungen im Bereich der Krankenversicherung; Rechtshilfedienstleistungen; Rechtsberatung; Rechtsberatung und -vertretung; Rechtsanwaltsdienste; Verwaltung von Urheberrechten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Νομική έρευνα· Συμβουλευτική σχετικά με δικαστικές διαφορές· Εκχώρηση αδειών χρήσης δικαιωμάτων πνευματικής ιδιοκτησίας· Υπηρεσίες διαιτησίας για εργασιακές σχέσεις· Νομική διαχείριση αδειών· Υπηρεσίες καταχώρισης (νομικές)· Υπηρεσίες διαιτησίας· Υπηρεσίες σύνταξης νομικών εγγράφων· Παροχή νομικών γνωμοδοτήσεων από εμπειρογνώμονες· Διαμεσολάβηση σε νομικές διαδικασίες· Επίλυση διαφορών χωρίς προσφυγή στη δικαιοσύνη ή σε διαιτησία· Υπηρεσίες μεσολάβησης· Υπηρεσίες παροχής συμβουλών σε θέματα πνευματικής ιδιοκτησίας· Νομική υποστήριξη κατά την κατάρτιση συμβάσεων· Υπηρεσίες κοινωνικής δικτύωσης επί γραμμής· Υπηρεσίες υποστήριξης για δικαστικές διαφορές· Υπηρεσίες άσκησης πίεσης για πολιτικούς σκοπούς· Υπηρεσίες διαιτησίας, μεσολάβησης και άλλων μορφών επίλυσης διαφορών· Παραχώρηση άδειας χρήσης λογισμικού ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών [νομικές υπηρεσίες]· Νομικές υπηρεσίες σε σχέση με τη διαπραγμάτευση συμβάσεων για λογαριασμό τρίτων· Χορήγηση αδειών χρήσης εμπορικών σημάτων [νομικές υπηρεσίες]· Υπηρεσίες ανίχνευσης απάτης στον τομέα της ασφάλειας υγείας· Υπηρεσίες νομικής αρωγής· Νομικές συμβουλές· Παροχή νομικών συμβουλών και εκπροσώπησης· Υπηρεσίες παρεχόμενες από δικηγόρους· Διαχείριση δικαιωμάτων πνευματικής ιδιοκτησίας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Legal research; Litigation consultancy; Licensing of intellectual property; Arbitration services relating to industrial relations; Legal administration of licences; Registration services (legal); Arbitration services; Legal document preparation services; Provision of expert legal opinions; Mediation in legal procedures; Alternative dispute resolution services; Mediation; Intellectual property consultancy; Legal assistance in the drawing up of contracts; Online social networking services; Litigation support services; Political lobbying services; Arbitration, mediation and dispute resolution services; Licensing of computer software [legal services]; Legal services in relation to the negotiation of contracts for others; Licensing of trademarks; Fraud detection services in the field of health care insurance; Legal aid services; Legal advice; Legal advice and representation; Barrister services; Copyright management.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Investigaciones jurídicas; Consultoría sobre litigios; Concesión de licencias de propiedad intelectual; Servicios de arbitraje relativos a las relaciones industriales; Administración jurídica de licencias; Servicios de registro (jurídicos); Servicios de arbitraje; Servicios de preparación de documentos jurídicos; Prestación de opiniones jurídicas especializadas; Mediación en trámites jurídicos; Servicios de solución extrajudicial de controversias; Mediación; Consultoría sobre propiedad intelectual; Asistencia jurídica para la redacción de contratos; Servicios de redes sociales en línea; Servicios jurídicos en caso de litigio; Servicios de grupos de presión política; Servicios de arbitraje, mediación y resolución de conflictos; Concesión de licencias de software [servicios jurídicos]; Servicios jurídicos relacionados con la negociación de contratos para terceros; Concesión de licencias de marcas [servicios jurídicos]; Servicios de detección de fraudes en el ámbito de los seguros de salud; Servicios de asistencia jurídica; Asesoramiento jurídico; Representación y asesoramiento jurídicos; Servicios de abogado; Gestión de derechos de autor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Juriidilised uuringud; Konsulteerimine kohtuprotsesside alal; Intellektuaalomandi litsentsimine; Tööstussuhetega seonduvad vahekohtuteenused; Litsentside juriidiline haldus; Juriidilised registreerimisteenused; Arbitraažiteenused; Juriidiliste dokumentide koostamise teenused; Juriidiliste ekspertarvamuste pakkumine; Juriidiliste toimingute vahendamine; Alternatiivsed vaidluste lahendamise teenused; Vahetalitus, lepitamine; Intellektuaalomandialane nõustamine; Juriidiline abi lepingute koostamisel; Suhtlusvõrgustike teenused arvutivõrgus; Kohtuprotsessidega seotud tugiteenused; Poliitilise lobitöö teenused; Vaidluste vahekohtuniku-, vahendamis- ja lahendamisteenused; Arvutitarkvara litsentsimine [juriidilised teenused]; Lepingute läbirääkimisega seotud juriidilised teenused; Kaubamärkide litsentsimine [juriidilised teenused]; Pettuste tuvastamise teenused tervishoiukindlustuse valdkonnas; Õigusabiteenused; Juriidiline nõustamine, õigusnõustamine; Juriidiline nõustamine ja esindamine; Advokaaditeenused; Autoriõiguse juhtimine, haldamine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Oikeustieteellinen tutkimus; Oikeudenkäynteihin liittyvä konsultointi; Teollisoikeuksien lisensointi; Työmarkkinasuhteisiin liittyvät välimiespalvelut; Lisenssien oikeudellinen hallinnointi; Oikeudelliset rekisteröintipalvelut; Välimiespalvelut; Oikeudellisten asiakirjojen laatiminen; Oikeudellisten asiantuntijalausuntojen tarjoaminen; Välitys oikeusprosesseissa; Vaihtoehtoiset riidanratkaisupalvelut; Sovittelupalvelut; Immateriaalioikeuksiin liittyvä konsultointi; Oikeusapu sopimusten laadinnassa; Online-muotoiset sosiaaliset verkostoitumispalvelut; Oikeuskiistoihin liittyvät tukipalvelut; Poliittiset edunvalvontapalvelut; Välimiesmenettelyyn, sovitteluun ja riitojen ratkaisuun liittyvät palvelut; Tietokoneohjelmistojen lisensointi [oikeuspalveluna]; Sopimusten neuvottelua muiden puolesta koskevat oikeudelliset palvelut; Tavaramerkkien lisensointi [oikeudelliset palvelut]; Petosten havaitsemispalvelut sairausvakuutusten alalla; Oikeusapupalvelut; Lainopillinen neuvonta; Oikeudellinen neuvonta ja edustaminen; Asianajopalvelut ylemmissä oikeusasteissa; Tekijänoikeuksien hallintapalvelut.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Recherches légales; Assistance en matière de contentieux; Concession de licences de propriété intellectuelle; Services d'arbitrages en matière de relations industrielles; Administration juridique de licences; Services d'enregistrement juridique; Services d'arbitrage; Services d'élaboration de documents juridiques; Mise à disposition d'expertises juridiques; Médiation dans le cadre de procédures juridiques; Services extrajudiciaires de résolution de différends; Médiation; Conseils en propriété intellectuelle; Assistance juridique pour la rédaction de contrats; Services de réseautage social en ligne; Services d'assistance en cas de litiges; Services de lobbying politique; Services de règlement de différends, de médiation et d'arbitrage; Concession de licences de logiciels [services juridiques]; Services juridiques en rapport avec la négociation de contrats pour des tiers; Octroi de licences de marques; Services de détection de fraudes dans le domaine de l'assurance maladie; Services d’assistance juridique; Conseils juridiques; Conseils et représentation juridiques; Services d'avocats; Gérance de droits d'auteur.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Sudske istrage; Konzultacije za vođenje parnica; Licenciranje intelektualnog vlasništva; Usluge posredovanja u industrijskim odnosima; Pravno administriranje licencija; Usluge registracije (Pravne -); Usluge arbitraže; Usluge izrade pravnih dokumenata; Pružanje stručnih pravnih mišljenja; Posredovanje u pravnim postupcima; Usluge alternativnog rješavanja sporova; Usluge medijacije; Savjeti u svezi intelektualnog vlasništva; Pravna pomoć za pripremu ugovora; Usluge online društvene mreže; Usluge podrške pri vođenju parnica; Usluge političkog lobiranja; Usluge arbitraže, posredovanja i rješavanja sporova; Ustupanje licenci za softvere [pravne usluge]; Pravne usluge povezane s pregovaranjem ugovora za druge osobe; Licenciranje žigova; Usluge otkrivanje prijevare u području zdravstvenog osiguranja; Usluge pravne pomoći; Pravni savjeti; Pravni savjeti i zastupanje; Usluge pravnog savjetnika; Upravljanje autorskim pravima.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Jogi kutatás; Peres ügyekkel kapcsolatos tanácsadás; Szellemi tulajdon licenszelése; Munkaügyi kapcsolatokhoz kapcsolódó arbitrációs szolgáltatások; Engedélyek jogi ügyintézése; Nyilvántartási szolgáltatások [jogi]; Arbitrációs szolgáltatások; Jogi dokumentumok elkészítése; Jogi szakvélemények biztosítása; Közvetítés jogi eljárásoknál; Alternatív vitarendezési szolgáltatások; Közbenjárás; Szellemi tulajdonnal kapcsolatos konzultáció; Jogi segítségnyújtás szerződések készítésénél; Online közösségi hálózatok szolgáltatásai; Litigációs segítségnyújtási szolgáltatások; Politikai lobbiszolgáltatások; Egyeztetési, közvetítési és békéltetetési szolgáltatások; Számítógépes szoftverek licenszelése, engedélyezése [jogi szolgáltatások]; Jogi szolgáltatások szerződések tárgyalásával kapcsolatban harmadik fél számára; Védjegyek engedélyeztetése [jogi szolgáltatások]; Csalások felderítésével kapcsolatos szolgáltatások az egészségbiztosítás területén; Jogsegély szolgáltatások; Jogi tanácsadás; Jogi tanácsadás és képviselet; Ügyvédi [barrister] szolgáltatások; Szerzői jogok kezelése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">ricerche legali; consulenza in materia di controversie; concessione di diritti di proprietà intellettuale; servizi di arbitrato  in materia di relazioni industriali; Amministrazione legale di licenze; servizi di registrazione (legali); servizi d'arbitrato; servizi di elaborazione documenti legali; fornitura di opinioni di esperti legali; mediazione in procedure legali; servizi di risoluzione alternativa delle controversie; mediazione; consulenza in proprietà intellettuale; assistenza legale nella redazione di contratti; fornitura di ricerche legali; servizi online di social networking.; ricerche giudiziarie; assistenza in materia di controversie; servizi di lobbying politica; servizi di arbitrato, mediazione e risoluzione di controversie; concessione di licenze di software [servizi giuridici]; servizi legali in relazione alla negoziazione di contratti per conto di terzi; concessione di licenze di marchi [servizi  legali]; servizi di accertamento di frodi  nel campo delle assicurazioni sanitarie; servizi di assistenza legale; consulenza legale; consulenze e rappresentanza legale; servizi di avvocati; gestione di diritti d'autore.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Teisiniai tyrimai; Bylinėjimosi konsultacijos; Intelektinės nuosavybės licencijavimas; Su darbo santykiais susijusios arbitražo paslaugos; Teisinis licencijų administravimas; Registravimo paslaugos (teisinės); Arbitražas; Teisinių dokumentų rengimas; Teisės ekspertų nuomonių teikimas; Tarpininkavimas teisiniuose procesuose; Alternatyvaus ginčų sprendimo paslaugos; Tarpininkavimas; Intelektinės nuosavybės konsultacijos; Teisinė pagalba, rengiant sutartis; Internetinių socialinių tinklų paslaugos; Bylinėjimosi pagalbos paslaugos; Politinio lobizmo paslaugos; Arbitražo, tarpininkavimo ir ginčų sprendimo paslaugos; Kompiuterinių programų licencijavimas [juridinės paslaugos]; Juridinės sutarčių derybų paslaugos (kitiems); Prekių ženklų licencijavimas [juridinės paslaugos]; Sukčiavimo atvejų sveikatos draudimo srityje nustatymo paslaugos; Teisinės pagalbos paslaugos; Teisinės konsultacijos; Teisiniai patarimai ir atstovavimas; Advokatų paslaugos; Autorių teisių vadyba.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Juridiskā izpēte; Tiesvedības konsultācijas; Intelektuālā īpašuma tiesību licencēšana; Arbitrāžas pakalpojumi saistībā ar industriālajām attiecībām; Licenču juridiskā pārvaldība; Juridiskie reģistrācijas pakalpojumi; Arbitrāžas pakalpojumi; Juridisko dokumentu sagatavošana; Ekspertu juridisko atzinumu nodrošināšana; Starpniecība juridiskajos procesos; Ārpustiesas strīdu risināšanas pakalpojumi; Mediācijas pakalpojumi; Konsultēšana intelektuālā īpašuma jomā; Juridiskā palīdzība līgumu sagatavošanā; Sociālās tīklošanās pakalpojumi tiešsaistē; Atbalsts tiesvedības procesos; Politiskās lobēšanas pakalpojumi; Arbitrāžas, starpniecības un strīdu izšķiršanas pakalpojumi; Datoru programmatūras licencēšana (juridiskie pakalpojumi); Juridiskie pakalpojumi, kas saistīti ar personu pārstāvēšanu sarunās par līgumu nosacījumiem; Preču zīmju licencēšana [juridiskie pakalpojumi]; Krāpšanas atklāšanas pakalpojumi veselības apdrošināšanas jomā; Juridiskās palīdzības pakalpojumi; Juridisko konsultāciju sniegšana; Juridiskās konsultācijas un pārstāvniecība; Zvērinātu advokātu pakalpojumi; Autortiesību pārvaldība.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Riċerka legali; Konsulenza dwar il-litigazzjoni; Liċenzjar ta' proprjetà intellettwali; Servizzi ta' arbitraġġ relatati mar-relazzjonijiet industrijali; Amministrazzjoni legali tal-liċenzji; Servizzi ta' reġistrazzjoni [legali]; Servizzi ta' arbitraġġ; Servizzi ta' preparazzjoni ta' dokumenti legali; Provvista ta' opinjonijiet legali mingħand esperti; Medjazzjoni dwar proċeduri legali; Servizzi ta' riżoluzzjoni alternattiva għat-tilwim; Medjazzjoni; Konsulenza dwar il-proprjetà intellettwali; Assistenza legali dwar it-tfassil ta' kuntratti; Servizzi ta' netwerking soċjali online; Servizzi ta' appoġġ għal-litigazzjoni; Servizzi ta' persważjoni politika; Servizzi ta' arbitraġġ, ta' medjazzjoni u ta' irranġar ta' tilwim; Liċenzjar ta' softwer tal-kompjuter [servizzi legali]; Servizzi legali relatati man-negozjati ta' kuntratti għal oħrajn; Għoti ta' liċenzji għal trade marks [servizzi legali]; Servizzi ta' ditezzjoni ta' frodi fil-qasam tal-assigurazzjoni tal-kura tas-saħħa; Servizzi ta' għajnuna legali; Pariri legali; Pariri u rappreżentanza legali; Servizzi ta' avukat [fil-qrati superjuri]; Ġestjoni tad-drittijiet tal-awtur.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Gerechtelijk onderzoek; Juridische advisering; Licentieverlening op het gebied van intellectuele eigendom; Arbitragediensten met betrekking tot arbeidsrelaties; Juridisch beheer van licenties; Registratiediensten [juridisch]; Arbitrage; Opstellen van juridische documenten; Verstrekken van deskundig juridisch advies; Mediation in juridische procedures [bemiddeling]; Beslechten van geschillen [buitengerechtelijke diensten]; Mediation [bemiddeling]; Advisering op het gebied van intellectuele eigendom; Juridische bijstand bij het opstellen van contracten; Online sociale netwerkdiensten; Ondersteuning bij rechtszaken; Lobbyen voor politieke doeleinden; Arbitrage, bemiddeling en geschillenbeslechting; Licentieverlening op het gebied van software [juridische diensten]; Juridische diensten met betrekking tot de onderhandeling van contracten voor anderen; Verlenen van licenties van merken [juridische diensten]; Opsporen van fraude op het gebied van ziektekostenverzekeringen; Juridische diensten; Juridisch advies; Juridisch advies en vertegenwoordiging; Juristen (Diensten van -); Beheer van auteursrechten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Badania prawne; Doradztwo w zakresie sporów sądowych; Licencjonowanie własności intelektualnej; Usługi arbitrażu w zakresie stosunków pracowniczych; Prawne administrowanie licencjami; Usługi rejestracyjne (prawne); Usługi arbitrażowe; Usługi w zakresie przygotowywania dokumentów prawnych; Udzielanie opinii prawnych przez ekspertów; Pośrednictwo w procedurach prawnych; Usługi alternatywnego rozwiązywania sporów; Mediacje; Doradztwo w zakresie własności intelektualnej; Pomoc prawna przy tworzeniu umów; Usługi serwisów społecznościowych online; Usługi wsparcia procesowego w sporach sądowych; Usługi w zakresie lobbingu politycznego; Usługi arbitrażu, mediacji i rozstrzygania sporów; Licencjonowanie oprogramowania komputerowego [usługi prawne]; Usługi prawne związane z negocjacją kontraktów dla osób trzecich; Licencjonowanie znaków towarowych [usługi prawne]; Usługi wykrywania oszustw w dziedzinie ubezpieczeń zdrowotnych; Usługi w zakresie pomocy prawnej; Doradztwo prawne; Porady prawne i zastępstwo procesowe; Usługi adwokackie; Zarządzanie prawami autorskimi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Investigação judicial; Consultadoria em matéria de contenciosos; Licenciamento da propriedade intelectual; Serviços de arbitragem relacionados com relações industriais; Gestão jurídica de licenças; Serviços de registo jurídico; Serviços de arbitragem; Serviços de elaboração de documentos jurídicos; Prestação de pareceres jurídicos; Mediação em processos jurídicos; Serviços de resolução alternativa de litígios; Mediação; Consultoria em propriedade intelectual; Assistência jurídica para a redação de contratos; Serviços de redes sociais on-line; Serviços de apoio em matéria de contencioso; Serviços de grupos de pressão política; Serviços de arbitragem, mediação e resolução de conflitos; Licenciamento de software [serviços jurídicos]; Serviços jurídicos elativos a negociação de contratos para terceiros; Licenciamento de marcas comerciais [serviços jurídicos]; Serviços de deteção de fraudes no âmbito dos seguros de saúde; Serviços de apoio jurídico; Consultadoria jurídica; Aconselhamento e representação jurídica; Serviços de advogados de barra de tribunal; Gestão de direitos de autor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Cercetări juridice; Consultanță în materie de litigii; Licențe de proprietate intelectuală (Concesiune de -); Servicii de arbitraj în legătură cu relațiile industriale; Administrarea juridică a licențelor; Servicii de înregistrare legală; Servicii de arbitraj; Servicii de pregătire a documentelor juridice; Furnizare de opinii juridice de specialitate; Intermediere în proceduri juridice; Servicii de soluționare alternativă a litigiilor; Mediere; Consiliere în domeniul proprietății intelectuale; Asistență juridică la întocmirea contractelor; Servicii de rețele de socializare on-line; Servicii de asistență pentru litigii; Servicii de lobby politic; Servicii de arbitraj, intermediere și conciliere privind conflicte; Acordare de licențe pentru software de calculator [servicii juridice]; Servicii juridice în legătură cu negocierea de contracte pentru alte persoane; Acordarea de licențe pentru mărci [servicii juridice]; Servicii de detectare a fraudelor în domeniul asigurărilor de sănătate; Servicii de consultanță juridică; Consiliere juridică; Consiliere și reprezentare juridică; Servicii furnizate de avocați pledanți; Gestionarea drepturilor de autor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Právny výskum; Poradenstvo v oblasti vedenia súdnych sporov; Udeľovanie licencií na práva duševného vlastníctva; Arbitrážne služby súvisiace s pracovnoprávnymi vzťahmi; Správa licencií (právne služby); Právne registračné služby; Arbitrážne služby; Vypracovávanie právnych dokumentov; Poskytovanie odborných právnych názorov; Sprostredkovanie pri právnych procesoch; Služby rozhodcovských súdov; Mediačné služby; Poradenstvo v oblasti práv duševného vlastníctva; Právna pomoc pri vypracovaní zmlúv; Online služby sociálnych sietí; Podporné služby pri litigácii [vedenie súdnych sporov]; Služby v oblasti politického lobizmu; Rozhodcovské, sprostredkovateľské služby a služby v oblasti urovnávania sporov; Udeľovanie licencií na počítačové programy (právne služby); Dohodovanie zmlúv pre tretie osoby (právne služby); Licencovanie ochranných známok [právne služby]; Služby odhaľovania podvodov v oblasti zdravotného poistenia; Služby právnej pomoci; Právne poradenstvo; Právne poradenstvo a zastupovanie; Služby právnych zástupcov; Spravovanie autorských práv.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Pravne raziskave; Svetovanje na področju pravnih sporov; Licenciranje intelektualne lastnine; Arbitražne storitve v zvezi z industrijskimi odnosi; Pravne storitve upravljanja dovoljenj; Storitve registracij [pravne storitve]; Arbitražne storitve; Storitve za pripravo pravnih dokumentov; Nudenje izvedenskih pravnih mnenj; Mediacija pri pravnih postopkih; Storitve alternativnega reševanja sporov; Posredovanje (mediacija); Svetovanje na področju intelektualne lastnine; Pravna pomoč pri pripravljanju pogodb; Spletne storitve družabnega mreženja; Storitve podpore pri pravdanju; Storitve političnega lobiranja; Storitve arbitraže, mediacije in reševanja sporov; Izdaja licenc za računalniško programsko opremo (pravne storitve); Pravne storitve v zvezi s pogajanjem o pogodbah za druge; Licenciranje znamk [pravne storitve]; Storitve odkrivanja goljufij na področju zdravstvenega zavarovanja; Storitve pravne pomoči; Pravno svetovanje; Pravno svetovanje in zastopstvo; Storitve odvetnikov; Upravljanje z avtorskimi pravicami.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Juridisk forskning; Rättstvistkonsultationer; Licensiering av immaterialrätter; Medlingstjänster som rör arbetsmarknadsrelationer; Juridisk administration av licenser; Juridiska registreringstjänster; Medlingstjänster; Upprättande av juridiska dokument; Tillhandahållande av juridiska expertbedömningar; Medling vid rättsliga förfaranden; Alternativa tvistelösningar; Förlikning; Immaterialrättsliga konsultationer; Juridisk assistans vid upprättande av kontrakt; Sociala nätverkstjänster online; Bistånd vid rättsliga processer; Tjänster avseende politisk lobbying; Tjänster avseende förlikning, medling och tvistlösning; Datorprogram (licensiering av -)[juridiska tjänster]; Juridiska tjänster med avseende på förhandling av kontrakt åt andra; Licensiering av varumärken [juridiska tjänster]; Tjänster avseende upptäckt av bedrägeri inom sjukvårdsförsäkringsområdet; Rättshjälpstjänster; Juridisk rådgivning; Juridisk rådgivning och juridiska ombud; Advokattjänster i högre domstolar; Förvaltning av upphovsrätter.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/146</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>704360</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>11418</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
