<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-12T08:41:18</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018225925</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018225925</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-08-11</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-12</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>Bul’Test</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>7</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Помпи [машини]; Клапани за налягане [части на машини]; Топлообменници [части на машини]; Части и компоненти за гореизброените стоки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Čerpadla [stroje]; Tlakové ventily [součásti strojů]; Tepelné výměníky [části strojů]; Části a vybavení výše uvedeného zboží.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Pumper [maskiner]; Trykventiler [dele af maskiner]; Varmevekslere [maskindele]; Dele og tilbehør til førnævnte varer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Pumpen [Maschinen]; Druckventile [Maschinenteile]; Wärmeaustauscher [Maschinenteile]; Teile oder Bestandteile für alle vorstehend genannten Waren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Αντλίες [μηχανές]· Πίεσης (βαλβίδες -) [μέρη μηχανών]· Εναλλάκτες θερμικοί [μέρη μηχανών]· Μέρη και εξαρτήματα για όλα τα προαναφερθέντα προϊόντα.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Pumps; Pressure valves (parts of machines); heat exchangers (parts of machines); parts and components of aforesaid goods.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Bombas [máquinas]; Válvulas de presión [partes de máquinas]; Intercambiadores térmicos [partes de máquinas]; Partes y accesorios de todos los productos citados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Pumbad [masinad]; Surveklapid [masinaosad]; Soojusvahetid [masinaosad]; Kõigi eelpoolmainitud toodete osad ja manused.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Pumput [koneina]; Paineventtiilit [koneiden osina]; Lämmönvaihtimet [koneiden osina]; Edellä mainittujen tavaroiden osat ja komponentit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Pompes [machines]; Soupapes de pression [pièces de machines]; Échangeurs de chaleur [parties de machines]; Pièces et accessoires des produits précités.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Crpke [strojevi]; Tlačni ventili [dijelovi strojeva]; Izmjenjivači topline [dijelovi strojeva]; Dijelovi i komponente navedenih proizvoda.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szivattyúk [gépek]; Nyomószelepek [géprészek]; Hőcserélők [gépalkatrészek]; A fent említett áruk alkatrészei és szerelvényei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Pompe; Valvole di pressione [parti di macchine]; Scambiatori di calore [parti di macchine]; Parti e componenti per i suddetti articoli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Siurbliai [mašinos]; Slėgio vožtuvai [mašinų dalys]; Šilumokaičiai [mašinų dalys]; Visų, pirmiau minėtų prekių dalys ir sudedamosios dalys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Sūkņi (mašīnas); Kompresijas vārsti [mašīnu daļas]; Siltummaiņi [mašīnu detaļas]; Visu iepriekšminēto preču daļas un piederumi.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Pompi [magni]; Valvoli tal-pressa [partijiet ta' magni]; Apparat għat-trasferiment ta' sħana minn medju għal ieħor [partijiet ta' magni]; Partijiet u komponenti għall-oġġetti msemmija.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Pompen [machines]; Drukventielen [machine-onderdelen]; Warmtewisselaars [machine-onderdelen]; Onderdelen en componenten van de voornoemde goederen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Pompy [maszyny]; Zawory ciśnieniowe [części maszyn]; Wymienniki ciepła [części maszyn]; Części i elementy wszystkich wyżej wymienionych towarów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Bombas [máquinas]; Válvulas de pressão [partes de máquinas]; Permutadores térmicos; Peças e componentes para os artigos atrás referidos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Pompe [maşini]; Presiune (supape de -) [organe de maşini]; Schimbătoare de căldură [organe de maşini]; Piese şi componente pentru toate bunurile menţionate anterior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Čerpadlá, pumpy (stroje); Výtlačné ventily (časti strojov); Výmenníky tepla (časti strojov); Časti a súčiastky pre vyššie uvedené výrobky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Črpalke [stroji]; Tlačni ventili [deli strojev]; Izmenjevalniki toplote [deli strojev]; Deli in pribor za vse omenjeno blago.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Pumpar [maskiner]; Tryckventiler [maskindelar]; Värmeväxlare [maskindelar]; Delar och komponenter för nämnda varor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Инспекционни, теглилни, измервателни, сигнални, контролни, надзорни; Апарати и уреди за провеждане, комутиране, трансформиране, акумулиране, регулиране и управление на електричество; Оборудване за обработка на данни и компютри; ЕЛЕКТРИЧЕСКИ УРЕДИ ЗА КОНТРОЛ, ТЕСТ И МОНИТОРИЗИРАНЕ; Апарати за наблюдение на машинни и индустриални процеси чрез отдалечен достъп; Апарати за температурен контрол; Топлинни регулатори; Хигрометри; Електрически кондензатори и оборудване за контрол на потока; Електронни лампи; Термостатично регулиращи се клапи; Термални контактни устройства; Максималнотокови релета; Температурен шалтер; Термоконтролери; Датчици [термостати]; Топлоенергийни измервателни апарати; Електронни лампи; Електрически клапани за регулиране; Софтуер за автоматизация на промишленото производство; Контролери за промишлена автоматизация; Аларми за засичане на изтичане на течности; Аларми за засичане на изтичане на течности за топлообменници; Уреди за наблюдение на течове от топлообменници чрез отдалечен достъп; Части и аксесоари за всички гореспоменати стоки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přístroje pro inspekci, pro vážení, měření, signalizaci, kontrolu (inspekci); Přístroje a nástroje pro vedení, přepínání, přeměnu, akumulaci, regulaci nebo řízení elektrického proudu; Zařízení ke zpracování dat a počítače; Elektrické přístroje pro kontrolu, testování a monitorování; Přístroje pro monitorování stavu strojových a průmyslových procesů vzdáleným přístupem; Termostaty; Regulátory tepla; Vlhkoměry; Elektrické kondenzátory a zařízení na regulaci průtoku; Elektronky; Termostaticky kontrolované ventily; Tepelné kontakty; Přepěťová relé; Tepelné spínače; Tepelné regulátory; Teplotní čidla (termostaty); Přístroje k měření tepelné energie; Elektronky; Elektrické kontrolní ventily; Software pro průmyslovou automatizaci; Průmyslové automatizační ovladače; Poplašná zařízení pro detekci úniku tekutin; Poplašná zařízení pro detekci úniku tekutin pro tepelné výměníky; Přístroje pro monitorování úniku z tepelného výměníku dálkovým přístupem; Části a vybavení výše uvedeného zboží.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Apparater til inspektion, vejning, måling, signalering, kontrol (overvågning); Apparater og instrumenter til ledning, omkobling, transformation, akkumulering, regulering eller kontrol af elektricitet; Databehandlingsudstyr; Elektriske kontrol-, test- og overvågningsapparater; Apparater til overvågning af maskin- og industriprocestilstande ved fjernadgang; Termostater; Varmeregulerende apparater; Hygrometre; Elektriske kapacitorer og flowstyringsudstyr; Glødekatoderør; Termostatkontrollerede ventiler; Termiske kontakter; Overbelastningsrelæer; Termoafbrydere; Termostyreenheder; Termiske sensorer [termostater]; Apparater til måling af termisk energi; Glødekatoderør; Elektriske kontrolventiler; Software til industriel automatisering; Automatiske kontrolenheder til industrielle formål; Alarmer til påvisning af væskelækager; Alarmer til detektion af væskelækager til varmevekslere; Apparater til overvågning af lækager fra varmevekslere via fjernadgang; Dele og tilbehør til ovennævnte varer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Prüf-,Wäge-, Mess-, Signal-, Kontrollapparate (Überwachung); Apparate und Instrumente zum Leiten, Schalten, Umwandeln, Speichern, Regeln und Kontrollieren von Elektrizität; Datenverarbeitungsgeräte und Computer; Elektrische Steuer-, Prüf- und Überwachungsgeräte; Apparate zur Überwachung des Zustands von Maschinen und industriellen Prozessen durch Fernzugriff; Temperaturregelungsgeräte; Wärmekontrollgeräte; Hygrometer [Feuchtigkeitsmesser]; Elektrische Kondensatoren und Durchflusssteuerungsgeräte; Elektronenröhren; Thermostatisch geregelte Ventile; Thermokontakte; Überlastrelais; Wärmeschutzschalter; Thermische Steuerungen; Wärmefühler [Thermostate]; Wärmeenergiemessgeräte; Elektronenröhren; Elektrische Regelventile; Software für die industrielle Automatisierung; Industrielle Automatisierungssteuerungen; Leckalarmgeräte für Flüssigkeiten; Leckalarmgeräte für Flüssigkeiten für Wärmetauscher; Apparate für die Überwachung von Lecks an Wärmetauschern mittels Fernzugriff; Teile der und Zubehör für die vorgenannten Waren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές επιθεώρησης, ζύγισης, μέτρησης, σηματοδότησης, ελέγχου (επίβλεψης)· Συσκευές και όργανα για την μεταφορά, διανομή, μετατροπή, συσσώρευση, ρύθμιση ή έλεγχο του ηλεκτρικού ρεύματος· Εξοπλισμός για την επεξεργασία δεδομένων και ηλεκτρονικοί υπολογιστές· Ηλεκτρικές συσκευές ελέγχου, δοκιμής και παρακολούθησης· Συσκευές παρακολούθησης της κατάστασης μηχανών και βιομηχανικών διεργασιών μέσω εξ αποστάσεως πρόσβασης· Συσκευές ρύθμισης θερμοκρασίας· Θερμότητας (Συσκευές ελέγχου -)· Υγρόμετρα· Ηλεκτρικοί και ηλεκτρονικοί πυκνωτές και εξοπλισμός ελέγχου ροής· Θερμιονικές βαλβίδες· Θερμοστατικά ελεγχόμενες βαλβίδες· Θερμικές επαφές· Ηλεκτρονόμοι υπερφόρτωσης· Θερμικοί διακόπτες (διμεταλλικοί)· Θερμικοί έλεγχοι· Θερμικοί αισθητήρες [θερμοστάτες]· Συσκευές μέτρησης θερμικής ενέργειας· Θερμιονικές βαλβίδες· Ηλεκτρικές βαλβίδες ελέγχου· Λογισμικό βιομηχανικού αυτοματισμού· Όργανα ελέγχου βιομηχανικών αυτοματισμών· Συναγερμοί ανίχνευσης διαρροής υγρών· Συναγερμοί ανίχνευσης διαρροών υγρών για εναλλάκτες θερμότητας· Συσκευές για παρακολούθηση διαρροής από εναλλάκτες θερμότητας μέσω εξ αποστάσεως πρόσβασης· Μέρη και εξαρτήματα για όλα τα προαναφερθέντα είδη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Apparatus for inspection, weighing, measuring, signalling, checking (supervision); apparatus and instruments for conducting, switching, transforming, accumulating, regulating or controlling electricity; data processing equipment and computers; electrical control, testing and monitoring apparatus; Apparatus for monitoring of machine and industrial process condition by remote access; thermostats; heat regulating apparatus; hygrometers; electric and electrical condensers and flow control equipment; Electronic valves [thermionic]; Thermostatically controlled valves; Thermal contacts; Thermal relays; Thermal switches; Thermal controls; Thermal sensors [thermostats]; Thermal energy measuring apparatus; Thermionic valves; Electric control valves; Industrial automation software; Industrial automation controls; fluid leakage detection alarms; fluid leakage detection alarms for heat exchangers; apparatus for monitoring of leakage from heat exchangers by remote access; parts and components of aforesaid goods.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos para inspeccionar, pesar, medir, señalizar y comprobar (supervisar); Aparatos e instrumentos de conducción, distribución, transformación, acumulación, regulación o control de la electricidad; Equipos para el tratamiento de la información y ordenadores; Aparatos eléctricos de control, ensayo y seguimiento; Aparatos para supervisar el estado de máquinas y procesos industriales mediante acceso remoto; Termostatos; Aparatos termorreguladores; Higrómetros; Condensadores eléctricos y equipos eléctricos de control de flujos; Válvulas termoiónicas; Válvulas controladas termostáticamente; Contactos térmicos; Relés de sobrecarga; Interruptores térmicos; Controles térmicos; Sensores térmicos [termostatos]; Aparatos de medida de energía térmica; Válvulas termoiónicas; Válvulas eléctricas de control; Software para la automatización industrial; Controles de automatización industrial; Alarmas de detección de fugas de fluidos; Alarmas de detección de fugas de fluidos para intercambiadores de calor; Aparatos para la monitorización de fugas de intercambiadores de calor mediante acceso remoto; Partes y componentes para todos los productos mencionados.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Inspektsiooni-, kaalumis-, mõõte-, signalisatsiooni-, kontroll-(järelevalve)seadmed; Elektrijuhtimis-, -jaotus-, -muundamis-, -akumuleerimis-, -reguleerimis- ja -kontrollseadmed ja -vahendid; Andmetöötlusseadmed ja arvutid; Elektrilised kontroll-, testimis- ja seireseadmed; Masinate ja tööstusprotsesside seisundi kaugseireseadmed; Termostaadid; Soojusregulaatorid; Niiskusmõõturid, hügromeetrid; Elektrilised kondensaatorid ja läbivoolu juhtimisseadmed; Raadiolambid, elektronlambid; Termostaatiliselt juhitavad ventiilid; Termokontaktid; Ülekoormusreleed; Termolülitid; Termojuhtseadmed; Termilised andurid [termostaadid]; Soojusenergia mõõteseadmed; Raadiolambid, elektronlambid; Elektrilised kontrollventiilid; Tööstusautomaatika tarkvara; Tööstusautomaatika juhtimisseadised; Vedelikulekke tuvastamise alarmid; Vedelikulekke tuvastamise alarmid soojusvahetitesse; Seadmed soojusvahetite lekete jälgimiseks kaugjuhtimise teel; Osad ja lisaseadmed eelpoolmainitud toodetele.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tarkastus-, punnitus-, mittaus-, merkinanto-, tarkastus- (valvonta-) laitteet; Laitteet ja kojeet sähkön johtamiseen, kytkemiseen, muuntamiseen, varaamiseen, säätämiseen tai hallintaan; Tietojenkäsittelylaitteet ja tietokoneet; Sähkötoimiset ohjaus-, testaus- ja valvontalaitteet; Laitteet koneiden ja teollisuusprosessien kunnon etävalvontaan; Lämpötilan säätölaitteet; Lämmönsäätölaitteet; Kosteusmittarit; Sähköiset kondensaattorit ja virtauksenohjauslaitteet; Elektroniputket; Termostaattiset ohjattavat venttiilit; Lämpökoskettimet; Ylikuormitusreleet; Lämpökytkimet; Lämpösäätimet; Lämpöanturit [termostaatit]; Lämpöenergian mittauslaitteet; Elektroniputket; Sähköllä toimivat valvontaventtiilit; Ohjelmistot teollisuuden automaatiota varten; Teollisuudessa käytettävät automaattiset ohjaimet; Nestevuotojen hälytysilmaisimet; Nestevuotojen hälytysilmaisimet lämmönvaihtimia varten; Laitteet etäyhteyden kautta tapahtuvaan lämmönvaihtimien vuotojen seurantaan; Edellä mainittujen tavaroiden osat ja tarvikkeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils d'inspection, de pesage, de mesurage, de signalisation, de contrôle (inspection); Appareils et instruments pour la conduite, la distribution, la transformation, l'accumulation, le réglage ou la commande du courant électrique; Équipements pour le traitement de l'information et les ordinateurs; Appareils électriques de commande, test et contrôle; Appareils pour la télésurveillance de l'état de machines et de procédés industriels; Appareils de réglage de la température; Appareils de contrôle de chaleur; Hygromètres; Condensateurs électriques et équipements de régulation du débit; Tubes thermoïoniques; Vannes thermostatiques; Contacts thermiques; Relais de surcharge; Interrupteurs thermiques; Commandes thermiques; Capteurs thermiques [thermostats]; Appareils de mesure de l'énergie thermique; Tubes thermoïoniques; Électrovannes de commande; Logiciels pour l’automatisation industrielle; Contrôles de production industrielle; Alarmes pour la détection de fuites de liquide; Alarmes pour la détection de fuites de liquide pour échangeurs thermiques; Appareils pour la télésurveillance de fuites provenant d'échangeurs thermiques; Pièces et composants des produits précités.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Uređaji za pregled, vaganje, mjerenje, signalizaciju, provjeru (nadzor); Aparati i instrumenti za vođenje, distribuiranje, transformiranje, akumuliranje, podešavanje ili upravljanje električne energije; Oprema za obradu podataka i računala; Uređaji za električnu provjeru, ispitivanje i nadzor; Uređaji za nadzor stanja strojnih i industrijskih procesa daljinskim pristupom; Instrumenti za kontrolu temperature; Toplina (uređaji za kontrolu topline); Higrometri; Električni i elektro kondenzatori i oprema za kontrolu protoka; Elektronske cijevi; Termostatički upravljani ventili; Termalni kontakti; Releji za preopterećenja; Termalni prekidači; Termički regulatori; Termalni senzori [termostati]; Uređaji za mjerenje termalne energije; Elektronske cijevi; Električni upravljački ventili; Softver za industrijsku automatizaciju; Upravljački elementi za industrijsku automatizaciju; Alarmi za otkrivanje istjecanja tekućine; Alarmi za otkrivanje istjecanja tekućine za izmjenjivače topline; Uređaji za nadziranje istjecanja iz izmjenjivača topline daljinskim pristupom; Dijelovi i dodatci za navedene proizvode.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Felügyeleti, súlymérő, mérő, jelző és ellenőrző (felügyeleti) berendezések; Elektromos energia vezetésére, kapcsolására, átalakítására, tárolására, szabályozására vagy ellenőrzésére szolgáló készülékek és berendezések; Adatfeldolgozási berendezések és számítógépek; Elektromos ellenőrző, tesztelő és folyamatosan ellenőrző felszerelések; Berendezések gépi és ipari folyamatok állapotának távoli eléréséhez; Hőmérséklet szabályozó készülékek; Hőmérsékletszabályozó készülékek; Nedvességmérők, higrométerek; Elektromos és villamos kondenzátorok és áramlásszabályozó berendezések; Elektroncső; Termosztatikusan vezérelt szelepek; Hőcsatolások; Túlterhelés-relék; Hőkapcsolók; Hőszabályzók; Hőérzékelők [termosztátok]; Hőenergia-mérőberendezések; Elektroncső; Elektromos vezérlőszelepek; Ipari automatizálási szoftverek; Ipari automatizálási vezérlők; Folyadékszivárgásjelző riasztások; Folyadékszivárgásjelző riasztások hőcserélőköz; Készülékek távcsatlakozással történő hőcserélőkből történő szivárgás ellenőrzésére; A fent említett áruk alkatrészei és szerelvényei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi di ispezione, pesata, di misura, di segnalazione, di controllo (supervisione); Apparecchi e strumenti per la conduzione, distribuzione, trasformazione, accumulazione, regolazione o controllo dell'elettricità; Apparecchiatura d'elaborazione dati ed elaboratori elettronici; Apparecchi elettrici di controllo, test e monitoraggio; Apparecchi per il monitoraggio di macchine e della condizione dei processi industriali tramite accesso remoto; Apparecchi di controllo della temperatura; Apparecchi di controllo del calore; Igrometri; Condensatori elettrici ed elettronici e apparecchiatura di controllo del flusso; Valvole termoioniche [radio]; Valvole a controllo termostatico; Contatti termici; Relè di sovraccarico; Interruttori termici; Controlli termici; Sensori termici [termostati]; Apparecchi di misurazione dell'energia termica; Valvole termoioniche [radio]; Valvole elettriche di regolazione; Software per automazione industriale; Comandi di automazione industriale; Strumenti di allarme per il rilevamento delle perdite di fluidi; Strumenti di allarme per il rilevamento delle perdite di fluidi per scambiatori termici; Apparecchi per il monitoraggio delle perdite da scambiatori termici tramite accesso remoto; Parti e componenti per i suddetti articoli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Tyrimų, svėrimo, matavimo, signalizavimo, tikrinimo (priežiūros) aparatai; Elektros praleidimo, perjungimo, transformavimo, akumuliavimo, reguliavimo ir valdymo aparatai ir prietaisai; Duomenų apdorojimo įrenginiai ir kompiuteriai; Valdymo, testavimo ir stebėjimo elektros prietaisai; Mašinų ir pramonės procesų būklės nuotoline prieiga stebėjimo aparatai; Termostatai; Šilumos reguliavimo aparatai; Higrometrai; Elektros ir elektriniai kondensatoriai ir srauto kontrolės įranga; Termoelektroniniai vamzdeliai; Termostatiškai valdomi vožtuvai; Terminiai kontaktai; Perkrovos relės; Šiluminiai jungikliai; Terminiai valdikliai; Šiluminiai jutikliai [termostatai]; Šiluminės energijos matavimo aparatai; Termoelektroniniai vamzdeliai; Elektriniai valdymo vožtuvai; Pramonės automatizavimo programinė įranga; Pramoninės automatikos valdikliai; Skysčio nuotėkio aptikimo aliarmo įrenginiai; Skysčio nuotėkio aptikimo aliarmo įrenginiai šilumokaičiams; Aparatai nuotėkio iš šilumokaičių nuotolinės prieigos stebėjimui; Pirmiau nurodytų prekių dalys ir reikmenys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Pārbaudes, svēršanas, mērīšanas, signalizācijas, pārbaudes (uzraudzības) iekārtas; Aparāti, ierīces un instrumenti elektriskās strāvas pārvadei, komutācijai, pārveidošanai, uzkrāšanai, regulēšanai vai kontrolei; Datu apstrādes iekārtas un datori; Elektriskas kontroles, testēšanas un pārraudzības ierīces; Iekārtas mašīnu un rūpniecisko procesu stāvokļa uzraudzībai ar attālinātu piekļuvi; Temperatūras kontroles aparatūra; Siltuma regulēšanas aparāti; Higrometri; Elektriski un elektriski kondensatori un plūsmas kontroles iekārtas; Elektronu lampas; Termostatiski vadāmi vārsti; Siltumjutīgi kontakti; Pārslodzes releji; Siltumjutīgi slēdži; Temperatūras regulēšanas ierīces; Termiski sensori (termostati); Siltumenerģijas mēraparāti; Elektronu lampas; Elektriskie kontroles vārsti; Ražošanas automatizācijas programmatūra; Rūpnieciskās automatizācijas kontrolierīces; Šķidruma noplūdes noteikšanas trauksmes signāli; Šķidruma noplūdes noteikšanas trauksmes signāli siltummaiņiem; Aparāti noplūdes kontrolei no siltummaiņiem, izmantojot attālinātu piekļuvi; Iepriekš minēto preču daļas un armatūra.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat għall-ispezzjoni, l-użin, il-kejl, is-sinjalar, l-iċċekkjar (superviżjoni); Apparat u strumenti li jittrażmettu, jikkonnettjaw, ibiddlu, jakkumulaw, jirregolaw u jikkontrollaw l-elettriku; Tagħmir u kompjuters li jipproċessaw id-dejta; Tagħmir elettriku għal skopijiet ta' kontroll, ittestjar u monitoraġġ; Apparat għall-monitoraġġ tal-kundizzjoni tal-magni u tal-proċess industrijali b'aċċess mill-bogħod; Apparat għall-kontroll tat-temperatura; Apparat li jirregola s-sħana; Igrometri; Kondensaturi elettriċi u tagħmir għall-kontroll tal-fluss; Tubi termjoniċi; Valvoli kkontrollati bit-termostat; Kuntatti termali; Rilejs għal tagħbijiet żejda ta' elettriku; Swiċċijiet termali; Kontrolli termali; Sensers termali [termostati]; Apparat għall-kejl tal-enerġija termika; Tubi termjoniċi; Valvoli għall-kontroll bl-elettriku; Softwer ta' awtomazzjoni industrijali; Kontrolli ta' awtomazzjoni industrijali; Allarmi li jiskopru nixxija ta' fluwidi; Allarmi għad-detezzjoni ta' nixxija ta' fluwidi għal skambjaturi tas-sħana; Apparat għall-monitoraġġ tan-nixxija minn skambjaturi tas-sħana b'aċċess mill-bogħod; Partijiet u fittings għall-oġġetti msemmija qabel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Inspectie-, weeg-, meet-, sein- en controle- (inspectie-) apparaten; Apparaten en instrumenten voor de geleiding, de verdeling, de omzetting, de opslag, het regelen en het sturen van elektrische stroom; Gegevensverwerkende apparatuur en computers; Elektrische bedienings-, test- en controleapparaten; Apparatuur voor het bewaken van de conditie van machines en industriële processen via toegang op afstand; Temperatuurregulerende apparatuur; Warmtecontrole-apparaten; Vochtigheidsmeters; Elektrische condensors en uitrusting voor stromingscontrole; Thermo-ionische buizen; Thermostatisch bestuurde kleppen; Contacten (Thermische -); Overbelastingsrelais; Warmteschakelaars; Thermoregulatoren; Sensoren (thermische -) [thermostaten]; Meetapparatuur voor thermische energie; Thermo-ionische buizen; Elektrische regelkleppen; Software voor industriële automatisering; Industriële automatiseringsbesturingen; Melders voor het detecteren van vloeistoflekken; Melders voor het detecteren van vloeistoflekken bij warmtewisselaars; Apparatuur voor het bewaken van lekkage van warmtewisselaars via toegang op afstand; Onderdelen en toebehoren van genoemde waren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia do inspekcji, urządzenia wagowe, pomiarowe, sygnalizacyjne, kontrolne; Urządzenia i przyrządy do przewodzenia, przełączania, przekształcania, gromadzenia, sterowania i regulacji energii elektrycznej; Urządzenia do przetwarzania informacji i komputery; Elektryczne urządzenia kontrolne, testujące i monitorujące; Urządzenia do monitorowania stanu procesów maszynowych i procesów przemysłowych za pomocą zdalnego dostępu; Aparatura do kontrolowania temperatury; Urządzenia do kontroli i regulacji ciepła; Wilgotnościomierze; Kondensatory elektryczne i elektroniczne oraz sprzęt do regulacji przepływu; Lampy elektronowe; Zawory termostatyczne; Styczniki termiczne; Przekaźniki nadmiarowe; Wyłączniki termiczne; Regulatory termiczne; Czujniki ciepła [termostaty]; Urządzenia do pomiaru energii cieplnej; Lampy elektronowe; Elektryczne zawory regulujące; Oprogramowanie do automatyzacji przemysłowej; Sterowniki automatyki przemysłowej; Alarmy do wykrywania wycieków cieczy; Alarmy do wykrywania wycieków cieczy do użytku w wymiennikach ciepła; Urządzenia do monitorowania wycieków z wymienników ciepła za pomocą zdalnego dostępu; Części i osprzęt do uprzednio wymienionych towarów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos de inspeção, de pesagem, de medida, de sinalização ou de controlo (inspeção); Aparelhos e instrumentos para a condução, distribuição, transformação, acumulação, regulação ou controlo da corrente eléctrica; Equipamento para o tratamento da informação e computadores; APARELHOS ELÉTRICOS DE CONTROLO, TESTE E MONITORIZAÇÃO; Aparelhos para monitorização do estado de processos mecânicos e industriais através de acesso remoto; Aparelhos para controlo da temperatura; Aparelhos de regulação térmica; Higrómetros; Condensadores elétricos e equipamentos de controlo de fluxo; Tubos de cátodo quente; Válvulas controladas por termostato; Contactos térmicos; Relés de sobrecarga; Comutadores térmicos; Controlos térmicos; Sensores térmicos [termóstatos]; Aparelhos de medição da energia térmica; Tubos de cátodo quente; Válvulas elétricas de controlo; Software para automação industrial; Controlos de automação industrial; Alarmes de deteção de fugas de líquidos; Alarmes de deteção de fugas de líquidos para permutadores de calor; Aparelhos para monitorização, via acesso remoto, de fugas em permutadores de calor; Peças e componentes para os artigos atrás referidos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate pentru verificare, cântărire, măsurare, semnalizare,verificare; Aparate si instrumente pentru conducerea, distribuirea, transformarea, acumularea, reglarea sau comanda curentului electric; Echipamente pentru prelucrarea informatiilor si calculatoare; Aparate electrice de control, verificare şi monitorizare; Aparate pentru monitorizarea condiției proceselor mașinilor și industriale prin acces de la distanță; Aparate de reglare a temperaturii; Aparate de reglare a căldurii; Higrometre; Condensatoare și echipamente de control al debitului electrice și electrice; Tuburi termionice; Supape termostatice; Contacte termice; Relee de supraîncărcare; Comutatoare termice; Comenzi termice; Senzori de căldură [termostate]; Aparate de măsurare a energiei termice; Tuburi termionice; Supape electrice de control; Software pentru automatizare industrială; Comenzi de automatizare industrială; Alarme pentru detectarea scurgerilor de lichide; Alarme pentru detectarea scurgerilor de lichide pentru schimbătoare de căldură; Aparate pentru monitorizarea scurgerilor din schimbătoare de lichide prin acces de la distanță; Părţi şi accesorii pentru articolele menţionate mai sus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Prístroje kontrolné, signalizačné, kontrolné (inšpekcia) a prístroje na meranie a váženie; Prístroje a nástroje na vedenie, distribúciu, transformáciu, akumuláciu, reguláciu alebo kontrolu elektrického prúdu; Vybavenie na spracovanie údajov a počítače; Elektrické ovládacie, testovacie a monitorovacie prístroje; Prístroje na monitorovanie stavu strojov a priemyselných procesov prostredníctvom prístupu na diaľku; Termostaty; Prístroje na reguláciu tepla; Hygrometre; Elektrické kondenzátory a zariadenia na reguláciu prúdu; Elektrónky so žeravou katódou; Termostaticky kontrolované ventily; Tepelné kontakty; Prepäťové relé; Tepelné spínače; Tepelné regulátory; Teplotné snímače (termostaty); Zariadenia na meranie tepelnej energie; Elektrónky so žeravou katódou; Elektrické kontrolné ventily; Softvér pre priemyselnú automatizáciu; Ovládače priemyselnej automatizácie; Poplašné prístroje na detekciu úniku kvapalín; Poplašné prístroje na detekciu úniku kvapalín pre výmenníky tepla; Zariadenia na monitorovanie úniku z výmenníkov tepla pomocou vzdialeného prístupu; Súčiastky a armatúry na vyššie uvedené tovary.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Aparati za nadzor, tehtanje, merjenje, signalizacijo, preverjanje (nadzor); Aparati in instrumenti za prevajanje, preklapljanje, transformiranje, akumuliranje, regulacijo ali kontrolo električne energije; Oprema in računalniki za procesiranje podatkov; Električne naprave za nadzor, testiranje in nadzorno spremljanje; Aparati za spremljanje stanja strojev in industrijskih procesov z oddaljenim dostopom; Aparati za uravnavanje temperature; Aparati za reguliranje toplote; Higrometri; Električni kondenzatorji in oprema za nadzor pretoka; Termoionske cevi; Termostatično krmiljeni ventili; Toplotni kontakti; Preobremenitveni releji; Toplotna stikala; Termični regulatorji; Toplotni senzorji [termostati]; Aparati za merjenje toplotne energije; Termoionske cevi; Električni kontrolni ventili; Programska oprema za industrijsko avtomatizacijo; Krmilniki za industrijsko avtomatizacijo; Alarmi za zaznavanje puščanja tekočin; Alarmi za odkrivanje puščanja tekočin za toplotne izmenjevalnike; Aparati za nadzor puščanja iz izmenjevalnikov toplote z daljinskim dostopom; Deli in montažna oprema za omenjeno blago.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Apparater för inspektion, vägning, mätning, signalering, kontroll (övervakning); Apparater och instrument för ledning, växling, transformering, ackumulering, reglering eller kontrollering av elektricitet; Databehandlingsutrustningar och datorer; Elektriska kontroll-, prov- och övervakningsapparater; Apparater för övervakning av maskin- och industriprocessförhållanden genom fjärråtkomst; Apparater för temperaturkontroll; Värmeregleringsapparater; Fuktighetsmätare; Elektriska och elektriska kondensatorer och flödesstyrutrustningar; Glödkatodrör; Termostatstyrda ventiler; Termokontakter; Maximalreläer; Värmeomkopplare; Termiska styranordningar; Värmesensorer [termostater]; Apparater för mätning av termisk energi; Glödkatodrör; Elektriska kontrollventiler; Programvara för industriautomation; Industriella automatiseringskontroller; Gasvarnare med larm för vätskeläckage; Detekteringslarm för vattenläckage i värmeväxlare; Apparater för övervakning av läckage från värmeväxlare genom fjärråtkomst; Delar och komponenter till ovannämnda varor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Апарати за отопление, възстановяване на топлина, пастьоризиране, парогенериране (изпарители), за готвене, кипене, концентриране, изстудяване, охлаждане, сушене, вентилация, водоснабдяване и общинско отопление и санитарни цели; Топлообменници, различни от части на машини; Части и компоненти от горепосочените стоки.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Přístroje pro topení, obnovu tepla, výrobu páry, pro vaření, tepelnou úpravu, koncentraci (výparníky), přístroje chladicí, ochlazovací, pro sušení, ventilaci, rozvod vody a pro ústřední topení a sanitární zařízení; Výměníky tepla, ne části strojů; Části a komponenty pro výše uvedené zboží.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Apparater til opvarmning, varmegenvinding, dampgenerering, madlavning, kogning, koncentrering (evaporatorer), nedkøling, køling, tørring, ventilation, vandforsyning samt til fjernvarme og sanitære formål; Varmevekslere, undtagen dele af maskiner; Dele og komponenter til førnævnte varer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Heizungs-, Wärmerückgewinnungs-, Dampferzeugungs-, Koch-, Siede-, Konzentriergeräte (Verdampfer), Gefrier-, Kühl-, Trocken-, Lüftungs-, Wasserleitungsgeräte sowie Fernheizungsgeräte und sanitäre Anlagen; Wärmetauscher, ausgenommen Maschinenteile; Teile und Komponenten der vorgenannten Waren.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές θέρμανσης, ανάκτησης θερμότητας, παραγωγής ατμού, μαγειρέματος, βρασμού, συμπύκνωσης (εξατμιστήρες), κατάψυξης, ψύξης, αποξήρανσης, αερισμού, υδροδότησης και τηλεθέρμανσης και υγιεινής· Εναλλάκτες θερμότητας, εκτός από μέρη μηχανών· Μέρη και εξαρτήματα για τα προαναφερόμενα είδη.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Apparatus for heating, heat recovering, steam generating, cooking, boiling, concentration (evaporators), refrigerating, cooling, drying, ventilation, water supply and for district heating and sanitation purposes; heat exchangers; parts and components of aforesaid goods.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de calefacción, recuperación del calor, producción de vapor, cocción, ebullición, concentración (evaporadores), refrigeración, enfriamiento, secado, ventilación, suministro de agua y calefacción central y saneamiento; Intercambiadores térmicos que no sean partes de máquinas; Partes y componentes de estos productos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Kütte-, soojustaaste-, aurutootmis-, toiduvalmistus-, keedu-, kontsentreerimisseadmed (aurustid), külmutus-, jahutus-, kuivatus-, ventilatsiooni-, veevarustusseadmed ja kaugkütte- ja sanitaarseadmed; Soojusvahetid, v.a masinaosad; Eelnimetatud kaupade osad ja komponendid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Laitteet lämmitys-, lämmön talteenotto-, höyrynkehitys-, keitto-, kiehutus-, rikastus- (haihdutus-), jäähdytys-, viilennys-, kuivatus-, ilmastointi-, vesihuolto-, kaukolämmitys- ja saniteettitarkoituksiin; Lämmönvaihtimet, paitsi koneiden osina; Edellä mainittujen tavaroiden osat ja komponentit.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils à des fins de chauffage, de récupération de chaleur, de production de vapeur, de cuisson, d'ébullition, de concentration (évaporateurs), de réfrigération, de refroidissement, de séchage, de ventilation, de distribution d'eau ainsi que de chauffage urbain et d'assainissement; Échangeurs thermiques autres que parties de machines; Pièces et composants des produits précités.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Uređaji za grijanje, obnovu topline, proizvodnju pare, kuhanje, vrenje, koncentraciju (isparivači), smrzavanje, hlađenje, sušenje, ventilaciju, vodoopskrbu i za daljinsko grijanje i sanitarne potrebe; Toplinski izmjenjivači [osim dijelova strojeva]; Dijelovi i komponente prethodno navedenih proizvoda.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Berendezések és készülékek fűtéshez, hővisszanyeréshez, gőzfejlesztéshez, főzéshez, forraláshoz, sűrítéshez (párologtatók), fagyasztáshoz, hűtéshez, szárításhoz, szellőztetéshez, vízellátáshoz és távfűtéshez, valamint higiéniai célokra; Hőcserélők, nem gépalkatrészek; Minden fent említett termék részei és komponensei.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Apparecchi per il riscaldamento, il recupero di calore, la produzione di vapore, la cottura, la bollitura, la concentrazione (evaporatori), la refrigerazione, il raffreddamento, l'essiccazione, la ventilazione, la fornitura di acqua, il riscaldamento urbano e la sanificazione; Scambiatori termici, diversi da parti di macchine; Parti e componenti dei suddetti articoli.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Šildymo, šilumos atstatymo, garų generavimo, virimo, virimo, koncentravimo (garintuvai), šaldymo, vėsinimo, džiovinimo, vėdinimo, vandens tiekimo ir centralizuoto šildymo bei sanitarijos reikmenys; Šilumokaičiai, ne mašinų dalys; Pirmiau išvardytų prekių dalys ir sudėtinės dalys.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Iekārtas apkurei, siltuma atgūšanai, tvaika ģenerēšanai, ēdiena gatavošanai, vārīšanai, koncentrācijai [iztvaicētāji], dzesēšanai, atvēsināšanai, kaltēšanai, ventilācijai, ūdens apgādei un centralizētās siltumapgādes un sanitārijas vajadzībām; Siltummaiņi, kas nav mašīnu daļas; Iepriekš minēto preču daļas un komponenti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat għat-tisħin, l-irkupru tas-sħana, il-ġenerazzjoni tal-fwar, it-tisjir, it-togħlija, il-konċentrazzjoni (evaporaturi), ir-refriġerazzjoni, it-tkessiħ, it-tnixxif, il-ventilazzjoni, il-provvista tal-ilma u għal skopijiet ta' tisħin u sanitizzazzjoni ta' distrett; Apparat għat-trasferiment tas-sħana minn medju għal ieħor, mhux partijiet minn magni; Partijiet u komponenti tal-prodotti msemmija qabel.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Verwarmings-, warmteterugwin-, stoomopwekkings-, kook-, concentratie- (verdampings-), koel-, droog-, ventilatie- en waterleidingsapparaten en stadsverwarmings- en sanitaire apparaten; Warmtewisselaars, anders dan machine-onderdelen; Onderdelen en componenten van de voornoemde goederen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia do ogrzewania, odzyskiwania ciepła, generowania pary, gotowania, wrzenia, zagęszczania (parowniki), chłodzenia, schładzania, suszenia, wentylacji, zaopatrywania w wodę oraz do ogrzewania osiedli i do celów celów sanitarnych; Wymienniki ciepła, inne niż części maszyn; Komponenty i części wyżej wymienionych towarów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Aparelhos para aquecimento, recuperação de calor, produção de vapor, cozedura, fervura, concentração (evaporadores), refrigeração, arrefecimento, secagem, ventilação, distribuição de água e aquecimento urbano e para saneamento; Permutadores térmicos, que não sejam partes de máquinas; Peças e componentes dos produtos atrás referidos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate pentru încălzire, recuperarea căldurii, producere de vapori, gătit, concentrare (evaporatoare), congelare, răcire, uscare, ventilare, alimentarea cu apă și pentru termoficare și uz sanitar; Schimbătoare de căldură, altele decât cele care sunt componente ale maşinilor; Piese şi componente pentru toate produsele menţionate anterior.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Zariadenia na vykurovanie, rekuperáciu tepla, parné kotly, zariadenia na varenie, koncentráciu (odparovače), chladenie a sušenie, vetracie, vodárenské a sanitárne zariadenia a zariadenia pre okrskové kúrenie; Výmenníky tepla (nie časti strojov); Časti a komponenty vymenovaných tovarov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Aparati za ogrevanje, pridobivanje toplote, proizvodnjo pare, kuhanje, vrenje, koncentriranje (uparjalniki), zamrzovanje, hlajenje, sušenje, prezračevanje, oskrbo z vodo ter za daljinsko ogrevanje in sanitarne namene; Izmenjevalci toplote, razen deli strojev; Deli in komponente omenjenih izdelkov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Apparater för uppvärmning, värmeåtervinning, ångalstring, matlagning, kokning, koncentration (förångare), kylning, kylning, torkning, ventilation, vattentillförsel och fjärrvärme och sanitära ändamål; Värmeväxlare, inte maskindelar; Delar och komponenter för nämnda varor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>37</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Инсталиране, строителство, поддръжка и ремонт на машини, уреди за контрол на кормуване и наблюдение, апарати за отопление, инсталации за паропроизводство, за готвене, охлаждане, за сушене, вентилация, водоснабдяване [транспорт] и санитарни цели и инсталации включени в системи за индустриални процеси, засичане на течове в сгради; Засичане на течове от топлообменници в сгради.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Instalace, stavba, údržba a opravy pro stroje, přístroje pro kontrolu řízení a monitorování, přístroje pro topení, výrobu páry, pro vaření, přístroje chladicí, pro sušení, ventilaci, rozvod vody a sanitární zařízení a instalace v průmyslových procesních systémech, detekce úniků v budovách; Detekce úniků z tepelných výměníků v budovách.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Installation, opførelse, vedligeholdelse og reparation af maskiner, styre- og overvågningsapparater, apparater til opvarmning, dampdannelse, madlavning, afkøling, tørring, ventilation, vandledning og sanitære formål, samt anlæg inkluderet i industriprocessystemer, påvisning af utætheder i bygninger; Påvisning af lækager fra varmevekslere i bygninger.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Installations-, Bau-, Wartungs- und Reparaturarbeiten in Bezug auf Maschinen, Kontroll-, Steuer- und Überwachungsgeräte, Heizungs-, Dampferzeugungs-, Koch-, Kühl-, Trocken-, Lüftungs-, Wasserleitungsgeräte und sanitäre Geräte und Anlagen, die in industrielle Prozessanlagen integriert sind, Feststellung von Leckagen in Gebäuden; Feststellung von Leckagen an Wärmetauschern in Gebäuden.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες εγκατάστασης, κατασκευής, συντήρησης και επισκευής σε σχέση με μηχανές, συσκευές για έλεγχο, οδήγηση και παρακολούθηση, συσκευές θέρμανσης, παραγωγής ατμού, μαγειρέματος, ψύξης, αποξήρανσης, αερισμού, υδροδότησης και εγκαταστάσεις υγιεινής και εγκαταστάσεις περιλαμβανόμενες σε συστήματα βιομηχανικών διεργασιών, ανίχνευση διαρροών σε κτίρια· Ανίχνευση διαρροών από εναλλάκτες θερμότητας σε κτίρια.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Installation, building, maintenance and repair services for machines, apparatus for control steering and monitoring, apparatus for heating, steam generating, cooking, cooling, drying, ventilation, water supply and sanitary purposes and installations included in industrial process systems, detection of leaks within buildings; detection of leaks from heat exchangers within buildings.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios de instalación, edificación, mantenimiento y reparación de máquinas, aparatos para el control y monitorización de la dirección, aparatos de calefacción, producción de vapor, cocción, enfriamiento, secado, ventilación, suministro de agua y saneamiento e instalaciones incluidas en sistemas de procesos industriales, detección de fugas en edificios; Detección de fugas de intercambiadores de calor en edificios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Paigaldamisteenused, ehitus, hooldusteenused ja masinate parandus, seadmed juhtimiseks ja seireks, kütteseadmed, aurugeneraatorid, toidu kuumtöötlusseadmed, jahutusseadmed, kuivatid, ventilatsiooniseadmed, veevarustus ja sanitaarseadmed ja tööstuslikes töötlussüsteemides leiduvad paigaldised, lekete tuvastamine hoonetes; Soojusvahetite lekete tuvastamine hoonetes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Seuraavien asennus-, rakennus-, huolto- ja korjauspalvelut: koneet, tarkastus-, ohjaus- ja valvontalaitteet, lämmitys-, höyrynkehitys-, keitto-, jäähdytys-, kuivaus-, ilmanvaihto-, vesihuolto- ja saniteettilaitteet sekä teollisuusprosessijärjestelmiin kuuluvat laitteet, laitteet vuotojen havaitsemiseen rakennuksissa; Rakennusten lämmönvaihtimien vuotojen havaitseminen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services d'installation, de construction, d'entretien et de réparation de machines, appareils pour la commande de direction et la surveillance, appareils à des fins de chauffage, de production de vapeur, de cuisson, de refroidissement, de séchage, de ventilation, de distribution d'eau et installations sanitaires ainsi qu'installations comprises dans des systèmes de procédés industriels, détection de fuites à l'intérieur de bâtiments; Détection de fuites provenant d'échangeurs thermiques à l'intérieur de bâtiments.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Usluge instalacije, izgradnje, održavanja i popravka strojeva, uređaja za kontroliranje upravaljača i nadzor, uređaja za grijanje, proizvodnju pare, kuhanje, hlađenje, sušenje, ventilacija, vodoopskrbu i sanitarnih uređaja te instalacija uključenih u sustave indusrijskih procesa, uređaja za otkrivanje izvora istjecanja unutar zgrada; Otkrivanje izvora istjecanja iz izmjenjivača topline unutar zgrada.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Szerelési, építési, karbantartási és javítási szolgáltatások az alábbiakhoz: gépek, kormányzás és ellenőrzés vezérlőberendezések, fűtőberendezések, gőzfejlesztő, főzési, hűtési, szárítási, szellőztetési, vízellátási és egészségügyi célokra szolgáló berendezések és ipari folyamatokba beépített berendezések, szivárgások észlelése épületeken belül; Az épületek hőcserélőinek szivárgásának észlelése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di installazione, costruzione, manutenzione e riparazione per macchine, apparecchi per il controllo della guida e il monitoraggio, apparecchi per il riscaldamento, la produzione di vapore, la cottura, il raffreddamento, l'essicazione, la ventilazione, la fornitura di acqua e per la sanificazione e impianti compresi in sistemi di processi industriali, il rilevamento di perdite all'interno di edifici; Rilevamento di perdite da scambiatori termici all'interno di edifici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Montavimo, statybos, priežiūros ir remonto paslaugos, susijusios su tokiomis sritimis kaip mašinos, vairavimo ir stebėjimo valdymo aparatai, šildymo, garų generavimo, virimo, vėsinimo, džiovinimo, vėdinimo, vandens tiekimo ir sanitarinės paskirties įrenginiai bei įrenginiai, įtraukti į pramoninių procesų sistemas, nuotėkių pastatuose nustatymas; Pastatų šilumokaičių nuotėkio aptikimas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Iekārtu uzstādīšanas, celtniecības, apkopes un remonta pakalpojumi, stūres vadības un uzraudzības aparāti, apkures, tvaika ģenerēšanas, vārīšanas, dzesēšanas, žāvēšanas, ventilācijas, ūdens apgādes un sanitārijas aparāti un iekārtas, kas iekļautas rūpniecisko procesu sistēmās, noplūžu noteikšana ēkās; Siltummaiņu noplūžu noteikšana ēkās.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' installazzjoni, kostruzzjoni, manutenzjoni u tiswija għal magni, apparat għall-kontroll tal-istering u għall-monitoraġġ, apparat għat-tisħin, għall-ġenerazzjoni tal-fwar, għat-tisjir, it-tkessiħ, it-tnixxif, il-ventilazzjoni, il-provvista tal-ilma u għal skopijiet sanitarji u installazzjonijiet inklużi f'sistemi tal-proċess industrijali, id-detezzjoni tan-nixxija fil-bini; Id-detezzjoni tan-nixxija minn skambjaturi tas-sħana fil-bini.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Installatie, bouw, onderhoud en reparatie van machines, controle-, stuur- en bewakingsapparaten, verwarmings-, stoomopwekkings-, kook-, koel-, droog-, ventilatie- en waterleidingsapparaten en sanitaire installaties alsmede installaties in industriële processystemen, opsporing van lekken in gebouwen; Opsporing van lekken bij warmtewisselaars in gebouwen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Usługi instalacyjne, budownictwa, usługi konserwacji i naprawa maszyn, urządzeń do sterowania kontrolą i monitorowania, urządzeń grzewczych, do generowania pary, gotowania, chłodzenia, suszenia, wentylacji, zaopatrzenia w wodę i do celów sanitarnych oraz instalacji ujętych w systemach procesów przemysłowych, urządzeń do wykrywania wycieków w budynkach; Wykrywanie wycieków z wymienników ciepła w budynkach.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de instalação, construção, manutenção e reparação de máquinas, aparelhos para controlo da direção e monitorização, aparelhos de aquecimento, de produção de vapor, de cozedura, de arrefecimento, de secagem, de ventilação, de distribuição de água e de saneamento e instalações incluídas em sistemas de processos industriais, bem como deteção de fugas em edifícios; Deteção de fugas em permutadores de calor instalados em edifícios.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de instalare, construcție, întreținere și reparare de mașini, aparate pentru direcția de control și monitorizare, aparate pentru încălzire, producere de abur, gătit, răcit, uscat, ventilat, alimentare cu apă și instalații sanitare și instalații din sisteme pentru procese industriale, detectarea scurgerilor din clădiri; Detectarea scurgerilor din schimbătoare de căldură din clădiri.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Služby inštalácie, výstavby, údržby a opravy strojov, zariadení na ovládanie a monitorovanie, zariadení na vykurovanie, rekuperáciu tepla, parné kotly, zariadení na varenie, koncentráciu (odparovače), chladenie a sušenie, vetracích, vodárenských a sanitárnych zariadení a zariadení pre okrskové kúrenie; Detekcia úniku kvapalín pre výmenníky tepla v budovách.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Montaža, gradbeništvo, vzdrževanje in popravilo strojev, aparatov za nadzor in spremljanje, aparatov za ogrevanje, proizvodnjo pare, kuhanje, hlajenje, sušenje, prezračevanje, oskrbo z vodo in sanitarne namene, ter napeljav, vključenih v industrijske obdelovalne sisteme, zaznavanje puščanja v zgradbah; Zaznavanje puščanja iz izmenjevalnikov toplote v zgradbah.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Installation, byggnation, underhåll och maskinreparationstjänster, apparater för kontrollstyrning och -övervakning, apparater för uppvärmning, ånggenererande, kokning, kylning, torkning, ventilationsinstallationer och -apparater, vattenförsörjning och sanitära ändamål och installationer inklusive i industriella processystem, uppspårning av läckor i byggnader; Detektion av läckage från värmeväxlare i byggnader.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>42</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Развитие на индустриални процеси и услуги за съвети; Продуктови проучвания и разработки; Проектиране и разработване на продуктов дизайн; Инженеринг; Инженеринг; Изпитване, удостоверяване и контрол на качеството; Мониторинг на състоянието на машини; Услуги за наблюдение и контрол на компютърни системи; Услуги за мониторинг на промишлени процеси; Мониторинг на състоянието на течности; Наблюдение на състоянието, свързано с вибрации; Наблюдение на процеси за поддръжка и осигуряване на качеството; Наблюдение на състоянието на машини и индустриални процеси чрез отдалечен достъп; Разработване на софтуер; Услуги за наблюдение на изтичане на течности; Наблюдение на състояние, свързано с теч от топлообменници.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Vývoj průmyslových postupů a související poradenství; Výzkum a vývoj výrobků; Návrhy a rozvoj výrobků; Inženýrské služby; Inženýrské služby; Služby testování, služby ověřování a služby kontroly kvality; Monitorování stavu strojů; Služby v oblasti monitorování počítačových systémů; Služby monitorování průmyslových procesů; Kontrola stavu kapalin; Monitorování stavu ve vztahu k vibracím; Sledování postupu pro údržbu a zajištění kvality; Monitorování stavu strojů a stavu průmyslových postupů vzdáleným přístupem; Vývoj softwaru; Monitorovací služby pro únik tekutin; Monitorování stavu s ohledem na úniky z tepelných výměníků.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Industriel procesudvikling og rådgivning; Produktforskning og -udvikling; Produktdesign og -udvikling; Ingeniørvirksomhed; Ingeniørvirksomhed; Afprøvning, verificering og kvalitetskontrol; Tilstandsovervågning af maskiner; Overvågning af computersystemer; Overvågning af industriprocesser; Overvågning af væsketilstande; Tilstandsovervågning vedrørende vibrationer; Procesovervågning med henblik på vedligeholdelse og kvalitetssikring; Overvågning af maskintilstand og industriel procestilstand ved fjernadgang; Softwareudvikling; Overvågning af væskelækager; Tilstandsovervågning i forbindelse med lækager fra varmevekslere.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Entwicklung und Beratung in Bezug auf industrielle Prozesse; Erforschung und Entwicklung von Produkten; Produktdesign und -entwicklung; Dienstleistungen von Ingenieuren; Dienstleistungen von Ingenieuren; Prüfung, Authentifizierung und Qualitätskontrolle; Maschinenzustandsüberwachung; Computersystemüberwachungsdienste; Überwachung industrieller Abläufe; Zustandsmessung von Flüssigkeiten; Zustandsüberwachung in Bezug auf Schwingungen; Prozessüberwachung für Wartung und Qualitätssicherung; Maschinenzustandsüberwachung und Überwachung des Zustands industrieller Prozesse durch Fernzugriff; Softwareentwicklung; Lecküberwachung in Bezug auf Flüssigkeiten; Zustandsüberwachung in Bezug auf Lecks an Wärmetauschern.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Υπηρεσίες ανάπτυξης και παροχής συμβουλών σε θέματα βιομηχανικών διεργασιών· Έρευνα και ανάπτυξη προϊόντων· Σχεδιασμός και ανάπτυξη προϊόντων· Μηχανολογικές υπηρεσίες· Μηχανολογικές υπηρεσίες· Δοκιμές, πιστοποίηση και ποιοτικός έλεγχος· Παρακολούθηση κατάστασης μηχανών· Υπηρεσίες παρακολούθησης συστημάτων ηλεκτρονικών υπολογιστών· Υπηρεσίες για την παρακολούθηση βιομηχανικών διαδικασιών· Παρακολούθηση κατάστασης σε σχέση με ρευστά· Παρακολούθηση της κατάστασης αναφορικά με δονήσεις· Παρακολούθηση διεργασιών για σκοπούς συντήρησης και διασφάλισης της ποιότητας· Παρακολούθηση της κατάστασης μηχανών και της κατάστασης βιομηχανικών διεργασιών μέσω εξ αποστάσεως πρόσβασης· Ανάπτυξη λογισμικού για ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Υπηρεσίες παρακολούθησης για την ανίχνευση διαρροών· Παρακολούθηση κατάστασης κτιρίων σε σχέση με την ανίχνευση διαρροών από εναλλάκτες θερμότητας.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Industrial process development and advisory services; Product research and development; Product design and development; Engineering; Engineering services; Testing, authentication and quality control; Machine condition monitoring; Computer system monitoring services; Services for monitoring industrial processes; Condition monitoring relating to fluids; Condition monitoring relating to vibrations; Process monitoring for maintenance and quality assurance; Monitoring of machine condition and industrial processes condition by remote access; Software development; fluid leakage monitoring services; condition monitoring relating to leakage from heat exchangers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Servicios desarrollo de procesos y de asesoramiento industriales; Investigación y desarrollo de productos; Diseño y desarrollo de productos; Servicios de ingeniería; Servicios de ingeniería; Pruebas, autenticaciones y control de calidad; Supervisión del estado de máquinas; Monitorización de sistemas informáticos; Servicios para supervisar procesos industriales; Monitorización del estado de fluidos; Supervisión del estado en cuanto a vibraciones; Supervisión de procesos para el mantenimiento y aseguramiento de la calidad; Supervisión del estado de máquinas y del estado de procesos industriales mediante acceso remoto; Desarrollo de software; Servicios de monitorización de fugas de fluidos; Monitorización de estado en relación con fugas de intercambiadores de calor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Tööstusprotsessi arendus- ja nõustamisteenused; Toodete teadus- ja arendustegevus; Tootekujundus ja -arendus; Inseneriteenused; Inseneriteenused; Testimine, autentimine ja kvaliteedikontroll; Masinate seisundi kontrollimine; Arvutisüsteemide monitooring; Tööstusprotsesside seire; Vedelike seisundi seire; Vibratsioonidega seotud seisundiseire; Hooldus- ja kvaliteedikontrolli protsessiseire; Masina seisundi ja tööstusprotsesside seisundi kaugseire; Tarkvara arendamine; Vedelikulekete seireteenused; Soojusvahetite leketega seotud seisukordade jälgimine.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Teollisuusprosesseihin liittyvät kehittämis- ja neuvontapalvelut; Tuotetutkimus ja -kehittely; Tuotesuunnittelu ja -kehitys; Insinööripalvelut; Insinööripalvelut; Testaus, todentaminen ja laadunvalvonta; Koneiden kunnonvalvonta; Tietokonejärjestelmien seurantapalvelut; Teollisten prosessien valvontapalvelut; Nesteiden kuntoon liittyvä seuranta; Tärinään liittyvä kunnon seuranta; Prosessinvalvonta huoltoa ja laadunvarmistusta varten; Koneiden kunnon ja teollisuusprosessien kunnon etävalvonta; Ohjelmistokehitys; Nestevuotojen seurantapalvelut; Kunnonvalvonta, joka liittyy lämmönvaihtimien vuotoihin.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Services de développement et de conseils en matière de procédés industriels; Recherche et développement de produits; Conception et développement de produits; Services d'ingénierie; Services d'ingénierie; Tests, authentification et contrôle de la qualité; Monitorage de l'état des machines; Services de surveillance de système informatique; Services de monitorage des processus industrielles; Contrôle de qualité de l'état des fluides; Surveillance d'état relative aux vibrations; Surveillance de procédés pour la maintenance et la garantie de qualité; Télésurveillance de l'état de machines et de l'état de procédés industriels; Développement de logiciels; Services de surveillance de fuites de liquide; Surveillance d'état relative aux fuites provenant d'échangeurs thermiques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Razvoj industrijskih postupaka i usluge savjetovanja; Istraživanje i razvoj proizvoda; Dizajn i razvoj proizvoda; Inženjerske usluge; Inženjerske usluge; Ispitivanje, provjera autentičnosti i kontrola kvalitete; Nadgledanje stanja strojeva; Usluge nadzora računalnih sustava; Usluge nadzora industrijskih postupaka; Praćenje stanja tekućina; Praćenje stanja koje se odnosi na vibracije; Nadgledanje procesa radi održavanja i osiguranja kvalitete; Nadgledanje stanja strojeva i stanja industrijskih procesa daljinskim pristupom; Razvoj softvera; Usluge nadzora istjecanja tekućine; Nadzor stanja u svezi s istjecanjem iz izmjenjivača topline.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Ipari folyamatfejlesztő és tanácsadási szolgáltatások; Termékkutatás és -fejlesztés; Terméktervezés és fejlesztés; Mérnöki munkák, szolgáltatások; Mérnöki munkák, szolgáltatások; Tesztelés, hitelesítés és minőségellenőrzés; Gépek állapotának megfigyelése, ellenőrzése; Számítógépes rendszerek monitorozása; Szolgáltatások ipari folyamatok figyelésére; Folyadékokkal kapcsolatos állapot-monitorozás; Vibrációval kapcsolatos állapotmegfigyelés; Folyamatkezelés karbantartáshoz és minőségbiztosításhoz; Gépek és ipari folyamatok állapotának megfigyelése távoli hozzáféréssel; Számítógépes szoftver fejlesztése; Folyadékszivárgás ellenőrző szolgáltatások; A hőcserélőkből történő szivárgás állapotának ellenőrzése.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Servizi di consulenza e sviluppo dei processi industriali; Ricerca e sviluppo di prodotti; Progettazione e sviluppo di prodotti; Servizi di ingegneria; Servizi di ingegneria; Collaudi, certificazioni e controllo di qualità; Monitoraggio delle condizioni di macchinari; Servizi di monitoraggio di sistemi informatici; Servizi per il monitoraggio di processi industriali; Monitoraggio delle condizioni in materia di fluidi; Monitoraggio delle condizioni relative alle vibrazioni; Monitoraggio dei processi per la manutenzione e la garanzia di qualità; Monitoraggio della condizione delle macchine e della condizione dei processi industriali tramite accesso remoto; Sviluppo di software; Servizi di monitoraggio di perdite di fluidi; Monitoraggio delle condizioni relative alle perdite di scambiatori termici.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Pramoninių procesų tobulinimo ir patariamosios paslaugos; Produktų tyrimai ir plėtra; Gaminių projektavimas (dizainas) ir plėtra; Inžinerijos paslaugos; Inžinerijos paslaugos; Bandymai, autentifikavimas ir kokybės tikrinimas; Aparatų būklės priežiūra; Kompiuterinių sistemų priežiūros paslaugos; Pramoninių procesų stebėjimas; Skysčių būklės stebėjimas; Būklės priežiūra, susijusi su virpesiais; Priežiūros ir kokybės užtikrinimo procesų stebėjimas; Mašinų būklės ir pramoninių procesų būklės stebėjimas nuotoline prieiga; Programinės įrangos tobulinimas; Skysčių nuotėkio stebėjimo paslaugos; Būklės stebėjimas, susijęs su nuotėkiu iš šilumokaičių.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Rūpniecisko procesu izstrāde un konsultāciju pakalpojumi; Produktu pētniecība un izstrāde (R un D); Produktu attīstīšana un dizaina izstrāde; Inženiertehniskie pakalpojumi; Inženiertehniskie pakalpojumi; Testēšana, autentifikācija un kvalitātes kontrole; Mašīnu stāvokļa kontrole; Datorsistēmu pārraudzība; Pakalpojumi ražošanas procesu uzraudzības jomā; Šķidrumu stāvokļa uzraudzība; Stāvokļa uzraudzība saistībā ar vibrācijām; Procesa uzraudzība uzturēšanai un kvalitātes nodrošināšanai; Mašīnas stāvokļa un rūpniecisko procesu stāvokļa uzraudzība, izmantojot attālinātu piekļuvi; Datoru programmatūru izstrāde; Šķidruma noplūdes uzraudzības pakalpojumi; Stāvokļa uzraudzība saistībā ar noplūdi no siltummaiņiem.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Servizzi ta' żvilupp u pariri dwar il-proċess industrijali; Riċerka u żvilupp ta' prodotti; Disinn u żvilupp ta' prodott; Servizzi ta' Inġinerija; Servizzi ta' Inġinerija; Ittestjar, awtentikazzjoni u kontroll tal-kwalità; Is-sorveljanza tal-kundizzjoni tal-magna; Servizzi ta' monitoraġġ ta' sistema tal-kompjuter; Servizzi għall-monitoraġġ ta' proċessi industrijali; Monitoraġġ tal-kundizzjoni ta' fluwidi; Monitoraġġ tal-kundizzjoni marbuta mal-vibrazzjonijiet; Monitoraġġ tal-proċess għall-manutenzjoni u l-assigurazzjoni tal-kwalità; Monitoraġġ tal-kundizzjoni tal-magni u tal-kundizzjoni tal-proċessi industrijali b'aċċess mill-bogħod; Żvilupp ta' softwer; Servizzi ta' monitoraġġ ta' nixxija tal-fluwidu; Il-monitoraġġ tal-kundizzjoni marbuta man-nixxija minn skambjaturi tas-sħana.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Ontwikkeling en advies op het gebied van industriële processen; Onderzoek en ontwikkeling van producten; Het ontwerpen en ontwikkelen van producten; Ingenieursdiensten; Ingenieursdiensten; Testen, authenticatie en kwaliteitscontrole; Machines (Toezicht houden op de toestand van -); Computersysteembewaking; Wetenschappelijke diensten met betrekking tot het toezicht op industriële processen; Statuscontrole met betrekking tot vloeistoffen; Toestandsbewaking in verband met trillingen; Procesbewaking ten behoeve van onderhoud en kwaliteitsbewaking; Bewaking van de conditie van machines en van industriële processen via toegang op afstand; Ontwikkeling van software; Bewaking van vloeistoflekkage; Conditiebewaking in verband met lekkage bij warmtewisselaars.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Rozwój procesów przemysłowych i usługi doradcze; Prace badawczo-rozwojowe w zakresie produktów; Wzornictwo i opracowywanie produktów; Usługi inżynieryjne; Usługi inżynieryjne; Testowanie, stwierdzanie autentyczności i kontrola jakości; Monitorowanie stanu maszyn; Usługi monitorowania systemów komputerowych; Usługi w zakresie monitorowania procesów przemysłowych; Monitorowanie stanu cieczy; Monitorowanie kondycji w odniesieniu do wibracji; Monitorowanie procesów w celu konserwacji i zapewniania jakości; Monitorowanie stanu maszyn i stanów procesów przemysłowych poprzez zdalny dostęp; Opracowywanie oprogramowania komputerowego; Usługi w zakresie monitorowania wycieków cieczy; Monitorowanie kondycji w zakresie wycieków z wymienników ciepła.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Serviços de desenvolvimento de processos industriais e serviços de assessoria conexos; Investigação e desenvolvimento de produtos; Design e desenvolvimento de produtos; Serviços de engenharia; Serviços de engenharia; Testes, autenticação e controlo de qualidade; Monitorização do estado das máquinas; Serviços de monitorização de sistemas informáticos; Serviços para monitorização de processos industriais; Monitorização de condições de fluidos; Monitorização de vibrações; Monitorização de processos para fins de manutenção e de garantia da qualidade; Monitorização do estado de máquinas e do estado de processos industriais através de acesso remoto; Desenvolvimento de software; Serviços de monitorização de fugas de líquidos; Monitorização de estado relacionado com fugas em permutadores de calor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Servicii de dezvoltare și asistență cu privire la procese industriale; Cercetare şi dezvoltare de produs; Design şi dezvoltare de produs; Inginerie; Inginerie; Testare, autentificare şi controlul calităţii; Monitorizarea stării utilajelor; Servicii de monitorizare a sistemelor informatice; Servicii de supraveghere a proceselor industriale; Monitorizarea stării fluidelor; Monitorizarea stării referitor la vibrații; Monitorizarea proceselor pentru mentenanță și asigurarea calității; Monitorizarea condiției mașinilor și condiției proceselor industriale prin acces de la distanță; Dezvoltare de software; Servicii de monitorizare a scurgerilor de lichide; Monitorizarea stării referitor la scurgerea din schimbătoare de căldură.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Vývoj priemyselných procesov a poradenské služby; Výskum a vývoj výrobkov; Navrhovanie a vývoj výrobkov; Inžinierske činnosti; Inžinierske činnosti; Skúšobníctvo, overovanie a kontrola kvality; Monitorovanie stavu strojov; Služby v oblasti monitorovania počítačových systémov; Monitorovanie priemyselných procesov; Sledovanie stavu kvapalín; Monitorovanie stavu v súvislosti s vibráciami; Monitorovanie procesov za účelom údržby a zabezpečovania kvality; Monitorovanie stavu strojov a stavu priemyselných procesov prostredníctvom prístupu na diaľku; Vývoj počítačového softvéru; Služby monitorovania úniku kvapalín; Monitorovanie stavu v súvislosti s únikom kvapalín z výmenníkov tepla.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Razvoj industrijskih procesov in storitve svetovanja; Raziskave in razvoj izdelkov; Oblikovanje in razvoj izdelkov; Inženirske storitve; Inženirske storitve; Testiranje, preverjanje avtentičnosti in kontrola kakovosti; Nadziranje stanja strojev; Storitve nadzora računalniških sistemov; Storitve za nadzor industrijskih procesov; Spremljanje stanja tekočin; Spremljanje stanja v zvezi s tresljaji; Spremljanje procesov za vzdrževanje in zagotavljanje kakovosti; Spremljanje stanja strojev in stanja industrijskih procesov z oddaljenim dostopom; Razvoj programske opreme; Storitve nadzora puščanja tekočin; Nadzor stanja v zvezi s puščanjem iz izmenjevalnikov toplote.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Industriprocessutveckling och rådgivningstjänster; Produktforskning och -utveckling; Produktformgivning och produktutveckling; Ingenjörstjänster; Ingenjörstjänster; Testning, verifieringstjänster och kvalitetskontroll; Övervakning av maskiners tillstånd; Övervakning av datorsystem; Övervakningstjänster avseende industriella processer; Övervakning av vätskors tillstånd; Övervakning av skickat avseende vibrationer; Processövervakning för underhåll och kvalitetssäkring; Övervakning av maskiners skick och industriprocesskondition via fjärråtkomst; Utveckling av mjukvara; Övervakning av vätskeläckage; Övervakning av tillstånd avseende läckage från värmeväxlare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/082</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-05-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/152</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-12</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<ApplicantDetails>
<ApplicantKey>
<Identifier>979845</Identifier>
</ApplicantKey>
</ApplicantDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>12865</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
