<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Transaction xmlns="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://euipo.europa.eu/trademark/data http://euipo.europa.eu/schemas/trademark/EM-TM-TradeMark-V3-4.xsd">
<TransactionHeader>
		<SenderDetails>
			<RequestProducerDateTime>2020-08-05T16:31:38</RequestProducerDateTime>
		</SenderDetails>
	</TransactionHeader>
<TradeMarkTransactionBody>
<TransactionContentDetails>
<TransactionIdentifier>018225935</TransactionIdentifier>
<TransactionCode>EM-Trade Mark</TransactionCode>
<TransactionData>
<TradeMarkDetails>
<TradeMark operationCode="Insert">
<RegistrationOfficeCode>EM</RegistrationOfficeCode>
<ApplicationNumber>018225935</ApplicationNumber>
<ApplicationDate>2020-04-16</ApplicationDate>
<RegistrationDate>2020-07-31</RegistrationDate>
<ApplicationLanguageCode>en</ApplicationLanguageCode>
<SecondLanguageCode>de</SecondLanguageCode>
<ExpiryDate>2030-04-16</ExpiryDate>
<MarkCurrentStatusCode milestone="23" status="1">Registered</MarkCurrentStatusCode>
<MarkCurrentStatusDate>2020-08-05</MarkCurrentStatusDate>
<KindMark>Individual</KindMark>
<MarkFeature>Word</MarkFeature>
<TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>false</TradeDistinctivenessIndicator>
<WordMarkSpecification>
<MarkVerbalElementText>BOCHAMTEC</MarkVerbalElementText>
</WordMarkSpecification>
<GoodsServicesDetails>
<GoodsServices>
 <ClassificationVersion/>
 <ClassDescriptionDetails>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>9</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Периферни устройства, пригодени за използване с компютри; Везни; Теглилни уреди; Измерватели; Сигнални фенери; Слушалки; Дигитални фоторамки; Слушалки; Усилватели; Кутии за високоговорители; Щепсели, фасунги и други контакти [електрически връзки]; Преобразуватели за електрически щепсели; Превключватели, електрически; Защитни устройства за лично ползване за защита при злополуки; Предпазни средства за глава; Слушалки; Електрически щепсели.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Periferní zařízení počítačů; Váhy; Vážicí stroje; Měřidla; Signální lampy; Sluchátka; Digitální fotorámečky; Sluchátka; Zesilovače; Reproduktorové skříně; Zásuvky, zástrčky a jiné elektrické kontakty (elektrické spojky); Měniče pro elektrické zástrčky; Elektrické vypínače a spínače; Osobní ochranné prostředky k prevenci nehod; Ochranné přílby; Sluchátka; Elektrické zástrčky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Perifere enheder til computere; Vægte; Vejemaskiner; Måleredskaber; Signallanterner; Høretelefoner; Digitale fotorammer; Hovedtelefoner; Forstærkere; Højttalerkabinetter; Elektriske stik; Konvertere til elektriske stik; Afbrydere, elektriske; Beskyttelsesindretninger til personlig brug mod ulykker; Hovedbeskyttelse; Hovedtelefoner; Elektriske stik.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">An Computer angepasste Peripheriegeräte; Waagen; Wägemaschinen; Maße; Signallaternen; Kopfhörer; Digitale Fotorahmen; Tonverstärker; Lautsprecherboxen; Elektrische Stecker; Adapter für elektrische Stecker; Schalter [Stromunterbrecher]; Unfallschutzvorrichtungen für den persönlichen Gebrauch; Kopfschutz; Kopfhörer; Kopfhörer; Elektrische Stecker.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Περιφερειακός εξοπλισμός προσαρμοσμένος για χρήση σε ηλεκτρονικούς υπολογιστές· Ζυγαριές· Όργανα μέτρησης του βάρους· Μέτρα προληπτικά· Φακοί για σήματα· Ακουστικά· Ψηφιακές κορνίζες φωτογραφιών· Κάσκες ακουστικών· Ενισχυτές· Κουτιά ηχείων· Ρευματοδότες,ρευματολήπτες και άλλες επαφές [ηλεκτρικές συνδέσεις]· Μετατροπείς για ρευματολήπτες [φις]· Διακόπτες ηλεκτρικοί· Ατυχημάτων (Μηχανισμοί ατομικής προστασίας κατά των -)· Προστατευτικά κεφαλής· Ακουστικά κεφαλής με μικρόφωνο· Ρευματολήπτες.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Computer peripheral devices; Scales; Weighing machines; Measures; Signal lanterns; Earphones; Digital photo frames; Headphones; Amplifiers; Cabinets for loudspeakers; Plugs, sockets and other contacts [electric connections]; Converters for electric plugs; Switches, electric; Protection devices for personal use against accidents; Protective helmets; Headsets; Electric plugs.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Dispositivos periféricos utilizados con ordenadores; Balanzas; Máquinas de pesaje; Medidores; Linternas de señales; Auriculares intraurales; Marcos para fotos digitales; Auriculares; Amplificadores; Cajas de altavoces; Enchufes macho; Convertidores de enchufe; Interruptores; Dispositivos de protección personal contra accidentes; Cascos de protección; Cascos con micrófono; Clavijas eléctricas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Arvutite välisseadmed; Kaalud; Kaalud; Mõõtevahendid; Signaallaternad; Kõrvaklapid; Digitaalsed pildiraamid; Kõrvaklapid; Võimendid; Kõlarikastid; Pistikud, pistikupesad jm ühendused [elektrilised ühendused]; Elektripistikute konverterid; Elektrilülitid; Individuaalkaitsevahendid; Peakaitsmed; Mikrofoniga kõrvaklapid; Elektripistikud.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Tietokoneiden oheislaitteet; Vaa’at; Painonmittausvälineet; Mitat; Vilkkulyhdyt; Kuulokkeet; Digitaaliset valokuvakehykset; Kuulokkeet; Vahvistimet; Kaiutinkotelot; Pistokkeet, pistorasiat ja muut sähköliittimet; Muuntimet sähköpistokkeita varten; Katkaisijat (Sähkö -); Suojalaitteet onnettomuuksien varalta, henkilökohtaiset; Päänsuojaimet; Kuulokkeet; Sähköpistokkeet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Périphériques adaptés pour utilisation avec des ordinateurs; Balances; Machines de pesage; Mesures; Lanternes à signaux; Casques d'écoute; Cadres de photos numériques; Casques à écouteurs; Amplificateurs; Boîtiers de haut-parleurs; Prises électriques mâles; Convertisseurs pour fiches électriques; Interrupteurs; Dispositifs de protection personnelle contre les accidents; Casques de protection; Casques d'écoute; Fiches électriques.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Periferni uređaji prilagođeni za uporabu s računalima; Vage; Instrumenti za mjerenje težine; Mjerila; Signalizacijske lanterne; Slušalice; Digitalni foto okviri; Slušalice; Pojačala; Kućišta razglasa; Utičnice, utikači i ostali kontakti [električni kontakti]; Pretvarači za električne utikače; Električne sklopke; Nesreće na radu (uređaji za osobnu zaštitu na radu); Zaštitna oprema za glavu; Slušalice; Utikači za struju.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Számítógéphez kialakított perifériák; Kiegyensúlyozó készülékek, mérlegek; Súlymérő berendezések; Mérőeszközök, mértékek; Jelzőlámpák; Fejhallgatók; Digitális fényképkeretek; Fejhallgatók; Erősítők; Hangszórószekrények, hangszóródobozok; Dugók, csatlakozó aljzatok és más kapcsolások [elektromos csatlakozások]; Átalakítók elektromos csatlakozókhoz; Kapcsolók, elektromos; Védőeszközök személyek balesetvédelmére; Fejvédő eszközök; Fejhallgatók; Elektromos csatlakozók, konnektor dugók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Periferiche concepite per essere utilizzate con i computer; Bilance; Macchine per pesare; Misure; Lanterne per segnali; Auricolari; Cornici per foto digitali; Cuffie per la musica; Amplificatori del suono; Casse acustiche; Prese elettriche maschili; Convertitori per prese elettriche; Interrutori elettrici; Dispositivi di protezione personale contro gli infortuni; Protezioni per la testa; Cuffie per la musica; Spine elettriche.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Kompiuterių išoriniai įrenginiai; Svarstyklės; Svėrimo mašinos; Matai; Signaliniai žibintai; Ausinės; Skaitmeninių nuotraukų rėmeliai; Radijo ausinės; Stiprintuvai; Garsiakalbių korpusai; Lizdai, kištukai ir kitokie kontaktai [elektros jungtys]; Elektros kištukų keitikliai; Elektros jungikliai; Asmeninės apsaugos priemonės nuo nelaimingų atsitikimų; Apsauginiai šalmai; Ausinės; Elektros kištukai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Datoru perifērijas ierīces; Balansēšanas ierīces; Svēršanas iekārtas; Mēri; Signāllukturi; Ieaušu austiņas; Digitālo fotogrāfiju rāmji; Austiņas; Pastiprinātāji; Skandu korpusi; Elektriskās kontaktdakšas; Pārveidotāji elektriskajiem slēdžiem; Elektriskie slēdži; Ierīces individuālai aizsardzībai pret nelaimes gadījumiem; Galvassegas galvas aizsardzībai; Radioaustiņas; Elektrības spraudkontakti.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Periferali addattati għall-użu mal-kompjuters; Apparat għall-użin; Strumenti għall-kejl tal-piż; Kejl; Lanterni tas-sinjali; Kuffji; Gwarniċi diġitali għar-ritratti; Kuffji; Amplifikaturi; Kabinetti għall-amplifikaturi tal-ħoss; Sòkits, plaggs u kuntatti oħrajn [konnessjonijiet elettriċi]; Konvertituri għall-plakek tal-elettriku; Swiċċijiet elettriċi; Tagħmir ta' protezzjoni għall-użu personali kontra l-inċidenti; Protezzjoni tar-ras; Kuffji; Plakek tal-elettriku.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Computerrandapparatuur; Weegschalen; Weegmachines; Maten; Signaallantaarns; Oortelefoons; Digitale fotolijsten; Hoofdtelefoons; Versterkers; Luidsprekerkasten; Elektrische stekkers; Omzetters voor elektrische stekkers; Elektrische schakelaars; Inrichtingen voor de bescherming van personen tegen ongevallen; Beschermers voor het hoofd; Hoofdtelefoons; Elektrische stekkers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Sprzęt peryferyjny do komputerów; Urządzenia do wyważania; Przyrządy do pomiaru wagi; Miary; Latarnie sygnalizacyjne; Słuchawki [douszne]; Ramki cyfrowe do zdjęć; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Wzmacniacze; Obudowy głośników; Gniazdka, wtyczki i inne kontakty [złącza elektryczne]; Przejściówki do wtyczek elektrycznych; Przełączniki elektryczne; Urządzenia do ochrony osobistej przed wypadkami; Osłony głowy; Słuchawki [zakładane na głowę]; Wtyczki elektryczne.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Periféricos adaptados para uso com computadores; Balanças; Máquinas de pesagem; Medidores; Lanternas de sinalização; Auriculares; Molduras digitais; Auriculares; Amplificadores; Caixas de altifalantes; Fichas elétricas; Conversores para fichas elétricas; Interruptores elétricos; Dispositivos de proteção pessoal contra os acidentes; Proteções para a cabeça; Auriculares; Fichas elétricas.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Periferice adaptate pentru a fi folosite la calculatoare; Balanțe; Instrumente pentru măsurarea greutății; Măsuri; Lanterne de semnalizare; Căști auriculare; Rame foto digitale; Căști audio; Amplificatoare; Cutii pentru difuzoare; Prize, fișe și alte dispozitive de cuplare [conexiuni electrice]; Convertoare pentru fișe electrice; Întrerupătoare; Dispozitive de protecție, de uz personal, împotriva accidentelor; Protecția capului; Căști; Fișe de conectare [electricitate].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Periférne zariadenia počítačov; Váhy; Stroje na váženie; Mierky; Signalizačné návestné lampáše; Slúchadlá; Digitálne fotorámiky; Slúchadlá; Zosilňovače; Reproduktorové skrinky; Elektrické zásuvky; Meniče pre elektrické zásuvky; Vypínače; Osobné ochranné prostriedky proti nehodám; Chrániče hlavy; Slúchadlá s mikrofónom; Elektrické zástrčky.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Zunanje enote, prilagojene za uporabo z računalniki; Tehtnice; Instrumenti za merjenje teže; Mere; Signalne svetilke; Slušalke; Okvirji za digitalne fotografije; Slušalke; Ojačevalniki; Ohišja zvočnikov; Vtikači, vtičnice in ostali kontakti [električni konektorji]; Pretvorniki za električne vtiče; Stikala, električna; Zaščitne naprave proti poškodbam, za osebno uporabo; Proizvodi za zaščito glave; Slušalke; Električni vtikači.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Kringutrustning anpassade för användning med datorer; Vågar; Vägningsmaskiner; Mått; Signallyktor; Hörlurar; Digitala fotoramar; On-ear hörlurar; Förstärkare; Högtalarlådor; Elektriska kontakter; Adaptrar till elkontakter; Elektriska strömbrytare; Skyddsanordningar mot olyckor för personligt bruk; Huvudskydd; Headsets; Elektriska stickproppsanslutningar.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>11</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Светодиоди [LED] за осветителни уреди; Подводни прожектори; Улични лампи; Електрическо фенерче; Светлини, електрически, за коледни елхи; Миньорски лампи; Обезопасени лампи за рудници; Осветителни крушки; Осветление за автомобили; Светлини за велосипеди; Фенери за осветление; Грилове за барбекю; Камини; Водни пречиствателни инсталации; Радиатори, електрически; Прожектори.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Osvětlovací zařízení vybavená elektroluminiscenčními diodami (LED); Potápěčská světla; Pouliční lampy; Vyhledávací světlomety; Elektrická osvětlení na vánoční stromky; Důlní lampy; Bezpečnostní lampy; Žárovky; Světla pro automobily; Světla pro jízdní kola; Lucerny; Venkovní grily; Domácí krby; Zařízení na čištění vody; Elektrické radiátory; Reflektory.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Lysemitterende dioder [LED]-belysningsapparater; Dykkerlamper; Gadelamper; Lyskastere; Juletræslys, elektriske; Minelamper; Sikkerhedslamper; Pærer til belysning; Lygter til automobiler; Cykellygter; Lanterner til belysning; Udendørs grill; Pejse; Vandrenseinstallationer; Radiatorer, elektriske; Projektør [søgelys].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Beleuchtungsgeräte mit Leuchtdioden [LEDs]; Tauchlampen; Straßenlampen; Suchscheinwerfer; Elektrische Christbaumbeleuchtungen; Grubenlampen; Sicherheitslampen; Glühbirnen für Beleuchtungszwecke; Leuchten für Kraftfahrzeuge; Fahrradleuchten; Laternen; Barbecues; Kamine; Wasserreinigungsanlagen; Elektrische Radiatoren; Suchscheinwerfer.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Συσκευές φωτισμού με φωτοδιόδους· Προβολείς κατάδυσης· Λάμπες για οδικό φωτισμό· Προβολείς εντοπισμού· Λαμπάκια ηλεκτρικά για δένδρα χριστουγεννιάτικα· Μεταλλωρύχοι (λυχνίες -ων)· Λυχνίες ασφαλείας· Λαμπτήρες· Οχημάτων φανάρια· Δικύκλων φανάρια· Φανοί φωτισμού· Μπάρμπεκιου· Εστίες· Ύδωρ (εγκαταστάσεις καθαρισμού του -ος)· Ηλεκτρικά θερμαντικά σώματα· Ανιχνευτικοί προβολείς.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Light-emitting diodes [LED] lighting apparatus; Diving lights; Street lamps; Flashlights [torches]; Electric lights for Christmas trees; Miners' lamps; Safety lamps; Light bulbs; Automobile lights; Bicycle lights; Lanterns for lighting; Barbecues; Fireplaces, domestic; Water purification installations; Radiators, electric; Search lights.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Aparatos de iluminación con diodos electroluminiscentes [LED]; Lámparas de buceo; Farolas; Proyectores de luz; Luces eléctricas para árboles de Navidad; Lámparas de minero; Lámparas de seguridad; Bombillas de iluminación; Luces para automóviles; Luces para bicicletas; Faroles de alumbrado; Barbacoas; Chimeneas; Instalaciones de depuración de agua; Radiadores eléctricos; Focos reflectores.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Valgustkiirgavatel dioodidel põhinevad (LED-) valgustid; Tuukrite lambid; Tänavalaternad; Taskulambid [valgustusseadmed], helgiheitjad, prožektorid; Jõulupuu elektriküünlad; Kaevurilambid; Turvalambid; Lambipirnid; Autolaternad; Jalgrattalaternad; Valgustuslaternad; Barbeque-ahjud; Kaminad; Veepuhastusseadmed; Elektriradiaatorid; Helgiheitjad.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">LED-valaistuslaitteet; Sukelluslamput; Jalkalamput; Soihdut valaistukseen; Joulukuusten sähkövalaisimet; Kaivoslamput; Turvalamput; Hehkulamput; Ajoneuvojen valaisimet; Lamput polkupyöriin; Lyhdyt valaistukseen; Ulkogrillit; Takat; Vedenpuhdistuslaitteet; Lämpöpatterit, sähkökäyttöiset; Etsintävalot.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Appareils d'éclairage à diodes électroluminescentes [DEL]; Projecteurs de plongée; Lampadaires; Projecteurs d'éclairage; Lampes électriques pour arbres de Noël; Lampes de mineurs; Lampes de sûreté; Ampoules d'éclairage; Feux pour automobiles; Feux pour bicyclettes; Lanternes d'éclairage; Barbecues; Cheminées d'appartement; Installations pour la purification de l'eau; Radiateurs électriques; Projecteurs [appareils d'éclairage].</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Rasvjetni uređaji sa diodama koje emitiraju svjetlo [LED]; Projektori za ronjenje; Stajaće svjetiljke; Džepne svjetiljke za rasvjetu; Svjećice (električne svjećice za božićna drvca); Rudarske svjetiljke; Svjetiljke, sigurnosne; Rasvjetne žaruljice; Svjetla za automobile; Svjetla za bicikle; Rasvjetni fenjeri; Roštilji na ugljen; Kamini; Uređaj za pročišćavanje vode; Radijatori, električni; Reflektori.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">LED-diódás világító berendezések; Búvárlámpák; Beltéri állólámpák; Keresőlámpák, zseblámpák; Lámpák karácsonyfákhoz, elektromos; Bányászlámpák; Biztonsági lámpák; Villanykörték; Lámpák járművekhez; Kerékpár lámpák; Lámpások világításra; Grillezők, grillsütők; Kandallók; Víztisztító berendezések; Radiátorok, elektromos; Fényszórók, keresőlámpák.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Diodi che emettono luce [LED]; Faretti da sub; Lampade a stelo; Proiettori; Lampadine elettriche per alberi di natale; Lampade per minatori; Lampade di sicurezza; Lampadine per illuminazione; Fanali per automobili; Fanali per biciclette; Lanterne per illuminazione; Barbecues; Caminetti; Impianti per la depurazione dell'acqua; Radiatori elettrici; Proiettori da ricerca.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Šviesadiodžio [LED] apšvietimo įrenginiai; Nardymo šviestuvai; Gatvių šviestuvai; Prožektoriai; Kalėdų eglučių elektros lemputės; Šachtininkų lemputės; Saugiosios lempos; Apšvietimo lemputės; Automobilių žibintai; Dviračių žibintai; Apšvietimo žibintai; Kepimo rėmai; Židiniai; Vandens valymo įrenginiai; Elektriniai radiatoriai; Prožektoriai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Gaismu emitējošu diožu (LED) apgaismes iekārtas; Ūdenslīdēju lukturi; Ielu apgaismošanas lampas; Prožektori; Elektriskās spuldzītes Ziemassvētku eglītēm; Kalnraču lampas; Eksplozijdrošas raktuvju lampas; Spuldzes; Automobiļu lukturi; Velosipēdu lukturi; Lukturi apgaismošanai; Ierīces cepšanai uz oglēm; Degtuves; Ūdens attīrīšanas iekārtas; Elektriskie radiatori; Prožektori (starmeši).</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Apparat li jdawwal b'dajowds li jarmu d-dawl [LED]; Lampi tal-għaddasa; Lampi stàndard; Torċ għad-dawl; Dwal elettriċi għas-siġar tal-Milied; Lampi tal-minaturi; Lampi tas-sigurtà; Bozoz tad-dawl; Dwal għall-vetturi; Dwal tar-roti; Fanali għad-dawl; Barbikjus; Fireplaces; Sistemi għat-tisfija tal-ilma; Radjaturi, tal-elettriku; Projetturi tad-dawl.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">LED-verlichtingsapparatuur; Duikerlampen; Lantaarnpalen; Toortsen voor verlichting; Elektrische lampen voor kerstbomen; Mijnwerkerslampen; Veiligheidslampen; Gloeilampen; Lichten voor automobielen; Fietslampen; Lantaarns voor verlichting; Barbecues; Open haarden; Waterzuiveringsinstallaties; Elektrische radiatoren; Zoeklichten.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Urządzenia do oświetlania za pomocą diod elektroluminescencyjnych [LED]; Lampy nurkowe; Lampy stojące; Latarki; Lampki elektryczne na choinki; Lampy górnicze; Lampy bezpieczeństwa; Żarówki oświetleniowe; Światła do pojazdów; Światła rowerowe; Latarnie oświetleniowe; Grill; Kominki; Instalacje do uzdatniania wody; Kaloryfery elektryczne; Reflektory poszukiwawcze.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Díodos emissores de luz [LED]; Projetores de mergulho; Lampadários; Tochas [archotes] para a iluminação; Lâmpadas elétricas para árvores de natal; Lâmpadas de mineiros; Lâmpadas de segurança; Lâmpadas de iluminação; Luzes para automóveis; Luzes para bicicletas; Lanternas de iluminação; Churrasqueiras; Lareiras; Instalações para a purificação da água; Radiadores elétricos; Holofotes.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Aparate de iluminat cu diode luminescente [LED]; Lanterne pentru scufundări; Lampadare; Lanterne pentru iluminat; Instalații luminoase pentru pomul de Crăciun; Lămpi pentru mineri; Lămpi de siguranță; Becuri de iluminat; Aparate de iluminat pentru vehicule; Lanterne de biciclete; Lanterne de iluminat; Grătare mari în aer liber; Șemineuri; Instalații pentru purificarea apei; Radiatoare electrice; Reflectoare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Elektroluminiscenčné osvetľovacie prístroje (s LED diódami); Potápačské svetlomety; Pouličné lampy; Baterky (svietidlá); Elektrické svetlá na vianočné stromčeky; Banské lampy; Bezpečnostné lampy; Žiarovky; Svetlá na automobily; Svietidlá na bicykle; Lampáše; Rošty na opekanie mäsa; Kozuby (domové); Zariadenia na úpravu vody; Elektrické radiátory; Reflektory.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Aparati za osvetljevanje z LED diodami; Potapljaške svetilke; Stoječe svetilke; Žepne svetilke za razsvetljavo; Električne lučke za božična drevesca; Rudarske svetilke; Varnostne svetilke; Žarnice za razsvetljavo; Naprave za osvetlitev za vozila; Kolesarske luči; Lanterne za razsvetljavo; Ražnji za uporabo na prostem (ne električni); Kamini; Čistilne naprave za vodo; Električni radiatorji; Iskalni reflektorji.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Belysningsapparater för lysdioder [LED]; Dykarlampor; Gatulampor; Handlyktor; Elektriska belysningar för julgranar; Gruvlampor; Säkerhetslampor; Glödlampor; Lyktor för bilar; Cykelbelysning; Lanternor för belysning; Utomhusgrillar; Eldstäder; Vattenreningsinstallationer; Elektriska element; Sökarljus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
  <ClassDescription>
   <ClassNumber>21</ClassNumber>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="bg">Чинии за еднократна употреба; Кухненски съдове, не от благороден метал; Панерчета за хляб; Кухненски принадлежности, не от благороден метал; Скари [прибори за готвене]; Кабаретни подноси, не от благороден метал; Аерозолни дозатори, не за медицински цели; Дъски за гладене; Четки за зъби, електрически; Козметични принадлежности; Кофи за лед; Термоси; Килимочистачки; Капани за насекоми; Ултразвукови устройства срещу комари.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="cs">Talíře na jedno použití; Kuchyňské dózy a krabičky; Nádoby na chleba; Kuchyňské potřeby; Kuchyňské rošty na pečení; Kabarety [dělené misky]; Aerosolové dávkovače, ne dávkovače pro léčebné účely; Žehlicí prkna; Elektrické zubní kartáčky; Kosmetické pomůcky; Kbelíky na led; Izolované lahve; Zametače na koberce; Pasti na hmyz; Ultrazvuková zařízení na odpuzování komárů.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="da">Engangstallerkener; Køkkenbeholdere; Brødkasser; Køkkenredskaber; Grillriste [køkkenredskaber]; Kabaret [serveringsbakke]; Aerosolapparater, ikke til medicinsk brug; Strygebrætter; Tandbørster, elektriske; Redskaber til kosmetisk brug; Isspande; Termoflasker; Tæppefejeredskaber; Insektfangere; Ultralydsapparater til fordrivelsae af myg.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="de">Wegwerfteller; Küchengefäße; Brotkästen; Küchengeräte; Grillroste [Küchengeräte]; Kabaretts [Servierplatten]; Aerosolzerstäuber, nicht für medizinische Zwecke; Bügelbretter; Elektrische Zahnbürsten; Kosmetische Geräte; Eiskübel; Isolierflaschen; Teppichkehrer; Insektenfallen; Ultraschallgeräte zur Mückenabwehr.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="el">Επιτραπέζια πιάτα μιας χρήσης· Δοχεία μαγειρικής χρήσης· Ψωμιέρες· Σκεύη μαγειρικής χρήσης· Ψηστιέρες [μαγειρικά σκεύη]· Δίσκοι σερβιρίσματος· Αεροζόλ (Συσκευές ρίψης -) για μη ιατρική χρήση· Σιδερώστρες· Οδοντόβουρτσες [ηλεκτρικές]· Καλλυντικά (Σκεύη -)· Κάδοι πάγου· Φιάλες ισοθερμικές· Σκούπες μηχανικές· Εντομοπαγίδες· Απωθητικά κουνουπιών με υπερήχους.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="en">Disposable table plates; Kitchen containers; Bread bins; Kitchen utensils; Grills [cooking utensils]; Cabarets [trays]; Aerosol dispensers, not for medical purposes; Ironing boards; Toothbrushes, electric; Cosmetic utensils; Ice pails; Vacuum bottles; Rug sweepers; Insect traps; Ultrasonic mosquito repellers.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="es">Platos desechables; Recipientes de cocina; Cajas para el pan; Utensilios de cocina; Parrillas [utensilios de cocina]; Licoreras [bandejas]; Aerosoles [recipientes] que no sean para uso médico; Tablas de planchar; Cepillos de dientes eléctricos; Utensilios cosméticos; Cubiteras; Botellas aislantes; Escobas mecánicas; Trampas para insectos; Repelentes de mosquitos que funcionan por ultrasonidos.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="et">Ühekorrataldrikud; Köögimahutid; Leivakastid; Köögitarbed; Grillid [köögiriistad]; Serveerimiskandikud; Aerosoolijaoturid, v.a meditsiinilised; Triikimislauad; Elektrihambaharjad; Kosmeetikatarbed; Jäänõud; Termospudelid; Mehaanilised vaibaharjad; Putukapüünised; Ultraheliga töötavad sääsetõrjevahendid.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fi">Kertakäyttölautaset; Keittiön säilytysastiat; Leipälaatikot; Keittokattilasarjat; Parilat [ruoanlaittovälineinä]; Tarjottimet; Aerosolisumuttimet, ei-lääketieteellisiin tarkoituksiin; Silityslaudat; Sähköhammasharjat; Kosmetiikkavälineet; Jääsangot; Termospullot; Mattomikot; Hyönteispyydykset; Hyttysten ultraäänikarkottimet.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="fr">Assiettes jetables; Récipients pour la cuisine; Boîtes à pain; Ustensiles de cuisine; Grils [ustensiles de cuisson]; Cabarets [plateaux à servir]; Appareils destinés à la projection d'aérosols non à usage médical; Planches à repasser; Brosses à dents électriques; Ustensiles cosmétiques; Seaux à glace; Bouteilles isolantes; Balais mécaniques; Pièges à insectes; Répulsifs anti-moustiques à ultrasons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hr">Jednokratni tanjuri; Kuhinjske posude; Kutije za kruh; Posuđe (kuhinjsko metalno posuđe); Ploče za pečenje [kuhinjska oprema]; Porculanski poslužavnici; Uređaji za raspršivanje aerosola, za nemedicinske potrebe; Daske za glačanje; Četkice za zube, električne; Kozmetički pribor; Led (posude za led); Izolacijske boce; Mehaničke metle; Zamke za insekte; Ultrazvučni uređaji za odbijanje komaraca.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="hu">Eldobható tányérok; Konyhai dobozok, tárolók; Kenyértartók; Konyhai eszközök, kis méretű; Grillek, rostélyok [sütőeszközök]; Porcelán tálcák; Aeroszol adagolók, nem gyógyászati használatra; Vasalódeszkák; Fogkefék (Elektromos -); Kozmetikai eszközök; Jegesvödrök, hűtővödrök; Termoszok; Szőnyegseprők; Rovarcsapdák; Ultrahangos szúnyogriasztók.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="it">Piatti usa e getta; Recipienti per la cucina; Recipienti per il pane; Utensili da cucina; Graticole; Vassoi [piatti per servire]; Apparecchi per la proiezione di aerosol per uso non medico; Tavoli da stiro; Spazzolini da denti elettrici; Utensili cosmetici; Secchio per il ghiaccio; Bottiglie isolanti; Scope meccaniche; Trappole per insetti; Repellenti a ultrasuoni per zanzare.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lt">Vienkartinės lėkštės; Virtuviniai konteineriai; Duoninės; Virtuviniai indai; Keptuvai [griliai]; Padėklai; Aerozoliniai įtaisai (išskyrus medicininius); Lyginimo lentos; Elektriniai dantų šepetukai; Kosmetikos reikmenys; Ledo kibirėliai; Termosai; Kilimų valymo įtaisai; Vabzdžių gaudyklės; Ultragarsiniai uodų atbaidymo prietaisai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="lv">Vienreizlietojamie šķīvji; Virtuves kārbas; Maizes kastes; Ēdienu gatavošanas trauku komplekti; Grili (restes cepšanai); Paplātes; Aerosolu izsmidzināšanas ierīces, ne medicīniskiem nolūkiem; Gludināmie dēļi; Elektriskās zobu sukas; Kosmētikas piederumi; Ledus spainīši; Termosi (vakuuma pudeles); Birstes tepiķu tīrīšanai; Kukaiņu lamatas; Ultraskaņas ierīces moskītu atbaidīšanai.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="mt">Platti tal-mejda, disponibbli; Reċipjenti tal-kċina; Laned tal-ħobż; Settijiet tal-borom għat-tisjir; Pjanċi għat-tisjir jew għall-ħami ta' kejkijiet ċatti [utensili tat-tisjir]; Gabarrejiet [trejs]; Dispensers tal-erosol, mhux għal skopijiet mediċi; Twavel tal-mogħdija; Xkupilji tas-snien, tal-elettriku; Utensili kożmetiċi; Bramel tas-silġ; Termos; Oġġetti li jikinsu t-twapet; Nases għall-insetti; Tagħmir ultrasoniku li jbiegħed lin-nemus.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="nl">Eetborden, voor eenmalig gebruik; Houders voor de keuken; Broodtrommels; Keukengerei; Braadroosters; Presenteerbladen; Spuitbussen, niet voor medisch gebruik; Strijkplanken; Elektrische tandenborstels; Cosmetisch gerei; Ijsemmers; Thermosflessen; Rolbezems; Insectenvallen; Ultrasone instrumenten voor het weren van muggen.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pl">Talerze jednorazowego użytku; Pojemniki kuchenne; Pojemniki na chleb; Przybory kuchenne; Ruszty [kuchenne]; Półmiski [tace]; Urządzenia rozpylające do aerozoli, nie do celów medycznych; Deski do prasowania; Szczoteczki do zębów elektryczne; Przybory kosmetyczne; Wiaderka do kostek lodu; Termosy; Szczotki do dywanów; Łapki na insekty; Ultradźwiękowe odstraszacze komarów.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="pt">Pratos descartáveis; Recipientes para cozinha; Caixas para pão; Utensílios para cozinha; Grelhas [utensílios para cozinhar]; Bandejas [tabuleiros]; Dispensadores de aerossóis, sem ser para uso médico; Tábuas de engomar; Escovas de dentes elétricas; Utensílios cosméticos; Refrigeradores [baldes para gelo]; Garrafas térmicas; Espanadores para carpetes; Armadilhas para insetos; Repelentes de mosquitos por ultrassons.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="ro">Farfurii de unică folosință; Bucătărie (Recipiente pentru -); Cutii pentru pâine; Ustensile de bucătărie; Grătare [ustensile pentru gătit]; Tăvi [platouri de servit]; Aerosoli (aparate pentru răspândirea -lor) [altele decât cele folosite în scopuri medicale]; Mese de călcat; Perii de dinți electrice; Cosmetice (Ustensile -); Recipiente pentru gheață; Termosuri; Mături mecanice; Capcane pentru insecte; Dispozitive cu ultrasunete pentru îndepărtarea țânțarilor.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sk">Jednorazové taniere; Kuchynské nádoby; Schránky na chlieb; Kuchynský riad; Grily, rošty (potreby na opekanie); Podnosy (tácne); Aerosólové dávkovače (nie na lekárske účely); Žehliace dosky; Elektrické zubné kefky; Kozmetické pomôcky; Vedierka na ľad; Termosky; Mechanické metly; Lapače hmyzu; Ultrazvukové zariadenia na odpudzovanie komárov.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sl">Namizni krožniki za enkratno uporabo; Kuhinjske posode; Posode za shranjevanje kruha; Kuharski pripomočki; Železne plošče za pečenje (pripomočki za kuhanje); Servirni pladnji; Pršilci aerosolov, ne za medicinske namene; Likalne mize; Zobne ščetke, električne; Kozmetični pripomočki; Vedra za led; Termovke; Pometači za preproge; Pasti za insekte; Ultrazvočne naprave za odganjanje komarjev.</GoodsServicesDescription>
   <GoodsServicesDescription languageCode="sv">Engångstallrikar; Köksbehållare; Brödskrin; Köksgeråd; Pannkakslaggar; Likörbrickor; Aerosolbehållare, inte för medicinska ändamål; Strykbrädor; Elektriska tandborstar; Kosmetikutensilier; Ishinkar; Termosflaskor; Mattsopare; Insektsfällor; Myggavvisande ultraljudsapparater.</GoodsServicesDescription>
  </ClassDescription>
 </ClassDescriptionDetails>
</GoodsServices>
</GoodsServicesDetails>
<PublicationDetails>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/076</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>A.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-04-22</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
       <Publication>
        <PublicationIdentifier>2020/146</PublicationIdentifier>
        <PublicationSection>B.1</PublicationSection>
        <PublicationDate>2020-08-04</PublicationDate>
        <PublicationPage>0</PublicationPage>
       </Publication>
      </PublicationDetails>
<RepresentativeDetails>
<RepresentativeKey>
<Identifier>87424</Identifier>
</RepresentativeKey>
</RepresentativeDetails>
</TradeMark>
</TradeMarkDetails>
</TransactionData>
</TransactionContentDetails>
</TradeMarkTransactionBody>
</Transaction>
